<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sterlite Technologies Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sterlite-technologies-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1675277</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675277</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Safari Industries (India) Ltd, Pearl Global Industries Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Surya Roshni Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 11 February 2026.

Safari Industries (India) Ltd, Pearl Global Industries Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Surya Roshni Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 11 February 2026. Sterlite Technologies Ltd crashed 8.60% to Rs 144.05 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 19.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.25 lakh shares in the past one month. Safari Industries (India) Ltd tumbled 7.88% to Rs 1977.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 4945 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1500 shares in the past one month. Pearl Global Industries Ltd lost 6.95% to Rs 1501. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 12933 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19682 shares in the past one month. Poly Medicure Ltd shed 6.38% to Rs 1391.6. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 26894 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 65449 shares in the past one month. Surya Roshni Ltd slipped 6.01% to Rs 234.55. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 74351 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12749 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SterliteTech_57490273283_21331.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude climbs above $64 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-climbs-above-64-per-barrel/1675275</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675275</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures climbed above $64 per barrel on Wednesday, snapping the previous session’s losses as persistent US-Iran tensions lent support to prices.

WTI crude oil futures climbed above $64 per barrel on Wednesday, snapping the previous session’s losses as persistent US-Iran tensions lent support to prices. Gains were capped after a US industry report showed a sharp rise in crude inventories, with stockpiles surging by 13.4 million barrels last week—the biggest build since November 2023 if confirmed by official data. Markets now await OPEC’s monthly outlook and the IEA’s assessment, which has warned that global supply is likely to outpace demand this year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold gains as fed cut bets grow and geopolitical risks linger]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-gains-as-fed-cut-bets-grow-and-geopolitical-risks-linger/1675274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675274</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices surged 1% to around $5,080 per ounce on Wednesday, supported by strong safe-haven demand and sustained central bank buying.

Gold prices surged 1% to around $5,080 per ounce on Wednesday, supported by strong safe-haven demand and sustained central bank buying. China extended its gold purchases for a 15th consecutive month, reinforcing bullish sentiment. The US dollar weakened ahead of the delayed January non-farm payrolls report. The dollar index slipped to around 96.4 after soft US retail sales data raised expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts. Geopolitical risks, including lingering US-Iran tensions and ongoing Russia-Ukraine hostilities despite diplomatic efforts, continued to underpin prices. In India, MCX April gold futures climbed over 1% to ₹1,58,140 per 10 grams, with investors now watching upcoming US jobs and inflation data closely.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tokyo Plast International Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tokyo-plast-international-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1675271</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675271</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[N K Industries Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd, Laxmi Dental Ltd and Som Distilleries & Breweries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 11 February 2026.

N K Industries Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd, Laxmi Dental Ltd and Som Distilleries & Breweries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 11 February 2026. Tokyo Plast International Ltd crashed 14.27% to Rs 101.5 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 648 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 530 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd lost 11.71% to Rs 60.04. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 20 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 285 shares in the past one month. Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd tumbled 10.38% to Rs 5.44. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15459 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6831 shares in the past one month. Laxmi Dental Ltd fell 9.29% to Rs 205.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 30227 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22827 shares in the past one month. Som Distilleries & Breweries Ltd corrected 8.99% to Rs 87.4. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.53 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 39959 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TokyoPlastInternationalLtd_60698755021_4159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI issues draft Directions for exemption from registration to eligible NBFCs not availing public funds and not having customer interface]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-issues-draft-directions-for-exemption-from-registration-to-eligible-nbfcs-not-availing-public-funds-and-not-having-customer-interface/1675272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675272</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has invited public comments on the draft Reserve Bank of India (Non-Banking Financial Companies – Registration, Exemptions and Framework for Scale Based Regulation) Amendment Directions, 2026.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has invited public comments on the draft Reserve Bank of India (Non-Banking Financial Companies – Registration, Exemptions and Framework for Scale Based Regulation) Amendment Directions, 2026. The central bank has proposed modifications to the existing Master Directions on NBFC Registration, Exemptions, and the Framework for Scale-Based Regulation (SBR). The key amendment provides for exemption from mandatory registration under Section 45IA of the RBI Act, 1934, for certain non-deposit taking NBFCs that do not accept public funds, do not have a customer interface, and have an asset size below Rs 1,000 crore. This measure is designed to alleviate the regulatory burden for low-risk entities. It noted that exemption is limited only to the requirement of obtaining a Certificate of Registration (CoR). Such entities will continue to remain under the regulatory and supervisory purview and the central bank retains powers to issue directions or take action if financial stability concerns arise. The draft changes are aligned with the Scale Based Regulation (SBR) framework, under which NBFCs are classified into different regulatory layers based on size, activity, and risk profile. Overall, the proposed amendments seek to balance ease of doing business for smaller NBFCs with continued prudential supervision by the RBI.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/euro-seem-money-finance_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Juniper Hotels rises after Q3 PAT spurts 101% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/juniper-hotels-rises-after-q3-pat-spurts-101-yoy/1675270</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675270</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, profit after tax more than doubled to Rs 65.4 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 101% YoY increase from Rs 32.5 crore.

On a consolidated basis, profit after tax more than doubled to Rs 65.4 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 101% YoY increase from Rs 32.5 crore. On a sequential basis, PAT rose sharply by 277% from Rs 16.8 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 295.1 crore in Q3 FY26, up 17% YoY from Rs 252.5 crore in Q3 FY25 and 28% QoQ from Rs 230.3 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA rose 31% YoY to Rs 132.4 crore from Rs 101.3 crore, while increasing 52% QoQ. EBITDA margin expanded to 44% in Q3 FY26 from 39% in Q3 FY25 and 37% in Q2 FY26. Adjusted EBITDA, which excludes other income, grew 37% YoY to Rs 127.5 crore, with margin improving to 43% from 37% in Q3 FY25 and 36% in Q2 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax surged to Rs 82.5 crore, up 90% YoY and 200% QoQ. After accounting for exceptional items, profit before tax stood at Rs 83.5 crore, up 92% YoY and 252% QoQ. Total expenditure remained broadly flat on a year-on-year basis at Rs 217.46 crore during the quarter. Cost of food and beverages consumed rose 8.96% YoY to Rs 22.62 crore, while employee benefit expenses increased 8.08% YoY to Rs 47.89 crore. Finance costs declined 28% YoY to Rs 21.7 crore, while depreciation and amortisation stood at Rs 28.2 crore, broadly stable year-on-year. The strong EBITDA performance was driven by a 14% YoY growth in RevPAR (Revenue per Available Room), supported by a sharper focus on higher-paying customer segments. Cluster efficiencies led to lower consumables, while a higher share of renewable energy sourcing helped reduce hotel-level power costs. However, employee benefit expenses increased due to augmentation of project teams, and sales and marketing costs rose on account of higher travel agent commissions and promotional spends. Juniper Hotels is a leading developer of big box luxury hotels and the largest owner of Hyatt affiliated hotels in India. The company is a strategic partnership between the Saraf group and Hyatt, a premier international hospitality player. The company operates 2,130 keys (including 245 serviced apartments) across 8 hotels in key metro and emerging cities as well as tourist destinations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JuniperHotelsLtd_98728017_28764.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade near flat line; PSU bank shares jump]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-near-flat-line-psu-bank-shares-jump/1675268</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675268</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded sideways in mid-afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded sideways in mid-afternoon trade. The Nifty traded near the 25,950 mark. PSU Bank shares jumped after declining in the past trading session. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 60.88 points or 0.07% to 84,213.04. The Nifty 50 index added 9.15 points or 0.03% to 25,944.05. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.17% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.01%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,855 shares rose and 2,245 shares fell. A total of 190 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index advanced 1.28% to 9,272.75. The index shed 0.19% in the past trading session. State Bank of India (up 3.23%), Union Bank of India (up 0.54%), Bank of Baroda (up 0.31%), Punjab National Bank (up 0.13%) surged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.18% to 6.715 compared with previous session close of 6.727. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6600 compared with its close of 90.5600 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.83% to Rs 158,109. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.29% to 96.58. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.22% to 4.136. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 97 cents or 1.41% to $69.77 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Britannia Industries gained 2.80% after reporting steady growth in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 679.96 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.89% YoY from Rs 581.69 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 3.89% from Rs 654.47 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 9.45% YoY to Rs 4,885.23 crore, compared with Rs 4,463.30 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue grew 2.80% from Rs 4,752.17 crore. Avantel rallied 3.79% after the company said that it has secured an order worth Rs 122.58 crore from NewSpace India for the supply of S/X-band with Ka-band-ready full-motion antennas. The contract, covering supply, installation, and commissioning, is scheduled for completion by August 2027. Key terms include a 2.5% security deposit and a 0.5% performance bank guarantee. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at HEG Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-heg-ltd-counter/1675266</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675266</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Century Plyboards (India) Ltd, PCBL Chemical Ltd, Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd, The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 11 February 2026.

Century Plyboards (India) Ltd, PCBL Chemical Ltd, Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd, The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 11 February 2026. HEG Ltd registered volume of 135.14 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 13.48 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 10.03 lakh shares. The stock slipped 5.12% to Rs.532.00. Volumes stood at 13.49 lakh shares in the last session. Century Plyboards (India) Ltd registered volume of 11.11 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.42 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.07 lakh shares. The stock slipped 2.65% to Rs.781.25. Volumes stood at 51771 shares in the last session. PCBL Chemical Ltd saw volume of 425.71 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.25 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 46.04 lakh shares. The stock increased 10.60% to Rs.325.00. Volumes stood at 17.77 lakh shares in the last session. Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd saw volume of 480.19 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.78 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 70.79 lakh shares. The stock dropped 5.98% to Rs.259.60. Volumes stood at 53.8 lakh shares in the last session. The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd notched up volume of 1.89 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.68 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 28278 shares. The stock rose 2.14% to Rs.1,845.00. Volumes stood at 28610 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HEG_82803491_251.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's petroleum and liquid fuel consumption to hit 5.92 mbpd in 2026 compared to 5.66 mbpd last year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-petroleum-and-liquid-fuel-consumption-to-hit-592-mbpd-in-2026-compared-to-566-mbpd-last-year/1675265</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675265</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US Energy Information Administration of EIA has stated in a latest monthly update that it expects India will increase its liquid fuels consumption by around 0.3 million b/d in next two years.

The US Energy Information Administration of EIA has stated in a latest monthly update that it expects India will increase its liquid fuels consumption by around 0.3 million b/d in next two years. It sees India’s consumption at 5.92 million barrels per day (mbpd) in 2026 and at 6.26 mbpd in 2027. This shows an impressive rise compared to 5.66 mbpd in 2025. India’s liquid fuel output is seen at 1.01 mbpd in 2025 and is expected to rise to 1.06 mbpd this year and to 1.09 mbpd next year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stack-of-four-black-car-tires-isolated-on-white-picture-id1_rubber.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BHEL tumbles after Government launches OFS to pare up to 5% stake]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bhel-tumbles-after-government-launches-ofs-to-pare-up-to-5-stake/1675245</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675245</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India, the company’s promoter, is offering a base lot of 10.44 crore shares, representing 3.00% of the company’s equity.

The Government of India, the company’s promoter, is offering a base lot of 10.44 crore shares, representing 3.00% of the company’s equity. The offer includes an oversubscription option for an additional 6.96 crore shares or 0.79% stake, taking the total potential divestment to 17.4 crore shares, or 5.00% stake. The floor price has been set at Rs 254 per share, a discount of 7.99% to the stock’s previous close of Rs 276.05 on January 27, 2026. The OFS opened on February 11 for non-retail investors. Retail investors can participate on February 12, along with non-retail bidders carrying forward unallotted bids. The offer is being conducted through a special window on the BSE and NSE during market hours. By 2:00 p.m. on T Day, the non-retail portion was subscribed 12.99% of the base offer size. Bids were received for 1.22 crore shares against 9.40 crore shares on base non-retail offer. As of December 2025, the Government of India held a 63.17% stake in Bharat Heavy Electricals. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) is an integrated power plant equipment manufacturer, engaged in the design, engineering, manufacturing, erection, testing, commissioning, and servicing of a diverse range of products and systems. The company caters to key sectors of the Indian economy, including power, transmission, industry, transportation, renewable energy, oil & gas, and defence. BHEL is the flagship engineering and manufacturing enterprise of India and is owned and operated by the Government of India. The company's consolidated net profit surged 189.82% to Rs 390.40 crore while revenue from operations rose 16.43% to Rs 8,473.10 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BHEL_16865551712_2306.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-bank-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1675219</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675219</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

HDFC Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 927.15, down 0.56% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25928.9. The Sensex is at 84179.58, down 0.11%.HDFC Bank Ltd has eased around 1.05% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which HDFC Bank Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 2.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60626.4, up 0.09% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 169.4 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 319.64 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 931.25, down 0.49% on the day. HDFC Bank Ltd jumped 8.64% in last one year as compared to a 12.51% rally in NIFTY and a 22.64% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 19.63 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCBank_24534281400_4987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil India Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-india-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1675220</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675220</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Oil India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 480.2, down 1.77% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25928.9. The Sensex is at 84179.58, down 0.11%.Oil India Ltd has gained around 12.83% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Oil India Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 5.56% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36671, down 0.77% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 67.65 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 70.63 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 476.1, down 1.59% on the day. Oil India Ltd jumped 15% in last one year as compared to a 12.51% rally in NIFTY and a 16.2% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 16.99 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OilIndia_41919311821_5452.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade sideways; IT shares drop; VIX slides 2.16%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-sideways-it-shares-drop-vix-slides-216/1675218</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675218</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded sideways in the afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded sideways in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,950 mark. Auto, pharma and PSU bank shares advanced while IT, private bank and media shares declined. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 59.75 points or 0.07% to 84,215.77. The Nifty 50 index rose 9.35 points or 0.04% to 25,943.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.11% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.05%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,798 shares rose and 2,238 shares fell. A total of 208 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 2.16% to 11.41. Gainers & Losers: Eicher Motors (up 6.16%), Apollo Hospitals Enterprise (up 4.70%), Max Healthcare Institute (up 2.95%), State Bank of India (up 2.79%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 1.58%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Coal India (down 2.34%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 1.88%), Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (down 1.41%), HCL Technologies (down 1.30%) and ITC (down 1.26%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Eicher Motors rose 6.16% after the company reported a 21.38% year-on-year (YoY) increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,170.50 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations surged 22.94% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,114.04 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Apollo Hospitals Enterprise jumped 4.70% after the company reported 34.91% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 502.29 crore on 17.19% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,477.40 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Stocks in Spotlight: Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) added 1.35% after its standalone net profit jumped 32.62% to Rs 3,931.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,964.31 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total income increased by 26.93% year on year to Rs 39,639.45 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Avantel advanced 4.95% after the company said that it has secured an order worth Rs 122.58 crore from M/s. NewSpace India for the supply of S/X-band with Ka-band-ready full-motion antennas. Karnataka Bank fell 1.64%. The bank has reported a 2.5% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 290.79 crore, on a 0.51% decline in total income to Rs 2,522.35 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. Titan Company fell 1.14%. The company has reported 61% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,684 crore on a 40% increase in total income to Rs 24,592 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. TVS Supply Chain Solutions surged 11.80% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 10.72 crore in Q3 December 2025 compared with a net loss of Rs 24.65 crore posted in Q3 December 2024. Revenue from operations jumped 11.09% YoY to Rs 2,715.81 crore during the quarter, supported by continued strength in Integrated Supply Chain Solutions (ISCS) segment and a significant recovery in volumes in the Global Forwarding Solutions (GFS) segment. Global Markets: European markets opened mixed on Wednesday as corporate earnings continue to stay in focus for regional investors. Asia market advanced, continuing their rally even as China's consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier, China’s National Bureau of Statistics data showed Wednesday. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. Japan’s markets are closed for a public holiday. In U.S, December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat following a 0.6% increase in November, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. Overnight, the S&P 500 slipped on Tuesday as investors reacted to weaker-than-expected retail sales data and grew concerned about the threat artificial intelligence poses to the financial sector. The broad-based index lost 0.33% and ended at 6,941.81, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.59% and closed at 23,102.47. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 52.27 points, or 0.10%, posting a closing record of 50,188.14. Financial stocks also took a hit Tuesday after tech platform Altruist launched a new AI-powered tax planning tool. Shares of LPL Financial declined 8.3%, while shares of Charles Schwab dropped 7.4% and Morgan Stanley dipped more than 2%. Investors await the release of big jobs report due on Wednesday, and the consumer price index data on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id51_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd spurts 5.92%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eicher-motors-ltd-spurts-592-gains-for-third-straight-session/1675211</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675211</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Eicher Motors Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 7728, up 5.92% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25916. The Sensex is at 84177.45, down 0.11%. Eicher Motors Ltd has risen around 3.93% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Eicher Motors Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.9% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28173.2, up 1.32% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 17.29 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.11 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 7772, up 6.39% on the day. Eicher Motors Ltd is up 59.36% in last one year as compared to a 12.46% spurt in NIFTY and a 27.39% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 42.62 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EicherMotors_60312767308_151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/samvardhana-motherson-international-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1675212</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675212</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 133, up 2.76% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25916. The Sensex is at 84177.45, down 0.11%. Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd has gained around 15.66% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.9% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28173.2, up 1.32% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 425.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 166.97 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 133.71, up 2.91% on the day. Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is up 55.1% in last one year as compared to a 12.46% jump in NIFTY and a 27.39% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 73.55 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MothersonSumi_60777480057_2966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1675213</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675213</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 385.4, up 1.59% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25916. The Sensex is at 84177.45, down 0.11%. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd has gained around 9.94% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.9% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28173.2, up 1.32% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 76.36 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 116.36 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 387.1, up 1.72% on the day. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd is down 6.97% in last one year as compared to a 12.46% jump in NIFTY and a 27.39% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 25.02 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataMotors_19446492084_560.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd up for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-forge-ltd-up-for-third-consecutive-session/1675214</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675214</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Bharat Forge Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1638, up 1.49% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25916. The Sensex is at 84177.45, down 0.11%. Bharat Forge Ltd has gained around 12.45% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bharat Forge Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.9% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28173.2, up 1.32% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.75 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.75 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1656, up 2.39% on the day. Bharat Forge Ltd is up 48.28% in last one year as compared to a 12.46% jump in NIFTY and a 27.39% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 56.72 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatForge_36016338711_69.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Uno Minda Ltd soars 1.1%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uno-minda-ltd-soars-11/1675215</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675215</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Uno Minda Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Uno Minda Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 1244.8, up 1.1% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25916. The Sensex is at 84177.45, down 0.11%. Uno Minda Ltd has risen around 2.88% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Uno Minda Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.9% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28173.2, up 1.32% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 7.64 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 9.24 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1249, up 1.19% on the day. Uno Minda Ltd is up 25.67% in last one year as compared to a 12.46% spurt in NIFTY and a 27.39% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 72.81 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MindaInds_25112038741_12295.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Britannia Industries rises after Q3 profit climbs 17% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/britannia-industries-rises-after-q3-profit-climbs-17-yoy/1675210</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675210</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 679.96 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.89% YoY from Rs 581.69 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 679.96 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.89% YoY from Rs 581.69 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 3.89% from Rs 654.47 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 9.45% YoY to Rs 4,885.23 crore, compared with Rs 4,463.30 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue grew 2.80% from Rs 4,752.17 crore. Profit before tax rose 18.07% YoY to Rs 919.03 crore from Rs 778.38 crore in Q3 FY25. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PBT increased 4.01% from Rs 883.62 crore. Total expenditure stood at Rs 3,992.49 crore, up 6.47% YoY, while increasing 2.65% sequentially. Raw material consumption rose marginally by 1.26% YoY to Rs 2,662.98 crore. Employee expenses more than doubled, increasing 102.86% YoY to Rs 214.73 crore, while interest costs declined 25.38% YoY to Rs 33.25 crore. Depreciation increased 2.59% YoY to Rs 84.51 crore. Management said the 9.5% revenue growth alongside 17% profit growth indicates a return to healthy expansion, supported by strong momentum in biscuits and adjacent categories, as well as a relatively stable commodity environment. The company noted that while the biscuit industry remains in a stabilization phase following the GST rate reduction, the business recorded around 12% growth in November and December, driven by sustained media investments and portfolio innovations such as the 50-50 Dipped range, ‘Veg’ cake variants and ‘Doodh’ Marie Gold. Looking ahead, Britannia said it will continue to focus on strengthening brand equity through elevated consumer experiences, sustained investments and localized product innovations tailored to diverse demographic and regional preferences across India. Britannia Industries is an Indian multinational food products company, which sells biscuits, breads and dairy products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BritanniaInds_60979410361_93.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd spurts 0.21%, gains for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-state-petronet-ltd-spurts-021-gains-for-fifth-straight-session/1675208</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675208</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Gujarat State Petronet Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 314, up 0.21% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25911.2. The Sensex is at 84112.36, down 0.19%. Gujarat State Petronet Ltd has gained around 2.48% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Gujarat State Petronet Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 5.45% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36671, down 0.87% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.15 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.98 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 24.92 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujStPetronet_95223652929_24065.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>