<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Responsive Industries slides as CFO Bhavneet Singh Chadha resigns]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/responsive-industries-slides-as-cfo-bhavneet-singh-chadha-resigns/1664700</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664700</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Responsive Industries is a leading India-based manufacturer of polyvinyl chloride (PVC)-based products.

Responsive Industries is a leading India-based manufacturer of polyvinyl chloride (PVC)-based products. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 8.1% to Rs 53.26 crore on a 10.2% drop in revenue from operations to Rs 313.75 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ResponsiveInd_23110225263_7102.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mini Diamonds India rises after bagging Rs 14-cr order from Aura Diamond]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mini-diamonds-india-rises-after-bagging-rs-14-cr-order-from-aura-diamond/1664698</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664698</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the order will be executed within four months from the date of order, while payment will be made on or before 150 days from completion.

The company said the order will be executed within four months from the date of order, while payment will be made on or before 150 days from completion. The company added that the transaction is not a related-party deal, and neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the entity awarding the order. Upendra N. Shah, chairman and MD, Mini Diamonds (India), said, “We are encouraged by the increasing momentum in the domestic market and the repeatability we are beginning to see in order sizes. This reflects customers’ confidence in our consistent quality standards, transparent specifications and competitive pricing. We remain focused on disciplined execution and timely fulfilment to deepen customer relationships and strengthen our presence in the lab-grown polished diamond segment.” Mini Diamonds (India) (MDIL) is engaged in the business of manufacturing and trading diamonds. The company reported a standalone net profit of Rs 1.82 crore in Q2 FY26, down 1.1% from Rs 1.84 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 12.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 100.46 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MiniDiamondsIndiaLtd_25057542520_2031.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd Spurts 1.47%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-ltd-spurts-147/1664696</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664696</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd rose 1.47% today to trade at Rs 639.1.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd rose 1.47% today to trade at Rs 639.1. The BSE Metal index is up 0.35% to quote at 37590.07. The index is up 7.54 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Vedanta Ltd increased 1.32% and APL Apollo Tubes Ltd added 0.79% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 35.48 % over last one year compared to the 8.97% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Zinc Ltd has added 12.51% over last one month compared to 7.54% gain in BSE Metal index and 2.18% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 45565 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 7.19 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 656.25 on 29 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 378.65 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Embassy Developments Ltd Falls 1.35%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/embassy-developments-ltd-falls-135/1664697</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664697</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Embassy Developments Ltd lost 1.35% today to trade at Rs 71.

Embassy Developments Ltd lost 1.35% today to trade at Rs 71. The BSE Realty index is down 0.63% to quote at 6650.18. The index is down 3.39 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Godrej Properties Ltd decreased 1.19% and Lodha Developers Ltd lost 0.96% on the day. The BSE Realty index went down 6.96 % over last one year compared to the 8.97% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Embassy Developments Ltd has added 4.49% over last one month compared to 3.39% fall in BSE Realty index and 2.18% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 3645 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 4.19 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 163.7 on 21 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 55.8 on 05 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndbullRealEst_49523889882_27800.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at flat opening for key indices; Japanese indices surge to record high levels]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-flat-opening-for-key-indices-japanese-indices-surge-to-record-high-levels/1664690</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664690</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 0.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 0.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,499.81 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,181.78 crore in the Indian equity market on 13 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 16,925.03 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asian market traded mixed even as Japanese indexes hit record highs on Wednesday. The rally in Japanese stocks was fuelled by expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi could call for a snap election, likely in February. If called, it will be Takaichi’s first time facing Japan’s voters in an election. Overnight in the U.S., all three major indexes fell as investors grappled with volatility from a flurry of proposals from U.S. President Donald Trump floated in the past few days. The S&P 500 dipped 0.19% as investors sold JPMorgan despite better-than-expected numbers, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.8%. The Nasdaq Composite fell 0.1%. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks closed lower on Tuesday after an early rebound fizzled out, leaving markets bruised by heavy intraday selling and fragile sentiment. The BSE Sensex slid as much as 995 points from the day’s high, while the Nifty 50 dropped 296 points as selling pressure intensified through the session. The Nifty, which touched an intraday high of 25,899.80 in early trade, slipped below the 25,750 mark by the close. Consumer durables and pharmaceutical stocks were among the worst hit. The decline was driven largely by profit-taking in heavyweight stocks after the recent rally, with investors choosing to lock in gains amid uncertain global cues. Rising crude oil prices added to the pressure, stoking concerns over inflation and the current account outlook. Persistent foreign institutional selling weighed on sentiment, even as domestic participation remained robust. The rupee’s weakness against the dollar further dampened risk appetite, especially for import-sensitive sectors. From a technical perspective, market indicators continued to flag fragile momentum, suggesting limited near-term upside and keeping traders cautious amid elevated volatility. The S&P BSE Sensex slipped 250.48 points or 0.30% to 83,627.69. The Nifty 50 index lost 57.95 points or 0.22% to 25,732.30.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Interarch Building Solutions bags Rs 130-cr pre-engineered steel building contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/interarch-building-solutions-bags-rs-130-cr-pre-engineered-steel-building-contract/1664686</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664686</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order, awarded by a domestic entity, will be executed over a period of 17 months and includes an advance payment of 10%.

The order, awarded by a domestic entity, will be executed over a period of 17 months and includes an advance payment of 10%. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the entity awarding the contract. Interarch Building Solutions provides turnkey pre-engineered steel construction solutions in India. The company’s standalone net profit soared 56.12% to Rs 32.27 crore on a 51.91% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 491.08 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Interarch Building Solutions fell 3.81% to close at Rs 2,075.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InterarchBuildingProductsPvtLtd_48358915_40098.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Tata Elxsi,  Just Dial, Hi-Tech Gears, Interarch Building Solutions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-tata-elxsi-just-dial-hi-tech-gears-interarch-building-solutions/1664680</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664680</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 14 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 14 January 2026. Result Today: Infosys, HDFC AMC, ICICI Prudential AMC, Union Bank of India, Billionbrains Garage Ventures (Groww), Anand Rathi Share and Stock Brokers, Aditya Birla Money, Den Networks, HDB Financial Services, Indian Overseas Bank, Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals, Network 18 Media & Investments, Plastiblends India, Indosolar, and Waaree Renewable Technologies will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Tata Elxsi reported a 45.28% decline in net profit to Rs 108.89 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 199 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 1.52% to Rs 953.47 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 939.17 crore in Q3 FY25. Just Dial reported a 10.18% decline in net profit to Rs 117.93 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 131.31 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 6.38% to Rs 305.69 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 287.33 crore in Q3 FY25. Hi-Tech Gears said Kapil Rajora has resigned from his position as chief financial officer, and the company has appointed Vinod Raheja as the new CFO, effective 14 January 2026. Interarch Building Solutions said it has received an order worth Rs 130 crore from a customer for the manufacture of a pre-engineered steel building system. NLC India said it has entered into a pact with the Gujarat government to develop large-scale renewable energy projects in the state.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>