<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI issues draft amendment directions for Advertising, Marketing and Sales of Financial Products and Services by Regulated Entities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-issues-draft-amendment-directions-for-advertising-marketing-and-sales-of-financial-products-and-services-by-regulated-entities/1675320</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675320</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated today that currently, instructions on customer appropriateness and suitability and other related matters in the context of insurance agency business have been issued to Scheduled Commercial Banks (excluding Regional Rural Banks) and Housing Finance Companies.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated today that currently, instructions on customer appropriateness and suitability and other related matters in the context of insurance agency business have been issued to Scheduled Commercial Banks (excluding Regional Rural Banks) and Housing Finance Companies. Upon a review, it has been decided to issue comprehensive instructions on advertising, marketing and sales of financial products and services (including third-party products and services) to all banks and NBFCs, which shall include various aspects related thereto, such as activities of Direct Sales Agents (DSAs) / Direct Marketing Agents (DMAs), dark patterns, prevention of mis-selling, etc. Accordingly, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has today issued the following draft Amendment Directions for public comments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/globe-on-top-of-financial-papers-picture-id184927604_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper swells around 3%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-swells-around-3/1675319</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675319</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper impressively today as metals jumped amid tepid US dollar.

COMEX Copper impressively today as metals jumped amid tepid US dollar. Equities were mixed. In Asai, Shanghai Composite index closed flat. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index added 0.31%. Japanese markets were closed for a holiday. European stocks mostly eased as earnings stayed in focus. The US stocks were choppy after recent surge. Dow hit a new record intraday high though. The US dollar index is at 96.50, holding around one and half week low and is pushing metals higher. COMEX Copper futures broke above $6 per pound and currently quote at $6.08 per pound, up 2.76% on the day. The metal has zoomed near one-week high with this spike. MCX Copper futures are up 3% at Rs 1270 per kg as a break above Rs 1250 per kg mark triggered excellent upmove in afternoon trades.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Fractal Analytics IPO subscribed 2.66 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fractal-analytics-ipo-subscribed-266-times/1675316</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675316</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Fractal Analytics received bids for 4,94,79,840 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026).

Fractal Analytics received bids for 4,94,79,840 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 2.66 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it will close on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 16 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The Rs 2,833.9 crore IPO comprises a fresh issue of 11,372,222 equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,023.5 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 20,115,556 equity shares worth Rs 1,810.4 crore at the upper price band of Rs 900. Fractal will utilize Rs 264.9 crore from the net fresh issue proceeds to invest in its unit, Fractal USA, for repayment of its borrowings; Rs 57.1 crore for the purchase of laptops; Rs 121.1 crore will be utilized for setting up of new office premises in India; and Rs 355.1 crore for investment in R&D and sales and marketing under Fractal Alpha. The remaining funds will be utilized for general corporate purposes. Fractal Analytics is an enterprise AI company providing end-to-end artificial intelligence solutions to global enterprises to support data-driven decision-making. With over 25 years of experience, the company operates through Fractal.ai and Fractal Alpha, serving clients across CPG and retail, TMT, healthcare and life sciences, and BFSI, with a customer base that includes several leading global corporations. Ahead of the IPO of Fractal Analytics on 6 February 2026, the company raised Rs 474.99 crore from anchor investors by allotting 52.77 lakh shares at Rs 900 each to 22 anchor investors. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 70.90 crore and sales of Rs 1,559 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee Fades]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-fades/1675314</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675314</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.7500 per Dollar on Wednesday (11 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.6025 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aye Finance IPO subscribed 97% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aye-finance-ipo-subscribed-97/1675315</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675315</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Aye Finance received bids for 4,42,21,288 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Aye Finance received bids for 4,42,21,288 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.97 times. The issue opened for bidding on Monday (9 February 2026) and it will be close on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 116 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue also consists of offer for sale (OFS) of Rs 300 crore through issuance of 2.33-2.46 crore equity shares. The OFS from investor selling shareholders is Rs 30 crore from Alpha Wave India I LP, Rs 139.763 crore from MAJ Invest Financial Inclusion Fund II K/S, Rs 82.5 crore from CapitalG L P, Rs 30 crore from LGT Capital Invest Mauritius PCC with Cell E/VP and Rs 17.737 crore from Vikram Jetley. The company proposes to utilize the net proceeds from the fresh issue towards augmenting the capital base to meet future capital requirements. Ahead of the IPO, Aye Finance Labs on 8 February 2026, the company raised Rs 454.49 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 3. 52 crore shares at Rs 129 each to 19 anchor investors. Aye Finance incorporated in 1993 is Delhi based non-banking financial company – middle layer (NBFC-ML) focused on providing loans to micro scale micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMEs) across India. It offers a range of small ticket business loans with average ticket size on disbursement at Rs 1.8 lakh for working capital and business expansion needs, against hypothecation of working assets or against security of property to customers across manufacturing, trading, service and allied agriculture sectors. Gross NPA ratio has increased from 2.49% at end March 2023 to 4.21% at end March 2025 and 4.85% end September 2025. The capital adequacy ratio was 32.27%, with Tier I capital comprising 32.27% and Tier II capital comprising Nil at end September 2025. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 64.6 crore and income from operations of Rs 733.83 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR ends on muted note amid choppy equities; Dollar demand from importers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-ends-on-muted-note-amid-choppy-equities-dollar-demand-from-importers/1675310</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675310</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee depreciated 14 paise to close at 90.70 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday, on dollar demand from importers and geopolitical tensions.

The Indian rupee depreciated 14 paise to close at 90.70 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday, on dollar demand from importers and geopolitical tensions. Local shares also ended on a muted note tracking mixed cues from global markets and amid profit taking after three days of gains on optimism surrounding an interim trade agreement with the United States. Higher oil prices also kept investors on edge ahead of a meeting between Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and U.S. President Donald Trump that would halt Iran's uranium enrichment. The benchmark BSE Sensex slipped 40.28 points to end at 84,233.64, while the broader NSE Nifty index closed up 18.70 points at 25,953.85. However, FPI inflows may support the local unit at lower levels. At the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 90.56 against the US dollar, and touched a low of 90.75 and a high of 90.46 against the greenback in intraday trade.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end flat; Nifty above 25,950 amid caution before US jobs data]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-flat-nifty-above-25950-amid-caution-before-us-jobs-data/1675308</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675308</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended almost flat on Wednesday, as gains in select sectors were offset by caution ahead of global triggers.

The key domestic indices ended almost flat on Wednesday, as gains in select sectors were offset by caution ahead of global triggers. The market opened on a positive note, with the Nifty reclaiming the 26,000 mark in early trade. However, momentum faded as the session progressed, and the index moved in a narrow range for the remainder of the day as investors refrained from aggressive bets ahead of Wednesday’s US jobs report. The Nifty eventually settled above the 25,950 mark. Sectorally, auto, PSU bank and pharma stocks witnessed buying interest, while IT and private bank shares came under pressure. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 40.28 points or 0.05% to 84,233.64. The Nifty 50 index rose 18.70 points or 0.07% to 25,953.85. TCS (down 2.51%), Infosys (down 1.75%) and HDFC Bank (down 0.54%) put pressure on the Nifty today. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index shed 0.02% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.13%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,913 shares rose and 2,316 shares fell. A total of 162 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1% to 11.56. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.25% to 6.710 compared with previous session close of 6.727. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6800 compared with its close of 90.5600 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 1.71% to Rs 159,485. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.34% to 96.53. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.39% to 4.129. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 93 cents or 1.35% to $69.73 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European indices declined as traders remained cautious ahead of closely watched U.S. jobs data later in the day that could reshape expectations for Federal Reserve interest rates. Asia market ended higher as investors assessed soft Chinese inflation figures. China's consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. Japan’s markets were closed for a public holiday. In U.S, December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat following a 0.6% increase in November, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. Overnight, the S&P 500 slipped on Tuesday as investors reacted to weaker-than-expected retail sales data and grew concerned about the threat artificial intelligence poses to the financial sector. The broad-based index lost 0.33% and ended at 6,941.81, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.59% and closed at 23,102.47. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 52.27 points, or 0.10%, posting a closing record of 50,188.14. Financial stocks also took a hit Tuesday after tech platform Altruist launched a new AI-powered tax planning tool. Shares of LPL Financial declined 8.3%, while shares of Charles Schwab dropped 7.4% and Morgan Stanley dipped more than 2%. Stocks in Spotlght: Eicher Motors rallied 6.53% after the company reported a 21.38% year-on-year (YoY) increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,170.50 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations surged 22.94% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,114.04 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) shed 0.02%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 32.62% to Rs 3,931.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,964.31 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total income increased by 26.93% year on year to Rs 39,639.45 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Britannia Industries gained 2.43% after reporting steady growth in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 679.96 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.89% YoY from Rs 581.69 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 3.89% from Rs 654.47 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 9.45% YoY to Rs 4,885.23 crore, compared with Rs 4,463.30 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue grew 2.80% from Rs 4,752.17 crore. Juniper Hotels gained 0.92% after the company reported a strong performance for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, profit after tax more than doubled to Rs 65.4 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 101% YoY increase from Rs 32.5 crore. On a sequential basis, PAT rose sharply by 277% from Rs 16.8 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 295.1 crore in Q3 FY26, up 17% YoY from Rs 252.5 crore in Q3 FY25 and 28% QoQ from Rs 230.3 crore in Q2 FY26. Titan Company fell 0.45%. The company has reported 61% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,684 crore on a 40% increase in total income to Rs 24,592 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Apollo Hospitals Enterprise jumped 3.93% after the company reported 34.91% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 502.29 crore on 17.19% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,477.40 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Britannia Industries gained 2.43% after reporting steady growth in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 679.96 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.89% YoY from Rs 581.69 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 3.89% from Rs 654.47 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 9.45% YoY to Rs 4,885.23 crore, compared with Rs 4,463.30 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue grew 2.80% from Rs 4,752.17 crore. Laxmi Dental dropped 9.07% after its consolidated net profit fell 59.45% to Rs 1.95 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 4.81 crore in Q3 FY25. However, total income rose 9.43% to Rs 68.11 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.24 crore in Q3 FY25. Avantel advanced 2.62% after the company said that it has secured an order worth Rs 122.58 crore from NewSpace India for the supply of S/X-band with Ka-band-ready full-motion antennas. The contract, covering supply, installation, and commissioning, is scheduled for completion by August 2027. Key terms include a 2.5% security deposit and a 0.5% performance bank guarantee. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) slumped 5.58% after the company’s promoter announced an offer for sale to pare its stake in the company. As of December 2025, the Government of India held a 63.17% stake in BHEL. The floor price has been set at Rs 254 per share, a discount of 7.99% to the stock’s previous close of Rs 276.05 on January 27, 2026. At 3:30 p.m. on T Day, the non-retail portion was subscribed 234.81% of the base offer size. Bids were received for 22.07 crore shares against 9.40 crore shares on base non-retail offer. TVS Supply Chain Solutions surged 14.01% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 10.72 crore in Q3 December 2025 compared with a net loss of Rs 24.65 crore posted in Q3 December 2024. Revenue from operations jumped 11.09% YoY to Rs 2,715.81 crore during the quarter, supported by continued strength in Integrated Supply Chain Solutions (ISCS) segment and a significant recovery in volumes in the Global Forwarding Solutions (GFS) segment. IPO Update: Fractal Analytics received bids for 4,94,59,568 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:50 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 2.66 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it will be close on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. Aye Finance received bids for 4,42,03,308 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:50 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.97 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it will be close on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI unveiles draft amendments to lending norms for Urban Cooperative Banks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-unveiles-draft-amendments-to-lending-norms-for-urban-cooperative-banks/1675306</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675306</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has unveiled draft amendments to lending norms for Urban Cooperative Banks (UCBs).

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has unveiled draft amendments to lending norms for Urban Cooperative Banks (UCBs). It is proposing to double the aggregate ceiling for unsecured advances to 20% of total assets. The proposals also include enhanced individual loan limits and deregulation for housing loans for certain UCB tiers. The RBI is launching Mission-SAKSHAM, a significant capacity-building program aimed at training over 1.4 lakh UCB personnel. As per the draft directions, Tier 3 and Tier 4 UCBs will be permitted to determine the tenure and moratorium period of housing loans in accordance with their Board-approved policies. In contrast, Tier 1 and Tier 2 UCBs will continue to be governed by a maximum housing loan tenor of 20 years, including the moratorium period, with the moratorium capped at 18 months. The RBI has also proposed revised limits for individual unsecured advances, linked to the tier of the UCB. Under the draft norms, the maximum unsecured loan per borrower has been fixed at Rs 5 lakh for Tier 1 UCBs, Rs 7.5 lakh for Tier 2 UCBs, and Rs 10 lakh for Tier 3 and Tier 4 UCBs, within the overall unsecured lending ceiling prescribed under the concentration risk framework. RBI has noted that moratorium in housing loans shall be permitted only for loans granted for construction of houses. Consequently, moratorium shall not be allowed in housing loans extended for the purchase of completed houses. The proposed amendments are scheduled to come into force from October 1, 2026, or earlier if adopted in entirety by a UCB, following finalisation after public consultation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/concept-money-tree-on-grass-picture-id462171033_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1675305</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675305</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,989.70 a premium of 35.85 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,953.85 in the cash market.

The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,989.70 a premium of 35.85 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,953.85 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index advanced 18.70 points or 0.07% to 25,953.85. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1% to 11.56. State Bank of India(SBI), Bharat Heavy Electrical (BHEL) and HDFC Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end near flat line; Nifty ends above 25,950 mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-near-flat-line-nifty-ends-above-25950-mark/1675299</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675299</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended sideways, amid mixed global cues.

The key domestic indices ended sideways, amid mixed global cues. The Nifty ended above the 25,950 mark. Auto, PSU Bank and pharma shares advanced while IT and private bank stocks declined. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 40.28 points or 0.05% to 84,233.64. The Nifty 50 index rose 18.70 points or 0.07% to 25,953.85. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index shed 0.02% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.13%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1% to 11.56. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Auto index (up 1.03%), the Nifty PSU bank index (up 1.03%) and the Nifty Pharma index (up 1.01%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 1.76%), the Nifty Private Bank index (down 0.16%) and the Nifty FMCG index (up 0.04%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.25% to 6.710 compared with previous session close of 6.727. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6800 compared with its close of 90.5600 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 1.71% to Rs 159,485. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.34% to 96.53. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.39% to 4.129. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 93 cents or 1.35% to $69.73 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets traded mixed as global investors awaited the US nonfarm payroll data. Asia market ended higher even as China's consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier, China’s National Bureau of Statistics data showed Wednesday. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. Japan’s markets were closed for a public holiday. In U.S, December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat following a 0.6% increase in November, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. Overnight, the S&P 500 slipped on Tuesday as investors reacted to weaker-than-expected retail sales data and grew concerned about the threat artificial intelligence poses to the financial sector. The broad-based index lost 0.33% and ended at 6,941.81, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.59% and closed at 23,102.47. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 52.27 points, or 0.10%, posting a closing record of 50,188.14. Financial stocks also took a hit Tuesday after tech platform Altruist launched a new AI-powered tax planning tool. Shares of LPL Financial declined 8.3%, while shares of Charles Schwab dropped 7.4% and Morgan Stanley dipped more than 2%. Investors await the consumer price index data on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers end sideways; auto shares jump]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-end-sideways-auto-shares-jump/1675295</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675295</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended with sideways trend, supported by mixed global cues.

The key domestic indices ended with sideways trend, supported by mixed global cues. Investors will continue to monitor the ongoing earnings season, US nonfarm payroll data, and other global developments. The Nifty ended above the 25,950 mark. Auto, PSU Bank and pharma shares advanced while IT and private bank stocks declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 40.28 points or 0.05% to 84,233.64. The Nifty 50 index rose 18.70 points or 0.07% to 25,953.85. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index shed 0.02% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.13%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,975 shares rose and 2,247 shares fell. A total of 169 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1% to 11.56. IPO Update: Fractal Analytics received bids for 4,91,39,568 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 2.64 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it will be close on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. Aye Finance received bids for 4,39,31,752 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.96 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it will be close on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index surged 1.30% to 28,538.70. The index climbed 3.7% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Eicher Motors (up 6.59%), Bharat Forge (up 3.87%), TVS Motor Company (up 2.73%), Bosch (up 2.53%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 1.76%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (up 1.3%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 1.25%), Uno Minda (up 1.19%), Bajaj Auto (up 0.98%) and Exide Industries (up 0.68%) surged. Eicher Motors rallied 6.59% after the company reported a 21.38% year-on-year (YoY) increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,170.50 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations surged 22.94% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,114.04 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Stocks in Spotlght: Titan Company fell 0.45%. The company has reported 61% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,684 crore on a 40% increase in total income to Rs 24,592 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Apollo Hospitals Enterprise jumped 4% after the company reported 34.91% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 502.29 crore on 17.19% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,477.40 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) shed 0.02%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 32.62% to Rs 3,931.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,964.31 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total income increased by 26.93% year on year to Rs 39,639.45 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Britannia Industries gained 2.60% after reporting steady growth in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 679.96 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.89% YoY from Rs 581.69 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 3.89% from Rs 654.47 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 9.45% YoY to Rs 4,885.23 crore, compared with Rs 4,463.30 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue grew 2.80% from Rs 4,752.17 crore. Avantel advanced 2.23% after the company said that it has secured an order worth Rs 122.58 crore from NewSpace India for the supply of S/X-band with Ka-band-ready full-motion antennas. The contract, covering supply, installation, and commissioning, is scheduled for completion by August 2027. Key terms include a 2.5% security deposit and a 0.5% performance bank guarantee. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) slumped 5.58% after the company’s promoter announced an offer for sale to pare its stake in the company. As of December 2025, the Government of India held a 63.17% stake in BHEL. The floor price has been set at Rs 254 per share, a discount of 7.99% to the stock’s previous close of Rs 276.05 on January 27, 2026. At 3:30 p.m. on T Day, the non-retail portion was subscribed 234.81% of the base offer size. Bids were received for 22.07 crore shares against 9.40 crore shares on base non-retail offer. Karnataka Bank rose 0.10%. The bank has reported a 2.5% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 290.79 crore, on a 0.51% decline in total income to Rs 2,522.35 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. TVS Supply Chain Solutions surged 14.01% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 10.72 crore in Q3 December 2025 compared with a net loss of Rs 24.65 crore posted in Q3 December 2024. Revenue from operations jumped 11.09% YoY to Rs 2,715.81 crore during the quarter, supported by continued strength in Integrated Supply Chain Solutions (ISCS) segment and a significant recovery in volumes in the Global Forwarding Solutions (GFS) segment. Global Markets: European markets traded mixed as global investors awaited the US nonfarm payroll data. Asia market ended higher even as China's consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier, China’s National Bureau of Statistics data showed Wednesday. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. Japan’s markets were closed for a public holiday. In U.S, December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat following a 0.6% increase in November, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. Overnight, the S&P 500 slipped on Tuesday as investors reacted to weaker-than-expected retail sales data and grew concerned about the threat artificial intelligence poses to the financial sector. The broad-based index lost 0.33% and ended at 6,941.81, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.59% and closed at 23,102.47. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 52.27 points, or 0.10%, posting a closing record of 50,188.14. Financial stocks also took a hit Tuesday after tech platform Altruist launched a new AI-powered tax planning tool. Shares of LPL Financial declined 8.3%, while shares of Charles Schwab dropped 7.4% and Morgan Stanley dipped more than 2%. Investors await the consumer price index data on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index declines 1.76%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-declines-176/1675294</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675294</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index ended down 1.76% at 35095.15 today.

Nifty IT index ended down 1.76% at 35095.15 today. The index is down 8.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, LTIMindtree Ltd slipped 2.59%, Persistent Systems Ltd shed 2.53% and Tata Consultancy Services Ltd dropped 2.51%. The Nifty IT index is down 16.00% over last one year compared to the 12.49% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Auto index added 1.30% and Nifty PSU Bank index added 1.03% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 recorded a gain of 0.07% to close at 25953.85 while the SENSEX is down 0.05% to close at 84233.64 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/blue-stock-chart-growth-picture-id174673054_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Laxmi Dental tanks as Q3 PAT drops 59% YoY to Rs 2 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/laxmi-dental-tanks-as-q3-pat-drops-59-yoy-to-rs-2-cr/1675291</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675291</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, total income jumped 9.43% to Rs 68.11 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.24 crore in Q3 FY25.

However, total income jumped 9.43% to Rs 68.11 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.24 crore in Q3 FY25. The company posted pre loss tax of Rs 1.28 crore in Q3 FY26 as against profit before tax of Rs 4.71 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA fell by 27.47% to Rs 6.97 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 9.61 crore recorded in the similar quarter last year. EBITDA Margin redcuced to 10.6% in Q3 FY26 as against 15.6% in Q3 FY25. Based on the requirements of the new labour codes, the company recorded an incremental impact of Rs 5.8 crore as an exceptional item for the quarter. Rajesh Khakhar, Chairperson and whole-time director (WTD) said, “In Q3FY26, the company delivered revenues of Rs 660 Mn as against Rs 61.7 cr in same period last year, recording a YoY growth of 7%. The performance is despite global macroeconomic and geopolitical challenges, underscoring the strength and resilience of our diversified portfolio. Gross profit margins witnessed minor improvement sequentially due to steady profitability in the laboratory and aligner business alongside a relatively lower contribution of scanner sales, which are low margin in nature. Scanner sales hold strategic importance for future growth across segments. During Q3, we had a full quarter impact of 150 bps on account of higher US tariffs. Additionally, we recorded a one-time exceptional provision of Rs 58 Mn towards gratuity past service liability under the new labour code. With US tariff normalization, positive development of EU FTA, multiple ongoing strategic initiatives, and consolidation in the domestic dental market, Laxmi Dental is well positioned to deliver resilient, industry-leading growth along with improved profitability going ahead.” Sameer Merchant, Managing Director and CEO, said, “For Q3FY26, our Dental Lab business recorded a healthy YoY growth of 10.4%, with the international business delivering robust 25.5% YoY growth, while the domestic lab remained soft. During the quarter, we implemented innovative strategies, which have started showing positive results in January 2026. Within the Aligner Solutions business, competitive pricing pressures on Bizdent are normalizing in Q4FY26, and we anticipate the situation to remain favorable throughout the quarter. With these new strategic initiatives, we are witnessing a strong recovery in our domestic Dental Lab and Bizdent businesses, and we expect both segments to deliver robust YoY performance in Q4FY26. On the back of these positive trends, we aim to close FY26 with a healthy exit quarter and begin FY27 on a stronger footing. Over the long term, we remain committed to promoting digital dentistry and leading this transformation across the Indian dental industry, leveraging our scanner solutions.” Laxmi Dental is an integrated dental products company offering a comprehensive portfolio of Dental Products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LaxmiDentalLtd_11720780_86134.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MIC Electronics gains on bagging Rs 4-cr order from Eastern Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mic-electronics-gains-on-bagging-rs-4-cr-order-from-eastern-railway/1675287</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675287</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order, awarded domestically through a tender, is scheduled for execution within six months.

The order, awarded domestically through a tender, is scheduled for execution within six months. The company stated that neither promoters nor promoter group companies have any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not qualify as a related party deal. Terms and conditions will be finalized at the time of agreement execution. MIC Electronics specializes in the design, development, and manufacturing of LED video displays as well as high-end electronics and telecommunications products. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 1.9% to Rs 2.17 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 2.13 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 38% YoY to Rs 37.89 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MICElectronics_24566174444_27654.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Surya Roshni tanks as Q3 PAT drops 11% YoY to Rs 80 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/surya-roshni-tanks-as-q3-pat-drops-11-yoy-to-rs-80-cr/1675282</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675282</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit after tax (PAT) for the quarter was impacted by inventory losses in the Steel Pipes business due to steel price corrections, partially offset by improved sequential operating performance.

Profit after tax (PAT) for the quarter was impacted by inventory losses in the Steel Pipes business due to steel price corrections, partially offset by improved sequential operating performance. However, revenue from operations rose 3.18% year on year to Rs 1,927.49 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 107.42 crore in the Q3 FY26, down 11% year-on-year (YoY). EBITDA fell by 5% to Rs 148 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 156 crore recorded in the similar quarter last year. The Lighting & Consumer Durables segment delivered steady growth, with revenue increasing 6% year-on-year to Rs 476 crore. Performance was supported by festive demand, strong traction in LED bulbs, battens and downlighters, and continued momentum in professional lighting, despite input cost pressures in select appliance categories. The Steel Pipes business reported stable revenue of Rs 1,451 crore, driven by higher dispatch volumes and a healthy product mix. EBITDA was impacted by inventory losses following a decline in steel prices, although value-added products and hollow sections continued to perform well. Commenting on the results, Managing Director Mr. Raju Bista said, “During Q3FY26, we delivered steady performance despite a volatile operating environment. Consolidated revenue increased 3% YoY to Rs 1,927 crore, with EBITDA at Rs 148 crore (7.7% margin). PAT stood at Rs 80 crore, lower YoY due to inventory losses in the Steel Pipes business following steel price corrections, though profitability improved sequentially. The Lighting & Consumer Durables segment grew 6% YoY to Rs 476 crore, led by festive demand and strong traction in consumer and professional lighting. Margins remained stable sequentially despite input cost pressures. The Steel Pipes business reported revenue of Rs 1,451 crore, supported by higher volumes and a healthy mix. EBITDA margins moderated due to steel price–related inventory losses, while underlying operations remained resilient.” Vinay Surya, Managing Director, added, “In Lighting, consumer categories delivered strong volume growth, particularly LED bulbs, battens and downlighters. Professional lighting continues to see robust demand, with an order book of Rs 150 crore. While appliances were relatively muted, recovery is expected in the coming quarters. In Steel Pipes, volume momentum remained healthy, with 2.37 lakh tonnes sold during the quarter. EBITDA per tonne stood at Rs 4,810, impacted by steel price correction. Value-added products contributed 42% of mix, and exports accounted for 19% of volumes. Capacity expansion across plants remains on track to support future growth.” Commenting on the financial performance, Bharat Bhushan Singal, CFO said, “For Q3FY26, revenue stood at Rs 1,927 crore, up 3% YoY. EBITDA and PAT were Rs 148 crore and Rs 80 crore, respectively, compared to Rs 156 crore and Rs 90 crore last year. For 9MFY26, revenue grew 2% YoY to Rs 5,377 crore, with EBITDA of Rs 371 crore and PAT of Rs 188 crore. In Lighting & Consumer Durables, Q3 revenue increased 6% YoY to Rs 476 crore, with EBITDA and PBT at Rs 42 crore and Rs 31 crore, respectively. For 9MFY26, revenue rose 6% to Rs 1,308 crore, with EBITDA of Rs 112 crore and PBT of Rs 82 crore. In Steel Pipes & Strips, Q3 revenue stood at Rs 1,451 crore, up 2% YoY. EBITDA per tonne was Rs 4,810. EBITDA and PBT were Rs 106 crore and Rs 76 crore, respectively. For 9MFY26, revenue was Rs 4,069 crore, with EBITDA of Rs 259 crore and PBT of Rs 171 crore. During Q3FY26, the Net Working Capital cycle stood at 61 days, with ROCE of 17.57% and ROE of 12.65%. Improved capacity utilization and working capital discipline enabled us to become debt-free, with a cash surplus of Rs 245 crore.” Surya Roshni incorporated in 1973 has emerged as India’s largest ERW Pipes exporter, largest GI Pipes producer, and the second largest in the lighting segment. Its focus is on developing the value-added product mix (3LPE Coated pipes, Alkyd pipes, etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuryaRoshni_1295167499_445.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AUM of mutual fund industry rises to Rs 81.01 lakh crore in Jan: AMFI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aum-of-mutual-fund-industry-rises-to-rs-8101-lakh-crore-in-jan-amfi/1675283</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675283</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The net assets under the management (AUM) of the Indian mutual fund industry at the end of January 2026 stood at Rs 81.01 lakh crore, according to data from the Association of Mutual Funds of India (AMFI).

The net assets under the management (AUM) of the Indian mutual fund industry at the end of January 2026 stood at Rs 81.01 lakh crore, according to data from the Association of Mutual Funds of India (AMFI). This is slightly higher as compared with the figure of Rs 80.23 lakh crore recorded in December 2025. The AUM of open-ended plans rose to Rs 80.76 lakh crore in January 2026 from Rs 79.98 lakh crore in December 2025. The equity plans in this category recorded net inflows of Rs 24,028.59 crore. Within equity, Flexi Cap Fund drew the most significant inflows in December, attracting Rs 7,672.36 crore. Mid Cap Funds followed suit with inflows of Rs 3,185.47 crore, while ELSS saw net outflows of Rs 593.69 crore. Debt funds witnessed net inflows in January, totaling Rs 74,827.13 crore. This category had recorded net outflows of Rs 1,32,410.37 crore in December. Overnight Funds recorded maximum inflows of Rs 46,280.05 crore. While segments like Liquid Funds and Money Market Funds saw total inflows of Rs 43,445.02 crore, Corporate Bond Funds recorded outflows of Rs 11,472.79 crore. Hybrid schemes, offering a mix of equity and debt exposure, recorded net inflows of Rs 17,356.02 crore in January 2026. This was largely driven by Multi Asset Allocation Funds, which attracted Rs 10,485.38 crore. The systematic investment plan (SIP) contributions remained unchanged at Rs 31,002 crore in January 2026 as compared to December 2025. The number of contributing SIP accounts also rose from 9.79 crore in December to 9.92 crore in January, while SIP assets under management (AUM) dipped marginally to Rs 16.36 lakh crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sterlite Technologies Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sterlite-technologies-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1675277</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675277</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Safari Industries (India) Ltd, Pearl Global Industries Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Surya Roshni Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 11 February 2026.

Safari Industries (India) Ltd, Pearl Global Industries Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Surya Roshni Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 11 February 2026. Sterlite Technologies Ltd crashed 8.60% to Rs 144.05 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 19.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.25 lakh shares in the past one month. Safari Industries (India) Ltd tumbled 7.88% to Rs 1977.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 4945 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1500 shares in the past one month. Pearl Global Industries Ltd lost 6.95% to Rs 1501. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 12933 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19682 shares in the past one month. Poly Medicure Ltd shed 6.38% to Rs 1391.6. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 26894 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 65449 shares in the past one month. Surya Roshni Ltd slipped 6.01% to Rs 234.55. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 74351 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12749 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SterliteTech_57490273283_21331.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude climbs above $64 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-climbs-above-64-per-barrel/1675275</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675275</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures climbed above $64 per barrel on Wednesday, snapping the previous session’s losses as persistent US-Iran tensions lent support to prices.

WTI crude oil futures climbed above $64 per barrel on Wednesday, snapping the previous session’s losses as persistent US-Iran tensions lent support to prices. Gains were capped after a US industry report showed a sharp rise in crude inventories, with stockpiles surging by 13.4 million barrels last week—the biggest build since November 2023 if confirmed by official data. Markets now await OPEC’s monthly outlook and the IEA’s assessment, which has warned that global supply is likely to outpace demand this year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold gains as fed cut bets grow and geopolitical risks linger]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-gains-as-fed-cut-bets-grow-and-geopolitical-risks-linger/1675274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675274</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices surged 1% to around $5,080 per ounce on Wednesday, supported by strong safe-haven demand and sustained central bank buying.

Gold prices surged 1% to around $5,080 per ounce on Wednesday, supported by strong safe-haven demand and sustained central bank buying. China extended its gold purchases for a 15th consecutive month, reinforcing bullish sentiment. The US dollar weakened ahead of the delayed January non-farm payrolls report. The dollar index slipped to around 96.4 after soft US retail sales data raised expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts. Geopolitical risks, including lingering US-Iran tensions and ongoing Russia-Ukraine hostilities despite diplomatic efforts, continued to underpin prices. In India, MCX April gold futures climbed over 1% to ₹1,58,140 per 10 grams, with investors now watching upcoming US jobs and inflation data closely.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tokyo Plast International Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tokyo-plast-international-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1675271</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675271</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[N K Industries Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd, Laxmi Dental Ltd and Som Distilleries & Breweries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 11 February 2026.

N K Industries Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd, Laxmi Dental Ltd and Som Distilleries & Breweries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 11 February 2026. Tokyo Plast International Ltd crashed 14.27% to Rs 101.5 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 648 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 530 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd lost 11.71% to Rs 60.04. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 20 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 285 shares in the past one month. Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd tumbled 10.38% to Rs 5.44. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15459 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6831 shares in the past one month. Laxmi Dental Ltd fell 9.29% to Rs 205.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 30227 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22827 shares in the past one month. Som Distilleries & Breweries Ltd corrected 8.99% to Rs 87.4. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.53 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 39959 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TokyoPlastInternationalLtd_60698755021_4159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>