<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waaree Energies Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waaree-energies-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679485</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679485</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SpiceJet Ltd, Websol Energy System Ltd, Premier Energies Ltd and Welspun Living Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 25 February 2026.

SpiceJet Ltd, Websol Energy System Ltd, Premier Energies Ltd and Welspun Living Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 25 February 2026. Waaree Energies Ltd tumbled 10.18% to Rs 2717.25 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 8.37 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 87566 shares in the past one month. SpiceJet Ltd lost 9.99% to Rs 12.88. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1923.14 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 127.55 lakh shares in the past one month. Websol Energy System Ltd crashed 7.33% to Rs 56.62. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 5.29 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.15 lakh shares in the past one month. Premier Energies Ltd fell 6.15% to Rs 730. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8.34 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.11 lakh shares in the past one month. Welspun Living Ltd dropped 4.81% to Rs 127.7. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 9.2 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.4 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WaareeEnergiesLtd_42747859_39763.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Electronics bags Rs 733-cr defence orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-electronics-bags-rs-733-cr-defence-orders/1679486</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679486</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders include TR modules, communication equipment, encryptors, radars, jammers, software solutions, test equipment, upgrades, and spares, further strengthening the company’s defence electronics order book.

The orders include TR modules, communication equipment, encryptors, radars, jammers, software solutions, test equipment, upgrades, and spares, further strengthening the company’s defence electronics order book. Bharat Electronics (BEL) is a Navratna PSU under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. It manufactures electronic products and systems for the army, navy, and air force. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 20.81% to Rs 1,590.06 crore on a 23.72% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,121.98 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company’s order book position stood at Rs 73,015 crore as of 1 January 2026. The counter rose 0.86% to Rs 438.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatElectron_81586952923_2298.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Acuité Ratings reaffirms ratings of Ashoka Buildconn at 'AA/A1+']]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acuit-ratings-reaffirms-ratings-of-ashoka-buildconn-at-aaa1/1679480</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679480</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘ACUITE A1+’.

The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘ACUITE A1+’. Acuité Ratings had previously placed the company’s rating on 'Rating Watch with Developing Implications' on account of impending asset monetisation transactions. Acuite notes that ABL has completed the monetization of 5 BOTs (build-operate-transfer) and 5 HAMs (hybrid annuity model) resulting in total proceeds of Rs 2817 crore. The proceeds have been utilized to provide an exit to SBI Macquarie, reduction in short term borrowings thereby strengthening the capital structure of the company, make payments to Viva Highways (VHL) to acquire stake in Jaora Nayagaon Toll Road Company (JNTCPL) and settle vendor payments to avail cash discounts. Hence, the rating has been removed from rating watch. The remaining monetization of 6 HAM assets are expected to be completed by Q1 FY27 with an inflow of Rs 1100 crore. the timely completion of this transaction will remain key monitorable factor. The rating reaffirmation reflects a steady scale of operations with comfortable order book albeit subdued operating performance. The company’s unexecuted order book remains robust at Rs.16,477 crore as of 06 February 2026, providing revenue visibility at 2.33x of FY25 revenue. The order book is well-diversified across roads, buildings, power and railways. Additionally, the company has established a subsidiary in Saudi Arabia to tap infrastructure opportunities in the Middle East. The rating further factors in moderation in the company’s financial risk profile due to decrease in debt protection metrics during FY25. The increase in debt has led to higher interest costs, while lower accruals have resulted in a decline in both interest coverage ratio (ICR) and debt service coverage ratio (DSCR). Despite this moderation, the company’s tangible net worth has increased, and gearing remained below unity in FY25. The working capital cycle remains intensive due to inherent nature of the business. Ashoka Buildcon undertakes engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) contracts for the road, railways, buildings and power sector. The company is also the leading players in the BOT (build, own, transfer) segment and hybrid annuity model (HAM). The scrip fell 1.82% to currently trade at Rs 137.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokaBuildcon_9945804621_25513.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Generic Engineering Construction & Projects Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/generic-engineering-construction-projects-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679477</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679477</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd, Commercial Syn Bags Ltd, GTPL Hathway Ltd and NINtec Systems Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 25 February 2026.

R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd, Commercial Syn Bags Ltd, GTPL Hathway Ltd and NINtec Systems Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 25 February 2026. Generic Engineering Construction & Projects Ltd tumbled 19.99% to Rs 47.46 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.89 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 28911 shares in the past one month. R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd crashed 19.98% to Rs 97.95. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 10.08 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5.87 lakh shares in the past one month. Commercial Syn Bags Ltd lost 19.93% to Rs 152.7. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.61 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10526 shares in the past one month. GTPL Hathway Ltd plummeted 17.03% to Rs 57.44. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 20926 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1943 shares in the past one month. NINtec Systems Ltd slipped 11.90% to Rs 286.9. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 898 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 687 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GenericEngineeringConstructionProjectsLtd_54372299201_7610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with moderate gains; pharma shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-moderate-gains-pharma-shares-rally/1679476</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679476</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity indices traded with minor gains in the mid-afternoon trade, supported by a recovery in technology stocks following the previous session’s sharp selloff that had dragged the indices lower.

The headline equity indices traded with minor gains in the mid-afternoon trade, supported by a recovery in technology stocks following the previous session’s sharp selloff that had dragged the indices lower. The Nifty traded above the 25,450 mark. Pharma shares extended gains for the fourth consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, rose 35.15 points or 0.05% to 82,261.11. The Nifty 50 index added 37.70 points or 0.14% to 25,463.85. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.44% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.27%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,930 shares rose and 2,169 shares fell. A total of 197 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 5.15% to 13.42. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index jumped 1.35% to 22,938.35. The index rallied 2.27% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Laurus Labs (up 3.65%), Aurobindo Pharma (up 3.18%), Mankind Pharma (up 3.13%), Ajanta Pharma (up 2.03%), Lupin (up 1.79%), Divis Laboratories (up 1.77%), Alkem Laboratories (up 1.6%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 1.57%), Zydus Lifesciences (up 1.35%) and Cipla (up 1.12%) advanced. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.13% to 6.676 compared with the previous session close of 6.685. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9450 compared with its close of 90.9500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement gained 0.77% to Rs 161,195. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.06% to 97.70. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.40% to 4.049. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 36 cents or 0.51% to $70.94 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Univastu India jumped 7.86% after the company said that it has received a letter of acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 485.67 crore from IRCON International for works on Mumbai Metro Line 6 (Swami Samarth Nagar to Vikhroli–EEH). Samhi Hotels rallied 3.33% after the company through its wholly-owned subsidiary, Duet India Hotels (Navi Mumbai), has signed operating agreements with Marriott Hotels India for two upcoming hotel projects in Navi Mumbai and Thane.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background-picture-i_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Concord Biotech Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-concord-biotech-ltd-counter/1679475</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679475</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Usha Martin Ltd, Schaeffler India Ltd, Waaree Energies Ltd, Star Health & Allied Insurance Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 25 February 2026.

Usha Martin Ltd, Schaeffler India Ltd, Waaree Energies Ltd, Star Health & Allied Insurance Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 25 February 2026. Concord Biotech Ltd notched up volume of 70.02 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 70.24 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 99683 shares. The stock rose 14.00% to Rs.1,226.80. Volumes stood at 56100 shares in the last session. Usha Martin Ltd recorded volume of 82.46 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 21.22 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3.89 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.73% to Rs.425.25. Volumes stood at 2.96 lakh shares in the last session. Schaeffler India Ltd recorded volume of 10.37 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 14.32 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 72399 shares. The stock gained 3.94% to Rs.4,245.90. Volumes stood at 2.77 lakh shares in the last session. Waaree Energies Ltd recorded volume of 130.42 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.41 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10.51 lakh shares. The stock lost 9.59% to Rs.2,733.40. Volumes stood at 22.95 lakh shares in the last session. Star Health & Allied Insurance Company Ltd witnessed volume of 24.84 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.96 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.08 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.11% to Rs.469.80. Volumes stood at 2 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ConcordBiotechLtd_67563462_72610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold holds above $5200 per ounce]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-holds-above-5200-per-ounce/1679473</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679473</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Gold soared today amid weakness in dollar overseas and sustained geopolitical risks.

COMEX Gold soared today amid weakness in dollar overseas and sustained geopolitical risks. The counter is currently quoting at $5212 per ounce, up 0.69% on the day. Silver futures zoomed 3.80% at $90.86 per ounce. Chinese precious metals traders are back after the Lunar New year holidays and both metals are finding it highly supportive. Gold raced near $5270 per ounce in last session, hitting around three-week highs but eased thereafter. With a 10% surge this month so far, the yellow metal is on track replicate its performance in January when it had gained around 9%. MCX Gold futures are trading at Rs 161217 per 10 grams, up 0.78% on the day after hitting highs above Rs 161600 per 10 grams. The counter lost around 1% in last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Univastu India gains on securing Rs 485.67-cr Metro Line 6 order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/univastu-india-gains-on-securing-rs-48567-cr-metro-line-6-order/1679469</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679469</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract covers the design, manufacture, supply, installation, integration, testing, and commissioning of power supply, traction, E&M, lifts, and escalators, along with 5 years of comprehensive maintenance after a 2-year defect liability period, providing extended revenue visibility.

The contract covers the design, manufacture, supply, installation, integration, testing, and commissioning of power supply, traction, E&M, lifts, and escalators, along with 5 years of comprehensive maintenance after a 2-year defect liability period, providing extended revenue visibility. The project timeline includes a 104-week design-build period. The award strengthens Univastu India’s metro rail infrastructure order book and reinforces its execution capabilities in system-based urban transit projects. The company’s total market cap on the BSE stands at Rs 246 crore. Univastu India operates in the construction sector. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 81.8% to Rs 5.51 crore on a 33.7% rise in revenue to Rs 56.16 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnivastuIndiaLtd_62157064244_70992.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Samhi Hotels gains as partners with Marriott to launch two new hotels in Navi Mumbai, Thane]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/samhi-hotels-gains-as-partners-with-marriott-to-launch-two-new-hotels-in-navi-mumbai-thane/1679467</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679467</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The proposed developments comprise an approximately 350-room upper-upscale hotel under the Westin Hotels & Resorts brand and a roughly 350-room upper mid-scale hotel under Fairfield by Marriott.

The proposed developments comprise an approximately 350-room upper-upscale hotel under the Westin Hotels & Resorts brand and a roughly 350-room upper mid-scale hotel under Fairfield by Marriott. The agreements further deepen SAMHI’s partnership with Marriott and strengthen its presence in the fast-growing Navi Mumbai–Thane hospitality corridor. The addition of upper-upscale and upper mid-scale assets is expected to enhance SAMHI’s branded portfolio, improve its positioning among corporate travellers and drive long-term asset utilisation in a high-growth urban micro-market. Separately, the company said its subsidiary ITHPL has received layout plan approval from the Karnataka Industrial Areas Development Board (KIADB) for a proposed hotel project in Whitefield, Bengaluru. The approval, granted on 23 February 2026, pertains to the development of a second hotel building at Plot Nos. 134, 135, 136 (P), EPIP, Whitefield Industrial Area. The new project will add around 235 rooms, complementing the existing 142-room facility, taking the total inventory to approximately 377 rooms across the upper-upscale and upscale segments. The development marks a significant expansion of SAMHI Hotels’ hospitality footprint in Bengaluru, reinforcing its strategy of scaling presence in high-demand commercial hubs. Samhi Hotels is a hotel development and investment company with focus on operating internationally branded hotels across key cities in the Indian sub- continent. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 75.1% to Rs 40.58 crore on 15.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 337.75 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SamhiHotelsLtd_78186805_74552.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade sideways; European markets opens higher]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-sideways-european-markets-opens-higher/1679465</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679465</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the afternoon trade, The Nifty traded above the 25,400 level.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the afternoon trade, The Nifty traded above the 25,400 level. Metal, auto and pharma shared advanced, while PSU bank, realty and FMCG shares declined. At 13:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, shed 22.60 points or 0.03% to 82,203.32. The Nifty 50 index added 23.60 points or 0.10% to 25,448.25. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.26% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.13%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,937 shares rose and 2,097 shares fell. A total of 201 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 4.82% to 13.47. Gainers & Losers: Tata Steel (up 2.56%), HCL Technologies (up 2.36%), Bajaj Auto (up 2.09%), Shriram Finance (up 2.03%) and Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 1.70%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. State Bank of India (down 1.50%), ITC (down 1.47%), Tata Consumer Products (down 1.17%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (down 1.08%) and Reliance Industries (TCS) (down 1.08%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) added 0.95%. The company said its Power Transmission & Distribution (PT&D) vertical has secured ‘major’ EPC orders to establish electricity grid system elements in India and overseas. Schaeffler India rallied 4.40% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 31.5% to Rs 327.96 crore on 26.9% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 2,643.06 crore in Q4 CY2025 over Q4 CY2024. Lupin rose 1.78%. The company said that it has received approval from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) for Brivaracetam oral solution 10 mg/mL. Biocon added 1.59%. The company said that it has received approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (U.S. FDA) for its complex formulation Liraglutide Injection. Zelio E-Mobility advanced 2.10% after the company announced the commissioning of a new manufacturing facility in Cuttack, Odisha, thereby increasing its total installed production capacity to 1,80,000 units per annum. H.G. Infra Engineering shed 0.61%. The company said it has been declared the lowest bidder (L1) by the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for a road project in Odisha under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) declined 1.38%. The company said that it has secured a domestic contract worth Rs 270.22 crore from Central Railway for execution of traction infrastructure works under an EPC model. Global Markets: European markets open higher on Wednesday as global market nerves eased after U.S. President Donald Trump’s universal 10% tariff came into effect rather than the threatened higher 15% rate. Most Asian markets advanced with South Korea and Japan stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Oil Corporation Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-oil-corporation-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1679453</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679453</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Oil Corporation Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Indian Oil Corporation Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 182.22, up 1.13% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25467.85. The Sensex is at 82264.76, up 0.05%. Indian Oil Corporation Ltd has risen around 14.68% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 11.13% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37028.1, down 0.08% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 127.51 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 162.72 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 182.58, up 0.77% on the day. Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is up 56.52% in last one year as compared to a 12.96% spurt in NIFTY and a 20.68% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 7.78 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IOCL_64283819279_12002.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mankind Pharma Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mankind-pharma-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1679454</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679454</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mankind Pharma Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Mankind Pharma Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2113.1, up 2.84% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25467.85. The Sensex is at 82264.76, up 0.05%. Mankind Pharma Ltd has gained around 0.9% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Mankind Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 5.38% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22632.05, up 1.45% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.22 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.54 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2126.3, up 2.78% on the day. Mankind Pharma Ltd is down 7.89% in last one year as compared to a 12.96% jump in NIFTY and a 13.66% jump in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 47.98 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MankindPharmaLtd_91606272_38451.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin Ltd spurts 1.61%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-ltd-spurts-161/1679455</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679455</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lupin Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Lupin Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 2286.5, up 1.61% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25467.85. The Sensex is at 82264.76, up 0.05%. Lupin Ltd has risen around 6.32% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Lupin Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 5.38% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22632.05, up 1.45% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.95 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 8.04 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2302.7, up 1.91% on the day. Lupin Ltd is up 20.91% in last one year as compared to a 12.96% spurt in NIFTY and a 13.66% spurt in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 18.61 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Acuité Ratings upgrades ratings of Permanent Magnets to 'BBB/A3+']]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acuit-ratings-upgrades-ratings-of-permanent-magnets-to-bbba3/1679452</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679452</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has also upgraded the company’s short-term rating to 'ACUITE A3+’ from ‘ACUITE A3’.

The agency has also upgraded the company’s short-term rating to 'ACUITE A3+’ from ‘ACUITE A3’. Acuité Ratings & Research stated that the rating upgrade factors in the group’s stable business risk profile which is expected to strengthen further with augmentation in capacity utilisations and addition of new capacities facilitating diversification in product mix. The rating also factors in group’s sustained healthy financial risk profile, supported by a strong net worth base, low gearing and comfortable debt protection metrics. The rating also reflects the group’s long standing operational track record and experienced management. However, the rating remains constrained by the group’s working capital-intensive operations and susceptibility of profitability to volatility in raw material prices in a highly competitive and fragmented industry. Permanent Magnets (PML) is engaged in manufacturing of Alnico (aluminium, nickel and cobalt) magnets & magnetic assemblies, parts and accessories of electricity meters, gas meters and electrical vehicles. The scrip rose 0.54% to currently trade at Rs 840.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PermanentMagnet_86331067735_433.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Biocon Ltd soars 0.99%, gains for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/biocon-ltd-soars-099-gains-for-fifth-straight-session/1679449</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679449</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Biocon Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Biocon Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 394.6, up 0.99% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25504.3. The Sensex is at 82333.07, up 0.13%. Biocon Ltd has gained around 8.04% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Biocon Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 5.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22632.05, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 19.62 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 31.82 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 397.7, up 1.21% on the day. Biocon Ltd is up 26.54% in last one year as compared to a 13.13% jump in NIFTY and a 13.84% jump in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 325.29 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Biocon_44501850463_14801.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd soars 0.79%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/torrent-pharmaceuticals-ltd-soars-079-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1679450</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679450</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 4432.5, up 0.79% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25504.3. The Sensex is at 82333.07, up 0.13%. Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd has risen around 10.88% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 5.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22632.05, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.01 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.99 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 4417.6, up 0.64% on the day. Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd is up 48.39% in last one year as compared to a 13.13% spurt in NIFTY and a 13.84% spurt in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 66.66 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TorrentPharma_35676110126_3616.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd gains for fifth session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/j-b-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-gains-for-fifth-session/1679451</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679451</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 2081.4, up 0.53% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25504.3. The Sensex is at 82333.07, up 0.13%. J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd has added around 10.86% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd is a constituent, has added around 5.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22632.05, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 86468 shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.2 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 45.69 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JBChemPharm_56046055785_303.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex rallies 418 pts; Nifty trades above 25,550 mark; VIX slumps 8.05% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-rallies-418-pts-nifty-trades-above-25550-mark-vix-slumps-805/1679446</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679446</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with decent gains in early afternoon trade.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with decent gains in early afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,550 mark. Auto shares advanced after declining for previous trading session. At 12:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, surged 418.47 points or 0.51% to 82,624.84. The Nifty 50 index gained 173.10 points or 0.68% to 25,597.75. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index jumped 0.77% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rallied 0.66%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,211 shares rose and 1,727 shares fell. A total of 211 shares were unchanged. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, slumped 8.05% to 13.01. The Nifty 30 March 2026 futures were trading at 25,755, at a premium of 1 points as compared with the spot at 25,597.75. The Nifty option chain for the 30 March 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 40.4 lakh contracts at the 27,000 strike price. Maximum put OI of 64.1 lakh contracts was seen at 25,000 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index 2.07% to 28,529.15. The index fell 0.45% in the past trading session. Hero MotoCorp (up 5.32%), Bosch (up 4.59%), Uno Minda (up 3.23%), TVS Motor Company (up 3.09%) and Bajaj Auto (up 3.03%), Tube Investments of India (up 1.97%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 1.84%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.8%), Exide Industries (up 1.74%) and Eicher Motors (up 1.7%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) added 1.24% after the company said its Power Transmission & Distribution (PT&D) vertical has secured ‘major’ EPC orders to establish electricity grid system elements in India and overseas. Schaeffler India rallied 4.04% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 31.5% to Rs 327.96 crore on 26.9% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 2,643.06 crore in Q4 CY2025 over Q4 CY2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Japanese yen stabilizes near 155.6 on policy caution signals  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/japanese-yen-stabilizes-near-1556-on-policy-caution-signals/1679445</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679445</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen bounced back toward 155.6 per dollar on Wednesday after sliding in the previous session, as comments from Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi signaling concern over further rate hikes reinforced expectations of a cautious Bank of Japan.

The Japanese yen bounced back toward 155.6 per dollar on Wednesday after sliding in the previous session, as comments from Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi signaling concern over further rate hikes reinforced expectations of a cautious Bank of Japan. The yen also drew support from a weaker US dollar, with the dollar index slipping below 97.6 after President Donald Trump offered no change to tariff policy in his State of the Union address. Markets remain alert to trade developments, especially after the US Supreme Court struck down tariffs imposed under emergency powers, keeping currency sentiment sensitive to policy clarity.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Secmark Consultancy Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/secmark-consultancy-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1679443</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679443</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jindal Poly Films Ltd, Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd, Sumeet Industries Ltd and A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 25 February 2026.

Jindal Poly Films Ltd, Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd, Sumeet Industries Ltd and A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 25 February 2026. Secmark Consultancy Ltd soared 19.97% to Rs 121.05 at 11:59 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 3418 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 381 shares in the past one month. Jindal Poly Films Ltd surged 11.98% to Rs 618.15. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 48384 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5184 shares in the past one month. Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd spiked 10.00% to Rs 97.02. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 456 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 850 shares in the past one month. Sumeet Industries Ltd spurt 10.00% to Rs 24.43. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 3807 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8855 shares in the past one month. A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd jumped 9.96% to Rs 17.44. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 58538 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 29409 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SecMarkConsultancyLtd._72779962_75094.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>