<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles on a lower note; Positive equities cap downside ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-on-a-lower-note-positive-equities-cap-downside/1674196</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674196</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee witnessed a volatile trading session and settled for the day on a lower note, down 9 paise at 90.74 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday.

The Indian rupee witnessed a volatile trading session and settled for the day on a lower note, down 9 paise at 90.74 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday. INR gave up early gains amid India-US interim trade framework. The rupee witnessed high volatility as the support from positive domestic equities and foreign fund inflows was negated by risk-off sentiments among investors. At the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 90.66 against the US dollar, then gained some ground to touch 90.37, registering a gain of 28 paise over its previous close. Indian shares rose notably on Monday after the United States and India unveiled an interim framework designed to reduce tariffs, redefine energy partnerships, and enhance economic collaboration. The benchmark BSE Sensex jumped 485.35 points, or 0.58 percent, to 84,065.75 while the broader NSE Nifty index closed up 173.60 points, or 0.68 percent, at 25,867.30.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India shows improved performance in Network Readiness Index 2025]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-shows-improved-performance-in-network-readiness-index-2025/1674195</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674195</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Communications has stated that India has improved its position by four slots and is now placed at 45th rank as per the Network Readiness Index 2025 (NRI 2025) report released on 4.2.2026.

Ministry of Communications has stated that India has improved its position by four slots and is now placed at 45th rank as per the Network Readiness Index 2025 (NRI 2025) report released on 4.2.2026. The report maps the network-based readiness landscape of 127 economies based on their performance in four pillars: Technology, People, Governance and Impact, covering a total of 53 indicators. The report has been prepared by the Portulans Institute, an independent, non-profit research and educational institute based in Washington DC. India has not only improved its ranking but has also improved its score from 53.63 out of 100 in 2024 to 54.43 out of 100 in 2025. It is noteworthy that India leads in several indicators. The report states that India secured 1st rank in “Annual investment in telecommunication services”, “AI scientific publications”, “ICT services exports” and “E-commerce legislation”, 2nd rank in “FTTH/Building Internet subscriptions”, “Mobile broadband internet traffic within the country” and “International Internet bandwidth”, and 3rd rank in “Domestic market scale” and “Income Inequality”.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/conference-microphone-picture-id483532705_Conference.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee Falls]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-falls/1674176</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674176</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.7650 per Dollar on Monday (09 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.7125 per Dollar last Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts fall further ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-fall-further/1674172</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674172</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 13911 contracts in the data reported through February 03, 2026. This was a weekly drop of 2251 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures flat around $5.90 per ounce]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-copper-futures-flat-around-590-per-ounce/1674118</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674118</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Copper stayed largely supported today though a sustained rise in LME inventories capped gains.

Copper stayed largely supported today though a sustained rise in LME inventories capped gains. Equities were firm. Asian markets saw excellent gains. Shanghai Composite index jumped 1.41%. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index soared 1.76%. Japanese stocks hit fresh record highs after Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s ruling party won a super majority in the lower house. Nikkei 225 index jumped 4.4%. European stocks edged higher with German DAX hitting two-week top. The Dow zoomed 2.5% to 50,115.67 on 6 February 2026, closing above 50000 mark for the first time. The index has zoomed around 12.70% over last one year. This rally in DOW had pushed up COMEX Copper than a percent on Friday and the metal is currently trading flat at $5.88 per pound. MCX Copper futures are trading at Rs 1243.80 per kg, up 0.08% on the day. The metal pulled back in afternoon trades after breaking under Rs 1250 per kg before witnessing some stability.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-city-stock-market-data-and-charts-on-skyscrapers-b_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro speculative net longs climb to around one-month high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-speculative-net-longs-climb-to-around-one-month-high/1674115</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674115</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market climbed near a one-month high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market climbed near a one-month high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Euro futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net long position of 163361 contracts in the data reported through February 03, 2026. This was a weekly addition of 31227 net long contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Fractal Analytics IPO subscribed 9% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fractal-analytics-ipo-subscribed-9/1674113</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674113</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Fractal Analytics received bids for 15,80,336 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (09 February 2026).

Fractal Analytics received bids for 15,80,336 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (09 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.09 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it will close on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 16 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The Rs 2,833.9 crore IPO comprises a fresh issue of 11,372,222 equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,023.5 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 20,115,556 equity shares worth Rs 1,810.4 crore at the upper price band of Rs 900. Fractal will utilize Rs 264.9 crore from the net fresh issue proceeds to invest in its unit, Fractal USA, for repayment of its borrowings; Rs 57.1 crore for the purchase of laptops; Rs 121.1 crore will be utilized for setting up of new office premises in India; and Rs 355.1 crore for investment in R&D and sales and marketing under Fractal Alpha. The remaining funds will be utilized for general corporate purposes. Fractal Analytics is an enterprise AI company providing end-to-end artificial intelligence solutions to global enterprises to support data-driven decision-making. With over 25 years of experience, the company operates through Fractal.ai and Fractal Alpha, serving clients across CPG and retail, TMT, healthcare and life sciences, and BFSI, with a customer base that includes several leading global corporations. Ahead of the IPO of Fractal Analytics on 6 February 2026, the company raised Rs 474.99 crore from anchor investors by allotting 52.77 lakh shares at Rs 900 each to 22 anchor investors. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 70.90 crore and sales of Rs 1,559 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aye Finance IPO subscribed 12%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aye-finance-ipo-subscribed-12/1674111</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674111</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Aye Finance received bids for 54,46,548 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (9 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Aye Finance received bids for 54,46,548 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (9 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.12 times. The issue opened for bidding on Monday (9 February 2026) and it closed on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 116 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue also consists of offer for sale (OFS) of Rs 300 crore through issuance of 2.33-2.46 crore equity shares. The OFS from investor selling shareholders is Rs 30 crore from Alpha Wave India I LP, Rs 139.763 crore from MAJ Invest Financial Inclusion Fund II K/S, Rs 82.5 crore from CapitalG L P, Rs 30 crore from LGT Capital Invest Mauritius PCC with Cell E/VP and Rs 17.737 crore from Vikram Jetley. The company proposes to utilize the net proceeds from the fresh issue towards augmenting the capital base to meet future capital requirements. Ahead of the IPO, Aye Finance Labs on 8 February 2026, the company raised Rs 454.49 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 3. 52 crore shares at Rs 129 each to 19 anchor investors. Aye Finance incorporated in 1993 is Delhi based non-banking financial company – middle layer (NBFC-ML) focused on providing loans to micro scale micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMEs) across India. It offers a range of small ticket business loans with average ticket size on disbursement at Rs 1.8 lakh for working capital and business expansion needs, against hypothecation of working assets or against security of property to customers across manufacturing, trading, service and allied agriculture sectors. Gross NPA ratio has increased from 2.49% at end March 2023 to 4.21% at end March 2025 and 4.85% end September 2025. The capital adequacy ratio was 32.27%, with Tier I capital comprising 32.27% and Tier II capital comprising Nil at end September 2025. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 64.6 crore and income from operations of Rs 733.83 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trade cheer and global cues push benchmarks higher; Nifty above 25,850]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trade-cheer-and-global-cues-push-benchmarks-higher-nifty-above-25850/1674078</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674078</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks closed sharply higher on Tuesday, extending their winning streak to a second straight session as risk appetite strengthened.

The key equity benchmarks closed sharply higher on Tuesday, extending their winning streak to a second straight session as risk appetite strengthened. Fresh foreign inflows, optimism around the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and supportive Asian market cues powered the rally, while sentiment received an added lift from key agreements signed between India and Malaysia. The Nifty 50 climbed above the 25,850 mark, led by strong buying in consumer durables and PSU banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 485.35 points or 0.58% to 84,065.75. The Nifty 50 index rallied 173.60 points or 0.68% to 25,867.30. In the two consecutive trading sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.90% and 0.88%, respectively. State Bank of India (up 7.63%), Shriram Finance (up 6.03%) and Titan Company (up 3.04%) boosted the Nifty today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 1.66% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index surged 2.45%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,110 shares rose and 1,254 shares fell. A total of 173 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 2.09% to 12.19. India-Malaysia sign key agreements: Prime Minister (PM) Narendra Modi visited Malaysia from 7 February to 8 February 2026 and held bilateral talks with Malaysian PM Anwar Ibrahim. The wide-ranging talks during the two-day official visit, marked a significant step in strengthening the Comprehensive Strategic Partnership between India and Malaysia. India and Malaysia has signed 11 Memorandums of Understanding (MoUs) and exchanged several bilateral documents across a broad range of sectors during Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s two-day official visit to Kuala Lumpur. The agreements, signed in the presence of PM Modi and his Malaysian counterpart Anwar Ibrahim following delegation-level talks, span trade and investment, semiconductors, digital economy, healthcare, security cooperation and peacekeeping, officials said. The two leaders launched Malaysia-India Digital Council (MLDC) and backed NPCI–PayNet payment link, paving way to introduce India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) system in Malaysia. This initiative will simplify cross-border payments for businesses and travellers and strengthen financial ties between the two economies. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.40% to 6.760 compared with previous session close of 6.733. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7400 compared with its close of 90.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 April 2026 settlement rose 0.77% to Rs 156,641. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.24% to 97.41. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.50% to 4.224. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell 11 cents or 0.16% to $67.94 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European market declined while Asian indices ended higher on Monday, led by a surge in Japanese stocks following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s historic landslide election victory. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party captured a two-thirds supermajority in the 465-seat lower house, public broadcaster NHK reported. A decisive win for Takaichi could be the “best outcome” for markets over the medium term, as strategic investments and tax reform bolster equities, said Sree Kochugovindan, media report said. Japanese stocks have hit several highs over the past few months, driven by the so-called 'Takaichi trade' as markets expect the prime minister’s economic policies — seen as growth‑focused continuation of Abenomics — to boost equities, while weakening the yen as she pushes for a looser monetary policy and higher government spending. U.S. President Donald Trump congratulated Takaichi on her victory in a TruthSocial post. Last Friday in the U.S., stocks surged as tech names recovered following several days of heavy selling in the sector and bitcoin rebounded following a rout that took the popular cryptocurrency down more than 50% from its high in October last year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 2.47%, closing at 50,115.67. Friday marked the first time the Dow exceeded the 50,000 level. The S&P 500 jumped 1.97%, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 2.18%. With those moves, the S&P 500 climbed back into the green for 2026. Stocks in Spotlight: State Bank of India has rallied 7.63% after the bank reported 24.49% jump in net profit to Rs 21,028 crore on a 9.69% increase in total income to Rs 1,40,915 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The bank has received a one-time dividend income of nearly Rs 2,200 crore from SBI Mutual Fund during the quarter, along with treasury gains of approximately Rs 3,280 crore. Tata Steel added 2.56% after the steelmaker reported a sharp 723.14% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 2688.70 crore on 6.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 56,646.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sky Gold and Diamonds surged 9.39% after the company reported a strong set of numbers for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 80.54 crore in Q3 FY26, up 120.42% YoY from Rs 36.54 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, PAT rose 20.23% from Rs 66.99 crore in Q2 FY26. Net sales jumped 77.13% YoY to Rs 1,767.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 997.97 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue increased 19.08% from Rs 1,484.46 crore. Sterlite Technologies rose 7.85% after the company said its board approved the issuance of up to 45.3 crore convertible warrants to promoter Twin Star Overseas on a preferential basis at Rs 110 per warrant, aggregating Rs 498.3 crore. Each warrant is convertible into one equity share within 18 months from the date of allotment. On a fully diluted basis, Twin Star Overseas’ shareholding is expected to increase to 47.75% from 42.9%, subject to full conversion of the warrants and shareholder approval. As on December 2025, total promoter shareholding in the company stood at 44.44%. Hi-Tech Pipes added 5.68% after the company announced the commencement of commercial production at its Sikandrabad, Unit-III (Uttar Pradesh) greenfield manufacturing facility. The Sikandrabad facility hosts a production capacity of 0.12 million tons. It would specialise in the production on ERW pipes and hollow sections. The company has reported 14.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.38 crore despite a 24.6% increase in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,069.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Ganesha Ecosphere hit an upper circuit of 20% after the company delivered a decisive sequential recovery in Q3 FY26. On a sequential basis, Ganesha Ecosphere returned to profitability in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit at Rs 4.75 crore compared with a loss of Rs 0.50 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations eased 1.7% QoQ to Rs 357.22 crore. On a year-on-year basis, consolidated net profit declined 84% YoY from Rs 29.71 crore in Q3 FY25, while revenue from operations fell 10.2% YoY from Rs 397.80 crore. Shipping Corporation of India surged 19.62% after the company reported a 436.24% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 404.97 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 75.52 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 22.5% year-on-year to Rs 1,611.67 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Kalyan Jewellers India zoomed 15.26% after its consolidated net profit surged 90.24% to Rs 416.29 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by a 42.17% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 10,343.4 crore compared to the same period last year. JK Tyre & Industries gained 2.42% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 294.96% to Rs 207.75 crore on a 14.95% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 4,222.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ram Ratna Wires soared 10.06% after the company reported a 73.1% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 31.28 crore on 43.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,277.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atul Auto surged 8.64% after the company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 98.06% to Rs 15.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7.75 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations grew by 18.39% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 230.86 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. IPO Update: Fractal Analytics received bids for 15,67,584 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:48 IST on Monday (9 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.08 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. Aye Finance received bids for 54,37,036 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:48 IST on Monday (9 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.12 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/diagram-1529671_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade slightly at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-slightly-at-premium/1674044</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674044</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,909, a premium of 41.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,867.30 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,909, a premium of 41.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,867.30 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index jumped 173.60 points or 0.68% to 25,867.30. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 2.09% to 12.19. State Bank of India (SBI), HDFC Bank and Kalyan Jewellers India were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices end with major gains; media index outperforms; VIX jumps 2% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-end-with-major-gains-media-index-outperforms-vix-jumps-2/1674042</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674042</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with significant gains, extending gains for second consecutive trading session, supported by FII buying amid optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues.

The key equity benchmarks ended with significant gains, extending gains for second consecutive trading session, supported by FII buying amid optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues. Sentiments further lifted by key agreements signed between India-Malaysia. Investors will continue to monitor developments in the ongoing Q3 earnings season. The Nifty ended above the 25,850 mark. the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 485.35 points or 0.58% to 84,065.75. The Nifty 50 index rallied 173.60 points or 0.68% to 25,867.30. In the two consecutive trading sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.90% and 0.88%, respectively. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 1.66% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index surged 2.45%. The market breadth was strong. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 2.09% to 12.19. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Media index (up 4.37%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 3.60%) and the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 3.34%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (up 0.02%), the Nifty Private Bank index (up 0.23%) and the Nifty FMCG index (up 0.32%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. India-Malaysia sign key agreements: Prime Minister (PM) Narendra Modi visited Malaysia from 7 February to 8 February 2026 and held bilateral talks with Malaysian PM Anwar Ibrahim. The wide-ranging talks during the two-day official visit, marked a significant step in strengthening the Comprehensive Strategic Partnership between India and Malaysia. India and Malaysia has signed 11 Memorandums of Understanding (MoUs) and exchanged several bilateral documents across a broad range of sectors during Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s two-day official visit to Kuala Lumpur. The agreements, signed in the presence of PM Modi and his Malaysian counterpart Anwar Ibrahim following delegation-level talks, span trade and investment, semiconductors, digital economy, healthcare, security cooperation and peacekeeping, officials said. The two leaders launched Malaysia-India Digital Council (MLDC) and backed NPCI–PayNet payment link, paving way to introduce India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) system in Malaysia. This initiative will simplify cross-border payments for businesses and travellers and strengthen financial ties between the two economies. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.40% to 6.760 compared with previous session close of 6.733. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7400 compared with its close of 90.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 April 2026 settlement rose 0.77% to Rs 156,641. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.24% to 97.41. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.50% to 4.224. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell 11 cents or 0.16% to $67.94 a barrel. Global Markets: European market advanced while Asian markets ended higher on Monday, led by a surge in Japanese stocks following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s historic landslide election victory. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party captured a two-thirds supermajority in the 465-seat lower house, public broadcaster NHK reported. A decisive win for Takaichi could be the “best outcome” for markets over the medium term, as strategic investments and tax reform bolster equities, said Sree Kochugovindan, media report said. Japanese stocks have hit several highs over the past few months, driven by the so-called 'Takaichi trade' as markets expect the prime minister’s economic policies — seen as growth‑focused continuation of Abenomics — to boost equities, while weakening the yen as she pushes for a looser monetary policy and higher government spending. U.S. President Donald Trump congratulated Takaichi on her victory in a TruthSocial post. Last Friday in the U.S., stocks surged as tech names recovered following several days of heavy selling in the sector and bitcoin rebounded following a rout that took the popular cryptocurrency down more than 50% from its high in October last year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 1,206.95 points, or 2.47%, closing at 50,115.67. Friday marked the first time the Dow exceeded the 50,000 level. The S&P 500 jumped 1.97% and ended at 6,932.30, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 2.18% to 23,031.21. With those moves, the S&P 500 climbed back into the green for 2026. Even with Friday’s rise, the S&P 500 posted a 0.1% decline for the week, while the Nasdaq fell 1.8% on the week. The 30-stock Dow rose 2.5% week to date, benefiting from some rotation into some economically cyclical stocks even as the overall market was weighed down by tech selling.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Media Index gains 4.37%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-media-index-gains-437/1674039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674039</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Media index closed up 4.37% at 1451.5 today.

Nifty Media index closed up 4.37% at 1451.5 today. The index has gained 2.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Saregama India Ltd added 6.64%, Sun TV Network Ltd gained 6.13% and Prime Focus Ltd rose 5.58%. The Nifty Media index has fallen 10.00% over last one year compared to the 9.79% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index gained 3.34% and Nifty Realty index added 2.61% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 added 0.68% to close at 25867.3 while the SENSEX recorded a gain of 0.58% to close at 84065.75 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/new-york-stock-exchange-1563631_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices extend gains for 2nd day; Nifty ends above 25,850 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-extend-gains-for-2nd-day-nifty-ends-above-25850-mark/1674040</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674040</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended with major gains, extending gains for second consecutive trading session, supported by FII buying amid optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues.

The key domestic indices ended with major gains, extending gains for second consecutive trading session, supported by FII buying amid optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues. Sentiments further lifted by key agreements signed between India-Malaysia. Investors will continue to monitor developments in the ongoing Q3 earnings season. The Nifty ended above the 25,850 mark. All the sectoral indices on the NSE were ended in the green, led by gains in Media, Consumer Durables and PSU Bank shares. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 485.35 points or 0.58% to 84,065.75. The Nifty 50 index rallied 173.60 points or 0.68% to 25,867.30. In the two consecutive trading sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.90% and 0.88%, respectively. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 1.66% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index surged 2.45%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,101 shares rose and 1,257 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 2.09% to 12.19. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index surged 4.37% to 1,451.50. The index declined 0.26% in the previous two trading sessions. Saregama India (up 6.2%), Sun TV Network (up 5.49%), Nazara Technologies (up 5.41%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (up 4.9%) and Prime Focus (up 4.48%) were the top gainers. Among the other gainers were Network 18 Media & Investments (up 4.18%), PVR Inox (up 3.88%), Tips Music (up 3.86%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 3.52%) surged. IPO Update: Fractal Analytics received bids for 15,47,776 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Monday (9 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.08 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. Aye Finance received bids for 53,93,420 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Monday (9 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.12 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. India-Malaysia sign key agreements Prime Minister (PM) Narendra Modi visited Malaysia from 7 February to 8 February 2026 and held bilateral talks with Malaysian PM Anwar Ibrahim. The wide-ranging talks during the two-day official visit, marked a significant step in strengthening the Comprehensive Strategic Partnership between India and Malaysia. India and Malaysia has signed 11 Memorandums of Understanding (MoUs) and exchanged several bilateral documents across a broad range of sectors during Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s two-day official visit to Kuala Lumpur. The agreements, signed in the presence of PM Modi and his Malaysian counterpart Anwar Ibrahim following delegation-level talks, span trade and investment, semiconductors, digital economy, healthcare, security cooperation and peacekeeping, officials said. The two leaders launched Malaysia-India Digital Council (MLDC) and backed NPCI–PayNet payment link, paving way to introduce India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) system in Malaysia. This initiative will simplify cross-border payments for businesses and travellers and strengthen financial ties between the two economies. Stocks in Spotlight: State Bank of India has rallied 7.46% after the bank reported 24.49% jump in net profit to Rs 21,028 crore on a 9.69% increase in total income to Rs 1,40,915 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Steel added 2.56% after the steelmaker reported a sharp 723.14% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 2688.70 crore on 6.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 56,646.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hi-Tech Pipes added 5.68% after the company announced the commencement of commercial production at its Sikandrabad, Unit-III (Uttar Pradesh) greenfield manufacturing facility. The Sikandrabad facility hosts a production capacity of 0.12 million tons. It would specialise in the production on ERW pipes and hollow sections. The company has reported 14.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.38 crore despite a 24.6% increase in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,069.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Ganesha Ecosphere hit an upper circuit of 20% after the company delivered a decisive sequential recovery in Q3 FY26. On a sequential basis, Ganesha Ecosphere returned to profitability in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit at Rs 4.75 crore compared with a loss of Rs 0.50 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations eased 1.7% QoQ to Rs 357.22 crore. On a year-on-year basis, consolidated net profit declined 84% YoY from Rs 29.71 crore in Q3 FY25, while revenue from operations fell 10.2% YoY from Rs 397.80 crore. Shipping Corporation of India hit the upper circuit of 20% after the company reported a 436.24% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 404.97 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 75.52 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 22.5% year-on-year to Rs 1,611.67 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Kalyan Jewellers India zoomed 15.26% after its consolidated net profit surged 90.24% to Rs 416.29 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by a 42.17% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 10,343.4 crore compared to the same period last year. JK Tyre & Industries gained 2.42% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 294.96% to Rs 207.75 crore on a 14.95% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 4,222.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ram Ratna Wires soared 10.06% after the company reported a 73.1% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 31.28 crore on 43.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,277.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atul Auto surged 8.64% after the company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 98.06% to Rs 15.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7.75 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations grew by 18.39% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 230.86 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: European market advanced while Asian markets ended higher on Monday, led by a surge in Japanese stocks following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s historic landslide election victory. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party captured a two-thirds supermajority in the 465-seat lower house, public broadcaster NHK reported. A decisive win for Takaichi could be the “best outcome” for markets over the medium term, as strategic investments and tax reform bolster equities, said Sree Kochugovindan, media report said. Japanese stocks have hit several highs over the past few months, driven by the so-called 'Takaichi trade' as markets expect the prime minister’s economic policies — seen as growth‑focused continuation of Abenomics — to boost equities, while weakening the yen as she pushes for a looser monetary policy and higher government spending. U.S. President Donald Trump congratulated Takaichi on her victory in a TruthSocial post. Last Friday in the U.S., stocks surged as tech names recovered following several days of heavy selling in the sector and bitcoin rebounded following a rout that took the popular cryptocurrency down more than 50% from its high in October last year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 1,206.95 points, or 2.47%, closing at 50,115.67. Friday marked the first time the Dow exceeded the 50,000 level. The S&P 500 jumped 1.97% and ended at 6,932.30, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 2.18% to 23,031.21. With those moves, the S&P 500 climbed back into the green for 2026. Even with Friday’s rise, the S&P 500 posted a 0.1% decline for the week, while the Nasdaq fell 1.8% on the week. The 30-stock Dow rose 2.5% week to date, benefiting from some rotation into some economically cyclical stocks even as the overall market was weighed down by tech selling.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sky Gold and Diamonds rallies after Q3 PAT soars 120% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sky-gold-and-diamonds-rallies-after-q3-pat-soars-120-yoy/1674028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674028</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 80.54 crore in Q3 FY26, up 120.42% YoY from Rs 36.54 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 80.54 crore in Q3 FY26, up 120.42% YoY from Rs 36.54 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, PAT rose 20.23% from Rs 66.99 crore in Q2 FY26. Net sales jumped 77.13% YoY to Rs 1,767.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 997.97 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue increased 19.08% from Rs 1,484.46 crore. Profit before tax more than doubled to Rs 106.13 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 115.01% YoY increase over Rs 49.36 crore in Q3 FY25. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PBT rose 20.74% from Rs 87.90 crore. Total expenditure rose 74.9% YoY to Rs 1,645.29 crore. Raw material consumption increased 56.17% YoY to Rs 1,624.94 crore, while employee expenses rose 88.93% YoY to Rs 15.19 crore. Interest cost climbed 73.75% YoY to Rs 21.18 crore, while depreciation declined 12.24% YoY to Rs 2.51 crore. Sky Gold and Diamonds is one of India's fastest-growing B2B jewellery manufacturers, specialising in lightweight, design-led and studded jewellery.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SkyGold_39345065_73265.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude oil stays slippery, WTI futures linger around $63 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-oil-stays-slippery-wti-futures-linger-around-63-per-barrel/1674027</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674027</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Crude oil futures eased on Monday as diplomatic talks between the US and Iran alleviated near-term supply concerns.

Crude oil futures eased on Monday as diplomatic talks between the US and Iran alleviated near-term supply concerns. The discussions, held in Oman on Friday, were described by Tehran as “a step forward,” signaling potential de-escalation in tensions over Iran’s nuclear program. Despite gains earlier in 2026 driven by geopolitical risks and supply disruptions, prices pulled back last week amid progress in negotiations. Investors are now awaiting this week’s OPEC+ and IEA reports for further guidance on global oil supply and market direction, while keeping an eye on upcoming US-Iran and US-Israel meetings. The WTI Crude oil futures are currently trading at $63.06 per barrel, down 0.72% on the day. Oil lost around 2.50% in last week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id5822566_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suprajit Engg slides after Q3 PAT drop 63% YoY to Rs 13 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suprajit-engg-slides-after-q3-pat-drop-63-yoy-to-rs-13-cr/1674026</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674026</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax tanked 32.31% year on year to Rs 40.80 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax tanked 32.31% year on year to Rs 40.80 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) edged up 0.04% year-on-year to Rs 111.9 crore in Q3 FY26, while the EBITDA margin slipped to 13% from 14.3% in the same quarter last year. Total expenses jumped 19.94% to Rs 9,41.15 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 784.62 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses were at Rs 224.68 crore (up 22.78% YoY), while the cost of material consumed stood at Rs 452.84 crore (up 4.25% YoY) during the period under review. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs 1.50 (150%) per equity share of face value Re. 1 each for FY26 and fixed Friday, February 13, 2026, as the record date for the payment of the interim dividend. Suprajit Engineering is engaged in the business of manufacturing auto components consisting mainly of control cables, speedo cables, auto lamps, and other components for automobiles and caters to both domestic and international markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuprajitEngg_27714167571_6045.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold gains steam as investors brace for jobs and CPI reports]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-gains-steam-as-investors-brace-for-jobs-and-cpi-reports/1674024</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674024</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold surged more than 1% in the electronic trades on Monday, rising above $5,050 per ounce in electronic trading as investors positioned for key US economic data later this week.

Gold surged more than 1% in the electronic trades on Monday, rising above $5,050 per ounce in electronic trading as investors positioned for key US economic data later this week. A softer US dollar, which fell 0.3% to 97.22, added support to the yellow metal ahead of the January jobs report, December retail sales, and the delayed CPI release. Markets currently anticipate the Federal Reserve will keep interest rates steady in March, with potential cuts later in the year. On the MCX, April gold futures rose 1.3% to Rs 157,450 per 10 grams, while March silver futures jumped nearly 5% to Rs 260,750 per kg. Traders are closely monitoring these data points for clues on inflation and the labor market, which could shape the Fed’s policy decisions. Safe-haven demand remains a key driver, as geopolitical and economic uncertainties continue to influence investor sentiment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-shelter-finance-corporation-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1674022</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674022</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Concord Biotech Ltd, REC Ltd, Westlife Foodworld Ltd and Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 February 2026.

Concord Biotech Ltd, REC Ltd, Westlife Foodworld Ltd and Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 February 2026. India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd lost 5.41% to Rs 746.85 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 80363 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 39433 shares in the past one month. Concord Biotech Ltd crashed 4.54% to Rs 1278.5. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 97986 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13484 shares in the past one month. REC Ltd tumbled 3.42% to Rs 359.75. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 14.12 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.92 lakh shares in the past one month. Westlife Foodworld Ltd corrected 3.37% to Rs 524. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 26416 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.44 lakh shares in the past one month. Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd plummeted 3.33% to Rs 1765. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 13073 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4450 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndiaShelterFinanceCorporationLtd_79307332_48455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Man Industries surges after strong Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/man-industries-surges-after-strong-q3-performance/1674020</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674020</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[EBITDA improved by 61.4% to Rs 136 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 84 crore in Q3 FY25.

EBITDA improved by 61.4% to Rs 136 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 84 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin was 16.2% in Q3 FY26, reflecting the highest consolidated quarterly margin achieved by the company to date. This strong performance was driven by a favourable product and geographic mix. The company maintained a net cash position of around Rs 38 crore as of 31 December 2025, reflecting a healthy balance sheet. The company’s executable order book stood at around Rs 4,000 crore, providing healthy revenue visibility over the next 6–12 months and underpinning growth momentum in the coming quarters. Man Industries’ strategic capacity expansion initiatives in Saudi Arabia and Jammu are progressing as planned, with key civil works and major equipment installations largely completed. The Saudi facility is expected to commence commercial production by Q1 FY27, strengthening the company’s regional footprint, while the Jammu facility remains on track for commissioning by Q2 FY27. The company added that the outlook for the year remains strong, supported by steady order execution and healthy order inflows, and reiterated its full-year revenue guidance of Rs 3,600–3,700 crore, implying 15–20% year-on-year growth in its core business. Nikhil Mansukhani, managing director, MAN Industries (India), said, "We are pleased to report our highest-ever quarterly EBITDA margins, reflecting the strength of our strategy, disciplined execution, and continued focus on operational efficiency. With a record order book, steady progress on our capacity expansions in Saudi Arabia and Jammu, and an expanding global footprint, we are well positioned for the next phase of growth. Our emphasis on value-added products, prudent capital allocation, and customer diversification will continue to support sustainable performance and strengthen our leadership in the global line pipe industry.” Man Industries is a leading manufacturer and exporter of large-diameter carbon steel line pipes for various high-pressure transmission applications for gas, crude oil, petrochemical products, and potable water.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManInds_64315062574_1369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE PAT rises 15% QoQ to Rs 2,408 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-pat-rises-15-qoq-to-rs-2408-crore/1674021</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674021</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 2,408 crore in Q3 FY26, up 15% QoQ from Rs 2,098 crore in Q2 FY26, but down 37% YoY compared with Rs 3,834 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 2,408 crore in Q3 FY26, up 15% QoQ from Rs 2,098 crore in Q2 FY26, but down 37% YoY compared with Rs 3,834 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit after tax margin improved to 54% in Q3 FY26 from 39% in Q2 FY26, though lower than 64% in Q3 FY25. Profit on sale of investment in associates was nil during the quarter, compared with Rs 1,201 crore in Q2 FY26 and Rs 1,155 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income came in at Rs 4,395 crore in Q3 FY26, rising 6% QoQ from Rs 4,160 crore in Q2 FY26, but declining 9% YoY from Rs 4,807 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 3,925 crore, up 7% QoQ, while falling 10% YoY. Operating EBITDA surged 92% QoQ to Rs 2,851 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,484 crore in the previous quarter. On a year-on-year basis, EBITDA declined 16% from Rs 3,398 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA margin improved sharply to 73% in Q3 FY26 from 40% in Q2 FY26, though lower than 78% reported a year ago. Revenue from transaction charges stood at Rs 3,033 crore in Q3 FY26, registering 9% QoQ growth, led by higher volumes across the equity cash market and derivatives segments. Revenue from data feed and terminal services came in at Rs 121 crore, up 5% QoQ, while revenue from listing services rose 25% QoQ to Rs 111 crore, reflecting increased listing-related activity. Total expenses declined sharply to Rs 1,234 crore in Q3 FY26, translating into a 48% QoQ decline, while increasing 14% YoY. In Q3FY26, the cash market trading segment recorded an average daily traded volume (ADTVs) of Rs 99,023 crore (up by 3% QoQ). The ADTV for equity futures segment in Q3FY26 stood at Rs 1,51,744 crore (up by 8% QoQ); while the ADTV for equity options (premium value) stood at Rs 53,248 crore (up by 15% QoQ). National Stock Exchange of India, which began operations in 1994, was the country’s first exchange to introduce electronic trading and has consistently ranked as India’s largest exchange by equity turnover since 1995, based on SEBI data. It operates a fully integrated business model spanning listings, trading, clearing and settlement, indices, market data, technology solutions and financial education, while overseeing regulatory compliance of market participants. Globally, NSE was the world’s largest derivatives exchange by trading volume in calendar year 2024 and ranked second worldwide in the equity segment by number of trades.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>