<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:54:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Properties climbs as Worli project clocks over Rs 2,000 crore sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-properties-climbs-as-worli-project-clocks-over-rs-2000-crore-sales/1670167</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670167</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project was launched in November 2025, with nearly 100 homes sold since launch.

The project was launched in November 2025, with nearly 100 homes sold since launch. Godrej Trilogy is spread across 2.63 acres and consists of three towers. In the initial phase, the company launched select floors in two towers, Seaturf and Seafront, with an opened inventory of approximately Rs 3,500 crore. The project offers 3-bedroom and 4-bedroom residences, with three apartments per floor. The development offers views of the Arabian Sea, the Mumbai skyline, and the Mahalaxmi Racecourse. Once completed, the towers are expected to be among the tallest residential buildings in India. The project is located on Dr. Annie Besant Road in Worli, with access to the Mumbai Coastal Road, the Bandra-Worli Sea Link, and Metro Line 3. Amenities at the project include a five-level clubhouse with a spa, racquet club, and fitness centres. Godrej Trilogy is an IGBC Platinum pre-certified project. In FY 2025, Godrej Properties retained its position as India’s largest developer by the value of residential sales achieved. The company's consolidated net profit jumped 20.84% to Rs 405.08 crore, despite a 32.27% fall in net sales to Rs 470.38 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejPropert_34796940031_15613.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki reports 12% YoY sales growth in January 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maruti-suzuki-reports-12-yoy-sales-growth-in-january-2026/1670163</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670163</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic passenger vehicle (PV) sales stood at 174,529 units, marginally higher by 0.5% YoY, while sales of light commercial vehicles (LCVs) declined 7.8% YoY to 3,771 units during the month.

Domestic passenger vehicle (PV) sales stood at 174,529 units, marginally higher by 0.5% YoY, while sales of light commercial vehicles (LCVs) declined 7.8% YoY to 3,771 units during the month. While the company’s total domestic sales (PV+LCV+OEM) rose 0.4% YoY to 185,943 units, export sales, however, surged 88.3% YoY to 51,020 units, marking an all-time monthly high. For the period from April to January of FY26, the company has registered total sales of 1,983,467 units, up 7.7% YoY. Maruti Suzuki India is engaged in the manufacture, purchase, and sale of motor vehicles, components, and spare parts (automobiles). The company reported a 4.08% YoY increase in net profit to Rs 3,879.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,726.9 crore in Q3 FY25, while revenue from operations rose 28.74% YoY to Rs 49,904.1 crore. Shares of Maruti Suzuki India rose 0.31% to Rs 14,244.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1670161</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670161</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Mutual Fund has announced 04 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option and under the Periodic IDCW Periodic-Payout/Reinvestment) of following schemes.

Tata Mutual Fund has announced 04 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option and under the Periodic IDCW Periodic-Payout/Reinvestment) of following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Tata Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan & Direct Plan: 0.36 each. Tata Equity Savings Fund – Regular Plan & Direct Plan: 0.059 each.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Latent View Analytics jumps after Q3 PAT climbs 20% YoY to Rs 50 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/latent-view-analytics-jumps-after-q3-pat-climbs-20-yoy-to-rs-50-cr/1670151</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670151</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 19.04% YoY to Rs 66.78 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 19.04% YoY to Rs 66.78 crore during the quarter. Rajan Sethuraman, chief executive officer, LatentView, said, “During the quarter, we added 6 new client logos, while renewing most of our existing contracts. Our Financial Services practice continued to be a key growth driver, witnessing sequential growth of 20.6% and reinforcing its strategic importance to our overall performance. As we enter FY27, we continue to see strong, sustained momentum in Financial Services, reflecting the deep strategic role LatentView plays in supporting our clients’ short-term priorities and long-term business goals.” 2026 marks our 20th anniversary, and our commitment to turn data into impactful business decisions is as strong as ever. Looking forward, we remain focused on scaling AI and Agentic AI frameworks across the organization and strengthening our position as a trusted AI consultant and thought partner of choice for our clients.” Rajan Venkatesan, chief financial officer, LatentView, said, “In Q3FY26, we reported revenue of Rs 278.0 crore, witnessing sequential growth of 7.9% in rupee terms and 5.7% in dollar terms, indicating strong momentum in topline performance. The growth was primarily led by the Financial Services and Technology practices, which grew by 20.6% and 6.2%, respectively. We maintained an adjusted EBITDA margin at 23.0%, supported by operational discipline, despite the impact of one time costs. Excluding these one time items, adjusted EBITDA margin for the quarter would have been 24.6%. Employee costs for the quarter included a one time catch up expense related to the implementation of the new labour code, with a total impact of Rs 4.6 crore at the group level. On a recurring basis, we expect this to result in an incremental impact of approximately 10-15 basis points on margins going forward. We are in the process of restructuring salary components to ensure full compliance with the new labour code and expect this exercise to be completed by March 31, 2026.” Latent View Analytics (LatentView) is a global data analytics company. The company provides a 360-degree view of the digital consumer, enabling companies to predict new revenue streams, anticipate product trends and popularity, improve customer retention rates, and optimize investment decisions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/latentviewanalytics_44641535_39858.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade with small gains; oil & gas shares advance; VIX jumps 1.52%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-small-gains-oil-gas-shares-advance-vix-jumps-152/1670149</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670149</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade after a sharp sell-off during a special trading session on Sunday.

The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade after a sharp sell-off during a special trading session on Sunday. Investor sentiment weakened after the Union Budget for FY 2026–27 fell short of market expectations, particularly on issues related to foreign investment and trading costs. The Nifty traded above the 24,800 level. Oil & Gas, metal and banks shares advanced while FMCG, IT and media shares declined. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 197.32 points or 0.24% to 80,921.92. The Nifty 50 index rose 32.80 points or 0.11% to 24,843.55. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.56% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index declined 0.94%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,297 shares rose and 1,651 shares fell. A total of 151 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 1.52% to 15.33. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 588.34 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 682.73 crore in the Indian equity market on 1 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Hero Motocorp rose 0.21%. The company’s total sales jumped 26% to 5,57,871 units in January 2026 compared with 442,873 units in January 2025. Latent View added 2.61% after the company reported a 19.68% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 501.42 crore on 22.02% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2780.09 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Studds Accessories declined 2.27%. The company reported a 26.3% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 20.7 crore on 9.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 163 crore in Q3 FY265 over Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.96% to 6.759 compared with previous session close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7300 compared with its close of 90.7875 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.95% to Rs 144,885. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.10% to 97.09. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.12% to 4.239. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell $2.84 or 4.10% to $64.21 a barrel. Brent crude prices slid after U.S. President Donald Trump said over the weekend that Iran was “seriously talking” with Washington, signaling a possible easing of tensions with the OPEC member. The comments helped temper fears of a potential military strike that had earlier pushed oil prices to multi-month highs. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 354 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. Asian equities slipped on Monday as investors digested fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold continued to slide after last week’s drop. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Patterns (India) Ltd Spurts 4.15%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/data-patterns-india-ltd-spurts-415/1670147</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670147</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Data Patterns (India) Ltd rose 4.15% today to trade at Rs 2573.

Data Patterns (India) Ltd rose 4.15% today to trade at Rs 2573. The BSE Capital Goods index is up 0.53% to quote at 64996.15. The index is down 4.24 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Cochin Shipyard Ltd increased 2.52% and Bharat Electronics Ltd added 2.22% on the day. The BSE Capital Goods index went up 3.86 % over last one year compared to the 3.93% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Data Patterns (India) Ltd has lost 1.84% over last one month compared to 4.24% fall in BSE Capital Goods index and 6.07% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1945 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 51904 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 3267.2 on 06 Jun 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 1350.5 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DataPatternsIndiaLtd_64674034_39972.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd Falls 10.65%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/optiemus-infracom-ltd-falls-1065/1670148</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670148</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd lost 10.65% today to trade at Rs 350.

Optiemus Infracom Ltd lost 10.65% today to trade at Rs 350. The BSE Telecommunication index is down 0.7% to quote at 2912.49. The index is down 8.57 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Tata Communications Ltd decreased 2.32% and Bharti Hexacom Ltd lost 1.63% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 5.35 % over last one year compared to the 3.93% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Optiemus Infracom Ltd has lost 31.01% over last one month compared to 8.57% fall in BSE Telecommunication index and 6.07% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 8471 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 712.95 on 25 Sep 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 02 Feb 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OptiemusInfra_38144306001_5004.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR stays pressured amid dollar strength overseas]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-stays-pressured-amid-dollar-strength-overseas/1670145</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670145</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee is staying almost flat against the dollar in opening trades on Monday tracking dollar strength overseas.

The Indian rupee is staying almost flat against the dollar in opening trades on Monday tracking dollar strength overseas. Meanwhile, not very encouraging cues from equities are also contributing to the decline. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty both fell over 2 percent on Sunday during the special weekend trading session after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced a hike in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures and options in her Budget 2026 speech. Today, INR opened at Rs 91.95 per dollar and recovered to a high of 91.71 so far during the day. On Friday, rupee ended at 91.93/$.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices seen opening mildly higher]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-seen-opening-mildly-higher/1670138</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670138</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 10 points, suggesting a mildly positive start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 10 points, suggesting a mildly positive start for the Nifty 50 today. Brent crude prices slid more than 3% on Monday after US President Donald Trump said over the weekend that Iran was “seriously talking” with Washington, a signal of easing tensions with the OPEC member. The comments tempered fears of a potential military strike that had earlier pushed oil prices to multi-month highs. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 588.34 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 682.73 crore in the Indian equity market on 1 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs sold shares worth Rs 38740.12 in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 190 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. Asian equities slipped on Monday as investors digested fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold continued to slide after last week’s drop. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House. Domestic Market: The benchmark equity indices witnessed a sharp sell-off during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of the Union Budget 2026 by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman. While the speech remained broadly market-friendly at the macro level—maintaining the fiscal deficit glide path at 4.4% in FY26 and 4.3% in FY27, raising capital expenditure to around Rs 12.2 lakh crore, and reiterating a declining debt-to-GDP trajectory—the positives were overshadowed by a key negative for markets. The sharp increase in Securities Transaction Tax on derivatives emerged as the primary trigger for the sell-off. STT on futures was raised from 0.02% to 0.05%, while the levy on options was increased to 0.15%. The move sparked aggressive unwinding in stocks linked to capital market sector, with brokerages, exchanges and other high-beta F&O counters bearing the brunt of the selling during the single special session. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,546 points or 1.88% to 80,722.94. The Nifty 50 index dropped 495.20 points or 1.96% to 24,825.45.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Studds Accessories, Hero Motocorp, TFCI ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-studds-accessories-hero-motocorp-tfci/1670135</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670135</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are ban from F&O trading on Monday, 2 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are ban from F&O trading on Monday, 2 February 2026. Earnings to Watch: Huyundai Motor India, PB Fintech, Utkarsh Small Finance Bank (SFB), Campus Activewear, Corona Remedies, Bajaj Housing Finance, Aether Energy, Aarti Industries, Akzo Nobel, Mahindra Lifespace Developers, Orectra Greentech, Railtel Corporation of India, Tata Chemicals Stocks to Watch: Auto stocks will be in focus as companies will declare their auto sales numbers Hero Motocorp’s total sales jumped 26% to 5,57,871 units in January 2026 compared with 442,873 units in January 2025. Latent View reported a 19.68% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 501.42 crore on 22.02% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2780.09 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Studds Accessories reported a 26.3% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 20.7 crore on 9.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 163 crore in Q3 FY265 over Q3 FY25. Toursim Finance Corporation of India (TFCI) decided to invest upto 5% of corpus fund in Oxyzo Credit Funds, a debt focused diversified sectors Category II Alternative Investment Fund registered with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI).

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp dispatches jump 26% YoY to 5,57,871 units in Jan’26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-dispatches-jump-26-yoy-to-557871-units-in-jan26/1670134</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670134</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic sales during the period aggregated to 5,20,208 units, up 26.14% YoY, while exports stood at 37,663 units, marking a 23.50% YoY increase.

Domestic sales during the period aggregated to 5,20,208 units, up 26.14% YoY, while exports stood at 37,663 units, marking a 23.50% YoY increase. Motorcycle sales reached 4,95,889 units, reflecting a 23.88% YoY growth. Scooter sales outperformed, surging 45.56% YoY to 61,982 units in January 2026. The company’s global business maintained strong momentum, with dispatches rising around 24% YoY to 37,663 units in January 2026, compared to 30,495 units in the same period last year. Strong consumer response to the premium portfolio supported growth across international markets. Hero MotoCorp is the world's largest manufacturer of motorcycles and scooters, with a global footprint spanning 48 countries across Asia, Africa, and Latin America. It has collaborations with Harley-Davidson and Zero Motorcycles and strategic investments in Ather Energy and Euler Motors. The company's standalone net profit rose 15.72% to Rs 1,392.83 crore on a 15.89% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 12,126.37 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.49% to Rs 5,508.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>