<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:09:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers drift lower in early trade; FMCG shares advance; VIX jumps 6.04%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-drift-lower-in-early-trade-fmcg-shares-advance-vix-jumps-604/1665541</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665541</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in early trade, pressured by renewed worries over a potential escalation in global trade tensions and a mixed set of earnings from heavyweight companies.

The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in early trade, pressured by renewed worries over a potential escalation in global trade tensions and a mixed set of earnings from heavyweight companies. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. FMCG and consumer durables shares advanced while all other index traded in red on the NSE. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 384.78 points or 0.46% to 83,193.96. The Nifty 50 index fell 125.30 points or 0.50% to 25,563.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.21% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.82%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,108 shares rose and 2,097 shares fell. A total of 236 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 6.04% to 12.06. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 4,346.13 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,935.31 crore in the Indian equity market on 16 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Reliance Industries (RIL) fell 1.28%. The company has reported 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. L&T Finance fell 1.77%. The company has reported 18% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 739 crore on a 18% increase in total income to Rs 2,920 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Yes Bank shed 0.64%. The company has reported a sharp improvement in its Q3 FY26 performance, with net profit surging 55.4% YoY to Rs 952 crore, driven by strong operating income, lower credit costs. Net interest income stood at Rs 2,466 crore, up 10.9% YoY and 7.2% QoQ, aided by a reduction in the cost of funds. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.47% to 6.678 compared with previous session close of 6.647. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7300 compared with its close of 90.7875 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 1.38% to Rs 144,487. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.20% to 99.19. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.17% to 4.240. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 8 cents or 0.12% to $64.21 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market mostly slipped Monday, as investors assessed threats from the Trump administration toward Greenland over the weekend, as well as key economic data from China out Monday. Over the weekend, U.S. President Donald Trump and European leaders exchanged tense rhetoric over the Arctic territory, with Trump threatening tariffs on eight European countries and demanding control of Greenland, which is part of Denmark. European leaders responded by calling the threats “completely wrong” and “unacceptable.” In Asia, China released its fourth-quarter GDP numbers, along with December figures for retail sales, urban investment and industrial output. China’s economic growth slowed to its weakest pace in nearly three years in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, though full-year growth matched Beijing’s target despite growing trade frictions with the U.S. and a prolonged real estate slump. Gross domestic product grew 4.5% in the October-to-December period, data from the National Statistics Bureau showed Monday. That marked a slowdown from 4.8% in the third quarter and was the weakest reading since the first quarter of 2023, when growth also came in at 4.5%. The full-year economic output came in at 5%, meeting the official target of around 5%. On Friday in the U.S., the S&P 500 ended just below the flatline and posted a losing week, while the Nasdaq Composite also inched down 0.06%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.17%. The three major indexes hit their session lows after Trump said in the White House on Friday that he’d rather have National Economic Council Director Kevin Hassett stay in his current role and that he might not be chosen to become the next U.S. Fed chair. Hassett has been seen as the more market-friendly option to replace current Fed chair than the new frontrunner nominee, former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, and is expected to be more willing to keep rates low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MRF Ltd Spurts 1.02%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mrf-ltd-spurts-102/1665539</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665539</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[MRF Ltd gained 1.02% today to trade at Rs 144332.05.

MRF Ltd gained 1.02% today to trade at Rs 144332.05. The BSE Auto index is up 0.23% to quote at 61455.8. The index is down 0.13 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Tube Investments of India Ltd increased 0.55% and Maruti Suzuki India Ltd added 0.19% on the day. The BSE Auto index went up 19.33 % over last one year compared to the 8.97% surge in benchmark SENSEX. MRF Ltd has lost 6.12% over last one month compared to 0.13% fall in BSE Auto index and 1.69% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 15 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 354 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 163500 on 24 Oct 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 100500 on 05 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MRF_74566371174_391.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sobha Ltd Slides 3.12%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sobha-ltd-slides-312/1665540</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665540</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sobha Ltd lost 3.12% today to trade at Rs 1479.2.

Sobha Ltd lost 3.12% today to trade at Rs 1479.2. The BSE Realty index is down 0.87% to quote at 6590.58. The index is down 4.07 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Brigade Enterprises Ltd decreased 2.11% and Embassy Developments Ltd lost 1.59% on the day. The BSE Realty index went down 10.9 % over last one year compared to the 8.97% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Sobha Ltd has added 1.29% over last one month compared to 4.07% fall in BSE Realty index and 1.69% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1715 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 15542 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 1732.45 on 22 Jul 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 1075.7 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Sobha_16954596303_27443.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Wipro skid after Q3 PAT drops 4% QoQ to Rs 3119 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wipro-skid-after-q3-pat-drops-4-qoq-to-rs-3119-cr/1665537</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665537</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 7% while revenue from operations increased 5.54% in Q3 FY26.

On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 7% while revenue from operations increased 5.54% in Q3 FY26. Adjusted for impact of labour code changes, net income for the quarter was Rs 3,360 crore ($374.3 million), increase of 3.6% QoQ and 0.3% YoY. Profit before tax (PBT) fell 6.59% YoY to Rs 3,145 crore during the quarter. In dollar terms, Wipro's gross revenue for Q3 FY26 stood at $2,622 million, registering a increase of 3.8% QoQ and up 5.5% YoY. IT services segment revenue was at $2,635.4 million in Q3 FY26, marking the growth of 1.2% QoQ and 0.2% YoY. IT services operating margin for Q3 FY26 was 17.6%, expansion of 0.9% QoQ and 0.1% on YoY basis. Total bookings stood at $3,335 million in Q3 FY26, down 5.7% YoY in constant currency. Large deal bookings stood at $871 million in Q3 FY26, down 8.4% YoY in constant currency. The company said that its closing employee count in IT Services stood at 242,021 in Q3 FY26. Voluntary attrition was at 14.2% on a trailing 12-month basis. Looking ahead, the company said that it expects revenue from IT Services business segment to be in the range of $2,635 million to $2,688 million. This translates to sequential guidance of 0% to 2.0% in constant currency terms. Srini Pallia, CEO and managing director, said “In Q3, we delivered broad-based growth in line with our expectations. As AI becomes a strategic imperative, Wipro Intelligence is emerging as a differentiator and contributed to several wins this quarter. We saw greater adoption of our AI-enabled platforms and solutions, scaled AI-led delivery through WINGS and WEGA, and expanded our innovation network across global locations.” Aparna Iyer, chief financial officer (CFO), said “Our IT services operating margins at 17.6% expanded both sequentially and on a year-on-year basis. This is our best margin performance in last few years. Our continued focus on execution rigour also reflects in our strong operating cash flow of 135% of net income in Q3. We are also pleased to share that the Board has declared an interim dividend of Rs 6 per share which will take the total payout for the year to $1.3 Billion.” Meanwhile, the company’s board declared a dividend of Rs 6 per share with a face value of Rs 2 each. The record date has been fixed as 27 January 2026 and dividend will be paid on 14 February 2026. Wipro is a leading technology services and consulting company focused on building innovative solutions that address clients' most complex digital transformation needs. The counter added 2.73% to end at Rs 267.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Wipro_36546468_614.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[InterGlobe Aviation receives 8 orders from DGCA for December's operational disruption]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/interglobe-aviation-receives-8-orders-from-dgca-for-decembers-operational-disruption/1665538</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665538</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The DGCA has levied a one-time systemic penalties of Rs 1.80 crore for non-compliances under applicable Civil Aviation Requirements (CARs) and penalty for continued non-compliance with revised FDTL CAR for 68 days (from 05 December 2025 to 10 February 2026) amounting to Rs 20.40 crore, aggregating to Rs 22.20 crore.

The DGCA has levied a one-time systemic penalties of Rs 1.80 crore for non-compliances under applicable Civil Aviation Requirements (CARs) and penalty for continued non-compliance with revised FDTL CAR for 68 days (from 05 December 2025 to 10 February 2026) amounting to Rs 20.40 crore, aggregating to Rs 22.20 crore. It has also issued a directive to furnish a bank guarantee of Rs 50 crore, to be governed under the IndiGo Systemic Reform Assurance Scheme (ISRAS), with phased release linked to DGCA-verified implementation of systemic reform measures. The DGCA has issued a caution note to the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) for inadequate overall oversight of flight operations. A warning has been issued to the accountable manager (chief operating officer – COO) for failure to adequately assess the impact of the Winter Schedule 2025 and the revised FDTL provisions, leading to widespread operational disruptions. The senior vice president – operations control centre (OCC) has also received a warning, along with directions to the company to relieve him of current operational responsibilities and not assign any accountable position. Lastlty, the deputy head – flight operations, AVP – crew resource planning and director – flight operations have also received warnings for operational, supervisory, and roster-management related lapses. The Chairman and Members of the Board Of Directors of InterGlobe Aviation said: "We are in receipt of the orders of the Directorate General of Civil Aviation of India in relation to the events which led to a major operational disruption of IndiGo's flights in early December, 2025. We would like to take this opportunity to inform all of our stakeholders that the board and the management of IndiGo are committed to taking full cognizance of the orders and will, in a thoughtful and timely manner, take appropriate measures. Additionally, an in-depth review of the robustness and resilience of the internal processes at IndiGo has been underway since the disruption to ensure that the airline emerges stronger out of these events." InterGlobe Aviation is amongst the fastest growing low-cost carriers in the world. It had a fleet of 417 aircraft and provided scheduled services to 94 domestic and 41 international destinations as of 30th September 2025. The company's consolidated net loss widened to Rs 2,582.1 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with net loss of Rs 986.7 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 9.34% YoY to Rs 18,555.3 crore in Q2 Sept 2025. The scrip rose 3.80% to currently trade at Rs 4918.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InterglobeAviat_28069694232_33159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests red opening for equities; China clocks GDP growth of 4.5% in Q4]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-red-opening-for-equities-china-clocks-gdp-growth-of-45-in-q4/1665527</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665527</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 94.00 points, hinting towards a negative opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 94.00 points, hinting towards a negative opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 4,346.13 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,935.31 crore in the Indian equity market on 16 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 26,052.40 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market mostly slipped Monday, as investors assessed threats from the Trump administration toward Greenland over the weekend, as well as key economic data from China out Monday. Over the weekend, U.S. President Donald Trump and European leaders exchanged tense rhetoric over the Arctic territory, with Trump threatening tariffs on eight European countries and demanding control of Greenland, which is part of Denmark. European leaders responded by calling the threats “completely wrong” and “unacceptable.” In Asia, China released its fourth-quarter GDP numbers, along with December figures for retail sales, urban investment and industrial output. China’s economic growth slowed to its weakest pace in nearly three years in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, though full-year growth matched Beijing’s target despite growing trade frictions with the U.S. and a prolonged real estate slump. Gross domestic product grew 4.5% in the October-to-December period, data from the National Statistics Bureau showed Monday. That marked a slowdown from 4.8% in the third quarter and was the weakest reading since the first quarter of 2023, when growth also came in at 4.5%. The full-year economic output came in at 5%, meeting the official target of around 5%. On Friday in the U.S., the S&P 500 ended just below the flatline and posted a losing week, while the Nasdaq Composite also inched down 0.06%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.17%. The three major indexes hit their session lows after Trump said in the White House on Friday that he’d rather have National Economic Council Director Kevin Hassett stay in his current role and that he might not be chosen to become the next U.S. Fed chair. Hassett has been seen as the more market-friendly option to replace current Fed chair than the new frontrunner nominee, former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, and is expected to be more willing to keep rates low. Domestic Market: Benchmark equity indices closed with modest gains on Friday, ending a two-day losing streak, as buying interest returned to IT stocks following Infosys’ better-than-expected quarterly performance and an upgrade to its full-year revenue growth outlook. Market sentiment also drew support from the ongoing December-quarter earnings season, with investors awaiting the Q3 results of Reliance Industries later in the day. Gains in IT shares, along with select banking stocks, helped the Nifty settle above the 25,650 level. Adding to the positive tone, early trends from the Maharashtra assembly elections showed the BJP-Shiv Sena alliance in the lead. Markets generally view political stability and continuity in governance as supportive for economic growth and policy direction. However, the broader upside was capped by weakness in pharma and healthcare stocks, which ended the session lower. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 187.64 points or 0.23% to 83,570.35. The Nifty 50 index added 28.75 points or 0.11% to 25,694.35. The 50-unit index fell 0.48% in the past two sessions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RVNL emerges L1 for South Eastern Railway’s VSS project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rvnl-emerges-l1-for-south-eastern-railways-vss-project/1665526</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665526</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order includes supply, installation and commissioning of IP based video surveillance system (VSS) in LHB coaches with 4 cameras as per RDSO Specification No.

The order includes supply, installation and commissioning of IP based video surveillance system (VSS) in LHB coaches with 4 cameras as per RDSO Specification No. RDSO/SPN/TC/106/2025, Version 3.1 or Latest including Rugged Hand Held Terminal (HHT)I Tablet along with 8 TB external SSD. The said order is valued at Rs 87.55 crore and it will be executed within 10 months from the date of issue of purchase order. Rail Vikas Nigam is in the business of executing all types of railway projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, construction of cable-stayed bridges, institution buildings, etc. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 19.73% to Rs 230.29 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 286.88 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5.22% YoY to Rs 5,122.98 crore in Q2 FY26. The scrip shed 0.90% to end at Rs 335.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: RIL, L&T Finance, Yes Bank, Tata Technologies, HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-ril-lt-finance-yes-bank-tata-technologies-hdfc-bank-icici-bank/1665516</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665516</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 19 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 19 January 2026. Result Today: LTIMindtree, Punjab National Bank, Tata Capital, Aarti Surfactants, Bharat Heavy Electricals, Ceat, Hatsun Agro Product, Havells India, Hindustan Zinc, Indian Railway Finance Corporation, Oberoi Realty, Apollo Techno Industries, and Atlanta Electricals will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Reliance Industries (RIL) has reported 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. L&T Finance has reported 18% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 739 crore on a 18% increase in total income to Rs 2,920 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Yes Bank reported a sharp improvement in its Q3 FY26 performance, with net profit surging 55.4% YoY to Rs 952 crore, driven by strong operating income, lower credit costs. Net interest income stood at Rs 2,466 crore, up 10.9% YoY and 7.2% QoQ, aided by a reduction in the cost of funds. Tata Technologies reported a 95.99% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 6.64 crore despite a 3.2% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1,365.73 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. HDFC Bank reported 11.46% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 18,563.75 crore on 2.91% increase in total income to Rs 90,005 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ICICI Bank has reported 4.02% fall in standalone net profit to Rs 11,318 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 11,792 crore in Q3 FY25. Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26. RBL Bank reported a massive 555.47% surge in standalone net profit to Rs 213.88 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 32.63 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 2.33% YoY to Rs 4,71,700 crore as on 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>