<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:28:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index advances well above 98 mark; US jobs data in focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-advances-well-above-98-mark-us-jobs-data-in-focus/1663785</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663785</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Dollar index ascends well into mid 98 mark on Thursday after the ISM reported on Wednesday that the US Services PMI rose to 54.4 in December from 52.6 in November.

Dollar index ascends well into mid 98 mark on Thursday after the ISM reported on Wednesday that the US Services PMI rose to 54.4 in December from 52.6 in November. This figure came in stronger than the expectation of 52.3. JOLTS Job Openings came in at 7.146 million in November. Meanwhile, ADP Employment Change showed an increase of 41,000 jobs in December, following a revised decline of 29,000 in November. Investors now turn attention to weekly jobless claims due Thursday and the December employment report on Friday for further cues on possible Federal stance going ahead. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies was quoting at 98.45, marginally higher on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 26,000 level; IT shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-26000-level-it-shares-decline/1663782</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663782</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded significant cuts in the mid-morning as concerns over U.S.

The key equity indices traded significant cuts in the mid-morning as concerns over U.S. tariffs and continued foreign fund outflows overshadowed pockets of optimism around earnings growth. The Nifty traded below 26,000 level. IT shares declined after advancing for previous two consecutive trading sessions. At 11:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 444.52 points or 0.52% to 84,515.60. The Nifty 50 index declined 168.15 points or 0.64% to 25,972.30. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 1.52% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.62%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,162 shares rose and 2,675 shares fell. A total of 209 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 1.51% to 38,105.75. The index rose 0.88% in the previous two consecutive trading session. Tata Consultancy Services (down 3.2%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.98%), Mphasis (down 1.83%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 1.82%), Wipro (down 1.68%), LTIMindtree (down 1.48%), Coforge (down 1.39%), Infosys (down 0.91%), Persistent Systems (down 0.88%) fell. Stocks in Spotlight: NCL Industries fell 1.96%. The company has recorded 5% growth in cement production in Q3 FY26, producing 6,94,854 MT of cement during the period under review as against 6,61,049 MT produced in Q3 FY25. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.19%. The company said it has received a supply order from the Corps of Electronics and Mechanical Engineers (EME) of the Indian Army for overhaul, upgrade, and obsolescence management of the indigenous Pinaka Multi-Rocket Launcher Systems. Granules India rose 1.07% after its arm Granules Pharmaceuticals, Inc has received tentative approval from the USFDA for its Abbreviated New Drug Application for generic Amphetamine Extended-Release Tablets, equivalent to DYANAVEL XR. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets traded mixed on Thursday after Wall Street closed lower amid rising geopolitical tensions and comments from U.S. President Donald Trump. U.S. defense stocks fell after Trump said he “will not permit” defense companies to issue dividends or stock buybacks until they address his complaints about the industry, including executive pay packages and production issues. In U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day winning streak, falling 466 points, or 0.94%, to close at 48,996.08. The S&P 500 declined 23.89 points or 0.34% to end at 6,920.93, while the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite edged up 37.10 points or 0.16% to close at 23,584.28.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel secures Rs 102-cr PFMS IT infrastructure order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-secures-rs-102-cr-pfms-it-infrastructure-order/1663781</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663781</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the establishment and managed operations of IT infrastructure, including Data Center (DC) and Disaster Recovery (DR) services, Security Operations Center (SOC) services, and data center colocation, to be executed by 31 January 2027.

The project involves the establishment and managed operations of IT infrastructure, including Data Center (DC) and Disaster Recovery (DR) services, Security Operations Center (SOC) services, and data center colocation, to be executed by 31 January 2027. RailTel Corporation, a "Navratna" PSU, is one of the largest neutral telecom infrastructure providers in the country, owning a Pan-India optical fiber network. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 4.72% to Rs 76.07 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 72.64 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 12.78% YoY to Rs 951.36 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of RailTel Corporation of India fell 1.23% to Rs 363.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at The Ramco Cements Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-the-ramco-cements-ltd-counter/1663775</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663775</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[eClerx Services Ltd, Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd, Aarti Industries Ltd, Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 08 January 2026.

eClerx Services Ltd, Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd, Aarti Industries Ltd, Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 08 January 2026. The Ramco Cements Ltd notched up volume of 3.97 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 27.12 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 14642 shares. The stock rose 0.96% to Rs.1,088.30. Volumes stood at 28560 shares in the last session. eClerx Services Ltd recorded volume of 60328 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 19.85 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3040 shares. The stock lost 0.82% to Rs.4,733.85. Volumes stood at 2341 shares in the last session. Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd registered volume of 42993 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 19.62 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2191 shares. The stock rose 7.25% to Rs.1,650.00. Volumes stood at 1671 shares in the last session. Aarti Industries Ltd recorded volume of 7.41 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 18.33 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 40413 shares. The stock lost 0.05% to Rs.375.75. Volumes stood at 18765 shares in the last session. Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd registered volume of 2.62 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 17.42 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 15042 shares. The stock slipped 1.04% to Rs.7,371.00. Volumes stood at 84880 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TheRamcoCement_41212181057_357.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NCL Industries clocks 5% YoY rise in Q3 cement production]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ncl-industries-clocks-5-yoy-rise-in-q3-cement-production/1663776</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663776</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cement dispatches also rose by 5% to 6,93,229 MT in the quarter ended on 31 December 2025 from 6,62,936 MT in the quarter ended on 31 December 2024.

Cement dispatches also rose by 5% to 6,93,229 MT in the quarter ended on 31 December 2025 from 6,62,936 MT in the quarter ended on 31 December 2024. The production and dispatches of cement boards in Q3 FY26 were 11,907 MT (down 41% YoY) and 14,096 MT (down 25% YoY), respectively. RMC production & sales for the December 2025 quarter were 65,939 CuM, down 18% YoY. The production & sales of doors dropped significantly to 42 units in Q3 FY26 from 8,680 units in Q3 FY25. The Hydro Power division produced 17.00 MU of energy in Q3 FY26, up 2% YoY. NCL Industries manufactures different varieties of cement, cement-bonded particle boards, ready-mix concrete and doors. The company's consolidated net profit surged to Rs 19.90 crore in the quarter ended September 2025 as against Rs 2.51 crore during the previous quarter ended September 2024. Sales rose 4.44% to Rs 345.05 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip shed 0.67% to currently trade at Rs 208.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NCLInds_59425784710_401.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Balaji Amines soars after Maharashtra incentives approval]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/balaji-amines-soars-after-maharashtra-incentives-approval/1663774</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663774</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The rally followed the company’s disclosure that the Directorate of Industries, Government of Maharashtra, has granted incentives for the expansion of Unit IV at Chincholi MIDC in Solapur under the Mega Projects category.

The rally followed the company’s disclosure that the Directorate of Industries, Government of Maharashtra, has granted incentives for the expansion of Unit IV at Chincholi MIDC in Solapur under the Mega Projects category. Under the scheme, Balaji Amines is eligible for Industrial Promotion Subsidy of up to Rs 258 crore. The subsidy is linked to 50% of the SGST payable on sales of eligible finished products within Maharashtra. The company will also benefit from electricity duty exemption. It has been granted a 100% waiver on stamp duty as well. These incentives will be available for seven years. The period runs from 1 January 2024 to 31 December 2030. Balaji Amines is engaged in the activity of manufacture and sale of Aliphatic Amines, speciality chemicals and its derivatives. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Balaji Amines declined 15.67% to Rs 34.56 crore while net sales declined 1.82% to Rs 340.55 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BalajiAmines_3829774406_5288.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ministry of Rural Development and Department of Posts Sign MoU to accelerate rural economic transformation ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ministry-of-rural-development-and-department-of-posts-sign-mou-to-accelerate-rural-economic-transformation/1663770</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663770</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Rural Development (MoRD) and the Department of Posts signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to institutionalize convergence for expanding financial services, logistics, and market access in rural areas.

Ministry of Rural Development (MoRD) and the Department of Posts signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to institutionalize convergence for expanding financial services, logistics, and market access in rural areas. The partnership gives concrete shape to the Union Budget 2025 vision of repositioning India Post as a key driver of rural economic transformation. Under the MoU, Deendayal Antodaya Yojana-National Rural Livelihoods Mission, Ministry of Rural Development, will promote adoption of savings, deposits, insurance, and pension products of India Post among SHG households. The Mission will identify and nurture SHG women as Business Correspondents (BC Sakhis), facilitating their training, certification, and deployment. India Post, through IPPB, will provide end-to-end support including onboarding, handholding, technology-enabled monitoring dashboards, and exploration of customised insurance solutions, thereby deepening last-mile financial access in rural areas The partnership will also unlock new market opportunities for women-led SHG enterprises by integrating them with India Posts logistics ecosystem. The Mission will identify SHG and federation-level enterprises with logistics potential and support capacity building in packaging, documentation, and export readiness. India Post will extend logistics, packaging, and export facilitation services, including through Dak Niryat Kendras, and explore promotional avenues for SHG products through its extensive postal network

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/agriculture-1551086__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Midwest gains after securing Quarry lease order from AP govt]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/midwest-gains-after-securing-quarry-lease-order-from-ap-govt/1663771</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663771</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the order, the company has been permitted to undertake quarrying operations for the extraction of coloured quartzite blocks useful for cutting and polishing purpose.

Under the order, the company has been permitted to undertake quarrying operations for the extraction of coloured quartzite blocks useful for cutting and polishing purpose. The lease cover an area of 21.012 hectares (51.92 acres) located at Hanumanthunipadu Village & Mandal in Prakasam, Andhra Pradesh for a period of 30 years, commencing from 06 January 2026 to 05 January 2056, subject to requisite statutory approvals and compliance with applicable conditions. The estimated available marketable coloured quartzite block in the quarry is 609,620 cubic meters. Midwest (ML) is engaged in the exploration, mining, processing, marketing, distribution, and export of natural stones. The company is a producer and exporter of black galaxy granite, a unique granite variety known for its sparkling golden flakes. On a consolidated basis, Midwest's net profit rose 86.82% to Rs 27.78 crore while net sales rose 12.38% to Rs 158.69 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MidwestLtd_60188168_94066.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Currency in circulation soars 10.2% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/currency-in-circulation-soars-102-on-year/1663769</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663769</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation edged up 0.30% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 39.23 lakh crore as on December 31, 2025.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation edged up 0.30% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 39.23 lakh crore as on December 31, 2025. The central bank stated further that the overall reserve money fell 0.50% in the same period to Rs 47.99 lakh crore. Currency in circulation soared 10.2% on a year ago basis compared to 5.9% rise at the same time last year. In the current fiscal year, the currency in circulation gained 5.3% so far while the reserve money has contracted 0.60%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/budget-planning-and-allocating-money-concept-picture-id5081_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T secures Pinaka system order from Indian Army ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-secures-pinaka-system-order-from-indian-army/1663767</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663767</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The program involves lifecycle support and modernization of in-service Pinaka regiments.

The program involves lifecycle support and modernization of in-service Pinaka regiments. Under the arrangement, 510 Army Base Workshop (ABW) of the Corps of EME will carry out overhauls and upgrades, while L&T, as the OEM, will supply critical spares and provide technical and quality support. In the initial phase, L&T and 510 ABW will jointly undertake a pilot overhaul of Pinaka Launchers and Battery Command Posts, after which the remaining systems will be overhauled by 510 ABW. The initiative reinforces the public-private partnership model in defence sustenance and aligns with the Aatmanirbhar Bharat program. Larsen & Toubro is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services. The company reported a 15.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Larsen & Toubro shed 0.23% to Rs 4,158.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Granules India gains after arm receives USFDA tentative approval for ADHD drug]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/granules-india-gains-after-arm-receives-usfda-tentative-approval-for-adhd-drug/1663768</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663768</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the ANDA has been determined by the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) to be eligible for 180-day exclusivity.

The company said the ANDA has been determined by the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) to be eligible for 180-day exclusivity. The product is indicated for the treatment of Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) and has an estimated market size of around $41 million. The exclusivity status strengthens Granules’ position in developing and commercializing complex and differentiated generic products for the US market. Earlier, on 22 December 2025, Granules Pharmaceuticals received tentative approval for Amphetamine Extended-Release Orally Disintegrating Tablets in multiple strengths, the generic equivalent of ADZENYS XR-ODT, also used for the treatment of ADHD. This product currently has only one approved generic and one authorized generic, with an addressable market of about $172 million. The company said the tentative approval for generic DYANAVEL XR tablets marks the second consecutive approval for Granules Pharmaceuticals within a few weeks, highlighting its growing capabilities in complex formulation development and regulatory execution. Dr. Krishna Prasad Chigurupati, chairman & managing director, Granules India, said, “Having a product that is eligible for 180-day exclusivity, Granules strongly validates our long-term strategy of building a differentiated portfolio of complex generics. It also reinforces our commitment to strengthening our presence in the central nervous system (CNS) therapeutic space while enhancing value creation in the U.S. generics market.” Granules India is primarily involved in the manufacturing and sale of active pharmaceutical ingredients (APIs), pharmaceutical formulation intermediates (PFIs), and finished dosages (FDs). The company’s consolidated net profit declined 16.3% to Rs 112.64 crore, while net sales increased 3.4% to Rs 1,208.79 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GranulesIndia_74697683931_12632.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade with minor losses; oil & gas shares decline for 4th day in row]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-minor-losses-oil-gas-shares-decline-for-4th-day-in-row/1663764</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663764</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the in the morning trade as concerns over U.S.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the in the morning trade as concerns over U.S. tariffs and continued foreign fund outflows overshadowed pockets of optimism around earnings growth. The Nifty traded near the 26,050 mark, while oil & gas shares extended losses for a fourth consecutive session. At 10:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 277.54 points or 0.33% to 84,683.60. The Nifty 50 index fell 90.25 points or 0.35% to 26,050.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.65% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.37%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,478 shares rose and 2,114 shares fell. A total of 194 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index fell 1.29% to 11,767.50. The index declined 4.63% in the four consecutive trading session. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 1.98%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 1.98%), Indian Oil Corporation (down 1.33%), Petronet LNG (down 1.31%), Oil India (down 1.24%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 1.22%), Reliance Industries (down 0.71%), GAIL (India) (down 0.51%), Castrol India (down 0.43%) and Indraprastha Gas (down 0.12%) declined. On the other hand, Gujarat State Petronet (up 0.63%), Adani Total Gas (up 0.55%) and Gujarat Gas (up 0.38%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) added 1.29%. The company has signed an MoU with the Government of Chhattisgarh to provide financial assistance of up to Rs 1 lakh crore over the next five years for housing and urban infrastructure development. Avantel rallied 1.58% after the company announced that it had received a purchase order valued at Rs 11.19 crore from NewSpace India. Gland Pharma jumped 0.60%. The company received an approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) filed for Olopatadine Hydrochloride Ophthalmic Solution USP, 0.7%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aditya-birla-sun-life-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663765</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663765</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has been announced that Ms.

Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has been announced that Ms. Sneha Suhas will be appointed as Key Personnel in the capacity of Chief Technology Officer with effect from Thursday, January 8, 2026: Details of Ms. Sneha Suhas Age: 55 years Designation: Chief Technology Officer Qualification: B.E. in Computer Engineering, MBA in IT & Systems

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Steel's India biz records 12% YoY rise in production in Q3; deliveries cross 6 million ton-mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-steels-india-biz-records-12-yoy-rise-in-production-in-q3-deliveries-cross-6-million-ton-mark/1663762</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663762</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The increase in production was primarily aided by higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities.

The increase in production was primarily aided by higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities. For 9M FY26, production was up 6% YoY to 17.2 million tons. The company further said that improved production led to ‘best-ever quarterly’ deliveries and Tata Steel India crossed the ‘6 million ton’ mark for the first time. The India deliveries increased by 14% YoY to 6.04 million tons in Q3 FY26, primarily aided by strong sales in the domestic market. For 9M FY26, deliveries rose by 6% YoY to 16.3 million tons. Tata Steel Netherlands liquid steel production in 3Q FY26 was 1.68 million tons (down 4.6% YoY) and deliveries were 1.40 million tons (down 8.5% YoY). The company said that seasonal factors and subdued market dynamics led to lower deliveries on QoQ basis. Tata Steel UK is serving its customers via downstream processing of purchased substrate. Deliveries for the quarter stood at 0.52 million tons. Enabling works for the EAF project have advanced and the site landscape is being reshaped for the next phase of construction. During the quarter, Tata Steel Thailand saleable steel production was 0.31 million tons (up 19.2% YoY) and deliveries were 0.29 million tons (up 3.6% YoY). The improvement in deliveries was primarily driven by strong domestic rebar sales. Tata Steel group is among the top global steel companies with an annual crude steel capacity of 35 million tonnes per annum. It is one of the world's most geographically diversified steel producers, with operations and commercial presence across the world. The company reported 4.19 times increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,183 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 759 crore recorded in Q2 FY25. Revenue rose by 9% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 58,689 crore during the quarter, primarily driven by higher deliveries in India and Netherlands despite drop in realisations. The scrip fell 1.44% to currently trade at Rs 181.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataSteel_98454158604_566.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aditya-birla-sun-life-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1663763</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663763</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 07 January 2026.

Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 07 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) Aditya Birla Sun Life Large Cap Fund Mr. Mahesh Patil Mr. Harish Krishnan Aditya Birla Sun Life Infrastructure Fund Mr. Mahesh Patil and Mr. Jonas Bhutta Mr. Jonas Bhutta

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HUDCO signs MoU with Chhattisgarh government]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hudco-signs-mou-with-chhattisgarh-government/1663760</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663760</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the non-binding MoU, HUDCO may extend financial assistance of up to Rs 20,000 crore per year, aggregating to Rs 1 lakh crore over the five-year period.

Under the non-binding MoU, HUDCO may extend financial assistance of up to Rs 20,000 crore per year, aggregating to Rs 1 lakh crore over the five-year period. Of the proposed outlay, infrastructure projects account for the largest share at Rs 70,000 crore, covering both core and non-core segments such as water supply, sewerage, drainage, roads, electricity, smart cities, metro rail projects, airports, industrial parks, social and commercial infrastructure, educational institutions, hospitals, logistics hubs, IT infrastructure, civil aviation, mining institutions, and rural infrastructure. The agreement is effective from the date of signing and will remain valid until the end of FY2030, with a provision for extension. It is an in-principle arrangement, with funding for individual projects subject to HUDCO’s due diligence and mutually agreed terms and conditions. Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) is primarily engaged in the business of financing housing and urban development activities in the country. The company had recorded a 3.08% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 709.83 crore on a 27.85% increase in revenue to Rs 3,219.03 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. Shares of Housing & Urban Development Corporation shed 0.66% to Rs 225.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HousingUrbanDevelopmentCorporationLtd_55509095_12197.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Avantel gains on securing Rs 11-cr order from NewSpace India]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avantel-gains-on-securing-rs-11-cr-order-from-newspace-india/1663752</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663752</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order comprises the supply, installation, and commissioning of devices for Xponders.

According to an exchange filing, the order comprises the supply, installation, and commissioning of devices for Xponders. The execution of the contract is scheduled to be completed by July 2026. The company also stated that the purchase order was received via email on 7 January 2026. Avantel is engaged in the business of designing, developing, and maintaining wireless and satellite communication products, defence electronics, radar systems, and the development of network management software applications for its customers, mainly from the aerospace and defence sectors. The company’s consolidated net profit tanked 81.39% to Rs 4.26 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 22.89 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 28.42% year-on-year to Rs 55.41 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Avantel_19473582893_20881.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gland Pharma climbs on USFDA nod for allergy eye drug]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gland-pharma-climbs-on-usfda-nod-for-allergy-eye-drug/1663728</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663728</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The said drug is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Pataday Once Daily Relief, 0.7%, of Alcon Laboratories Inc (Alcon).

The said drug is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Pataday Once Daily Relief, 0.7%, of Alcon Laboratories Inc (Alcon). The said drug indicated for the treatment of ocular itching associated with allergic conjunctivitis. Gland Pharma is one of the largest and fastest-growing injectable-focused companies, with a global footprint across 60 countries, including the United States, Europe, Canada, Australia, India, and other markets. It has a wide range of injectables, including vials, ampoules, pre-filled syringes, lyophilized vials, dry powders, infusions, oncology, and ophthalmic solutions. The company also pioneered Heparin technology in India. The company’s consolidated net profit increased 12.3% to Rs 183.68 crore on 5.8% rise in net sales to Rs 1486.88 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlandPharmaLtd._31222392_14546.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers drift lower in early trade; realty shares advance ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-drift-lower-in-early-trade-realty-shares-advance/1663726</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663726</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor losses in early trade, extending their decline to a fourth consecutive session, as concerns over U.S.

The domestic equity indices traded with minor losses in early trade, extending their decline to a fourth consecutive session, as concerns over U.S. tariffs and continued foreign fund outflows overshadowed pockets of optimism around earnings growth. The Nifty traded below the 26,100 level. Barring the realty index, all other indices traded in the red on the BSE. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 232.38 points or 0.24% to 84,769.97. The Nifty 50 index fell 71.80 points or 0.27% to 26,068.95. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.39% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.19%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,353 shares rose and 1,640 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 0.82% to 10.03. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 107.63 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,749.35 crore in the Indian equity market on 06 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services rose 0.50%. The company announced that it has entered into an agreement with Cubastion Consulting. Tata Steel shed 0.11%. The company’s India crude steel production stood at 6.34 million tons in Q3 FY26, up 12% QoQ and YoY, primarily aided by higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities. Meesho tanked 4.49% after its general manager- business, Megha Agarwal has tendered her resignation with effect from 7 January 2026. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.11% to 6.618 compared with previous session close of 6.612. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9700 compared with its close of 89.8700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.22% to Rs 137,700. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.04% to 98.71. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.12% to 4.144. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement added 27 cents or 0.45% to $60.23 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets traded mixed on Thursday after Wall Street closed lower amid rising geopolitical tensions and comments from U.S. President Donald Trump. U.S. defense stocks fell after Trump said he “will not permit” defense companies to issue dividends or stock buybacks until they address his complaints about the industry, including executive pay packages and production issues. In U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day winning streak, falling 466 points, or 0.94%, to close at 48,996.08. The S&P 500 declined 23.89 points or 0.34% to end at 6,920.93, while the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite edged up 37.10 points or 0.16% to close at 23,584.28.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ACS Tech gains after bagging Rs 4-cr work order from Mahindra Defence Systems]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acs-tech-gains-after-bagging-rs-4-cr-work-order-from-mahindra-defence-systems/1663727</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663727</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order pertains to the supply, installation, testing, commissioning, and integration (SITCI) of security and communication systems.

The order pertains to the supply, installation, testing, commissioning, and integration (SITCI) of security and communication systems. The execution of the contract will be carried out in accordance with site-specific requirements. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It further stated that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. ACS Technologies is primarily engaged in the business of system integration, security and surveillance, IOT solutions, and software products and services in the area of information technology. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 46% to Rs 2.19 crore on a 45.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 48.25 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LNIndustries_79964971756_5092.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>