<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:49:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper off four-week low amid intense volatility]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-off-four-week-low-amid-intense-volatility/1670446</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670446</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper saw intense volatility today, sliding heavily in Asian trades in tune with equities and testing a four-week low under $5.60 per pound.

COMEX Copper saw intense volatility today, sliding heavily in Asian trades in tune with equities and testing a four-week low under $5.60 per pound. Shanghai Composite index slumped 2.50% as property market worries weighed. Overall sentiments in Asian markets were tepid as Hong Kong's Hang Seng index lost 2.20%. With this slide, the Shanghai Composite index has slipped near four-week low. In other indices, Hong Kong's Hang Seng index lost 2.20% while Japanese Nikkei 225 index fell 1.25%. Copper cut losses thereafter though and currently trades at $5.87 per pound, down 0.75% on the day. MCX Copper futures are trading at Rs 1245.20 per kg, up 1.26% on the day, bouncing nearly Rs 100 per kg in intraday moves.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/INR and JPY/INR futures fall nearly 1%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurinr-and-jpyinr-futures-fall-nearly-1/1670436</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670436</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures fell nearly half a percent to end at 91.65.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures fell nearly half a percent to end at 91.65. GBP/INR slipped 0.74% to close at 125.65. Meanwhile, EUR/INR and JPY/INR ended nearly 1% down at 108.80 and 59.29 respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR rebounds well on first trading day post Union Budget; Sharp fall in international crude prices supports]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-rebounds-well-on-first-trading-day-post-union-budget-sharp-fall-in-international-crude-prices-supports/1670434</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670434</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee rebounded well on Monday, the first session after Union Budget 2026-27 was presented yesterday.

The Indian rupee rebounded well on Monday, the first session after Union Budget 2026-27 was presented yesterday. Rupee gained 42 paise to close at 91.51 (provisional) against the US dollar, largely supported by sharp fall in international crude oil prices and positive cues from local equities. Crude oil prices were down more than 5 percent in European trade after U.S. President Donald Trump said he was hopeful of agreeing a deal with Iran. At the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 91.95 against the US dollar, then gained some ground to touch an intraday high of 91.45 and a low of 91.95 against the greenback. Indian shares bounced back on Monday after tumbling during the special weekend trading session on Sunday amid disappointment over the government's budget proposal to increase taxes on equity derivatives trading. The benchmark BSE Sensex jumped 943.52 points, or 1.17 percent, to 81,666.46, after having fallen nearly 2 percent the previous day - marking the second sharpest fall on Budget Day since 2014. The broader NSE Nifty index surged 262.95 points, or 1.06 percent, to 25,088.40. India’s foreign exchange reserves hit a fresh record high in the week ended January 23, rising due to a sharp gain in gold holdings and foreign currency assets, according to the latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India. The country’s forex reserves jumped by USD 8.053 billion during the week to USD 709.413 billion, surpassing the earlier peak of USD 704.89 billion recorded in September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Unichem Laboratories’ Kolhapur API Facility clears USFDA inspection ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/unichem-laboratories-kolhapur-api-facility-clears-usfda-inspection/1670391</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670391</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The inspection concluded with five observations, all pertaining to procedural changes, with none related to data integrity.

The inspection concluded with five observations, all pertaining to procedural changes, with none related to data integrity. The company said it will submit the required response to the USFDA within the stipulated 15-day period. Unichem Laboratories is engaged in manufacturing of pharmaceutical products. The company’s consolidated jumped 83.9% to Rs 45.30 crore on 14.1% increase in net sales to Rs 578.96 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Unichem Laboratories rose 0.16% to Rs 374.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnichemLabs_94962320329_577.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hyundai Motor India Q3 PAT rises 6% YoY to Rs 1,234 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hyundai-motor-india-q3-pat-rises-6-yoy-to-rs-1234-crore/1670390</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670390</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operations grew 7.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 17,973.49 crore during the quarter.

Total revenue from operations grew 7.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 17,973.49 crore during the quarter. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 1,666.03 crore, up 6.61% from Rs 1,562.73 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, EBITDA rose 7.61% YoY to Rs 2,018.30 crore from Rs 1,875.50 crore in Q3 FY25, while the EBITDA margin declined marginally to 11.2% from 11.3% in the year-ago quarter. On a nine-month basis, the company reported a 3.72% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 4,175.89 crore in 9M FY26, compared with Rs 4,025.86 crore in 9M FY25. Revenue from operations rose 1.16% YoY to Rs 51,847.18 crore in 9M FY26. Tarun Garg, managing director & chief executive officer, said, “The third-quarter performance underscores our resilience and strong execution of “Quality of Growth” strategy, marked by healthy growth in volumes, revenue and profitability. Notably on a year-to-date basis, EBITDA margins expanded to 12.8% as against 12.5% last year, supported by our efforts towards improving sales mix and prudent cost control measures. As we move ahead, the robust January’26 sales number gives us great momentum towards a healthy 2026.” Hyundai Motor India manufactures and sells passenger cars, along with vehicle parts and accessories. The counter rose 0.60% to settle at Rs 2,196.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HyundaiMotorIndiaLtd_73449848_16486.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee buoys]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-buoys/1670389</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670389</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 91.6500 per Dollar on Monday (02 February 2026), versus its previous close of 92.0400 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Housing Finance Q3 PAT rallies 21% YoY to Rs 665 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-housing-finance-q3-pat-rallies-21-yoy-to-rs-665-cr/1670371</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670371</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net Interest Income (NII) for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 963 crore, up 19% as against Rs 806 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net Interest Income (NII) for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 963 crore, up 19% as against Rs 806 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in the December 2025 quarter stood at Rs 864.54 crore, up 21.25% from Rs 713.02 crore posted in the corresponding quarter of the previous fiscal year. The company reported strong quarterly performance for Q3 FY26, with assets under management (AUM) rising 23% to Rs 1,33,412 crore as of 31 December 2025, up from Rs 1,08,314 crore a year ago. Net interest income grew 19% to Rs 963 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 806 crore in Q3 FY25, while net total income surged 24% to Rs 1,153 crore from Rs 933 crore. Operating expenses to net total income improved to 19% from 19.8% in the year-ago period. Exceptional items of Rs 13.14 crore included a one-time impact from higher gratuity liability following changes in the New Labour Codes issued by the government in November 2025. Loan losses and provisions increased to Rs 56 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 35 crore in Q3 FY25, including a Rs 10 crore management overlay release. The asset quality remained healthy, with gross and net NPA at 0.27% and 0.11% as of 31 December 2025, versus 0.29% and 0.13% a year ago. The provisioning coverage ratio on stage-3 assets stood at 59%. The capital adequacy ratio, including Tier-II capital, was 23.15%. The company continues to enjoy the highest credit ratings of AAA/Stable for its long-term debt programme and A1+ for short-term debt from CRISIL and India Ratings. Bajaj Housing Finance is a non-deposit-taking housing finance company (HFC) registered with the National Housing Bank (NHB) since 2015 and has been offering mortgage loans. Shares of Bajaj Housing Finance shed 0.06% to end at Rs 89.63 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajHousingFinanceLtd_53485527_67886.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Equities snap two-session losing streak on budget assessment, Nifty retakes 25,050]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/equities-snap-two-session-losing-streak-on-budget-assessment-nifty-retakes-25050/1670355</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670355</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Equity benchmarks staged a sharp comeback on Monday, breaking a two-session slide as investors weighed the union budget's implications for market sentiment and capital flows.

Equity benchmarks staged a sharp comeback on Monday, breaking a two-session slide as investors weighed the union budget's implications for market sentiment and capital flows. Buying momentum returned despite proposals to raise securities transaction taxes on derivatives and the absence of fresh steps to lure foreign capital. The Nifty reclaimed territory above the 25,050 mark, powered by firm gains in auto, energy and metal stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 943.52 points or 1.17% to 81,666.46. The Nifty 50 index jumped 262.95 points or 1.06% to 25,088.40. In the past two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.73% while the Nifty fell 0.91%. Reliance Industries (up 3.28%), Larsen & Toubro (up 2.86%) and ICICI Bank (up 1.31%) boosted the indices today. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 Mid-Cap index rose 0.86% and the S&P BSE 250 Small-Cap index added 0.28%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 2,039 shares rose and 2,220 shares fell. A total of 169 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 8.14% to 13.87. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 1.15% to 6.772 compared with previous session close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.5200 compared with its close of 90.9350 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.79% to Rs 145,398. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.08% to 97.07. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.59% to 4.219. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement dropped $3.01 or 4.34% to $66.31 a barrel. Brent crude prices slid after U.S. President Donald Trump said over the weekend that Iran was “seriously talking” with Washington, signaling a possible easing of tensions with the OPEC member. The comments helped temper fears of a potential military strike that had earlier pushed oil prices to multi-month highs. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 133 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European equities advanced on Monday at the start of a data-heavy week featuring major corporate earnings, central bank meetings, and key macroeconomic releases. Data released earlier showed German retail sales rose 0.1% month-on-month in December, reversing a 0.5% decline in the previous month. Asian equities ended lower as investors assessed fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold extended losses following last week’s decline. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House. Stocks in Spotlight: The Nifty Auto index rose 2.13% to close at 26,749.15, recovering from a 2.09% decline in the previous session. Gains were led by Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles, which jumped 5.61%, followed by Bharat Forge up 4.65% and Ashok Leyland rising 3.12%. Uno Minda gained 3.05%, while Mahindra & Mahindra advanced 2.71% and Hero MotoCorp added 2.43%. Samvardhana Motherson International rose 2.10% and Sona BLW Precision Forgings climbed 2.03%. TVS Motor Company gained 1.70%, Exide Industries rose 1.69%, Eicher Motors advanced 1.34%, Maruti Suzuki India added 1.26%, and Bosch edged up 0.97%. Maruti Suzuki India rose after the company reported total sales of 236,963 units in January 2026, registering an 11.6% YoY growth compared with 212,251 units sold in January 2025. Atul Auto soared 7.16% after the company reported a 30.09% rise in total sales to 3,606 units in January 2026 as against 2,772 units sold in January 2025. Shares of cigarette and tobacco manufacturers declined after cigarette prices rose sharply from February 1 following the introduction of additional excise duty. Against this backdrop, VST Industries fell 1.72%, ITC declined 1.68%, while Godfrey Phillips India slid 2.59%, as investors reacted to higher prices triggered by the revised tax structure. From February 2026, cigarettes and tobacco products will attract additional excise duty and cess over and above the highest 40% GST slab, replacing the earlier regime of 28% GST plus compensation cess. The Central Excise Act has also been amended to impose a per-stick excise duty on cigarettes, with rates linked to cigarette length. Bharat Electronics rose 3.33% to Rs 439.10 after a foreign brokerage raised its price target on the stock to Rs 508 from Rs 418. Latent View Analytics added 9.16% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 19.69% to Rs 50.14 crore on 22.02% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 278 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Godrej Properties rose 3.44% after the company reported sales of over Rs 2,000 crore in Phase 1 of its residential project Godrej Trilogy in Worli. Gokaldas Exports dropped 4.61% after the company reported 70.97% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 14.61 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 50.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations shed 0.92% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 978.65 crore during the quarter. Bartronics India fell 1.48%. The company reported standalone net profit of Rs 2.44 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with net loss of Rs 0.32 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 48.34 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 455.63%, compared with Rs 8.70 crore in Q3 FY25. Brahmaputra Infrastructure rose 2.12% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 68.91 crore from the Water Resources Department, Assam, for riverbank protection works in the state.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts fall further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-fall-further/1670326</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670326</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 16162 contracts in the data reported through January 27, 2026. This was a weekly drop of 5818 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1670325</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670325</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,149.60, a premium of 61.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,088.40 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,149.60, a premium of 61.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,088.40 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index added 262.95 points or 1.06% to 25,088.40. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 8.14% to 13.87. HDFC Bank, State Bank of India and Reliance Industries were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Lifespace gains after reporting turnaround Q3 numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-lifespace-gains-after-reporting-turnaround-q3-numbers/1670309</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670309</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations surged 174.48% year-on-year to Rs 459.16 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations surged 174.48% year-on-year to Rs 459.16 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 32.27 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a pre-tax loss of Rs 15.11 crore in the year-ago quarter. An exceptional item of Rs 25.83 crore was recorded during the quarter under review. Total expenses increased 117.44% YoY to Rs 436.81 crore in Q3 FY26. The company maintained a strong balance sheet and healthy collections, with a net debt-to-equity ratio of -0.12 (cash surplus) as of 31 December 2025. The company achieved consolidated sales (Residential and IC&IC) of Rs 707 crore. Gross development value (GDV) additions in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 1,010 crore. Residential pre-sales in Q3 FY26 were Rs 572 crore (saleable area of 0.60 msft and RERA carpet area of 0.45 msft), compared with Rs 334 crore in Q3 FY25. On a nine-month basis, the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 208.02 crore in 9M FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 23.79 crore in 9M FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 40.12% YoY to Rs 508.69 crore in 9M FY26. For the nine-month period, consolidated sales (Residential and IC&IC) stood at Rs 2,125 crore. GDV additions in 9M FY26 were Rs 10,560 crore, in addition to Rs 18,100 crore in FY25. Residential pre-sales in 9M FY26 were Rs 1,773 crore (saleable area of 2.35 msft and RERA carpet area of 1.76 msft), compared with Rs 1,749 crore in 9M FY25. Amit Kumar Sinha, MD & CEO, Mahindra Lifespace Developers, said, “We are thrilled to announce a strong quarterly result. On the residential side, we had 3 project completions that contributed to our PAT. We have a strong pipeline of residential launches leading into FY27. On the IC&IC side, we are seeing healthy demand for high quality industrial plots in our industrial parks. We launched phase 2A of Origins by Mahindra in Chennai in December 25.” Mahindra Lifespaces Developers, the real estate arm of the Mahindra Group, has a development footprint of 53.65 million sq. ft across seven cities and over 5,000 acres of industrial clusters. Its portfolio includes premium residences, affordable homes under the Happinest brand, and integrated cities under Mahindra World City and Origins.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahindraLife_17004584737_20728.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axtel Industries Q3 PAT spurts 145% YoY to Rs 8 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axtel-industries-q3-pat-spurts-145-yoy-to-rs-8-cr/1670310</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670310</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales jumped 45.09% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 58.63 crore during the quarter.

Net sales jumped 45.09% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 58.63 crore during the quarter. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 10.83 crore, up by 118.35% from Rs 4.96 crore in Q3 FY25. Total operating expenditure rose by 34.83% to Rs 49.24 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of material consumed was at Rs 22.85 crore (up 41.08% YoY), employee benefit expense stood at Rs 11.14 crore (up 7.43% YoY), and other expense was at Rs 10.84 crore (up 57.56% YoY) during the period under review. Axtel Industries (AIL) manufactures custom-designed food processing plants and machinery tailored to clients’ requirements. Shares of Axtel Industries declined 1.57% to close at Rs 426.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AxtelIndustries_77645227543_2905.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Campus Activewear rallies after Q3 PAT climbs 37% YoY to Rs 64 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/campus-activewear-rallies-after-q3-pat-climbs-37-yoy-to-rs-64-cr/1670307</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670307</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 37.39% YoY to Rs 86.06 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 37.39% YoY to Rs 86.06 crore during the quarter. EBITDA stood at Rs 115.8 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 34.8% compared with Rs 85.9 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 19.5% in Q3 FY26 as against 16.6% in Q3 FY25. Sales volume rose 8.6% to 82.8 lakh pairs during the quarter, compared with 76.2 lakh pairs sold in Q3 FY25. Average selling price (ASP) increased 5.2% to Rs 711 per pair in Q3 FY26, from Rs 675 per pair in Q3 FY25. Advertisement and sales promotion expenses grew sharply by 17.3% to Rs 65 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 55.4 crore in Q3 FY25. Campus Activewear is primarily engaged in the business of manufacturing and trading of footwear and accessories through its retail and wholesale network.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/campusactivewearpvtltd_31564636_76331.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude oil cracks lower after recent surge]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-oil-cracks-lower-after-recent-surge/1670306</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670306</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures tumbled more than 4% toward $62 per barrel on Monday, retreating from multi-month highs after OPEC+ confirmed it would keep production unchanged in March and signs emerged of easing tensions between the United States and Iran.

WTI crude oil futures tumbled more than 4% toward $62 per barrel on Monday, retreating from multi-month highs after OPEC+ confirmed it would keep production unchanged in March and signs emerged of easing tensions between the United States and Iran. President Donald Trump expressed optimism about a potential deal with Tehran, softening last month’s intense rhetoric that had fueled geopolitical risk premiums. Downside pressure was reinforced by expectations of ample global supply, with the International Energy Agency projecting a record oil glut as demand growth slows while output rises from non-OPEC producers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/steel-long-pipes-in-crude-oil-factory-during-sunset-picture_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices snap 2-day losses; auto index rallies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-snap-2-day-losses-auto-index-rallies/1670300</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670300</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with major gains today, snapping a two-day losing streak, as investors assessed the federal budget’s impact on markets and capital flows.

The key equity benchmarks ended with major gains today, snapping a two-day losing streak, as investors assessed the federal budget’s impact on markets and capital flows. The rebound came despite proposals to raise transaction taxes on derivatives and the lack of fresh measures to attract foreign investment. The Nifty settled above the 25,050 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 943.52 points or 1.17% to 81,666.46. The Nifty 50 index jumped 262.95 points or 1.06% to 25,088.40. In the past two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.73% while the Nifty fell 0.91%. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index rose 0.86% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index added 0.28%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 8.14% to 13.87. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Auto index (up 2.13%), the Nifty Oil& Gas index (up 2.04%) and the Nifty Metal index (up 1.88%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 0.47%), the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.08%) and the Nifty PSU bank index (up 0.87%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 1.15% to 6.772 compared with previous session close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.5200 compared with its close of 90.9350 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.79% to Rs 145,398. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.08% to 97.07. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.59% to 4.219. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement dropped $3.01 or 4.34% to $66.31 a barrel. Brent crude prices slid after U.S. President Donald Trump said over the weekend that Iran was “seriously talking” with Washington, signaling a possible easing of tensions with the OPEC member. The comments helped temper fears of a potential military strike that had earlier pushed oil prices to multi-month highs. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 137 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European equities traded lower on Monday as a sell-off in precious metals dented investor sentiment at the start of a data-heavy week marked by key corporate earnings, central bank meetings, and macroeconomic releases. Data released earlier showed that German retail sales edged up 0.1% month-on-month in December, improving from a 0.5% decline recorded in the previous month. Asian equities ended lower as investors digested fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold continued to slide after last week’s drop. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Infrastructure Index records a surge of 2.26%, NIFTY climbs 1.06% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-infrastructure-index-records-a-surge-of-226-nifty-climbs-106/1670275</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670275</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Infrastructure index ended up 2.26% at 9125.25 today.

Nifty Infrastructure index ended up 2.26% at 9125.25 today. The index has lost 7.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd jumped 7.58%, Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd gained 5.05% and Bharat Forge Ltd rose 4.80%. The Nifty Infrastructure index has increased 11.00% over last one year compared to the 6.84% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Auto index increased 2.13% and Nifty PSE index increased 2.04% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 witnessed a rise of 1.06% to close at 25088.4 while the SENSEX witnessed a rise of 1.17% to close at 81666.46 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-background-design-picture-id511195524_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 944 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,050 mark; VIX slumps 8.14%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-944-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25050-mark-vix-slumps-814/1670274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670274</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with major gains today, snapping a two-day losing streak, as investors assessed the federal budget’s impact on markets and capital flows.

The key equity benchmarks ended with major gains today, snapping a two-day losing streak, as investors assessed the federal budget’s impact on markets and capital flows. The rebound came despite proposals to raise transaction taxes on derivatives and the lack of fresh measures to attract foreign investment. The Nifty settled above the 25,050 level. All NSE indices closed in the green, except for the IT index. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, zoomed 943.52 points or 1.17% to 81,666.46. The Nifty 50 index jumped 262.95 points or 1.06% to 25,088.40. Over the past two trading sessions, the Sensex slipped 0.73%, while the Nifty dropped 0.91%. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index rose 0.86% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index added 0.28%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 2,045 shares rose and 2,209 shares fell. A total of 174 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 8.14% to 13.87. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. Politics: Sunetra Pawar was sworn in Maharashtra's first woman Deputy Chief Minister on 31 January 2026, days after her husband Ajit Pawar's fatal plane crash on January 28 near Baramati Airport. A former Rajya Sabha MP and social activist from Baramati, Sunetra Pawar took oath at Lok Bhavan in Mumbai and said she would carry forward Ajit Pawar’s legacy of public service, focusing on social equality, women and youth empowerment, rural upliftment, and administrative reform. She will work alongside Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis and Deputy Chief Minister Eknath Shinde, strengthening the Mahayuti alliance. Sunetra Pawar is expected to handle portfolios such as Excise, Sports, and Youth Welfare and Minorities Development, with the Finance portfolio temporarily retained by the chief minister. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index added 2.13% to 26,749.15. The index fell 2.09% in the past trading session. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 5.35%), Bharat Forge (up 4.81%), Uno Minda (up 3.13%), Ashok Leyland (up 3.07%) and Mahindra & Mahindra (up 2.86%), Hero MotoCorp (up 2.26%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (up 2.12%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 1.95%), Eicher Motors (up 1.43%) and TVS Motor Company (up 1.42%) added. On the other hand, Tube Investments of India (down 0.46%), Bajaj Auto (down 0.04%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Atul Auto soared 7.86% after the company reported a 30.09% rise in total sales to 3,606 units in January 2026 as against 2,772 units sold in January 2025. Gokaldas Exports dropped 4.61% after the company reported 70.97% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 14.61 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 50.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations shed 0.92% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 978.65 crore during the quarter. Maruti Suzuki India added 1.27% after the company reported total sales of 236,963 units in January 2026, registering an 11.6% YoY growth compared with 212,251 units sold in January 2025. Bartronics India fell 2.03%. The company reported standalone net profit of Rs 2.44 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with net loss of Rs 0.32 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 48.34 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 455.63%, compared with Rs 8.70 crore in Q3 FY25. Brahmaputra Infrastructure rose 2.12% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 68.91 crore from the Water Resources Department, Assam, for riverbank protection works in the state. Latent View Analytics added 8.33% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 19.69% to Rs 50.14 crore on 22.02% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 278 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Godrej Properties rose 3.44% after the company reported sales of over Rs 2,000 crore in Phase 1 of its residential project Godrej Trilogy in Worli. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 129 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European equities edged higher on Monday, recovering from a sell-off in precious metals that had weighed on investor sentiment at the start of a data-heavy week featuring key corporate earnings, central bank meetings, and macroeconomic releases. Data released earlier showed that German retail sales edged up 0.1% month-on-month in December, improving from a 0.5% decline recorded in the previous month. Asian equities ended lower as investors digested fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold continued to slide after last week’s drop. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[National Statistics Office proposes to conduct a survey on migration ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/national-statistics-office-proposes-to-conduct-a-survey-on-migration/1670272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670272</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Statistics Office (NSO), Ministry of Statistics and Programme Implementation (MoSPI) has proposed to conduct a Survey on Migration during July 2026-June 2027.

National Statistics Office (NSO), Ministry of Statistics and Programme Implementation (MoSPI) has proposed to conduct a Survey on Migration during July 2026-June 2027. Migration surveys have been conducted by MoSPI in regular intervals; the most recent data on migration were collected through the Periodic Labour Force Survey (PLFS) 2020–21 and the Multiple Indicator Survey (2020–21). The forthcoming Survey on Migration is expected to provide comprehensive and up-to-date data on the extent and patterns of migration, both rural–urban and inter-state, along with reasons for migration, return migration, seasonal migration, employment profiles of migrants, etc. The results will be instrumental in understanding labour mobility, remittance flows, etc. Such information will greatly benefit policymakers, planners, researchers, and development practitioners by enabling more targeted interventions in areas such as urban planning, housing, transportation, employment generation, social security and skill development.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/statistics-227173__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WPIL gains after Q3 PAT spurts 104% YoY to Rs 76 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wpil-gains-after-q3-pat-spurts-104-yoy-to-rs-76-cr/1670269</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670269</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax increased 139.47% to Rs 109.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 45.63 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

Profit before tax increased 139.47% to Rs 109.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 45.63 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Total expense stood at Rs 447.68 crore (up 26.83% YoY), cost of material consumed was at Rs 115.63 crore (up 6.67% YoY), employee benefit expense stood at Rs 79.65 crore (up 34.52% YoY), and finance cost was at Rs 11.35 crore (up 1.7% YoY) during the period under review. WPIL is principally engaged in designing, developing, manufacturing, erecting, commissioning, and servicing pumps & pumping systems.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WPIL_44160601558_615.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold pulls back sharply after six-month rally as margin hikes spark selloff]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-pulls-back-sharply-after-six-month-rally-as-margin-hikes-spark-selloff/1670266</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670266</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold recovered part of its losses in Asian electronic trading on Monday, with international bullion futures trading near $4,671 per ounce after briefly sliding to around $4,423 earlier in the session.

Gold recovered part of its losses in Asian electronic trading on Monday, with international bullion futures trading near $4,671 per ounce after briefly sliding to around $4,423 earlier in the session. The partial rebound followed a steep selloff on Friday, when prices plunged over 11% amid aggressive profit-taking triggered by higher margin requirements imposed by the CME Group. The margin hike — raising gold margins from 6% to 8% and silver from 11% to 15% — prompted leveraged traders to rapidly unwind positions across COMEX and MCX. Despite the sharp correction from recent record highs, gold remains on course for a sixth consecutive monthly gain, supported by geopolitical risks, economic uncertainty, and persistent weakness in the US dollar. In India, MCX April gold futures slipped nearly 2% to ₹145,396 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>