<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:55:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Meta Infotech bags orders worth Rs 4 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/meta-infotech-bags-orders-worth-rs-4-crore/1678773</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678773</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company received a fresh order worth Rs 2.58 crore from one of India’s leading stock exchanges for software subscription services for the period from 31 January 2026 to 31 January 2027.

The company received a fresh order worth Rs 2.58 crore from one of India’s leading stock exchanges for software subscription services for the period from 31 January 2026 to 31 January 2027. The contract entails a three-year commitment with annual renewal and is to be executed within 90 days. Further, the company has obtained a renewal order worth Rs 1.56 crore from a leading private sector bank for Database Activity Monitoring (DAM) licenses for the period from 4 January 2026 to 22 October 2026. The order is to be executed within 15 days. Both contracts are awarded by domestic entities. The promoter/promoter group has no interest in the awarding entities, and the transactions do not fall under related party transactions. Meta Infotech is engaged in trading and providing services related to cybersecurity software products. The company reported a 60.7% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 10.51 crore, while revenue from operations rose 40.3% to Rs 152.13 crore in FY25 over FY24. Shares of Meta Infotech slipped 1.30% to end at Rs 92.14 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end steeply lower as bears take control of D-Street]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-steeply-lower-as-bears-take-control-of-d-street/1678776</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678776</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a dramatic reversal of recent gains, the Indian benchmark indices experienced a severe broad-based sell-off on Thursday, as the Sensex plummeted by 1,236 points and the Nifty 50 slipped below the 25,500 mark.

In a dramatic reversal of recent gains, the Indian benchmark indices experienced a severe broad-based sell-off on Thursday, as the Sensex plummeted by 1,236 points and the Nifty 50 slipped below the 25,500 mark. This massive decline has reportedly wiped out over Rs 7.5 lakh crore in investor wealth in a single session. The crash was triggered by several factors, including escalating geopolitical tensions between the U.S. and Iran and a sharp spike in global crude oil prices. Additionally, deep-seated uncertainty regarding the U.S. Federal Reserve's interest rate trajectory weighed on sentiment following its latest meeting minutes. Despite a resilient opening, fueled by the IT sector, the market succumbed to aggressive profit booking as risk-off sentiment took hold. This dragged every major sectoral index, particularly auto, realty, and banking, into the red and the benchmark indices snapped their robust three-day winning streak. The barometer S&P BSE Sensex declined 1.48% to close at 82,498.14. The Nifty 50 index dropped 365 points or 1.41%, to end the session at 25,454.35. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 1.54% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 1.16%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,209 shares rose and 3,011 shares fell. A total of 159 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 10.12% to 13.46. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced the MANAV Vision for AI, where MANAV stands for M – Moral and Ethical System, A – Accountable Governance, N – National Sovereignty (right to data), A – Accessible and Inclusive, and V – Valid and Legitimate. Apart from PM Modi, key business and technology leaders such as Mukesh Ambani, Sam Altman and Sundar Pichai also delivered keynote addresses. French President Emmanuel Macron also spoke at the Delhi AI Summit. Tata Sons Chairman N. Chandrasekaran said, “I would like to thank the vision of our Prime Minister, which has enabled us to make a serious foray into chips and semiconductors. Our next step is to build chips that are highly domain-centric and fully AI-optimized for every industry. We will initially focus on developing and launching them for the automotive sector.” Numbers to Track: In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6850 compared with its close of 90.7200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement added 0.08% to Rs 155,879. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.02% to 97.64. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.34% to 4.094. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 74 cents or 1.05% to $71.09 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: TIL jumped 9.22%. The company said that its board will meet on Monday (23 February 2026) to consider a proposal to raise funds via issuance of either equity or equity-linked securities. Tata Consultancy Services advanced 0.65%. The company has announced a multi-dimensional strategic partnership with OpenAI to drive AI-powered innovation across enterprise, consumer, and social sectors. Pine Labs advanced 2.91%. The company has announced collaboration with OpenAI, marking its move beyond traditional automation to build agentic commerce. The company will embed OpenAI APIs models into the core of a global merchant ecosystem. B. L. Kashyap and Sons rose 0.24%. The company said that it secured a contract worth Rs 300 crore from CRC Greens for a group housing project in Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) fell 1.40%. The company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from Northern Railway for a project worth Rs 1,201.35 crore. This contract is for the construction of a major multi-modal infrastructure project in Varanasi designed to replace the functionality of the aging 137-year-old Malviya Bridge. Hemant Surgical Industries fell 3.99%. The company announced that it has received an order worth Rs 264.33 crore from the Central Medical Services Society (CMSS), under the Ministry of Health and Family Welfare, Government of India. The contact is for supplying flat panel detectors with two batteries and a router, hard travel cases along with other utilities, and X-ray generators. GNG Electronics fell 1.38%. The company announced the signing of strategic distribution partnerships with Ingram Micro India and Supertron Electronics for the nationwide distribution of its refurbished computers across India. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 158 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European markets traded lower on Thursday as investors assessed the minutes of the US Federal Reserve’s January meeting which revealed divisions within the committee over the future policy trajectory. While some members signalled openness to rate cuts if inflation continues to moderate, others indicated a willingness to tighten policy further if price pressures remain persistent. In Asia, stocks ended higher, supported by gains in technology giants on Wall Street. Hong Kong and mainland China markets remained closed for the Lunar New Year break. In Malaysia, headline inflation rose 1.6% year-on-year in January 2026, with the consumer price index (CPI) increasing to 135.7 from 133.6 in the same month last year, according to the Department of Statistics Malaysia (DOSM). Meanwhile, Indonesian and U.S. companies signed deals worth $38.4 billion ahead of Indonesian President Prabowo Subianto’s meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump, covering mining, energy, agribusiness, textiles, furniture, and technology sectors. Oil prices edged higher as investors digested the latest developments between the U.S. and Iran. Vice President JD Vance reportedly said Tuesday that Iran failed to address U.S. red lines in this week’s nuclear talks and that military action is still a possibility. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 moved higher, supported by gains in key technology names, as traders weighed the release of the minutes from the Federal Reserve’s most recent policy meeting. The broad-based index climbed 0.56% to end at 6,881.31, while the Nasdaq Composite added 0.78% to settle at 22,753.63. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.26% to close at 49,662.66.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India to lead global critical minerals journey with Rs 32000 crore mission, says Minister of Coal & Mines]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-to-lead-global-critical-minerals-journey-with-rs-32000-crore-mission-says-minister-of-coal-mines/1678774</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678774</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[G Kishan Reddy, Minister of Coal & Mines, Government of India today called for a decisive shift from resource dependency to value creation in critical minerals.

G Kishan Reddy, Minister of Coal & Mines, Government of India today called for a decisive shift from resource dependency to value creation in critical minerals. He added that India is positioning itself as an attractive destination in the global critical minerals landscape to secure its strategic and economic future. Addressing the second edition of ‘Indian Critical Minerals Landscape: Foundation for a Sustainable Future - Empowering Innovation, Growth & Self-Reliance’, organised by FICCI, jointly with the Ministry of Mines, Govt of India, Reddy highlighted that India is currently 95 per cent dependent on imports of critical minerals and underscored the urgency of building a resilient, self-reliant ecosystem across exploration, extraction, processing, recycling and advanced manufacturing. Minister added that 9 Centers of Excellence (CoE) have been identified to bolster R&D, innovation and skill development in the sector. He also stated that work has commenced under the National Critical Minerals Mission with an outlay of Rs 32,000 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/mineral-oil-297487__340_crude_oil.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1678761</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678761</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,410, a premium of 44.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,454.35 in the cash market.

The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,410, a premium of 44.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,454.35 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index fell 365 points or 1.41%, to 25,454.35. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 10.12% to 13.46. Axis Bank, Bajaj Finance and Bharti Airtel were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends with deep cuts; Nifty settles below 25,500 level; VIX surge 10.12%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-with-deep-cuts-nifty-settles-below-25500-level-vix-surge-1012/1678759</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678759</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices ended with major losses, snapping a three-day winning streak, as a surge in crude oil prices, mixed signals from the Fed, and profit booking across sectors weighed on sentiment.

The domestic equity indices ended with major losses, snapping a three-day winning streak, as a surge in crude oil prices, mixed signals from the Fed, and profit booking across sectors weighed on sentiment. The Nifty ended below the 25,500 level. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 1,236.11 points or 1.48% to 82,498.14. The Nifty 50 index fell 365 points or 1.41%, to 25,454.35. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 1.54% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 1.16%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 10.12% to 13.46. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Chemical index (down 0.46%), the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.50%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 1.02%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Realty index (down 2.56%), Nifty Media index (up 2.23%) and the Nifty Auto index (down 2.10%) the underperformed the Nifty 50 index. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced the MANAV Vision for AI, where MANAV stands for M – Moral and Ethical System, A – Accountable Governance, N – National Sovereignty (right to data), A – Accessible and Inclusive, and V – Valid and Legitimate. Apart from PM Modi, key business and technology leaders such as Mukesh Ambani, Sam Altman and Sundar Pichai also delivered keynote addresses. French President Emmanuel Macron also spoke at the Delhi AI Summit. Tata Sons Chairman N. Chandrasekaran said, “I would like to thank the vision of our Prime Minister, which has enabled us to make a serious foray into chips and semiconductors. Our next step is to build chips that are highly domain-centric and fully AI-optimized for every industry. We will initially focus on developing and launching them for the automotive sector.” Numbers to Track: In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6850 compared with its close of 90.7200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement added 0.08% to Rs 155,879. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.02% to 97.64. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.34% to 4.094. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 74 cents or 1.05% to $71.09 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets traded lower on Thursday as investors assessed the minutes of the US Federal Reserve’s January meeting which revealed divisions within the committee over the future policy trajectory. While some members signalled openness to rate cuts if inflation continues to moderate, others indicated a willingness to tighten policy further if price pressures remain persistent. Most Asian stocks ended higher, supported by gains in technology giants on Wall Street, while lingering U.S.-Iran tensions kept oil prices elevated. In Malaysia, headline inflation rose 1.6% year-on-year in January 2026, with the consumer price index (CPI) increasing to 135.7 from 133.6 in the same month last year, according to the Department of Statistics Malaysia (DOSM). Hong Kong and mainland China markets remained closed for the Lunar New Year break. Meanwhile, Indonesian and U.S. companies signed deals worth $38.4 billion ahead of Indonesian President Prabowo Subianto’s meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump, covering mining, energy, agribusiness, textiles, furniture, and technology sectors. In Australia, the unemployment rate steadied at 4.1% in January, as per data from the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS). Oil prices edged higher as investors digested the latest developments between the U.S. and Iran. Vice President JD Vance reportedly said Tuesday that Iran failed to address U.S. red lines in this week’s nuclear talks and that military action is still a possibility. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 moved higher, supported by gains in key technology names, as traders weighed the release of the minutes from the Federal Reserve’s most recent policy meeting. The broad-based index climbed 0.56% to end at 6,881.31, while the Nasdaq Composite added 0.78% to settle at 22,753.63. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.26% to close at 49,662.66. Investors mulled over the minutes from the Fed’s January meeting, which revealed that participants largely approved of the central bank’s decision to leave its key interest rate unchanged at a range of 3.5% to 3.75%. However, officials were divided on the direction of monetary policy thereafter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Unilever board OKs Rs 2,000-cr capex for capacity expansion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-unilever-board-oks-rs-2000-cr-capex-for-capacity-expansion/1678757</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678757</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The proposed investment is in line with the company’s strategy of focusing on fewer, bigger bets and strengthening its presence in high-growth demand spaces, including premium skin care and hair care and personal care & home care liquids.

The proposed investment is in line with the company’s strategy of focusing on fewer, bigger bets and strengthening its presence in high-growth demand spaces, including premium skin care and hair care and personal care & home care liquids. Priya Nair, CEO and managing director, HUL, said: "This investment reflects our strategic focus on scaling our brands and creating categories of the future to meet evolving consumer needs. It also underscores our commitment to building a resilient, technology-enabled supply chain that delivers superior value to consumers." Hindustan Unilever is in the FMCG business comprising primarily of Home Care, Beauty & Personal Care and Foods & Refreshment segments. The Company has manufacturing facilities across the country and sells primarily in India. The company's consolidated net profit zoomed 120.91% to Rs 6,603 crore on 5.74% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 16,235 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter fell 1.90% to end at Rs 2279.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindUnilever_85453091314_255.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 1,236 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,500 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-1236-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25500-level/1678756</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678756</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended with sharp losses, snapping a three-session winning streak, as a surge in crude oil prices, mixed signals from the Fed, and profit booking across sectors weighed on sentiment.

The key domestic indices ended with sharp losses, snapping a three-session winning streak, as a surge in crude oil prices, mixed signals from the Fed, and profit booking across sectors weighed on sentiment. The Nifty ended below the 25,500 level. All sectoral indices on the NSE ended in the red, led by losses in realty, media and auto stocks. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 1,236.11 points or 1.48% to 82,498.14. The Nifty 50 index fell 365 points or 1.41%, to 25,454.35. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 1.54% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 1.16%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,273 shares rose and 2,930 shares fell. A total of 164 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 10.12% to 13.46. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced the MANAV Vision for AI, where MANAV stands for M – Moral and Ethical System, A – Accountable Governance, N – National Sovereignty (right to data), A – Accessible and Inclusive, and V – Valid and Legitimate. Apart from PM Modi, key business and technology leaders such as Mukesh Ambani, Sam Altman and Sundar Pichai also delivered keynote addresses. French President Emmanuel Macron also spoke at the Delhi AI Summit. Tata Sons Chairman N. Chandrasekaran said, “I would like to thank the vision of our Prime Minister, which has enabled us to make a serious foray into chips and semiconductors. Our next step is to build chips that are highly domain-centric and fully AI-optimized for every industry. We will initially focus on developing and launching them for the automotive sector.” Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 2.56% to 817.85. The index rose 0.62% in the past trading session. Lodha Developers (down 4.1%), Godrej Properties (down 4%), DLF (down 3.7%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 2.69%), SignatureGlobal India (down 2.5%), Oberoi Realty (down 2.42%), Anant Raj (down 2.4%), Phoenix Mills (down 1.82%), and Brigade Enterprises (down 0.03%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Multi Commodity Exchange of India (MCX) gained 1.04% after the exchange announced the withdrawal of additional margins imposed on gold and silver futures contracts with effect from 19 February 2026. TIL jumped 9.22% after the company’s board will meet on 23 February 2026, to consider raising funds via different routes. The company will raise capital by way of a rights issue, preferential allotment, qualified institutional placement, or any other permissible mode and/or combination thereof, through the issuance of equity shares, equity-linked securities, warrants, and/or any other eligible securities. Tata Consultancy Services advanced 0.65%. The company announced a multi-dimensional strategic partnership with OpenAI to drive AI-powered innovation across enterprise, consumer, and social sectors. Spicejet shed 0.59%. The company said it has received a memorandum of understanding (MoU) for the induction of 10 aircraft, marking a fresh step in its capacity expansion and network rebuilding plans. ITCONS E-Solutions added 1.01% after it secured a domestic contract from Uranium Corporation of India (UCIL), which operates under the Department of Atomic Energy, PMO. Pine Labs advanced 2.91% after the company announced collaboration with OpenAI, marking its move beyond traditional automation to build agentic commerce. B. L. Kashyap and Sons rose 0.24%. The company said that it secured a contract worth Rs 300 crore from CRC Greens for a group housing project in Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) fell 1.40%. The company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from Northern Railway for a project worth Rs 1,201.35 crore. Dhabriya Polywood zoomed 2.98% after it announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Dynasty Modular Furnitures, had received letters of intent (LOIs) from the Godrej Group aggregating to Rs 25.30 crore. Atishay fell 2.09%. The company said that it has secured a domestic work order from the State Health Assurance Society (SHAS), Government of Maharashtra. Hemant Surgical Industries fell 3.99%. The company announced that it has received an order worth Rs 264.33 crore from the Central Medical Services Society (CMSS), under the Ministry of Health and Family Welfare, Government of India. R P P Infra Projects rose 3.07% after the company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 52.17 crore from the Water Resources Department, Tamil Nadu. The contract has been awarded by the Superintending Engineer, Palar Basin Circle, Chepauk, Chennai. According to the company’s exchange filing, the scope of work includes the formation of new tanks, construction of peripheral earthen drains, cut-and-cover channels, and capacity enhancement of surrounding tanks. The project also involves flood mitigation works for the proposed Global Sports City at Semmancheri, Chennai. GNG Electronics fell 1.38%. The company announced the signing of strategic distribution partnerships with Ingram Micro India and Supertron Electronics for the nationwide distribution of its refurbished computers across India. Global Markets: European markets traded lower on Thursday amid escalating tensions between the United States and Iran, weighed on market sentiment. Most Asian stocks ended higher, supported by gains in technology giants on Wall Street, while lingering U.S.-Iran tensions kept oil prices elevated. In Malaysia, headline inflation rose 1.6% year-on-year in January 2026, with the consumer price index (CPI) increasing to 135.7 from 133.6 in the same month last year, according to the Department of Statistics Malaysia (DOSM). Hong Kong and mainland China markets remained closed for the Lunar New Year break. Meanwhile, Indonesian and U.S. companies signed deals worth $38.4 billion ahead of Indonesian President Prabowo Subianto’s meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump, covering mining, energy, agribusiness, textiles, furniture, and technology sectors. In Australia, the unemployment rate steadied at 4.1% in January, as per data from the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS). Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 moved higher, supported by gains in key technology names, as traders weighed the release of the minutes from the Federal Reserve’s most recent policy meeting. The broad-based index climbed 0.56% to end at 6,881.31, while the Nasdaq Composite added 0.78% to settle at 22,753.63. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.26% to close at 49,662.66. Investors mulled over the minutes from the Fed’s January meeting, which revealed that participants largely approved of the central bank’s decision to leave its key interest rate unchanged at a range of 3.5% to 3.75%. However, officials were divided on the direction of monetary policy thereafter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index registers a drop of 2.56%, NIFTY Crashes  1.41% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-registers-a-drop-of-256-nifty-crashes-141/1678755</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678755</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index closed down 2.56% at 817.85 today.

Nifty Realty index closed down 2.56% at 817.85 today. The index has added 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Lodha Developers Ltd dropped 3.71%, DLF Ltd shed 3.42% and Godrej Properties Ltd fell 3.23%. The Nifty Realty index has decreased 3.00% over last one year compared to the 10.99% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Media index has slid 2.23% and Nifty Auto index has dropped 2.10% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 1.41% to close at 25454.35 while the SENSEX has slid 1.48% to close at 82498.14 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DCX Systems secures orders worth Rs 45-cr from domestic, global clients]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dcx-systems-secures-orders-worth-rs-45-cr-from-domestic-global-clients/1678752</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678752</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders pertain to the manufacture and supply of cable and wire harness assemblies, the company said in a regulatory filing.

The orders pertain to the manufacture and supply of cable and wire harness assemblies, the company said in a regulatory filing. Separately, the company’s wholly owned subsidiary, Raneal Advanced Systems, has secured purchase orders worth about Rs 1.42 crore from a domestic customer for the manufacture and supply of printed circuit board assemblies. With these contracts, the total order inflow stands at around Rs 45.48 crore, reinforcing DCX Systems’ order book in the defence and aerospace electronics segment. DCX Systems is one of the leading Indian Defence Manufacturing player offering a full service and manufacture of Electronic Systems and Cable Harnesses for both International and Domestic reputed customers. The company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 2.43 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net profit of Rs 10.01 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 39.5% year on year to Rs 121.06 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of DCX Systems fell 2.21% to Rs 178.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DCXSystemsLtd_25003026_76686.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alembic Pharma slumps after receiving two USFDA observations for karakhadi facility]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alembic-pharma-slumps-after-receiving-two-usfda-observations-for-karakhadi-facility/1678750</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678750</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The inspection was conducted from 9th February to 18th February 2026.

The inspection was conducted from 9th February to 18th February 2026. At the end of the inspection, a ‘Form 483’ was issued with 2 observations and the company said that it will respond to the US FDA within the stipulated timelines. Alembic Pharmaceuticals, a vertically integrated research and development company, is engaged in the manufacture and marketing of generic pharmaceutical products across global markets. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 3.9% to Rs 132.97 crore despite a 10.8% jump in net sales to Rs 1,876.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlembicPharma_46538273359_40294.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Puravankara launches premium residential project ‘Purva Silversky’ in Bengaluru’s electronic city]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/puravankara-launches-premium-residential-project-purva-silversky-in-bengalurus-electronic-city/1678747</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678747</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Spread across approximately 6.99 acres, the project comprises 356 exclusive residences across three 32-storey towers, with nearly 88% open-to-sky spaces.

Spread across approximately 6.99 acres, the project comprises 356 exclusive residences across three 32-storey towers, with nearly 88% open-to-sky spaces. Positioned as a low-density development with just four units per floor, Purva Silversky promises enhanced privacy, openness, and elevated living experiences. Strategically located in one of Bengaluru’s established technology corridors, the project offers seamless connectivity to major IT hubs, corporate parks, educational institutions, healthcare facilities, and retail destinations. It is situated about 900 metres from Huskur Metro Station and within a 10-minute radius of over 15 IT parks. The development features expansive 3, 4, and 5 BHK residences, along with select larger-format homes, with sizes ranging from 1,864 sq ft to over 5,300 sq ft. Each unit is designed to maximise natural light, ventilation, and spatial efficiency, complemented by premium finishes and private decks. The residences offer 270-degree open views, providing a sense of space and visual openness rarely seen in urban projects. Purva Silversky focuses on holistic wellbeing and community living, featuring a 17,700 sq ft clubhouse and more than 45 lifestyle amenities across a 1.7-acre elevated podium. The project also includes landscaped open spaces and a forest walkway with over 200 trees, catering to the wellness, leisure, and recreational needs of modern urban families. Puravankara is engaged in the business of real estate development. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 59.34 crore in Q3 FY26 as net loss of Rs 93.16 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations zoomed 236.1% year on year to Rs 1,069.31 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of Puravankara fell 1.04% to Rs 232.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Puravankara_83213463793_25459.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lloyds-metals-energy-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678746</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678746</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lloyds Enterprises Ltd, Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd and Easy Trip Planners Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026.

Lloyds Enterprises Ltd, Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd and Easy Trip Planners Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026. Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd tumbled 6.69% to Rs 1130.8 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 6.7 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.04 lakh shares in the past one month. Lloyds Enterprises Ltd lost 4.62% to Rs 55.97. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 66398 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.76 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd crashed 4.34% to Rs 437.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 82436 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.69 lakh shares in the past one month. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd dropped 4.29% to Rs 245.45. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 63223 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.03 lakh shares in the past one month. Easy Trip Planners Ltd plummeted 4.25% to Rs 9.23. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 95.62 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 47.1 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsMetals_76757705405_2629.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hemant Surgical Industries rallies after bagging Rs 264-cr order from CMSS ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hemant-surgical-industries-rallies-after-bagging-rs-264-cr-order-from-cmss/1678745</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678745</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the supply of flat panel detectors with two batteries and a router, hard travel cases along with other utilities, and X-ray generators.

According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the supply of flat panel detectors with two batteries and a router, hard travel cases along with other utilities, and X-ray generators. The final commercial terms, including the delivery schedule of the purchase orders, are currently under discussion and subject to finalisation. The company stated that the order will be executed in tranches by 30 September 2026, subject to negotiations and terms, including any extension requested by Hemant Surgical Industries to CMSS. Hemant Surgical Industries clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It further stated that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Hemant Surgical Industries is in the business of medical equipment & supplies. The company's standalone net profit fell 17% to Rs 8.13 crore on a 0.9% rise in revenue to Rs 106.53 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HemantSurgicalIndustriesLtd_35472315_40414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pine Labs gains after joining hands with OpenAI for agentic commerce]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pine-labs-gains-after-joining-hands-with-openai-for-agentic-commerce/1678743</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678743</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company will embed OpenAI APIs models into the core of a global merchant ecosystem.

The company will embed OpenAI APIs models into the core of a global merchant ecosystem. This transition shift represents a fundamental evolution from the deterministic "if/then" logic that has defined fintech for years. By embedding OpenAI’s intelligence into the core of its stack, Pine Labs is engineering a Reasoning Layer for commerce, transforming its infrastructure into a dynamic system capable of understanding context and weighing probabilities, all while operating within a secure, compliant framework designed for high-stakes financial environments. Users will no longer just "search" for products; they will delegate entire financial lifecycles to intelligent agents within a single dialogue. In this architecture, an agent can autonomously navigate complex tasks—such as negotiating supplier terms, optimizing cross-border settlement cycles, or managing recurring payments— within pre-defined user guardrails. OpenAI provides the critical decision-making intelligence, while while Pine Labs’ payment rails will function as the regulated execution layer. This intelligence is deployed within the company’s enterprise-grade security and compliance architecture. The company also plans to open this agentic stack to its developer ecosystem, providing the tools for third-party innovators to build next-generation, AI-native fintech applications on a trusted foundation. B Amrish Rau, CEO, Pine Labs, said, “For decades, commerce has been built on passive systems that simply follow instructions, At Pine Labs, we are moving beyond that era to build an active, intelligent layer for business. Our work with OpenAI ensures that our infrastructure is no longer just a participant in a trade, but a driver of efficiency and growth. We are building the first agentic stack for the next generation of the global economy.” Oliver Jay, managing director, International, OpenAI, said, “The next phase of AI is about moving from information to action, by combining our advanced reasoning capabilities with Pine Labs’ deep merchant infrastructure, we are helping to create a powerful engine for innovation that turns complex financial workflows into seamless, agentic experiences at scale.” Pine Labs is a technology company focused on digitizing commerce through digital payments and issuing solutions for merchants, consumer brands and enterprises, and financial institutions. The company reported net profit of Rs 42.39 crore in Q3 FY26 comapred with net loss of Rs 56.67 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales jumped 23.7% YoY to Rs 744.27 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PineLabsLtd_41545070_77096.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/veer-global-infraconstruction-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678742</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678742</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hilton Metal Forging Ltd, Sharika Enterprises Ltd, JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd and Primo Chemicals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026.

Hilton Metal Forging Ltd, Sharika Enterprises Ltd, JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd and Primo Chemicals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026. Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd crashed 10.96% to Rs 84.8 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2266 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 922 shares in the past one month. Hilton Metal Forging Ltd tumbled 10.49% to Rs 21.24. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 78114 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 24860 shares in the past one month. Sharika Enterprises Ltd lost 8.94% to Rs 11.2. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.82 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53589 shares in the past one month. JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd fell 7.19% to Rs 24.52. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 38 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 827 shares in the past one month. Primo Chemicals Ltd shed 7.10% to Rs 20.81. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5420 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 20123 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VeerGlobalInfraconstructionLtd.._40400431_75110.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold rebounds sharply amid Fed split and Dollar pullback]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-rebounds-sharply-amid-fed-split-and-dollar-pullback/1678741</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678741</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures climbed above $5,000 per ounce on Thursday, extending a strong rebound of over $100 from the previous session as investors focused on upcoming US PCE inflation and GDP data for cues on Federal Reserve policy.

Gold futures climbed above $5,000 per ounce on Thursday, extending a strong rebound of over $100 from the previous session as investors focused on upcoming US PCE inflation and GDP data for cues on Federal Reserve policy. The dollar index eased slightly to 97.5 after a prior-session surge, while Fed minutes from January revealed a split among officials—some favored pausing rate cuts for now, others supported maintaining a two-sided outlook that could allow future hikes or easing. In domestic markets, MCX April 2026 gold futures gained over ₹1,000 to ₹156,935 per 10 grams, recovering sharply from this year’s low of ₹137,000.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex sinks 901 pts; media shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-sinks-901-pts-media-shares-tumble/1678739</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678739</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major cuts in mid-afternoon trade, pressured by broad-based selling across sectors.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major cuts in mid-afternoon trade, pressured by broad-based selling across sectors. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. Media shares witnessed profit booking after rising in the previous two consecutive trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 901.29 points or 1.08% to 82,832.96. The Nifty 50 index fell 254.65 points or 0.99% to 25,558.70. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.92% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.66%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,449 shares rose and 2,610 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced the MANAV Vision for AI, where MANAV stands for M – Moral and Ethical System, A – Accountable Governance, N – National Sovereignty (right to data), A – Accessible and Inclusive, and V – Valid and Legitimate. Apart from PM Modi, key business and technology leaders such as Mukesh Ambani, Sam Altman and Sundar Pichai also delivered keynote addresses. French President Emmanuel Macron also spoke at the Delhi AI Summit. Tata Sons Chairman N. Chandrasekaran said, “I would like to thank the vision of our Prime Minister, which has enabled us to make a serious foray into chips and semiconductors. Our next step is to build chips that are highly domain-centric and fully AI-optimized for every industry. We will initially focus on developing and launching them for the automotive sector.” Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 1.99% to 1,434.35. The index advanced 0.92% over the previous two trading sessions. PVR Inox (down 3.71%), D B Corp (down 2.87%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 2.65%), Prime Focus (down 1.94%), Tips Music (down 1.89%), Saregama India (down 1.83%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 1.77%), Sun TV Network (down 1.37%), Nazara Technologies (down 0.87%) and Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 0.44%) rose. Numbers to Track: In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6850 compared with its close of 90.7200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.76% to Rs 156,940. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.11% to 97.63. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.44% to 4.098. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose $1.03 cents or 1.46% to $71.38 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: SpiceJet shed 0.53%. The company said it has received a memorandum of understanding (MoU) for the induction of 10 aircraft, marking a fresh step in its capacity expansion and network rebuilding plans. R P P Infra Projects rose 1.93% after the company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 52.17 crore from the Water Resources Department, Tamil Nadu.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Tata Investment Corporation Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-tata-investment-corporation-ltd-counter/1678738</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678738</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Godrej Industries Ltd, NCC Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, India Cements Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 19 February 2026.

Godrej Industries Ltd, NCC Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, India Cements Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 19 February 2026. Tata Investment Corporation Ltd notched up volume of 192.65 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 38.75 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4.97 lakh shares. The stock rose 9.42% to Rs.704.65. Volumes stood at 8.16 lakh shares in the last session. Godrej Industries Ltd notched up volume of 9.64 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.83 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 60913 shares. The stock rose 5.16% to Rs.1,035.90. Volumes stood at 27086 shares in the last session. NCC Ltd clocked volume of 215.76 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.67 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 28.14 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.41% to Rs.149.14. Volumes stood at 23.48 lakh shares in the last session. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd recorded volume of 545.12 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.22 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 87.58 lakh shares. The stock gained 18.30% to Rs.628.85. Volumes stood at 212.78 lakh shares in the last session. India Cements Ltd recorded volume of 11.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.87 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.89 lakh shares. The stock lost 1.63% to Rs.423.20. Volumes stood at 1.62 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataInvCorpn_86313365626_298.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude holds around $65 per barrel after massive spike in last session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-holds-around-65-per-barrel-after-massive-spike-in-last-session/1678737</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678737</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures traded above $65 per barrel on Thursday, holding onto the strongest rally since late October after surging more than 4% in the previous session.

WTI crude oil futures traded above $65 per barrel on Thursday, holding onto the strongest rally since late October after surging more than 4% in the previous session. Support came from signs of tightening US supply, with industry data showing crude inventories fell by 0.61 million barrels last week, partially reversing the sharp build seen earlier. Geopolitical risk also remained firmly in focus as negotiations between the US and Iran continued without a clear breakthrough, despite Tehran citing a “general agreement” on the framework of a potential nuclear deal. Meanwhile, the dollar index hovered near 97.5 after a sharp rise in the prior session, underpinned by strong US economic data and hawkish signals from the Federal Reserve. Minutes from the Fed’s latest meeting highlighted divisions among policymakers and kept the option of further rate hikes on the table should inflation remain elevated, adding to broader market uncertainty.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Holidays launches Club Mahindra Nadiya Parao resort in Jim Corbett]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-holidays-launches-club-mahindra-nadiya-parao-resort-in-jim-corbett/1678735</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678735</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The new resort launch aligns with the company’s accelerated expansion strategy and its ambition to become India’s leading leisure hospitality player, driven by robust resort additions, portfolio premiumisation, and disciplined capital allocation.

The new resort launch aligns with the company’s accelerated expansion strategy and its ambition to become India’s leading leisure hospitality player, driven by robust resort additions, portfolio premiumisation, and disciplined capital allocation. This marks MHRIL’s second resort in Jim Corbett, one of India’s most preferred destinations for nature-led travel. The addition supports the company’s near-term target of 1,000 room additions by FY26 and its longer-term goal of scaling to 10,000 keys under Club Mahindra and 12,000 keys overall by FY30. Spanning around 10 acres, the 57-room resort combines premium leisure stays with extensive event infrastructure, including large landscaped lawns, a banquet hall, and riverfront access. The property is designed to cater to diverse segments, including holidaying families, destination weddings, and corporate offsites, unlocking multiple revenue streams from a single asset. Manoj Bhat, managing director & chief executive officer, Mahindra Holidays & Resorts India, said, “Our ambition is to lead leisure hospitality in India, with families at the heart of everything we do. The launch of Nadiya Parao is another step forward in our expansion journey, in a destination where demand is strong and growing. As we expand, we’re not just adding resorts; we’re delivering superior experience, sharpening execution, and building for the future”. Mahindra Holidays & Resorts India (MHRIL), part of the diversified Mahindra Group, is India’s leading leisure hospitality company. Established in 1996, the company pioneered the vacation ownership model in India and has since redefined family holidays through thoughtfully designed resorts, curated experiences, and a commitment to sustainable tourism. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 93.6% to Rs 2.23 crore on 10.9% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 752.70 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahindraHoliday_70394943904_18268.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>