<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:35:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[South Indian Bank Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/south-indian-bank-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1669092</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669092</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd, Hindustan Copper Ltd, Vedanta Ltd and National Aluminium Company Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 30 January 2026.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd, Hindustan Copper Ltd, Vedanta Ltd and National Aluminium Company Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 30 January 2026. South Indian Bank Ltd lost 15.04% to Rs 37.61 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 158.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 30.68 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Zinc Ltd tumbled 11.49% to Rs 633.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 33 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12.64 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Copper Ltd crashed 10.59% to Rs 678.8. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 127.5 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 50.37 lakh shares in the past one month. Vedanta Ltd corrected 10.00% to Rs 689.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 21.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12.49 lakh shares in the past one month. National Aluminium Company Ltd plummeted 9.09% to Rs 389.95. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 31.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13.58 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SouthIndBank_65437939_6263.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Gold tumbles around 4%, crashes under $5200 per ounce]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-gold-tumbles-around-4-crashes-under-5200-per-ounce/1669089</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669089</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Gold futures melted today, sliding around 4% amid speculations the US Federal Reserve might receive a more hawkish chair.

COMEX Gold futures melted today, sliding around 4% amid speculations the US Federal Reserve might receive a more hawkish chair. Hefty profit selling was seen after the counter hit a fresh record high of $5626 per ounce in last session. The metal is still on track for its greatest monthly gain since 1982 as investors rushed to the safe haven amid persisting geopolitical and economic concerns. COMEX Gold futures are currently trading at $5151 per ounce, down 3.80% on the day. Gold has rallied around 80% in last one month. Latest data is reflecting some concerns over retail buying as total global gold jewellery fabrication demand dropped around 19% on year to 1638 tonnes in 2025. MCX Gold is also witnessing intense volatility after opening sharply lower and currently trades down 6% at Rs 172925 per 10 grams. Intraday gains above Rs 180000 per 10 grams mark earlier in the day evaporated quickly.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/california-software-company-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-losers-in-b-group/1669087</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669087</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Meera Industries Ltd, Alacrity Securities Ltd, Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd and Plaza Wires Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 January 2026.

Meera Industries Ltd, Alacrity Securities Ltd, Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd and Plaza Wires Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 January 2026. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup crashed 14.82% to Rs 3.62 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 25797 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1589 shares in the past one month. Meera Industries Ltd tumbled 14.00% to Rs 81. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 69081 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 46608 shares in the past one month. Alacrity Securities Ltd lost 9.98% to Rs 49. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15882 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21243 shares in the past one month. Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd slipped 8.05% to Rs 23.3. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 11 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1980 shares in the past one month. Plaza Wires Ltd pared 7.76% to Rs 40.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6405 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5835 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with modest losses; Oil & gas share slides]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-modest-losses-oil-gas-share-slides/1669082</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669082</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks trimmed some losses and traded with modest declines in mid-afternoon trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026.

The headline equity benchmarks trimmed some losses and traded with modest declines in mid-afternoon trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments for fresh direction. Investor focus is also on quarterly results due later today from key companies such as Bajaj Auto, NTPC, Power Grid Corporation of India, Nestlé India, and Ambuja Cements. Reflecting the subdued sentiment, the Nifty slipped below the 25,300 level during morning trade. Metal, IT and oil & gas shares declined, while media, FMCG and realty shares advanced. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 272.19 points or 0.33% to 82,286.02. The Nifty 50 index lost 87.35 points or 0.34% to 25,330.45. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.14% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.19%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,422 shares rose and 1,704 shares fell. A total of 171 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, advanced 2.97% to 13.77. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index fell 0.63% to 11,780.85. The index jumped 4.84% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 2.10%), Petronet LNG (down 1.84%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 1.7%), Oil India (down 1.59%), Indraprastha Gas (down 1.52%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 1.02%), Gujarat State Petronet (down 0.51%), GAIL (India) (down 0.44%), Mahanagar Gas (down 0.33%) and Indian Oil Corporation (down 0.32%) declined. On the other hand, Aegis Logistics (up 5.77%), Gujarat Gas (up 0.67%) and Reliance Industries (up 0.36%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.09% to 6.693 as compared with the previous close of 6.699. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9300 compared with its close of 91.9950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement dropped 3.78% to Rs 1,62,999. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.23% to 96.36. The United States 10-year bond yield gained 1.14% to 4.276. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement lost $1.01 or 1.45% to $68.67 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Cupid surged 7.84% after the company reported a 196.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 32.83 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 11.08 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 101.70% YoY to Rs 93.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. TD Power Systems zoomed 9.29% after the company reported a 25.4% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 56.32 crore on a 26.4% rise in net sales to Rs 442.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Motors CV slips after Q3 hit by exceptional costs ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-motors-cv-slips-after-q3-hit-by-exceptional-costs/1669080</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669080</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit declined 48% YoY to Rs 705 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,355 crore a year ago.

On a consolidated basis, net profit declined 48% YoY to Rs 705 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,355 crore a year ago. Sequentially, it returned to profit from a loss of Rs 867 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue rose 16.2% YoY to Rs 21,732 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 18,697 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, revenue increased 17.5% QoQ from Rs 18,491 crore. Profit before tax fell 39.6% YoY to Rs 925 crore compared with Rs 1,531 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, PBT improved sharply from a loss of Rs 561 crore in Q2 FY26. On the cost front, total expenditure increased 22.6% YoY to Rs 20,607 crore. Raw material consumption climbed 20.0% YoY to Rs 12,531 crore. Employee expenses edged up 3.9% YoY to Rs 1,450 crore. Interest costs declined 43.8% YoY to Rs 198 crore, while depreciation fell 13.3% YoY to Rs 483 crore. Earnings during the quarter were impacted by exceptional losses of Rs 1,643 crore, linked to the implementation of the new labour code, demerger-related expenses and acquisition costs. Operationally, CV wholesales stood at 116.8 thousand units, up 20% YoY. Domestic volumes rose 18% YoY, while export volumes surged 70% YoY. The company’s domestic CV VAHAN market share improved by 100 bps sequentially to 35.5% in Q3 FY26. Industry-wise, management expects demand to strengthen further in Q4 FY26, aided by the government’s sustained infrastructure push and improving activity across end-use sectors. With an optimised product portfolio, pricing discipline and deeper customer engagement, Tata Motors expects to remain well positioned to capture incremental CV demand. Girish Wagh, MD & CEO, Tata Motors said: "Disciplined execution of an agile strategy delivered yet another strong financial performance this quarter, supported by demand tailwinds from GST 2.0 and the festive season. Our recent launch of 17 next-generation trucks under the ‘Better Always’ philosophy sets new benchmarks in safety, total cost of ownership, and smarter, emission-free mobility, reinforcing our commitment to innovation and industry leadership. With infrastructure spending accelerating, we are well positioned to sustain momentum and drive continued growth." GV Ramanan, CFO, Tata Motors said: "We delivered another strong quarter, translating robust operational execution and healthy demand across key segments into meaningful financial outcomes. The quarter marked significant milestones, including our 10th consecutive quarter of double-digit EBITDA margins and achievement of double-digit EBIT margins. This strong operating performance coupled with disciplined working capital management, led to robust free cash flow generation. With this trajectory, we remain confident of delivering on our stated financial guidance." Tata Motors is India's largest commercial vehicles (CV) manufacturer with the widest product and service portfolio across cargo and public transportation segments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataMotorsLtd_65899190_93137.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Vardhman Textiles Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-vardhman-textiles-ltd-counter/1669074</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669074</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Syrma SGS Technology Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Aurobindo Pharma Ltd, RHI Magnesita India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 30 January 2026.

Syrma SGS Technology Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Aurobindo Pharma Ltd, RHI Magnesita India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 30 January 2026. Vardhman Textiles Ltd notched up volume of 74.52 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 24.36 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.06 lakh shares. The stock rose 8.86% to Rs.450.20. Volumes stood at 1.27 lakh shares in the last session. Syrma SGS Technology Ltd recorded volume of 112.81 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.68 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9.66 lakh shares. The stock gained 5.23% to Rs.761.90. Volumes stood at 11.36 lakh shares in the last session. SignatureGlobal India Ltd witnessed volume of 44.3 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.43 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4.25 lakh shares. The stock increased 8.26% to Rs.906.00. Volumes stood at 2.79 lakh shares in the last session. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd clocked volume of 56.47 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.21 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.13 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.51% to Rs.1,202.50. Volumes stood at 5.77 lakh shares in the last session. RHI Magnesita India Ltd recorded volume of 15.67 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.76 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.79 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.71% to Rs.439.65. Volumes stood at 1.8 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VardhmanTextile_60310538344_932.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Allied Blenders rises after Q3 PAT jumps 11% YoY to Rs 64 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/allied-blenders-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-11-yoy-to-rs-64-cr/1669071</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669071</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased by 2.98% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,002.98 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased by 2.98% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,002.98 crore in Q3 FY26. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 92.29 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 80.11 crore a year ago. The quarter included exceptional items of Rs 3.19 crore, reflecting a one-time impact from the implementation of India’s new labour codes (effective 21 November 2025) related to long-term employee benefits. EBITDA for the quarter stood at Rs 137 crore in Q3 FY26, reflecting a 14.1% increase compared to Rs 120 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin was 13.6% in Q3 FY26, compared to 12.3% in Q3 FY25. The prestige & above (P&A) portfolio continued to post healthy growth in Q3 FY26, with volumes rising 1.3% YoY to 9.0 million cases, supported by a 16.9% increase in the P&A segment. The company also expanded its international footprint to 31 countries during the quarter, compared with 23 countries in FY25, and is targeting presence in 35 countries by March 2026, stated the exchange filing. Alok Gupta, Managing Director of ABD, stated, “As we transition into a future-ready organization, our leadership structure must mirror our strategic ambitions. The realignment of Jayant and Ramki allows us to bifurcate our focus: Jayant will spearhead our long-term strategic investments and digital evolution, while Ramki brings his unparalleled institutional knowledge back to the helm of our financial stewardship. This dual-engine financial leadership ensures that as we scale our luxury portfolio and expand our manufacturing footprint, we maintain the highest standards of operational excellence and value creation for our stakeholders.” In a separate filing, ABD announced a strategic realignment of its senior finance leadership. Jayant Manmadkar, currently chief financial officer, will transition to the newly created role of group finance director, effective 2 February 2026. The company also announced the return of Ramakrishnan Ramaswamy as chief financial officer. Ramaswamy brings over three decades of experience and has been associated with ABD for more than 14 years, having played a key role in the company’s July 2024 IPO. This transition is designed to bolster the Group's next phase of growth, entry into the luxury segment via its new division, ABD Maestro, and to oversee its value-accretive capacity expansion and backward integration program, the company said. Separately, Allied Blenders and Distillers said it will invest up to Rs 54 crore in its subsidiary Minakshi Agro Industries LLP to set up a bottling facility and acquire land at its Aurangabad distillery in Maharashtra. The arm’s-length related-party transaction will not result in any change in ownership and is aimed at enhancing manufacturing capacity to support rising domestic and export demand. In January 2026, the company announced the acquisition of a non-operational distillery with a bottling facility in Moradabad, Uttar Pradesh. The deal, valued at up to Rs 110 crore, will enhance backward integration, expand bottling capacity, and strengthen margins and supply chain efficiency, supporting long-term growth and operational flexibility. Allied Blenders and Distillers (ABD) is engaged in the manufacturing, procurement, and sale of alcoholic beverages.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlliedBlendersDistillersLtd_14707910_68245.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cupid gains after Q3 PAT skyrockets 196% YoY to Rs 33 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cupid-gains-after-q3-pat-skyrockets-196-yoy-to-rs-33-cr/1669069</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669069</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 101.70% YoY to Rs 93.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 101.70% YoY to Rs 93.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 43.27 crore in Q3 FY26, up 207.09% from Rs 14.09 crore reported in the same period year ago. EBITDA for Q3 FY26 soared 201% to Rs 34.30 crore, compared to Rs 11.39 crore in Q3 FY25. The EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 stood at 37%, compared to 25% in the same quarter year ago. The company reported its strongest-ever quarterly performance in Q3 FY26, supported by steady demand and disciplined execution. The robust showing was driven by strength in export-led B2B operations, continued scaling of the domestic FMCG business, and improving traction in the diagnostics segment. Management said operational momentum remains strong as the company enters calendar year 2026, with better execution visibility for the rest of FY26 and beyond. The company’s domestic FMCG business continues to scale, with rising market acceptance across India. Growth has been supported by new product additions in the personal care and wellness segments, along with an expanding retail and distribution footprint. The company currently operates with over 58 super stockists, more than 1,050 distributors and a sales force of 325+ members, enabling presence across over 1.50 lakh retail outlets nationwide. Management said the FMCG segment adds a fast-growing B2C layer to the company’s strong export-led B2B model, aiding margin diversification and long-term brand building. The company’s export-led B2B business continued to perform strongly during the quarter and remains a key driver of both revenue and profitability. The segment is supported by multi-year international programs, repeat orders from institutional and non-institutional customers, and a strong execution track record across more than 125 export markets. A key growth driver is the South Africa National Female & Male Condom Programme, a five-year contract spanning 2025–2030, with a total annual allocation value of around $12.98 million (approximately Rs 115 crore). Under the programme, the company is expected to supply about 23.4 million female condoms and nearly 153 million male condoms annually. Management highlighted markets such as Tanzania, Brazil, Kenya, Ethiopia, the Philippines, CIS countries, the European Union and the Middle East as important growth regions over the coming years. The company’s diagnostics (IVD) business is emerging as a key growth engine, supported by expanding manufacturing capabilities and improving demand visibility. The current portfolio includes 15 rapid IVD test kits in production across segments such as HIV, syphilis, pregnancy and Hepatitis B, with three additional kits under development. Manufacturing capacity stands at over 1.5 lakh kits per day and is targeted to scale up to around 4 lakh kits per day by the end of 2026, aided by increased automation. The diagnostics facilities have received multiple regulatory approvals and certifications, including CDSCO, ICMR, NIMR, NIB and RGCB, along with ISO 13485, ISO 9001 and ISO 14001 certifications. On the demand front, the company is eligible to participate in central and state government tenders and supplies diagnostic kits to more than 120 ESIC hospitals through the GeM platform. Its products are also available across chemist stores and diagnostic laboratories nationwide. Recent CE (EU IVDR) certifications are expected to enable entry into European and other regulated global markets, improving long-term growth visibility. On its outlook, “the company expects FY26 to be the strongest year in its history, backed by a robust order pipeline and improving execution. Management said it is confident of surpassing its FY26 revenue guidance of Rs 335 crore, while net profit is expected to exceed Rs 100 crore for the year. The second half of FY26 is likely to remain stronger than the first, supported by a record order book, long-duration international programmes, and enhanced operational readiness. The company added that the current momentum is expected to continue into FY27 and beyond.” Commenting on the performance, Aditya Kumar Halwasiya, chairman and managing director (MD) of Cupid, said, “Q3 FY26 was the strongest quarter in the company’s history, driven by disciplined execution and strong momentum across businesses. He said the company’s order book stands at an all-time high, providing clear revenue visibility and confidence in sustained performance. Halwasiya added that the company continues to strengthen its overseas presence, including in the GCC region, while capacity expansion at the Palava manufacturing facility is progressing as planned in line with its growth roadmap. The domestic FMCG portfolio is witnessing rising acceptance, supported by new product launches and a wider retail footprint. To accelerate FMCG growth, the company is working towards entering the UAE and Saudi Arabia markets. He said the combined expansion across India and the GCC positions Cupid for sustained global growth with scale, efficiency and flexibility. The diagnostics (IVD) business is also emerging as a key future growth driver, supported by regulatory certifications, rising demand, in-house R&D capabilities and increasing automation. Based on strong Q3 performance, a record order book and improving execution, Halwasiya said FY26 is expected to be the strongest year in the company’s history. The company is confident of surpassing its FY26 revenue guidance of ₹335 crore, with net profit expected to exceed Rs 100 crore, while continuing to focus on building a balanced, scalable and future-ready business.” CUPID is an India's premier manufacturer and brand of male and female condoms, water based personal lubricants, IVD kits, deodorants, perfumes, almond hair oil, body oils, petroleum jelly and other FMCG Products. The company operates with a strong commitment to public health and well-being, maintaining ethical business practices aligned with international standards.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cupid_16723626520_5185.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Consumer Products Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-consumer-products-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1669048</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669048</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Godrej Consumer Products Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Godrej Consumer Products Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1153.5, down 0.16% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.73% on the day, quoting at 25232.6. The Sensex is at 82000.06, down 0.69%.Godrej Consumer Products Ltd has eased around 5.62% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Godrej Consumer Products Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 8.53% in last one month and is currently quoting at 50523.9, up 0.44% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 4.75 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 11.51 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1160.6, up 0.3% on the day. Godrej Consumer Products Ltd jumped 2.88% in last one year as compared to a 7.33% rally in NIFTY and a 10.49% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 84.71 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejConsumer_25192758531_21960.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Varun Beverages Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/varun-beverages-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1669049</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669049</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Varun Beverages Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Varun Beverages Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 464.75, down 0.49% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.73% on the day, quoting at 25232.6. The Sensex is at 82000.06, down 0.69%.Varun Beverages Ltd has lost around 5.12% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Varun Beverages Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 8.53% in last one month and is currently quoting at 50523.9, up 0.44% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 32.28 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 47.93 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 467.45, down 0.55% on the day. Varun Beverages Ltd tumbled 13.41% in last one year as compared to a 7.33% rally in NIFTY and a 10.49% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 60.28 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VarunBeveragesLtd_58326939712_24608.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade with substantial losses; European markets edge higher ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-with-substantial-losses-european-markets-edge-higher/1669055</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669055</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on February 1.

Domestic equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on February 1. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments for fresh direction. Investor focus is also on quarterly results due later today from key companies such as Bajaj Auto, NTPC, Power Grid Corporation of India, Nestlé India, and Ambuja Cements. Reflecting the subdued sentiment, the Nifty slipped below the 25,300 level during morning trade. Metal, IT and oil & gas shares declined, while media, FMCG and realty shares advanced. At 13:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 525.14 points or 0.63% to 82,041.36. The Nifty 50 index lost 164.25 points or 0.65% to 25,250.50. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index dropped 0.55% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.10%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,200 shares rose and 1,851 shares fell. A total of 186 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 4.80% to 14.01. Gainers & Losers: Tata Consumer Products (up 1.95%), Apollo Hospitals Enterprise (up 1.70%), Nestle India (up 0.94%), State Bank of India (up 0.80%) and ITC (up 0.71%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Hindalco Industries (down 6.15%), Tata Steel (down 5.10%), Coal India (down 3.96%), Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (down 2.46%) and Power Grid Corporation of India (down 2.23%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Nippon Life India Asset Management rallied 3.15% after its consolidated net profit jumped 36.74% to Rs 403.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 295.36 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income jumped 29.38% to Rs 780.55 crore in the third quarter of FY26, as against Rs 603.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Blue Star jumped 4.50%. The company reported 39.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 80.55 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 132.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased by 4.2% to Rs 2,925.31 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as compared to Rs 2807.36 crore during the same period in the previous year. ITC rose 0.91%. The company reported 5.6% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 4934.80 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5016.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose by 6.2% year-on-year to Rs 17857.56 crore during the period under review. One 97 Communications slipped 3.44%. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 225 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 208 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations during the period under review increased by 20.02% YoY to Rs 2,194 crore Colgate-Palmolive (India) shed 0.63%. The company reported a marginal 0.3% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 323.9 crore, while revenue from operations rose 1.4% to Rs 1,472.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dabur India slipped 0.73%. The company reported a 7.3% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 553.61 crore on a 6.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3,558.65 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) fell 0.14%. The company said that it has secured a domestic contract from Pawan Hans for the supply of 10 Dhruv NG helicopters, along with associated spares and accessories. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Friday, as international relations and corporate earnings remained in focus. Asian markets traded mixed as U.S. President Donald Trump said that he will announce his choice for the next Federal Reserve chair on Friday. Speaking at the premiere of Melania, a film about first lady Melania Trump, he said the five-month search to replace current chair Jerome Powell was nearing its conclusion. The process for selecting Powell’s replacement began in September with an 11-candidate field that included past and current Fed officials, economists, and Wall Street investment professionals. Trump also endorsed a Senate deal to fund the vast majority of the federal government through the remainder of the fiscal year, easing near-term political uncertainty for investors. Senators clinched a deal with just over a day until a partial government shutdown. They agreed to remove funding for the Department of Homeland Security from the package and pass the other five bills, while DHS will be funded by a stopgap. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index slipped 0.13% to close at 6,969.01, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 0.72% to end at 23,685.12. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.11%, or 55.96 points, and settled at 49,071.56.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Gas Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-gas-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1669039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669039</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat Gas Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Gujarat Gas Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 426.7, up 1.52% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.5% on the day, quoting at 25293. The Sensex is at 82170.1, down 0.48%. Gujarat Gas Ltd has gained around 3.52% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Gujarat Gas Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35335.2, down 1.1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.77 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.32 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 24.95 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujaratGas_6190462003_43934.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Breweries Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-breweries-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1669040</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669040</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[United Breweries Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

United Breweries Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1480.1, up 3.67% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.5% on the day, quoting at 25293. The Sensex is at 82170.1, down 0.48%. United Breweries Ltd has slipped around 8.73% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which United Breweries Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 8.03% in last one month and is currently quoting at 50523.9, up 0.98% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.02 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.04 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 99.37 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnitedBreweries_49738308528_23220.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Spirits Ltd soars 1.89%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-spirits-ltd-soars-189-up-for-third-straight-session/1669041</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669041</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[United Spirits Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

United Spirits Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1355.5, up 1.89% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.5% on the day, quoting at 25293. The Sensex is at 82170.1, down 0.48%. United Spirits Ltd has dropped around 6.11% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which United Spirits Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 8.03% in last one month and is currently quoting at 50523.9, up 0.98% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.11 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.7 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1359, up 1.66% on the day. United Spirits Ltd is down 4.81% in last one year as compared to a 7.59% gain in NIFTY and a 10% gain in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 55.38 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnitedSpirits_20574926747_8036.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aurobindo-pharma-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1669042</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669042</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1187.9, up 3.24% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.5% on the day, quoting at 25293. The Sensex is at 82170.1, down 0.48%. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd has gained around 0.41% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 4.67% in last one month and is currently quoting at 21564, up 0.46% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 49.13 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 8.28 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1187.9, up 3.04% on the day. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is up 1.37% in last one year as compared to a 7.59% jump in NIFTY and a 1.05% jump in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 33.07 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurobindoPharma_66877283489_4666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gland Pharma Ltd spurts 2.88%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gland-pharma-ltd-spurts-288-gains-for-third-straight-session/1669043</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669043</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gland Pharma Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Gland Pharma Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 1852, up 2.88% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.5% on the day, quoting at 25293. The Sensex is at 82170.1, down 0.48%. Gland Pharma Ltd has added around 7.55% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Gland Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has added around 4.67% in last one month and is currently quoting at 21564, up 0.46% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.46 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.85 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 24.98 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlandPharmaLtd._31222392_14546.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty tad below 25,300 level; IT shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-tad-below-25300-level-it-shares-decline/1669028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669028</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in the early afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in the early afternoon trade. The Nifty traded a tad below the 25,300 level. IT stocks extended losses for the second consecutive trading session. At 12:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 357.87 points or 0.43% to 82,208.50. The Nifty 50 index dropped 119.60 points or 0.49% to 25,295.25. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 1.02%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,304 shares rose and 1,688 shares fell. A total of 190 shares were unchanged. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 3.68% to 13.86. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures were trading at 25,397.20, at a premium of 101.95 points as compared with the spot at 25,295.25. The Nifty option chain for the 24 February 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 49.4 lakh contracts at the 26,000 strike price. Maximum put OI of 53.1 lakh contracts was seen at 25,000 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index fell 1.22% to 37,962.45. The index dropped 1.97% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Infosys (down 2.08%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 1.44%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.43%), Wipro (down 1.36%), HCL Technologies (down 1.34%), Coforge (down 0.92%), Mphasis (down 0.92%), LTIMindtree (down 0.63%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.55%) and Persistent Systems (down 0.42%) tumbled. Stocks in Spotlight: Nippon Life India Asset Management added 3.91% after its consolidated net profit jumped 36.74% to Rs 403.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 295.36 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income jumped 29.38% to Rs 780.55 crore in the third quarter of FY26, as against Rs 603.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Blue Star rose 3.97%. The company reported 39.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 80.55 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 132.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased by 4.2% to Rs 2,925.31 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as compared to Rs 2807.36 crore during the same period in the previous year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Paras Petrofils Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/paras-petrofils-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1669025</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669025</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Raymond Realty Ltd, Magadh Sugar & Energy Ltd, Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Ltd and Integra Essentia Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 January 2026.

Raymond Realty Ltd, Magadh Sugar & Energy Ltd, Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Ltd and Integra Essentia Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 January 2026. Paras Petrofils Ltd soared 18.67% to Rs 2.67 at 12:01 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 6.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 58791 shares in the past one month. Raymond Realty Ltd surged 16.44% to Rs 500.1. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.21 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9169 shares in the past one month. Magadh Sugar & Energy Ltd spiked 15.69% to Rs 483. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 840 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 214 shares in the past one month. Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Ltd jumped 13.05% to Rs 34.83. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 13.52 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.37 lakh shares in the past one month. Integra Essentia Ltd exploded 12.82% to Rs 1.76. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 12.6 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.69 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ParasPetrofils_93905986310_4664.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund Change in Minimum SIP Amount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-mutual-fund-change-in-minimum-sip-amount/1669024</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669024</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund has announced that the minimum application amount for the Systematic Investment Plan (“SIP”) under Axis Silver Fund of Fund (“the Scheme”) stands revised, as under: effective from February 09, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Existing Provisions Revised provisions effective from February 09, 2026 Axis Silver Fund of Fund Rs.

Axis Mutual Fund has announced that the minimum application amount for the Systematic Investment Plan (“SIP”) under Axis Silver Fund of Fund (“the Scheme”) stands revised, as under: effective from February 09, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Existing Provisions Revised provisions effective from February 09, 2026 Axis Silver Fund of Fund Rs. 1,000 and 6 in multiples of installments Re. 1/- 6 installments Rs. 100 and in 6 multiples of installments Re. 1/- thereafter. 6 installments

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Silver cools below $108 after explosive 50% January rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/silver-cools-below-108-after-explosive-50-january-rally/1669018</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669018</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Silver futures eased below the $108 per ounce level, declining over 4% as month-end and pre-weekend profit-taking emerged in the aftermath of January’s blistering 50% rally.

Silver futures eased below the $108 per ounce level, declining over 4% as month-end and pre-weekend profit-taking emerged in the aftermath of January’s blistering 50% rally. The pullback reflects tactical position trimming following an overheated advance, rather than a breakdown in the underlying narrative. Structural tailwinds — including persistent geopolitical uncertainty, expectations of lower global interest rates, constrained supply dynamics, and surging industrial consumption — continue to anchor silver’s medium-term outlook. In the domestic market, MCX benchmark silver futures plunged by more than ₹20,000 to trade near ₹3,80,649 per kg, underscoring heightened volatility after an exceptional run-up.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silver-trophy-1310083_silver.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>