<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:17:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee eases after recent gains]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-eases-after-recent-gains/1661912</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661912</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee slipped today, giving up after recent rebound took it near three week high against the US dollar.

Indian rupee slipped today, giving up after recent rebound took it near three week high against the US dollar. Quarter and year end trades saw steady demand for the dollar and INR eased 12 paise to 89.75 per US dollar. The INR has been under stress recently but sustained uptick in equities recently and comfortable forex cover could cap losses now. India's forex reserves jumped by $1.689 billion to $688.949 billion during the week ended December 12, the Reserve Bank of India said last week. The US dollar index trades well under 98 mark today, lingering around ten-week low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-accountant-financial-papers-analysis-charts-pict_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India has witnessed remarkable economic transformation over last decade]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-has-witnessed-remarkable-economic-transformation-over-last-decade/1661910</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661910</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vice-President of India, C.

Vice-President of India, C. P. Radhakrishnan has stated that over the past decade, India has witnessed remarkable economic transformation and renewed national confidence. He said that today Bharat has emerged as the fourth largest economy in the world and is also the fastest-growing major economy. The Vice-President pointed out that structural reforms such as insolvency laws, digital governance and transparent banking systems were not merely policy initiatives but bold steps aimed at eliminating decades-old inefficiencies and corruption. He noted that the JAM trinity (Jan Dhan–Aadhaar–Mobile) has enabled direct benefit transfers, reduced leakages, and enhanced transparency and efficiency in governance. So far, he said, over Rs 47 lakh crore has been directly transferred into beneficiaries’ bank accounts. The Vice-President said India’s economic empowerment has been driven by a strong focus on inclusion. Initiatives such as Digital India, Make in India, Startup India and the rapid expansion of UPI have empowered citizens, entrepreneurs and small businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/growth-951606__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee sheds tears]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-sheds-tears/1661911</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661911</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 89.8400 per Dollar on Wednesday (24 December 2025), versus its previous close of 89.6750 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality IPO subscribed 5.21 times ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-kidney-and-super-speciality-ipo-subscribed-521-times/1661906</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661906</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 6,89,68,576 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Wednesday (24 December 2025).

Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 6,89,68,576 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Wednesday (24 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. The IPO comprises fresh issue of equity shares, aggregating up to Rs 250.8 crore. The objectives of the fresh issue are to utilize Rs 77 crore towards the acquisition of Parekh’s Hospital in Ahmedabad; Rs 12.4 crore will be used for part-payment of the purchase consideration for the already acquired Ashwini Medical Centre; Rs 10.78 crore is earmarked for the acquisition of additional shareholding in the subsidiary, Harmony Medicare, located in Bharuch; Rs 30.09 crore towards funding its capital expenditure requirements; Rs 6.82 crore will be utilized for the purchase of robotics equipment for Gujarat Kidney & Super Specialty Hospital in Vadodara; Rs 1.2 crore will be used for the repayment and/or prepayment of certain outstanding borrowings; and the remaining proceeds will be used for general corporate purposes. The promoters are Dr. Pragnesh Yashwantsinh Bharpoda, Dr. Bhartiben Pragnesh Bharpoda, Dr. Yashwantsingh Motisinh Bharpoda and Anitaben Yashwantsinh Bharpoda. The promoters and promoter group hold an aggregate of 5,63,33,900 equity shares, aggregating to 99.1% of the pre-offer issued and paid-up equity share capital. Their post IPO shareholding is expected to be around 71.45%. Ahead of the IPO, Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality on 22 December 2025, the company raised Rs 100.01 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 87.73 lakh shares at Rs 114 each to 10 anchor investors. Gujarat Kidney & Super Speciality specializes in providing multispeciality healthcare services, including secondary and tertiary care, across multiple locations in Gujarat, India. The company operates seven multispeciality hospitals and four pharmacies with a total bed capacity of 490 beds, an approved capacity of 455 beds, and an operational capacity of 340 beds. Comprehensive medical care is provided across a range of specialty and super-specialty services. Treatment is offered across areas such as internal medicine, general surgery, nephrology, urology, cardiology, and orthopedics, while also focusing on advanced super-specialty care including renal transplantation, vascular surgery, and hematology among others. Healthcare services are categorized as secondary services, which are surgical services, and tertiary Services, which are super speciality surgical services. Central, state and local government bodies contributed 5.46% to its revenue, Insurers through third party administrators 13.9%, and Self-payers and others 80.64% in Q1 FY2026. For the three month ended 30 June 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 4.84 crore and income from operations of Rs 15.26 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper consolidates around five-month high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-consolidates-around-five-month-high/1661905</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661905</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper raced higher in year-end trades, consolidating near five-month highs.

COMEX Copper raced higher in year-end trades, consolidating near five-month highs. Cues from equities are stable. Asian stocks ended mixed on Wednesday, as traders stayed away on the sidelines ahead of Christmas holidays. China's Shanghai Composite index added 0.45% while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index edged up 0.17%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index moved up 0.11% on the day. European stocks rose modestly. The S&P 500 reached a new all-time high on December 24, 2025, extending winning streak to a fourth straight session. The benchmark index gained around 0.5 percent. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.57% while Dow rose 0.16%. Copper is currently trading at $5.63 per pound following this, up 1.50% on the day. The metal has zoomed around 7% this month so far.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices slip in thin pre-Christmas trade; Nifty ends below 26,150]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-slip-in-thin-pre-christmas-trade-nifty-ends-below-26150/1661900</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661900</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domesic equity benchmarks slipped into the red on Wednesday in a quiet, pre-Christmas session marked by light volumes and subdued risk-taking.

Domesic equity benchmarks slipped into the red on Wednesday in a quiet, pre-Christmas session marked by light volumes and subdued risk-taking. Foreign investors turned net sellers, while the absence of fresh cues capped buying interest. Weakness in oil and gas and IT stocks weighed on sentiment. The Nifty gave up early gains after hitting an intraday high of 26,236.40 and ended the day below the 26,150 mark, as traders squared off positions ahead of the holiday break. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 116.14 points or 0.14% to 85,408.70. The Nifty 50 index fell 35.05 points or 0.13% to 26,142.10. Interglobe Aviation (down 1.55%), Adani Enterprises (down 1.37%) and Reliance Industries (down 0.64%) were major Nifty drags. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.37% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 0.14%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,841 shares rose and 2,346 shares fell. A total of 150 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tumbled 1.99% to 9.19. The stock market will be closed tomorrow, 25 December 2025, on account of Christmas. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 1.46% to 6.540 compared with previous session close of 6.637. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.7600 compared with its close of 89.6300 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.32% to Rs 138,325. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.11% to 97.50. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.22% to 4.160. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement rose 14 cents or 0.23% to $62.01 a barrel. Global Markets: European indices saw muted trading on Wednesday during a shortened Christmas Eve session. Asian market ended mixed, breaking ranks with Wall Street that saw key benchmarks advance overnight after better-than-expected economic growth data. Media reports from Japan said that the country was set to issue about 29.6 trillion yen (about $190 billion) in new government bonds to fund its fiscal 2026 budget. The South Korean won strengthened against the greenback after media reports stated that South Korea’s national pension fund was carrying out strategic foreign exchange hedging activities. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose for a fourth straight session as artificial intelligence names continued to outperform during a holiday-shortened week. US GDP grew 4.3% in third quarter compared with 3.8% growth recorded in Second quarter. This is also the highest quarterly GDP growth in the US economy in the past 2 years. The S&P 500 added 0.46%, closing at a record level of 6,909.79. The broad market index is now just below its intraday all-time high of 6,920.34. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.57% to end at 23,561.84. Gains in tech giants such as Nvidia and Broadcom lifted the index. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 79.73 points, or 0.16%, and settled at 48,442.41. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.26%. The company announced that its transportation infrastructure business vertical has secured a significant order for Mumbai metro railway project. As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore. Vikran Engineering jumped 11.24% after the company announced a major solar EPC order win. The company has secured a work order worth Rs 2,035.26 crore from Onix Renewables to set up 600 MW AC solar power projects across multiple locations in Maharashtra. The order will be executed on a turnkey EPC basis. Ceinsys Tech hit an upper limit of 5% after it has bagged three major consultancy assignments from the State Water & Sanitation Mission, Uttar Pradesh, for third party inspection (TPI) & monitoring of rural water supply projects. Based on the company’s estimates linked to the underlying project costs, the total value of work orders for the extended duration is pegged at Rs 107.07 crore. However, the actual contract value will depend on the execution achieved by the respective contractors during the extension period. ITCONS E-Solutions surged 4.28% afyer it announced that it has received a work order worth Rs 1.59 crore from the Directorate of Enforcement, Department of Revenue, Ministry of Finance. The order is for the deployment of 38 resources under manpower outsourcing services. GK Energy jumped 2.96% after the company received an amended Letter of Empanelment from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company. The LoE is for 10,000 off-grid DC solar water pumping systems. The pumps include 3 HP, 5 HP and 7.5 HP variants. They will be supplied across Maharashtra under the Magel Tyala Saur Krushi Pump Yojana and the PM-KUSUM B scheme.The order is valued at Rs 254.30 crore. The installation is to be completed within 60 days from the work order or notice to proceed. Captain Polyplast rallied 3.62% after the company announced that it has received an additional empanelment for 1,000 solar pumps under the PM KUSUM B scheme from MSEDCL, with an aggregate order value of Rs 27.69 crore. Monarch Surveyors and Engineering Consultants added shed 0.42%. The company secured a contract worth Rs 7.83 crore from the Nashik Municipal Corporation. The contract involves carrying out survey and allied works for lands requisitioned for the Sinhastha Kumbh Mela 2027-28 in Nashik and Trimbak. Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals fell 0.83%. The company announced that it has received an order worth Rs 46.20 crore from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company (MSEDCL). The order covers 2,000 solar water pumping systems, with a total work order value of Rs 46,20,48,229. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers & Chemicals (GNFC) dropped 0.30%. The company said that it has awarded a contract worth Rs 0360 crore to Toyo Engineering India for the supply of an Ammonium Nitrate-II plant on a LEPC (lump-sum engineering, procurement & construction) basis. IPO Update: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 6,86,15,936 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:42 IST on Wednesday (24 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 5.19 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concepts-picture-id519261614_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty December futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-december-futures-trade-at-premium/1661898</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661898</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 30 December 2025 futures closed at 26,164.10, a premium of 22 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,142.10 in the cash market.

The Nifty 30 December 2025 futures closed at 26,164.10, a premium of 22 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,142.10 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index declined 35.05 points or 0.13% to 26,142.10. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 1.99% to 9.19. HDFC Bank, Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and Infosys were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The December 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 30 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends with minor losses; VIX slides 1.99%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-with-minor-losses-vix-slides-199/1661897</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661897</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks ended with marginal losses today amid foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and the expiry of Sensex weekly derivatives contracts.

Domestic equity benchmarks ended with marginal losses today amid foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and the expiry of Sensex weekly derivatives contracts. The Nifty closed below the 26,150 level after touching an intraday high of 26,236.40 in morning trade. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 116.14 points or 0.14% to 85,408.70. The Nifty 50 index fell 35.05 points or 0.13% to 26,142.10. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.37% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 0.14%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tumbled 1.99% to 9.19. The stock market will be closed tomorrow, 25 December 2025, on account of Christmas. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Media index (up 0.44%), the Realty index (up 0.17%) and the Nifty Metal (up 0.15%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 0.76%), the Nifty Chemical index (down 0.61%) and the Nifty IT index (down 0.51%), underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: On 23 December 2025, Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated that on a review of current liquidity, it has decided to conduct the operations to inject liquidity into the banking system. It includes open market operations (OMO) purchase auctions of Government of India securities for an aggregate amount of Rs 2,00,000 crore in four tranches of Rs 50,000 crore each to be held on December 29, 2025, January 05, 2026, January 12, 2026, and January 22, 2026 and USD/INR Buy/Sell Swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of 3 years to be held on January 13, 2026. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 1.46% to 6.540 compared with previous session close of 6.637. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.7600 compared with its close of 89.6300 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.32% to Rs 138,325. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.11% to 97.50. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.22% to 4.160. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement rose 14 cents or 0.23% to $62.01 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets saw muted trading on Wednesday during a shortened Christmas Eve session. Asian market ended mixed, breaking ranks with Wall Street that saw key benchmarks advance overnight after better-than-expected economic growth data. Media reports from Japan said that the country was set to issue about 29.6 trillion yen (about $190 billion) in new government bonds to fund its fiscal 2026 budget. The South Korean won strengthened against the greenback after media reports stated that South Korea’s national pension fund was carrying out strategic foreign exchange hedging activities. Spot gold prices hit another record Wednesday, crossing $4,500 per ounce for the first time, driven by a weaker dollar, geopolitical tensions and U.S. Federal Reserve rate-cut expectations. Gold has notched a series of all-time highs this year, soaring over 70% year to date. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose for a fourth straight session as artificial intelligence names continued to outperform during a holiday-shortened week. US GDP grew 4.3% in third quarter compared with 3.8% growth recorded in Second quarter. This is also the highest quarterly GDP growth in the US economy in the past 2 years. The S&P 500 added 0.46%, closing at a record level of 6,909.79. The broad market index is now just below its intraday all-time high of 6,920.34. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.57% to end at 23,561.84. Gains in tech giants such as Nvidia and Broadcom lifted the index. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 79.73 points, or 0.16%, and settled at 48,442.41.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Pharma Index declines 0.51%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-pharma-index-declines-051/1661896</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661896</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Pharma index ended down 0.51% at 22757.4 today.

Nifty Pharma index ended down 0.51% at 22757.4 today. The index is up 1.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Ajanta Pharma Ltd added 2.49%, Gland Pharma Ltd shed 2.24% and Mankind Pharma Ltd dropped 1.63%. The Nifty Pharma index is up 1.00% over last one year compared to the 10.18% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty IT index is down 0.51% and Nifty PSU Bank index is down 0.46% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 0.13% to close at 26142.1 while the SENSEX has dropped 0.14% to close at 85408.7 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty ends below 26,150 mark; oil & gas shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-ends-below-26150-mark-oil-gas-shares-tumble/1661895</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661895</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with minor losses today, amid foreign institutional investors (FII) selling and Sensex's weekly derivatives contract expiry today.

The key equity benchmarks ended with minor losses today, amid foreign institutional investors (FII) selling and Sensex's weekly derivatives contract expiry today. Market participants will closely monitor rupee movement, FII activity, IPO-related developments, and global cues. The Nifty settled below the 26,150 mark after hitting day’s high of 26,236.40 in morning trade. Oil & gas, pharma and It stocks declined while media and metal shares advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 116.14 points or 0.14% to 85,408.70. The Nifty 50 index fell 35.05 points or 0.13% to 26,142.10. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.37% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 0.14%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,843 shares rose and 2,342 shares fell. A total of 152 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tumbled 1.99% to 9.19. The stock market will be closed tomorrow, 25 December 2025, on account of Christmas. IPO Update: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 6,48,11,264 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Wednesday (24 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 4.90 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. Economy: On 23 December 2025, Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated that on a review of current liquidity, it has decided to conduct the operations to inject liquidity into the banking system. It includes open market operations (OMO) purchase auctions of Government of India securities for an aggregate amount of Rs 2,00,000 crore in four tranches of Rs 50,000 crore each to be held on December 29, 2025, January 05, 2026, January 12, 2026, and January 22, 2026 and USD/INR Buy/Sell Swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of 3 years to be held on January 13, 2026. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil& Gas index declined 0.78% to 11,959.40. The index jumped 1.73% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Mahanagar Gas (down 1.33%), Indian Oil Corporation (down 1.32%), Aegis Logistics (down 1.29%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 1.2%), Indraprastha Gas (down 1.19%), Gujarat Gas (down 1.13%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 0.96%), GAIL (India) (down 0.73%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 0.73%) and Reliance Industries (down 0.69%). Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.26%. The company announced that its transportation infrastructure business vertical has secured a significant order for Mumbai metro railway project. As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore. GK Energy jumped 3.39% after the company received an amended Letter of Empanelment from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company. The LoE is for 10,000 off-grid DC solar water pumping systems. The pumps include 3 HP, 5 HP and 7.5 HP variants. They will be supplied across Maharashtra under the Magel Tyala Saur Krushi Pump Yojana and the PM-KUSUM B scheme.The order is valued at Rs 254.30 crore. The installation is to be completed within 60 days from the work order or notice to proceed. Captain Polyplast rallied 3.62% after the company announced that it has received an additional empanelment for 1,000 solar pumps under the PM KUSUM B scheme from MSEDCL, with an aggregate order value of Rs 27.69 crore. Monarch Surveyors and Engineering Consultants added shed 0.42%. The company secured a contract worth Rs 7.83 crore from the Nashik Municipal Corporation. The contract involves carrying out survey and allied works for lands requisitioned for the Sinhastha Kumbh Mela 2027-28 in Nashik and Trimbak. Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals fell 0.83%. The company announced that it has received an order worth Rs 46.20 crore from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company (MSEDCL). The order covers 2,000 solar water pumping systems, with a total work order value of Rs 46,20,48,229. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers & Chemicals (GNFC) dropped 0.30%. The company said that it has awarded a contract worth Rs 0360 crore to Toyo Engineering India for the supply of an Ammonium Nitrate-II plant on a LEPC (lump-sum engineering, procurement & construction) basis. Global Markets: European markets saw muted trading on Wednesday during a shortened Christmas Eve session. Asian market ended mixed, breaking ranks with Wall Street that saw key benchmarks advance overnight after better-than-expected economic growth data. Media reports from Japan said that the country was set to issue about 29.6 trillion yen (about $190 billion) in new government bonds to fund its fiscal 2026 budget. The South Korean won strengthened against the greenback after media reports stated that South Korea’s national pension fund was carrying out strategic foreign exchange hedging activities. Spot gold prices hit another record Wednesday, crossing $4,500 per ounce for the first time, driven by a weaker dollar, geopolitical tensions and U.S. Federal Reserve rate-cut expectations. Gold has notched a series of all-time highs this year, soaring over 70% year to date. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose for a fourth straight session as artificial intelligence names continued to outperform during a holiday-shortened week. US GDP grew 4.3% in third quarter compared with 3.8% growth recorded in Second quarter. This is also the highest quarterly GDP growth in the US economy in the past 2 years. The S&P 500 added 0.46%, closing at a record level of 6,909.79. The broad market index is now just below its intraday all-time high of 6,920.34. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.57% to end at 23,561.84. Gains in tech giants such as Nvidia and Broadcom lifted the index. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 79.73 points, or 0.16%, and settled at 48,442.41.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/USD sustains above 1.3500 mark, FTSE100 up 20% this year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpusd-sustains-above-13500-mark-ftse100-up-20-this-year/1661893</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661893</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound is holding near three-month high against the US dollar.

British Pound is holding near three-month high against the US dollar. UK equities have been stable with the FTSE100 index consolidating around six-week high and rising near 20% this year. GBP/USD pair is quoting at 1.3524, up 0.21% on the day. The pair is up 1% this week. British consumer confidence edged higher in December, reaching its joint-highest level of the year, though sentiment remains weak by historical standards, according to a closely watched monthly survey from GfK. The GfK consumer confidence index rose to -17 in December, matching levels last seen in October and August.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-markets-currency-trading-concept-picture-id609801990_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ceinsys Tech hits the roof after bagging rural water supply consultancy orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ceinsys-tech-hits-the-roof-after-bagging-rural-water-supply-consultancy-orders/1661891</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661891</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The extensions have been awarded through a Quality and Cost Based Selection (QCBS) process and pertain to three clusters—Lucknow, Devipatan and Chitrakoot.

The extensions have been awarded through a Quality and Cost Based Selection (QCBS) process and pertain to three clusters—Lucknow, Devipatan and Chitrakoot. Based on the company’s estimates linked to the underlying project costs, the total value of work orders for the extended duration is pegged at Rs 107.07 crore. However, the actual contract value will depend on the execution achieved by the respective contractors during the extension period. For the Lucknow cluster, the contract has been extended till March 31, 2027, with an estimated work order value of Rs 69.43 crore for the extended period. Ceinsys Tech had originally received the letter of award for this cluster in FY22, which was subsequently extended up to February 28, 2025, and has now been further extended. For the Devipatan cluster, the consultancy contract has also been extended till March 31, 2027, with the estimated value of work during the extension period at Rs 34.28 crore. The original order for this cluster was awarded in FY22 and had earlier been extended up to February 28, 2025. For the Chitrakoot cluster, the extension has been granted till March 31, 2026, with an estimated work order value of Rs 3.36 crore. This contract too was originally awarded in FY22 and extended earlier up to February 28, 2025. Under all three assignments, Ceinsys Tech will act as a consultant for Third Party Inspection and monitoring of physical and financial progress of rural water supply projects, in line with the terms, specifications and conditions stipulated in the original bidding documents issued by SWSM. The contracts have been awarded by a domestic entity and do not fall within related party transactions. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding authority. The extensions further strengthen Ceinsys Tech’s order book and reinforce its presence in the water and sanitation infrastructure segment, particularly in large-scale government-led rural water supply initiatives in Uttar Pradesh. Ceinsys Tech is primarily dealing in providing Enterprise Geospatial & Engineering Services and sale of software and power generation. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 120.9% to Rs 25.74 crore on 81.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 163.45 in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CeinsysTech_6030738597_45949.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude holds around two-week top as rebound sustains on Venezula worries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-holds-around-two-week-top-as-rebound-sustains-on-venezula-worries/1661888</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661888</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures stayed well supported near two-week high above $58 per barrel amid positive cues from equities.

WTI Crude oil futures stayed well supported near two-week high above $58 per barrel amid positive cues from equities. The US stocks hovered around record high amidst sustained uptick in technology stocks. WTI Crude oil is currently trading at $58.45 per barrel, up 0.14% on the day. The US actions against Venezuelan tankers spark fresh supply fears for oil as the US President Donald Trump on Monday said the US will keep crude oil and tankers seized near Venezuela. Falling rig count is also supporting sentiments after oil prices tested near four-year low. Oil is up 3.50% this week. MCX Crude oil futures are also up 0.63% at Rs 5287 per barrel after hitting a high of Rs 5303 per barrel.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Construction Company Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-construction-company-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1661879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661879</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prism Johnson Ltd, Avanti Feeds Ltd, Kajaria Ceramics Ltd and Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 December 2025.

Prism Johnson Ltd, Avanti Feeds Ltd, Kajaria Ceramics Ltd and Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 December 2025. Hindustan Construction Company Ltd lost 4.69% to Rs 18.68 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 36.45 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 43.86 lakh shares in the past one month. Prism Johnson Ltd tumbled 4.45% to Rs 145. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2.3 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 81392 shares in the past one month. Avanti Feeds Ltd crashed 4.00% to Rs 823. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 60292 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 34775 shares in the past one month. Kajaria Ceramics Ltd dropped 3.73% to Rs 977.15. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 24656 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14450 shares in the past one month. Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd plummeted 3.38% to Rs 3306.85. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2869 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10758 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindConstruct_79074190705_245.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps India gains after securing Rs 65-cr solar pump order from MPUVN]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shakti-pumps-india-gains-after-securing-rs-65-cr-solar-pump-order-from-mpuvn/1661878</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661878</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order involves the design, manufacture, supply, transportation, installation, testing and commissioning of 1,897 stand-alone off-grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems under Component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order involves the design, manufacture, supply, transportation, installation, testing and commissioning of 1,897 stand-alone off-grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems under Component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme. The total order value is around Rs 65.20 crore. The company added that the project is scheduled to be executed within 120 days from the date of the work order. Shakti Pumps (India) manufactures solar pumps, energy-efficient stainless-steel submersible pumps, pressure booster pumps, pump motors, and other products. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 10.56% to Rs 90.71 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 101.42 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5% YoY to Rs 666.35 crore in Q2 Sept 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShaktiPumps_14702424257_6580.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Krishival Foods Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/krishival-foods-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1661877</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661877</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd, Rajnish Wellness Ltd, Tijaria Polypipes Ltd and KSR Footwear Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 December 2025.

Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd, Rajnish Wellness Ltd, Tijaria Polypipes Ltd and KSR Footwear Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 December 2025. Krishival Foods Ltd lost 9.99% to Rs 364.45 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 4779 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6901 shares in the past one month. Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd tumbled 8.77% to Rs 118. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 10316 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 613 shares in the past one month. Rajnish Wellness Ltd crashed 8.20% to Rs 0.56. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 327.27 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 76.39 lakh shares in the past one month. Tijaria Polypipes Ltd corrected 7.46% to Rs 4.96. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 34702 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9486 shares in the past one month. KSR Footwear Ltd pared 7.09% to Rs 14.8. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 10669 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 55213 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EmpyreanCashewsLtd_26993846_76458.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KPI Green Energy gains on bagging Rs 128-cr NTPC order for green hydrogen project ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kpi-green-energy-gains-on-bagging-rs-128-cr-ntpc-order-for-green-hydrogen-project/1661876</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661876</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves establishing a 1 tonne-per-day (TPD) green hydrogen plant using plasma-induced radiant energy gasification technology, which converts municipal solid waste (MSW), refuse-derived fuel (RDF) and agricultural waste into synthesis gas for hydrogen production.

The project involves establishing a 1 tonne-per-day (TPD) green hydrogen plant using plasma-induced radiant energy gasification technology, which converts municipal solid waste (MSW), refuse-derived fuel (RDF) and agricultural waste into synthesis gas for hydrogen production. The initiative aims to support waste-to-energy solutions while reducing landfill dependency and environmental impact. The scope of work under the NOAs includes design, engineering, manufacturing and supply of plant and equipment, transportation, erection, installation, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning, along with operation and maintenance of the plant for a period of two years. Civil and structural steel works are also part of the overall project execution, as per NTPC’s bidding documents. The aggregate contract value of the awards stands at Rs 128.49 crore. This marks KPI Green Energy’s entry into the green hydrogen segment and is among the early plasma gasification-based green hydrogen projects in India. The company said the order represents a strategic expansion of its renewable energy portfolio, which currently includes solar, wind and hybrid power projects, and underscores its intent to scale up presence in emerging clean energy technologies such as waste-to-energy and green hydrogen. KPI Green Energy develops, builds, owns, operates, and maintains solar and hybrid power plants as an Independent Power Producer (IPP) and as a service provider to Captive Power Producers (CPP) under the brand name of 'Solarism.' NTPC (National Thermal Power Corporation) along with its subsidiaries/ associates & JVs is primarily involved in generation and sale of bulk power to State power utilities. Other business of the group includes providing consultancy, project management & supervision, energy trading, oil & gas exploration and coal mining. Shares of NTPC fell 0.15% to Rs 322.75 on the NSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/K.P.I.GlobalInfrastructureLtd._85264125_73584.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade in negative terrain; oil & gas shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-in-negative-terrain-oil-gas-shares-tumble/1661875</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661875</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in mid-afternoon trade, amid foreign institutional investors (FII) selling and Sensex's weekly derivatives expiry today.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in mid-afternoon trade, amid foreign institutional investors (FII) selling and Sensex's weekly derivatives expiry today. Market participants will closely monitoring rupee movement, FII activity, IPO-related developments, and global cues. The Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark. Oil & gas shares declined after witnessing buying demand for three consecutive trading sessions. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 115.14 points or 0.14% to 85,411.90. The Nifty 50 index fell 35.85 points or 0.14% to 26,141.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.18% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.02%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,833 shares rose and 2,260 shares fell. A total of 165 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 1.57% to 9.23. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index declined 0.64% to 11,973.95. The Index rose 1.73% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Indraprastha Gas (down 1.18%), Aegis Logistics (down 1.06%), Indian Oil Corporation (down 1%), Mahanagar Gas (down 0.98%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 0.89%), Reliance Industries (down 0.79%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 0.78%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 0.69%), Gujarat Gas (down 0.4%) and Oil India (down 0.39%) declined. Economy: On 23 December 2025, Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated that on a review of current liquidity, it has decided to conduct the operations to inject liquidity into the banking system. It includes open market operations (OMO) purchase auctions of Government of India securities for an aggregate amount of Rs 2,00,000 crore in four tranches of Rs 50,000 crore each to be held on December 29, 2025, January 05, 2026, January 12, 2026, and January 22, 2026 and USD/INR Buy/Sell Swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of 3 years to be held on January 13, 2026. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper declined 1.28% to 6.552 compared with previous session close of 6.637. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.7550 compared with its close of 89.6300 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 1.22% to Rs 138,416. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.26% to 98.01. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.26% to 4.158. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement fell 4 cents or 0.06% to $62.03 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: GK Energy jumped 3.13% to Rs 156.60 after the company received an amended Letter of Empanelment from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI announces sale of dated Government Securities for Rs 32000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-announces-sale-of-dated-government-securities-for-rs-32000-crore/1661873</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661873</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Government of India has announced the sale (re-issue) of Government Securities for a total of Rs 32000 crore through auction to be held on December 26, 2025.

Government of India has announced the sale (re-issue) of Government Securities for a total of Rs 32000 crore through auction to be held on December 26, 2025. These consist of 5.91% GS 2028 (Rs 9,000 crore), 6.28% GS 2032 (Rs 11,000 crore) and 7.24% GS 2055 (Rs 12,000 crore).

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dev IT bags Rs 9-cr orders across government, enterprise segments]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dev-it-bags-rs-9-cr-orders-across-government-enterprise-segments/1661874</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661874</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said it has received an order worth Rs 6.97 crore from the Knowledge Consortium of Gujarat, a Government of Gujarat entity.

In an exchange filing, the company said it has received an order worth Rs 6.97 crore from the Knowledge Consortium of Gujarat, a Government of Gujarat entity. The contract involves Microsoft Office Suite–based automation across government educational institutions and is scheduled to be completed on or before 5 February 2026. The company has also bagged an order worth Rs 0.93 crore from National Informatics Centre Services Incorporated (NICSI). The scope of work includes application software and website development for the Bureau of Indian Standards, New Delhi, with an expected execution period of around six months. Additionally, Dev Information Technology secured an enterprise segment order worth Rs 0.71 crore from Vishakha Group. This project includes enterprise software licensing, migration of over 550 users, and IT infrastructure implementation and is expected to be executed within three to four months. The company said these order wins are expected to improve resource utilisation across its delivery teams and drive steady execution, operating leverage, and disciplined growth. The balanced mix of government and enterprise contracts also reinforces Dev IT’s positioning in large-scale ABCD (AI, Blockchain, Cybersecurity, Data) digital transformation programs. Pranav Pandya, founder & chairman, said, "We are encouraged by the steady momentum in order inflows across government and enterprise segments, which strengthens our near-term order book visibility. We will continue to prioritize timely execution and delivery quality.” Dev Information Technology (Dev IT) is in the business of providing IT-enabled services. The company's consolidated net profit climbed 786.3% to Rs 71.88 crore on a 35% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 48.51 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DevInformationTechnologyLtd_93091952440_70312.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>