<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI says banking sector remained resilient, highlights strengthening asset quality]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-says-banking-sector-remained-resilient-highlights-strengthening-asset-quality/1662292</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662292</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India released the Report on Trend and Progress of Banking in India 2024-25.

The Reserve Bank of India released the Report on Trend and Progress of Banking in India 2024-25. This Report presents the performance of the banking sector, including commercial banks, co-operative banks and non-banking financial institutions, during 2024-25 and 2025-26 so far. It noted that the Indian commercial banking sector remained resilient during 2024-25, supported by double-digit balance sheet expansion. Deposits and credit of scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) grew in double digits, albeit with a moderation from the previous year. The capital to risk weighted assets ratio of SCBs was 17.4 per cent at end-March 2025 and 17.2 per cent at end-September 2025. Asset quality strengthened further, with the gross non-performing assets (GNPA) ratio declining to a multi-decadal low of 2.2 per cent at end-March 2025 and 2.1 per cent at end-September 2025. Profitability of the SCBs remained robust with the return on assets (RoA) at 1.4 per cent and return on equity (RoE) at 13.5 per cent in 2024-25. During H1: 2025-26, RoA and RoE of the SCBs stood at 1.3 per cent and 12.5 per cent, respectively. The consolidated balance sheet of urban co-operative banks recorded higher growth in 2024-25 than that in the previous year. Their asset quality improved for the fourth consecutive year, alongside strengthening of their capital buffers and profitability. The non-banking financial companies continued to record double digit credit growth along with robust capital buffers. Their asset quality also improved during the year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-growth-1-1057028_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper crashes after 5% spike in last session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-crashes-after-5-spike-in-last-session/1662290</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662290</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures melted today, giving up after sharp gains in last session as metals saw selling pressure amid year-end trades.

COMEX Copper futures melted today, giving up after sharp gains in last session as metals saw selling pressure amid year-end trades. Asian stock markets recorded a mixed performance on Monday amidst a weak sentiment reflected in Wall Street Futures and rising geopolitical tensions. China's Shanghai Composite Index closed flat while the Hang Seng Index of the Hong Kong fell 0.71%. The Japanese benchmark Nikkei 225 lost 0.51%. COMEX Copper futures are trading at $5.60 per pound, down 4.10% on the day, giving up near 5% rally in last session. The metal is up 6% in December-25. MCX Copper futures are trading at Rs 1246 per kg, down 2.40% on the day after a freakish opening near Rs 1400 per kg.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee slips back to 90-mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-slips-back-to-90-mark/1662286</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662286</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.3600 per Dollar on Monday (29 December 2025), versus its previous close of 89.9050 per Dollar last Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slips 346 pts, Nifty slips below 25,950 amid FII outflows, thin year-end trade]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slips-346-pts-nifty-slips-below-25950-amid-fii-outflows-thin-year-end-trade/1662283</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662283</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks closed lower on Monday, with the Sensex and Nifty giving up early gains as muted year-end trading volumes and sustained foreign fund outflows curbed risk appetite.

Domestic equity benchmarks closed lower on Monday, with the Sensex and Nifty giving up early gains as muted year-end trading volumes and sustained foreign fund outflows curbed risk appetite. Investors stayed cautious ahead of the upcoming Q3 corporate earnings season. The Nifty settled below the 25,950 mark after touching an intraday high of 26,106.80, weighed down by weakness in consumer durables and IT stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 345.91 points or 0.41% to 84,695.54. The Nifty 50 index lost 100.20 points or 0.38% to 25,942.10. Adani Ports & SEZ (down 2.27%), Reliance Industries (down 0.8%) and ICICI Bank (down 0.5%) were major drags today. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.45% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.58%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,568 shares rose and 2,748 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s Index of Industrial Production (IIP) grew 6.7% year-on-year in November, accelerating from the upwardly revised 0.5% increase in the previous month. Growth was noted in manufacturing (8% vs 2% in October) on higher output of basic and fabricated metal products, pharmaceuticals, and motor vehicles. Growth was also sharp for mining (5.4% vs -1.8%) as the closure of the monsoon season supported operations. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.11% to 6.567 as compared with the previous close of 6.560. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9850 compared with its close of 89.9000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement fell 0.98% to Rs 138,507. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.01% to 98.03. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.56% to 4.108. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added $1.24 or 2.04% to $61.88 a barrel. Prices of spot silver rose to a fresh record high of above $80 per ounce before pulling back sharply to $77. Silver’s recent surge was driven by speculative buying and lingering supply tightness, said experts. Media report further stated silver’s rally this year reflects a depletion of freely traded inventory, amplifying price moves as demand increases. Global Markets: European market advanced, while most Asian market ended mixed on Monday as investors kicked off the final trading week of the year. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 reached a new high and posted weekly gains as traders came back from the Christmas holiday. The broad market index closed down 0.03% to end at 6,929.94. At its high, the S&P 500 was up 0.2%, reaching 6,945.77. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.09% and closed at 23,593.10. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 20.19 points, or 0.04%, and settled at 48,710.97. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.17%. The company announced that its transportation infrastructure business vertical has secured a significant order for Hyderabad Greenfield Radial Road. Solarworld Energy Solutions climbed 5.64% after the company announced that it has received a letter of award for the EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project worth Rs 725.33 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy. Coforge rose 0.55%. The company said that it has signed definitive agreements to acquire Encora, an AI native firm born in the Silicon Valley with deep strengths across AI driven engineering underlaid by Cloud and Data. Siyaram Recycling Industries added 1.55% after the company has secured a significant order from The Supreme Industries, Jalgaon (F) – MDP, for the supply of 1/2" female insert (new modified) and female insert 1/2" CPVC/aqua topper. Sigachi Industries fell 4.89% after the company disclosed that its managing director and chief executive officer Amit Raj Sinha has been remanded in connection with a fire incident at its Hyderabad unit. Timex Group India fell 6.33% after the company’s promoter announced an offer for sale to reduce its stake. Promoter Timex Group Luxury Watches BV is offering a base lot of 45.09 lakh shares, representing 4.47% of the company’s equity. The offer includes an oversubscription option for an additional 4.47%, taking the total potential divestment to 90.18 lakh shares, or 8.93%. The floor price has been set at Rs 275 per share, a discount of 21.82% to the stock’s previous close of Rs 351.75 on 26 December 2025. The discounted pricing and large offer size weighed on investor sentiment. Ceigall India gained 3.56% after the company’s subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects has received a LoA from Madhya Pradesh Road Development Corporation for the construction of the Indore-Ujjain access-controlled four-lane greenfield highway. Vikran Engineering rose 2.58% after it has secured letter of awards (LoA) from M.P. Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of power plants with a total capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh. Jindal Steel rose 0.50%. The company announced a significant expansion of its structural steel manufacturing capabilities at its Raigarh facility. This expansion would double the company’s existing structural steel capacity from 1.2 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) to 2.4 MTPA by mid 2028. VA Tech Wabag declined 1.62%. The company has received a letter of award from the Saudi Water Authority for a large repeat EPC order to build a 50 MLD advanced BWRO plant at Aljouf, Saudi Arabia.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JPY/INR futures fall slightly to settle at 57.40]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jpyinr-futures-fall-slightly-to-settle-at-5740/1662282</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662282</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures added gains to end at 90.35.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures added gains to end at 90.35. EUR/INR and GBP/INR also gained marginally to settle at 106.46 and 121.93 respectively. Meanwhile, JPY/INR futures slipped 0.17% to close at 57.40.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR slides amid sustained foreign fund outflows ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-slides-amid-sustained-foreign-fund-outflows/1662281</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662281</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee depreciated eight paise to close at 89.98 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday, weighed down by foreign fund outflows and a negative trend in domestic equities.

The Indian rupee depreciated eight paise to close at 89.98 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday, weighed down by foreign fund outflows and a negative trend in domestic equities. India's benchmark indexes Sensex and the Nifty50 ended weak on Monday, as sustained selling by foreign portfolio investors weighed on stocks. The benchmark BSE Sensex settled at 84,695.54, losing 345.91 points or 0.41%, while the National Stock Exchange's Nifty50 ended with a loss of 100.20 points or 0.38% at 25,942.10. The Sensex extended its losing streak to a fourth straight session. Persistent capital withdrawals from foreign investors, alongside heightened dollar demand from importers, dented investor sentiments. At the interbank foreign exchange, the local unit opened at 89.95 against the dollar and touched an intra-day low of

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's industrial production grows 6.7% in November]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-industrial-production-grows-67-in-november/1662276</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662276</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to the data released by the Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation, India's industrial production as shown by the index of Industrial Production (IIP) recorded a 6.7 % year-on-year growth in November 2025, driven by 8.0% growth in manufacturing sector.

According to the data released by the Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation, India's industrial production as shown by the index of Industrial Production (IIP) recorded a 6.7 % year-on-year growth in November 2025, driven by 8.0% growth in manufacturing sector. The growth is led by Manufacture of basic metals and fabricated metal products, pharmaceuticals and motor vehicles. Growth in the Mining sector at 5.4% has also rebounded due to closure of monsoon season and strong growth in metallic minerals such as Iron ore. The growth rates of the three sectors, Mining, Manufacturing and Electricity for the month of November 2025 are 5.4 percent, 8.0 percent and (-)1.5 percent respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/female-manager-working-on-tablet-in-factory-picture-id52704_commodities.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude sees steady action]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-sees-steady-action/1662274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662274</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures are witnessing sustained gains, staying near two-week high above $58 per barrel amid positive cues from equities.

WTI Crude oil futures are witnessing sustained gains, staying near two-week high above $58 per barrel amid positive cues from equities. The US stocks hovered around record high amidst sustained uptick in technology stocks. The US actions against Venezuelan tankers spark fresh supply fears for oil and new worries are emerging now after the US attacks on Nigeria. Falling rig count is also supporting sentiments after oil prices tested near four-year low. US demand outlook also remains steady. A report released by the Commerce Department showed the US economy grew steadily in the third quarter of 2025. The Commerce Department said real gross domestic product spiked by 4.3% in the third quarter after surging by 3.8% in the second quarter. The stronger GDP growth in the third quarter reflected increases in consumer spending, exports, and government spending that were partly offset by a decrease in investment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-on-the-north-sea-picture-id48328_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty December futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-december-futures-trade-at-premium/1662275</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662275</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 30 December 2025 futures closed at 25,955.80, a premium of 13.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,942.10 in the cash market.

The Nifty 30 December 2025 futures closed at 25,955.80, a premium of 13.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,942.10 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index declined 100.20 points or 0.38% to 25,942.10. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 6.22% to 9.72. HDFC Bank, Reliance Industries and ICICI Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The December 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 30 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 346 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,950]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-346-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25950/1662269</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662269</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended with modest cuts today amid persistent foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and a weakening rupee while investors remained cautious ahead of the upcoming corporate earnings season.

The key equity indices ended with modest cuts today amid persistent foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and a weakening rupee while investors remained cautious ahead of the upcoming corporate earnings season. The Nifty settled below the 25,950 mark after touching the day’s high of 26,106.80 in early trade. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 345.91 points or 0.41% to 84,695.54. The Nifty 50 index lost 100.20 points or 0.38% to 25,942.10. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.45% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.58%. The market breadth was weak. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Media index (up 0.93%), the Nifty FMCG index (up 0.11%) and the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 0.05%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Consumer Durables index (down 0.91%), the Nifty IT index (down 0.75%) and the Nifty Realty index (down 0.67%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.11% to 6.567 as compared with the previous close of 6.560. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9850 compared with its close of 89.9000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement fell 0.98% to Rs 138,507. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.01% to 98.03. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.56% to 4.108. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added $1.24 or 2.04% to $61.88 a barrel. Global Markets: European market declined, while most Asian markets ended higher on Monday as investors kicked off the final trading week of the year. Prices of spot silver rose to a fresh record high of above $80 per ounce before pulling back sharply to $77. Silver’s recent surge was driven by speculative buying and lingering supply tightness, said experts. Media report further stated silver’s rally this year reflects a depletion of freely traded inventory, amplifying price moves as demand increases. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 reached a new high and posted weekly gains as traders came back from the Christmas holiday. The broad market index closed down 0.03% to end at 6,929.94. At its high, the S&P 500 was up 0.2%, reaching 6,945.77. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.09% and closed at 23,593.10. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 20.19 points, or 0.04%, and settled at 48,710.97.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Media Index gains 0.93%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-media-index-gains-093/1662268</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662268</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Media index ended up 0.93% at 1424.05 today.

Nifty Media index ended up 0.93% at 1424.05 today. The index has slipped 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Nazara Technologies Ltd rose 6.70%, Prime Focus Ltd shed 3.16% and Network 18 Media & Investments Ltd dropped 2.48%. The Nifty Media index has fallen 23.00% over last one year compared to the 8.94% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty IT index has dropped 0.75% and Nifty Realty index has dropped 0.67% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 0.38% to close at 25942.1 while the SENSEX has slid 0.41% to close at 84695.54 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-mutual-funds-picture-id157281690_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty ends below 25,950 mark; consumer durables shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-ends-below-25950-mark-consumer-durables-shares-decline/1662266</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662266</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with modest losses today amid persistent foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and a weakening rupee while investors remained cautious ahead of upcoming corporate earnings season.

The key equity barometers ended with modest losses today amid persistent foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and a weakening rupee while investors remained cautious ahead of upcoming corporate earnings season. The Nifty settled below the 25,950 mark after touching day’s high of 26,106.80 in early trade. Media, FMCG and PSU Bank shares advanced while consumer durables, IT and realty shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 345.91 points or 0.41% to 84,695.54. The Nifty 50 index lost 100.20 points or 0.38% to 25,942.10. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.45% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.58%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,579 shares rose and 2,730 shares fell. A total of 212 shares were unchanged. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9725 compared with its close of 89.9000 during the previous trading session. Economy: The Index of Industrial Production (IIP) grew 6.7% year-on-year in November, compared with a 0.4% expansion in October, marking a two-year high in factory output. Growth was led by the manufacturing sector, which expanded 8%, driven by higher production of basic and fabricated metal products, pharmaceuticals, and motor vehicles. Improved performance in the mining sector also supported the overall rise in IIP, with output increasing 5.4% in November compared with a contraction of 1.8% in October. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index declined 0.91% to 36,487.40. The index rose 0.34% in the past trading session. Dixon Technologies (India) (down 3.93%), Amber Enterprises India (down 2.35%), Blue Star (down 1.98%), PG Electroplast (down 1.25%) and Kalyan Jewellers India (down 1.1%), Century Plyboards (India) (down 0.97%), Bata India (down 0.96%), Cera Sanitaryware (down 0.79%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (down 0.74%) and Kajaria Ceramics (down 0.44%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.26%. The company announced that its transportation infrastructure business vertical has secured a significant order for Hyderabad Greenfield Radial Road. Coforge rose 0.22%. The company said that it has signed definitive agreements to acquire Encora, an AI native firm born in the Silicon Valley with deep strengths across AI driven engineering underlaid by Cloud and Data. Siyaram Recycling Industries added 1.55% after the company has secured a significant order from The Supreme Industries, Jalgaon (F) – MDP, for the supply of 1/2" female insert (new modified) and female insert 1/2" CPVC/aqua topper. Ceigall India gained 2.91% after the company’s subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects has received a LoA from Madhya Pradesh Road Development Corporation for the construction of the Indore–Ujjain access-controlled four-lane greenfield highway. Vikran Engineering rose 2.23% after it has secured letter of awards (LoA) from M.P. Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of power plants with a total capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh. Jindal Steel rose 0.50%. The company announced a significant expansion of its structural steel manufacturing capabilities at its Raigarh facility. This expansion would double the company’s existing structural steel capacity from 1.2 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) to 2.4 MTPA by mid 2028. VA Tech Wabag declined 1.62%. The company has received a letter of award from the Saudi Water Authority for a large repeat EPC order to build a 50 MLD advanced BWRO plant at Aljouf, Saudi Arabia. Solarworld Energy Solutions climbed 4.11% after the company announced that it has received a letter of award for the EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project worth Rs 725.33 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy. Global Markets: European market declined, while most Asian markets ended higher on Monday as investors kicked off the final trading week of the year. Prices of spot silver rose to a fresh record high of above $80 per ounce before pulling back sharply to $77. Silver’s recent surge was driven by speculative buying and lingering supply tightness, said experts. Media report further stated silver’s rally this year reflects a depletion of freely traded inventory, amplifying price moves as demand increases. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 reached a new high and posted weekly gains as traders came back from the Christmas holiday. The broad market index closed down 0.03% to end at 6,929.94. At its high, the S&P 500 was up 0.2%, reaching 6,945.77. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.09% and closed at 23,593.10. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 20.19 points, or 0.04%, and settled at 48,710.97.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan Bank receives RBI nod for reappointment of Executive Director ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-bank-receives-rbi-nod-for-reappointment-of-executive-director/1662261</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662261</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank said the reappointment of Kesh as Executive Director and Chief Operating Officer, and as Key Managerial Personnel, will be subject to approval by the shareholders at the ensuing general meeting.

The bank said the reappointment of Kesh as Executive Director and Chief Operating Officer, and as Key Managerial Personnel, will be subject to approval by the shareholders at the ensuing general meeting. He will be liable to retire by rotation. The bank clarified that Kesh is not related to any of the other directors of the bank. It also stated that he has not been debarred or disqualified from holding the office of director by any order of the Securities and Exchange Board of India or any other regulatory authority. Bandhan Bank is a private sector bank. Its distribution network spans nearly 6,350 outlets. It added 9 lakh customers during the quarter, and current customers stand at over 3.23 crore customers. The bank currently has over 73,500 employees. The bank’s net profit plunged 88.1% year-on-year to Rs 112 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 937 crore in Q2 FY25, primarily due to a steep rise in provisions. Net total income declined 11.5% YoY to Rs 3,135 crore from Rs 3,543 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. The scrip rose 0.93% to Rs 146.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BandhanBankLtd_94952261769_68090.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waa Solar hits the roof after bagging Rs 225-cr solar project from MPUVNL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waa-solar-hits-the-roof-after-bagging-rs-225-cr-solar-project-from-mpuvnl/1662260</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662260</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is part of the Surya Mitra Krishi Feeders Scheme, with a feeder solarisation component under the PM-KUSUM-C scheme.

The project is part of the Surya Mitra Krishi Feeders Scheme, with a feeder solarisation component under the PM-KUSUM-C scheme. The project involves development of solar power plants for the sale of electricity to Madhya Pradesh Power Management Company (MPPMCL). The contract is a domestic order and is required to be executed within 18 months from the date of signing of the Power Purchase Agreement (PPA). The company clarified that neither the promoters nor the promoter group have any interest in MPUVNL, and the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions. Waa Solar is mainly engaged in solar power generation by setting up Solar Power Project companies which are engaged in solar power generation activities. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 5.1% to Rs 6.97 crore in FY26, on a 5.8% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 28.25 crore, compared with FY25. As of 29 Decemeber 2025, the company's market cap stood at Rs 73.79 crore in the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WaaSolarLtd_21004299397_72526.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ACME Solar Holdings gains after incorporating new renewable energy subsidiary]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acme-solar-holdings-gains-after-incorporating-new-renewable-energy-subsidiary/1662272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662272</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to the company’s exchange filing, ACME Greentech Nineteen was incorporated on 23 December 2025 and has its registered office in Gurugram, Haryana, India.

According to the company’s exchange filing, ACME Greentech Nineteen was incorporated on 23 December 2025 and has its registered office in Gurugram, Haryana, India. The subsidiary has been incorporated with the objective of undertaking businesses related to the development, establishment, and operation of power generation and renewable energy projects. ACME Solar Holdings has subscribed to 100% of the initial paid-up share capital of the subsidiary in cash, amounting to Rs 1 lakh, comprising 10,000 equity shares of face value Rs 10 each. ACME Solar Holdings is a fully integrated renewable energy company in India with a diversified portfolio across solar, wind, storage, hybrid and Firm and Dispatchable Renewable Energy (FDRE) projects. The company’s consolidated net profit stood at Rs 115.06 crore in Q2 FY26, up 652.51% as against Rs 15.29 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 80.18% YoY to Rs 467.74 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ACMESolarHoldingsLtd_41904745_71636.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts ease from six year high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-ease-from-six-year-high/1662258</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662258</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a six high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

Large currency speculators reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a six high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 48498 contracts in the data reported through December 16, 2025. This was a weekly drop of 27017 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[All Australian tariff lines to go zero-duty for Indian exports from January 1: Piyush Goyal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/all-australian-tariff-lines-to-go-zero-duty-for-indian-exports-from-january-1-piyush-goyal/1662259</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662259</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal said all Australian tariff lines for Indian exports will become zero-duty from January 1, opening new opportunities for labour-intensive sectors.

Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal said all Australian tariff lines for Indian exports will become zero-duty from January 1, opening new opportunities for labour-intensive sectors. Marking three years of the India-Australia Economic Cooperation & Trade Agreement (Ind-Aus ECTA), he said the pact has boosted exports, expanded market access, and strengthened supply chains. India’s exports to Australia rose 8% in 2024-25, improving the trade balance, with strong growth across manufacturing, chemicals, textiles, pharmaceuticals, petroleum products, and gems and jewellery. Gems and jewellery exports rose 16% between April and November, while agri-exports saw broad-based growth, led by fruits, vegetables, marine products, spices, and coffee.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Green Energy arm incorporates new renewable energy subsidiary]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-green-energy-arm-incorporates-new-renewable-energy-subsidiary/1662257</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662257</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to the company’s exchange filing, ERL was incorporated on 26 December 2025 and is registered with the Registrar of Companies, Gujarat, at Ahmedabad.

According to the company’s exchange filing, ERL was incorporated on 26 December 2025 and is registered with the Registrar of Companies, Gujarat, at Ahmedabad. The new entity is yet to commence its business operations. The primary objective of ERL is to generate, develop, distribute, transmit, sell, and supply power using renewable energy sources such as solar, wind and other clean energy technologies. Adani Renewable Energy Holding Eleven Limited holds 100% of the share capital of ERL. The newly incorporated subsidiary has an authorised capital of Rs 1 lakh and a paid-up capital of Rs 1 lakh. Adani Green Energy is India’s largest and one of the leading renewable energy companies in the world enabling the clean energy transition. It develops, owns, and operates utility scale grid-connected solar, wind, hybrid and hydro pumped storage renewable power plants. The company has set a target of achieving 50 GW by 2030 aligned to India’s decarbonization goals. The company reported a 111.2% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 583 crore despite of 5.3% decline in net sales to Rs 2,824 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter slipped 1.29% to Rs 1,004.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniGreenEnergyLtd_74416007001_70666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Gold off record highs on Monday]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-gold-off-record-highs-on-monday/1662256</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662256</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Gold futures eased today, coming off record high.

COMEX Gold futures eased today, coming off record high. The metal jumped to a record high on Friday, witnessing excellent buying support on safe-haven demand and rising expectations of further interest rate cuts by the US Federal Reserve. The US dollar index is trading in a very lax manner and is down around 1.60% this month. COMEX Gold futures soared 4% last week. Indian spot retail demand in thin right now and a meaningful pick-up could be seen only after the year-end. Meanwhile, the US President Donald Trump has said that he expects the next chairman of the US Federal Reserve to keep interest rates low and never disagree with him. This is keeping overall mood upbeat for the bullion counters. Gold has soared sharply after an escalation in tensions between the United States and Venezuela. The yellow metal currently trades at $4498 per ounce, down 1.20% on the day. MCX Gold futures are also down 1% at Rs 138459 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s growth momentum backed by domestic drivers-led by robust private consumption]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-growth-momentum-backed-by-domestic-drivers-led-by-robust-private-consumption/1662254</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662254</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Government has highlighted in a latest update that India is among the world’s fastest-growing major economies and is well-positioned to sustain this momentum.

Government has highlighted in a latest update that India is among the world’s fastest-growing major economies and is well-positioned to sustain this momentum. With the ambition of attaining high middle-income status by 2047- the centenary year of its independence- the country is building on strong foundations of economic growth, structural reforms, and social progress. With GDP valued at USD 4. 18 trillion, India has surpassed Japan to become the world’s fourth-largest economy and is poised to displace Germany from the third rank in the next 2.5 to 3 years with projected GDP of USD 7.3 trillion by 2030. The growth momentum further surprised on the upside, with GDP expanding to a six-quarter high in Q2 of 2025-26, reflecting India’s resilience amid persistent global trade uncertainties. Domestic drivers-led by robust private consumption-played a central role in supporting this expansion. High-frequency indicators point to sustained economic activity: inflation remains below the lower tolerance threshold, unemployment is on a declining trajectory, and export performance continues to improve. Furthermore, financial conditions have stayed benign, with strong credit flows to the commercial sector, while demand conditions remain firm, supported by a further strengthening of urban consumption. India’s real GDP grew 8.2% in Q2 FY 2025-26, up from 7.8% in the previous quarter and 7.4% in Q4 of 2024-25, led by resilient domestic demand amidst global trade and policy uncertainties. Real gross value added (GVA) expanded by 8.1%, catalysed by buoyant industrial and services sectors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-petrochemical-plant-equipment-picture-id627839_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>