<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:15:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dsp-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1662160</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662160</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026.

DSP Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) DSP Credit Risk Fund Mr. Vivek Ramakrishnan Ms. Shalini Vasanta Mr. Vivek Ramakrishnan Ms. Shalini Vasanta Mr. Kunal Khudania DSP Liquidity Fund Mr. Karan Mundhra Ms. Shalini Vasanta Mr. Karan Mundhra Ms. Shalini Vasanta Mr. Kunal Khudania DSP Overnight Fund Mr. Karan Mundhra Ms. Shalini Vasanta Mr. Karan Mundhra Ms. Shalini Vasanta Mr. Shantanu Godambe

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-scheme/1662158</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662158</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from January 1, 2026.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from January 1, 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager New Fund Manager ICICI Prudential Business Cycle Fund • Anish Tawakley • Manish Banthia • Manan Tijoriwala • Anish Tawakley • Manish Banthia • Manan Tijoriwala • Divya Jain ICICI Prudential Dynamic Asset Allocation Active FOF (Erstwhile ICICI Prudential Asset Allocator (FOF)) • Sankaran Naren • Dharmesh Kakkad • Manish Bhantia • Ritesh Lunawat • Dharmesh Kakkad • Manish Bhantia • Ritesh Lunawat • Sharmila D’silva

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PPFAS Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ppfas-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1662153</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662153</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PPFAS Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

PPFAS Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Darsh Thakker has been appointed as Deputy Manager - Debt Dealer and shall be a Key Personnel of that the Board of Directors of PPFAS Asset Management Private Limited with effect from December 15, 2025. Details of Mr. Darsh Thakker Age: 26 years Designation: Deputy Manager - Debt Dealer Qualification: M.B.A in Finance B.Com

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Navi Mutual Fund announces change in scheme name]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/navi-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-scheme-name/1662152</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662152</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Navi Mutual Fund has announced change in scheme name under the following schemes, with immediate effect: Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in the name of the Scheme: Existing Scheme Name Revised Scheme Name Navi US Nasdaq 100 FoF Navi Nasdaq100 US Specific Equity Passive FOF Navi US Total Stock Market FoF Navi Total Stock Market US Specific Equity Passive FoF

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/aktienkurse-analog-und-digital-picture-id672450302_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICRA revises ratings outlook of Rama Phosphates to ‘stable’; reaffirms ratings at 'A-/A2+']]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icra-revises-ratings-outlook-of-rama-phosphates-to-stable-reaffirms-ratings-at-a-a2/1662149</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662149</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at '[ICRA] A2+’.

The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at '[ICRA] A2+’. ICRA stated that the revision in the outlook factors in an improvement in the company’s overall credit profile, supported by a strong recovery in operating performance in FY2025 and H1 FY2026. The remunerative subsidy rates and retail prices for single super phosphate (SSP) supported the improved performance. Additionally, there has been a sharp uptick in profitability from the sale of sulphuric acid amid its constrained availability in the domestic market. As a result, the credit metrics are expected to witness a significant improvement in FY2026. ICRA expects RPL’s profitability to remain healthy, given the Government of India's (GoI’s) focus on maintaining adequate availability of fertilisers and RPL’s backward integrated operations supported by sulphuric acid manufacturing, which will keep the credit metrics stable. ICRA notes that the company is in the final stages of commissioning the Dhule plant, wherein the company is adding 0.22 MMT of SSP capacity. The commissioning of the Dhule plant in March 2026 will help scale up the revenue FY2027 onwards. The company is also looking to set up a sulphuric acid manufacturing capacity of 90,000 MT at Dhule in FY2027 at a total capital outlay of Rs 30 crore, to be funded through a term loan of Rs. 20 crore and the rest from internal accruals. ICRA expects the company to maintain a stable credit profile while incurring the aforementioned capex. The ratings assigned to the bank lines of RPL continue to factor in the company’s established presence as a manufacturer of SSP fertiliser acrossMaharashtra, Madhya Pradesh, Rajasthan, Karnataka, Gujarat, Uttar Pradesh, Haryana, etc. The ratings favourably consider the extensive experience of the promoters of more than five decades in the fertiliser and chemical businesses along with a diversified product portfolio comprising phosphate fertilisers, sulphuric acid and soya-based products. The ratings also factor in the integrated operations of the company wherein it also manufactures sulphuric acid which is usedas an input for manufacturing SSP. The backward integration ensures assured availability of the raw materialfor the company. The capital structure remains comfortable, with total debt-to-OPBDITA expected to remain in the range of 1.2x–1.5x, despite the ongoing capex for capacity expansion. The ratings, however, are constrained by the volatility in raw material prices, majorly rock phosphate and sulphuric acid along with volatility in the foreign exchange rates. The profitability remains vulnerable to foreign currency riskas a large part of the rock phosphate requirement and some part of the sulphur requirement is met through imports while the company does not hedge its forex exposure. Further, the overall realisations on the sale of SSP comprise subsidy payable by the GoI and the retail price. The subsidy rates are usually fixed for a period of six months and there is limited flexibility in revising the retail prices owing to the price sensitive nature of the end user i.e. farmers. Hence, the company’s profitability remains exposed to the volatility in raw material prices. The company’s profitability is also exposed to regulatory risks pertaining to the announcement of subsidy by the GoI, which is a key driver of the industry’s profitability. This, along with the schedule of the subsidy release, determines the working capital cycle of fertiliser companies. The company is also present in the soya oil division which involves the sale of unrefined soya oil and de-oiled soya cakes as animal feed. The segment has been posting minor losses for the last few yearsand the subdued performance is expected to continue amid volatile prices for soya oil. RPL manufactures phosphatic fertilisers -single super phosphate (SSP), fortified fertilisers namely boronated SSP as well as sulphuric acid and its derivatives. It also has a soya oil division which is engaged in the extraction of soya oil. The scrip had fallen 2.50% to end at Rs 159.75 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RamaPhosphates_71626639238_1473.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel secures Rs 20-cr order from MEA for Data Centre in Ethiopia]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-secures-rs-20-cr-order-from-mea-for-data-centre-in-ethiopia/1662147</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662147</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the project involves providing implementation services for setting up a data centre inside the existing building of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Federal Democratic Republic of Ethiopia.

According to an exchange filing, the project involves providing implementation services for setting up a data centre inside the existing building of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Federal Democratic Republic of Ethiopia. The order valued at Rs 19.83 crore, is scheduled to be completed by 25 December 2029. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It also stated that the transaction does not constitute a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. RailTel Corporation, a "Navratna" PSU, is one of the largest neutral telecom infrastructure providers in the country, owning a Pan-India optical fiber network. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 4.72% to Rs 76.07 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 72.64 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 12.78% YoY to Rs 951.36 crore in Q2 FY26. The counter jumped 6.03% to end at Rs 378.05 on Friday, 26 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crisil Ratings reaffirms ratings of LG Electronics at 'AAA/A1+']]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crisil-ratings-reaffirms-ratings-of-lg-electronics-at-aaaa1/1662145</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662145</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Crisil Ratings stated that the company’s revenue remained flattish in the first half of fiscal 2026 due to moderation in sales of cooling appliances (ACs and refrigerators) in the first quarter led by early onset of monsoon and goods and services tax (GST)-related sale deferrals in the second quarter of fiscal 2026.

Crisil Ratings stated that the company’s revenue remained flattish in the first half of fiscal 2026 due to moderation in sales of cooling appliances (ACs and refrigerators) in the first quarter led by early onset of monsoon and goods and services tax (GST)-related sale deferrals in the second quarter of fiscal 2026. The revenue is expected to start picking momentum in the second half of fiscal 2026, driven by GST rate cuts, wedding & festive season and upcoming summer seasons. The operating margin improved by nearly 2% to 12.8% in fiscal 2025 due to softening of raw material prices and economies of scale. However, the margin moderated to 10.2% in the first half of fiscal 2026 due to elevated commodity prices and strong festive promotions amid weak demand, which led to increase in discounts amidst intense competition. The company has taken price hikes of 2% post festive period in some of the product category, which along with expected stable demand in the second half of this fiscal is expected to improve profitability. The financial risk profile remains robust, backed by strong networth and nil debt. Networth improved to Rs 5,961 crore as of 31 March 2025, as compared to Rs 3,764 crore a year ago. Also, the company has capital expenditure (capex) of Rs 5,000 crore for the next 4-5 years for a greenfield manufacturing facility at Sri City (Andhra Pradesh) for ACs, AC compressor, washing machines and refrigerators in a phased manner. This phased investment is expected at Rs 1,000-1,200 crore per year and will be funded via internal cash accrual. Liquidity has been strong, with cash and cash equivalents of Rs 3,741 crore as on 31 Marsh 2025, which increased to Rs 4,284 crore as of September 2025. Further, unutilised fund-based limit will aid liquidity. The ratings continue to reflect the company’s leading position across diversified product portfolio, robust financial risk profile, strong operating capabilities and operational and technological links with LG Electronics Inc (South Korea). These strengths are partially offset by exposure to intense competition in the consumer durables segment and susceptibility to volatility in raw material prices and foreign exchange (forex) rates. LG India is a subsidiary of LG Electronics Inc, South Korea. The company has one of the widest product portfolios among consumer durables players in India. The scrip shed 0.78% to end at Rs 1521.90 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LGElectronicsIndiaLtd_35129397_18787.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Magellanic Cloud's subsidiary bags work order from IRCTC]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/magellanic-clouds-subsidiary-bags-work-order-from-irctc/1662140</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662140</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract, valued at Rs 2.25 crore, involves the deployment of a real-time, AI-enabled CCTV live-streaming and analytics solution for monitoring IRCTC-authorized kitchen units through a centralized portal.

The contract, valued at Rs 2.25 crore, involves the deployment of a real-time, AI-enabled CCTV live-streaming and analytics solution for monitoring IRCTC-authorized kitchen units through a centralized portal. The project is aimed at enhancing hygiene compliance, governance, transparency, and proactive detection of operational irregularities in catering operations. Joseph Sudheer Reddy Thumma, Global CEO & managing director, Magellanic Cloud, said: "The deployment of an AI-driven live-streaming and analytics platform reflects the company’s advanced domain expertise in next-generation surveillance systems and its commitment to enabling higher standards of transparency, quality assurance, and operational oversight through technology.” Magellanic Cloud specializes in offering services pertaining to software development, digital transformation, generative artificial intelligence (GenAI), the internet of things (IoT), e-surveillance and advanced drone-based applications. The company's consolidated net profit rose 14.43% to Rs 27.83 crore on a 4.54% increase in revenue to Rs 164.44 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip had risen 0.50% to currently trade at Rs 26.26 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MagellanicCloudLtd_76970750_24555.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund announces change in Exit Load Structure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-india-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-exit-load-structure/1662133</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662133</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following scheme stands revised with effect from December 29, 2025 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Load Revised Load Nippon India Arbitrage Fund 0.25% if redeemed or switched out on or before completion of 1 month from the date of allotment of units.

Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following scheme stands revised with effect from December 29, 2025 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Load Revised Load Nippon India Arbitrage Fund 0.25% if redeemed or switched out on or before completion of 1 month from the date of allotment of units. Nil, thereafter 0.25% if redeemed or switched out on or before completion of 15 days from the date of allotment of units. Nil, thereafter

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lenskart Solutions arm Stellio to incorporate UK subsidiary ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lenskart-solutions-arm-stellio-to-incorporate-uk-subsidiary/1662129</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662129</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The proposed entity will be named Stellio Ventures UK.

The proposed entity will be named Stellio Ventures UK. The proposed entity is being incorporated with the objective of establishing and operating retail stores in the United Kingdom for the sale of eyewear products and related accessories under the ‘Meller’ brand. Stellio will subscribe GBP 100 in Stellio Ventures UK and Lenskart Solutions will indirectly hold 84.21% of the equity in the proposed step-down subsidiary through Stellio. Lenskart Solutions is a technology-led eyewear company involved in designing, manufacturing, branding and retailing prescription glasses, sunglasses, contact lenses and related accessories. The company's consolidated net profit rose 19.60% to Rs 102.22 crore on a 20.77% increase in revenue to Rs 2096.15 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The counter fell 0.62% to end at Rs 449.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LENSKARTSOLUTIONSLIMITED_69247877_68840.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-india-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-scheme/1662127</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662127</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following scheme, With effect from 01 January 2026.

Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following scheme, With effect from 01 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) Revised Fund Manager(s) Nippon India Balanced Advantage Fund Ashutosh Bhargava, Sushil Budhia, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru Ashutosh Bhargava, Bhavik Dave, Sushil Budhia, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru Nippon India Retirement Fund - Income Generation Scheme Pranay Sinha, Ashutosh Bhargava, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru Pranay Sinha, Ritesh Rathod, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru Nippon India Retirement Fund - Wealth Creation Plan Ashutosh Bhargava, Pranay Sinha, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru Ritesh Rathod, Pranay Sinha, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru Nippon India Multi Asset Allocation Fund Ashutosh Bhargava, Vikram Dhawan, Sushil Budhia, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru Ashutosh Bhargava, Vinay Sharma, Vikram Dhawan, Sushil Budhia, Kinjal Desai, Divya Dutt Sharma, Lokesh Maru

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manappuram Finance appoints Buvanesh Tharashankar as Group CFO]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/manappuram-finance-appoints-buvanesh-tharashankar-as-group-cfo/1662120</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662120</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In his role as Group CFO, Buvanesh will provide strategic financial leadership across the Manappuram Group.

In his role as Group CFO, Buvanesh will provide strategic financial leadership across the Manappuram Group. He will work closely with the leadership team to strengthen financial governance, support long-term business strategy, enhance capital efficiency and enable sustainable value creation while ensuring strong regulatory and compliance standards. Buvanesh is a highly accomplished finance professional and a Chartered Accountant with nearly three decades of experience across leading banking and financial services institutions, having held senior roles across RBL Bank (CFO), Jana Small Finance Bank (CFO), and Citibank in India and overseas. His career spans critical areas such as financial strategy, capital and balance sheet management, regulatory interface, governance, investor engagement, and business analytics. He has consistently partnered business leadership in driving disciplined growth, strengthening controls, and enhancing organizational resilience. Meanwhile, the board also approved an investment of Rs 250 crore in Asirvad Micro Finance (AMFL), a subsidiary of the company, in single/ different tranches. The funds will be used to support AMFL’s capital expenditure and working capital requirements. Founded in 1949, Manappuram Finance is a leading non-banking financial institution and the 2nd largest financier in the gold loan segment in India, Over the years, it has evolved into a diversified financial services provider, offering a wide range of products including gold loans, microfinance, housing finance, vehicle loans, and SME financing. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 61.5% to Rs 219.88 crore on 13.3% fall in total income to Rs 2,285.36 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.22% to settle at Rs 313.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManappuramFin_40714085963_6083.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Solarworld Energy Solutions bags Rs 725-cr EPC order from NTPC Renewable Energy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/solarworld-energy-solutions-bags-rs-725-cr-epc-order-from-ntpc-renewable-energy/1662119</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662119</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is scheduled to be completed in the financial year 2026–27, in accordance with the terms of the order.

The project is scheduled to be completed in the financial year 2026–27, in accordance with the terms of the order. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It also stated that the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions under applicable regulatory norms. Solarworld Energy Solutions is a leading renewable energy company. It offers end-to-end solar EPC, large-scale solar park development, and customized rooftop and ground-mounted solar solutions for commercial, industrial, and utility clients. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 58.3% to Rs 9.29 crore on a 2.9% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 137.88 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter slipped 2.60% to end at Rs 264.15 on Friday, 26 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SolarworldEnergySolutionsLtd_63857359_94042.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikran Engg secures LoAs for 45.75 MW solar PV Capacity ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikran-engg-secures-loas-for-4575-mw-solar-pv-capacity/1662094</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662094</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the awards, Vikran Engineering will act as a Renewable Power Generator (RPG) for the implementation of the solar power plants.

Under the awards, Vikran Engineering will act as a Renewable Power Generator (RPG) for the implementation of the solar power plants. The projects will have a power purchase tenure of 25 years, with tariffs ranging between Rs 2.75 per kWh to Rs 2.80 per kWh, as specified in the LOAs The projects will be developed under the Surya Mitra Krishi Feeders Scheme, with feeder solarisation as part of the PM KUSUM-C scheme, for sale of power to Madhya Pradesh Power Management Company (MPPMCL). Vikran Engineering is a diversified EPC player. The company provides end-to-end turnkey solutions spanning conceptualization, design, supply, installation, testing, and commissioning, enabling it to capture the full value chain of project execution. On a standalone basis, net profit of Vikran Engineering rose 339.42% to Rs 9.14 crore while net sales increased 10.71% to Rs 176.29 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. The counter rallied 4.40% to end at Rs 100.75 on Friday, 26 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VikranEngineeringLtd_15725401_76742.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>