<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:01:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Stainless Ltd Surges 2.61%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-stainless-ltd-surges-261/1664465</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664465</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jindal Stainless Ltd gained 2.61% today to trade at Rs 791.05.

Jindal Stainless Ltd gained 2.61% today to trade at Rs 791.05. The BSE Metal index is up 0.71% to quote at 37576.06. The index is up 7.68 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd increased 1.23% and Vedanta Ltd added 0.73% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 40.18 % over last one year compared to the 10.15% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Jindal Stainless Ltd has added 0.75% over last one month compared to 7.68% gain in BSE Metal index and 1.39% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1557 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 27428 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 883.25 on 07 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 497 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalStain_15230115440_24610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suyog Telematics Ltd Falls 0.7%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suyog-telematics-ltd-falls-07/1664466</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664466</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Suyog Telematics Ltd lost 0.7% today to trade at Rs 558.15.

Suyog Telematics Ltd lost 0.7% today to trade at Rs 558.15. The BSE Telecommunication index is down 0.11% to quote at 3048.07. The index is down 1.83 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Bharti Hexacom Ltd decreased 0.63% and Route Mobile Ltd lost 0.48% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 12.64 % over last one year compared to the 10.15% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Suyog Telematics Ltd has lost 12.36% over last one month compared to 1.83% fall in BSE Telecommunication index and 1.39% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 70 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 1861 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 1713.9 on 21 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 552.35 on 12 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuyogTelematics_40570848390_43958.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VA Tech WABAG jumps on securing large BPCL water treatment order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/va-tech-wabag-jumps-on-securing-large-bpcl-water-treatment-order/1664463</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664463</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order falls under the ‘Large’ category domestically, valued between Rs 250–600 crore.

The order falls under the ‘Large’ category domestically, valued between Rs 250–600 crore. The order covers a comprehensive Water Block Package, including a Raw Water Treatment Plant (RWTP), a Reverse Osmosis-based Demineralization Plant (RODMP), and a Zero Liquid Discharge Plant (ZLDP) for the BPCL Bina refinery. WABAG will undertake the design, engineering, procurement, construction, installation, testing, and commissioning (EPC) of the facilities. The project is expected to be completed over a 22-month period. Commenting on the development, S Natrajan, Head – Sales & Marketing, India Cluster, said, "We are delighted to receive this ‘Large’ industrial water treatment order, including a ZLD solution from BPCL, and sincerely thank them for the confidence reposed in WABAG’s technological expertise and execution capabilities. This award further reinforces WABAG’s leadership position in the Oil & Gas sector and underscores our strong track record in delivering complex, technology-intensive water projects. We remain fully committed to executing this state-of-the-art project to the highest standards of quality, reliability, and operational performance." Va Tech Wabag is engaged in the business of the water treatment field. Its principal activities include design, supply, installation, construction, and operational management of drinking water, wastewater treatment, industrial water treatment, and desalination plants. The company reported standalone net profit surged 22.05% to Rs 70.3 crore on a 12.51% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 690 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Bharat Petroleum Corporation is a public sector company which is engaged in the business of refining crude oil and marketing petroleum products. The company reported a 168.74% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 6,442.53 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 2,397.23 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 2.09% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,04,912.47 crore in the September 2025 quarter. Shares of Bharat Petroleum Corporation rose 0.28% to Rs 359.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VaTechWabag_99536256518_36019.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty indicates flat opening for key indices; Trump targets Iran-linked trade with 25% tariffs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-indicates-flat-opening-for-key-indices-trump-targets-iran-linked-trade-with-25-tariffs/1664458</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664458</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 38.00 points, indicating a muted opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 38.00 points, indicating a muted opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,638.40 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,839.32 crore in the Indian equity market on 12 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 15,425.22 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market traded higher on Tuesday as traders shrugged off geopolitical flashpoints in Iran and Venezuela, as well as a criminal investigation into the U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Japan’s benchmark Nikkei 225 jumped 3.4% to lead gains in the region. Japan’s ruling Liberal Democratic Party is expected to dissolve the country’s Lower House later this month and opt for a snap election likely in February, according to media reports. Traders will also be keeping a close eye on oil prices amid ongoing protests in Iran. President Donald Trump is reportedly weighing options for intervention in Iran, according to multiple media reports. Trump in a social media post on Monday stateside reportedly said any country doing business with Iran will face a 25% tariff “on any and all business being done with the United States of America.” That new tariff on imports from Iran’s trading partners is “effective immediately.” Overnight in the U.S., stocks rallied off their session lows, with the S&P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average hitting new all-time highs. The S&P 500 rose 0.16% to end at 6,977.27, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average ticked up 86.13 points, or 0.17%, and settled at 49,590.20. Both indexes touched fresh all-time intraday highs and closed at records. The Nasdaq Composite was up 0.26% and closed at 23,733.90. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks snapped a five-day losing streak on Monday after a sharp intraday rebound. The move was driven by positive global cues, value buying and reassuring comments on India-US trade ties from newly appointed US Ambassador to India Sergio Gor. The Sensex, which was down over 700 points in early trade, recovered more than 1,000 points from the day’s low by the close. The Nifty also climbed back above the 25,790 level as sentiment improved, with metals, PSU banks and energy stocks leading the recovery. The market reacted after Gor said India and the US remain actively engaged on trade and that talks are continuing despite differences. He also conveyed greetings from President Donald Trump to Prime Minister Narendra Modi. Sentiment received an added boost after Gor announced that India would be invited next month to join PaxSilica. The recovery was broad-based. Bank Nifty rebounded sharply, while midcap and smallcap indices erased a large part of their early losses. Export-oriented stocks also gained as fears of an immediate tariff escalation eased after weeks of sustained selling and foreign fund outflows. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 301.93 points or 0.36% to 83,878.17. The Nifty 50 index gained 106.95 points or 0.42% to 25,790.25. In the past five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JTL Industries bags PSTCL order for 220 kV transmission towers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jtl-industries-bags-pstcl-order-for-220-kv-transmission-towers/1664449</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664449</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order, awarded by the domestic entity PSTCL, is scheduled to be executed within FY26.

The order, awarded by the domestic entity PSTCL, is scheduled to be executed within FY26. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity. JTL Industries is amongst the fastest-growing steel tube manufacturers, and its registered office is in Chandigarh. The company has manufacturing facilities in Punjab, Maharashtra, and Chhattisgarh. Its product offering includes GI pipes, MS black pipes, hollow sections, and solar structures, which cater to diverse industrial and infrastructural applications. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 46.83% to Rs 163.24 crore, despite a 5.47% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5,438.60 crore in Q1 FY26 over Q1 FY25. The counter surged 19.64% to close at Rs 61.66 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JTLInfra_2194853731_41375.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: HCL Tech, Tata Consultancy Services, TVS Supply Chain, PSP Projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-hcl-tech-tata-consultancy-services-tvs-supply-chain-psp-projects/1664448</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664448</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 13 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 13 January 2026. Result Today: ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company, ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company, Tata Elxsi, 5paisa Capital, Just Dial, Bank of Maharashtra, Navkar Corporation, Oriental Hotels, Sigma Solve, and Tokyo Plast International will release their quarterly earnings later today. Key Events: German Chancellor Friedrich Merz will be in Bengaluru on the second day of his visit. Stocks to Watch: HCL Technologies’ consolidated net profit declined 3.75% to Rs 4,076 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,235 crore in Q2 FY26. However, revenue from operations increased 6.04% to Rs 33,872 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 31,942 crore posted in Q2 FY26. Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) reported an 11.74% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 10,657 crore, despite 1.96% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,087 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. TVS Supply Chain Solutions said that it has secured a three-year contract from Daimler India Commercial Vehicles to manage warehouse operations at the latter’s Chennai manufacturing facility. PSP Projects said that it has secured an arbitration award of Rs 61.4 crore in its favour against the Bhiwandi Nizampur City Municipal Corporation Kirloskar Oil Engines said that its registrar of companies has approved the change in name of the company’s arm from La-Gajjar Machineries to Koel Fluid Dynamics. Gillette India said that it has appointed Rohini Venkateswaran as a whole-time director for a five-year term.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>