<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro surges from six-week low, IMF ups Eurozone growth estimate]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-surges-from-six-week-low-imf-ups-eurozone-growth-estimate/1665914</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665914</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro has surged after recent losses after Eurozone inflation eased more than initially estimated in December.

Euro has surged after recent losses after Eurozone inflation eased more than initially estimated in December. Final data from Eurostat showed on Monday that the harmonized index of consumer prices rose by revised 1.9% year-on-year following an increase of 2.1% in each of the previous two months. Core inflation, which excludes prices of energy and fresh food, also slowed to 2.3%. This capped the downside for EUR/USD pair after it tested around six-week low of 1.1600. The pair moved up impressively and currently quotes at 1.1695, up 0.58% on the day. The US dollar index has slipped well under 99 mark. Meanwhile, the IMF has said it expects Eurozone to grow at 1.3% in 2026, up from the 1.1% expansion forecast last October. On NSE, EUR/INR futures are quoting at 106.20, up 0.36% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aarti Surfactants hits the roof after PAT surges to Rs 3.66 crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aarti-surfactants-hits-the-roof-after-pat-surges-to-rs-366-crore-in-q3/1665911</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665911</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales increased by 27.7% YoY to Rs 207.79 crore during the quarter.

Net sales increased by 27.7% YoY to Rs 207.79 crore during the quarter. Total operating expenditure rose by 26.8% to Rs 195.09 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax for the December’25 quarter stood at Rs 5.10 crore, which is over four times the pre-tax profit of Rs 1.21 crore recorded in the same period last year. Aarti Surfactants is engaged in the product portfolio includes surfactants, mild surfactants, rheology modifiers, pearlizing agents, UV filters, syndet and soap bases, and active ingredients, as well as conditioning agents, blends, proteins, and quats. It serves skin care, oral, hair, cosmetics, bath and shower, sun care, fabric/laundry care, dishwashing, toilet care, and surface care segments. On the BSE, nearly 0.18 lakh shares had changed hands at the counter as compared with the average trading volume of 662 shares traded in the past two weeks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AartiSurfactantsLtd._85951232_73396.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Deepak Nitrite jumps on Dahej plant commissioning]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/deepak-nitrite-jumps-on-dahej-plant-commissioning/1665910</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665910</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said its wholly owned subsidiary, Deepak Chem Tech, commissioned a nitration and second hydrogenation plant on 19 January 2026.

The company said its wholly owned subsidiary, Deepak Chem Tech, commissioned a nitration and second hydrogenation plant on 19 January 2026. The facility is located at Dahej in Bharuch district, Gujarat. Total capital expenditure incurred so far is around Rs 85 crore. Deepak Nitrite is a chemical intermediates company in India with a diversified portfolio of products that cater to multiple industries with varied applications. The company's consolidated net profit declined 38.86% to Rs 118.71 crore on 6.40% decrease in revenue from operations to Rs 1,901.89 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DeepakNitrite_13794654982_136.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slides 333 pts; IT shares lag]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slides-333-pts-it-shares-lag/1665908</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665908</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest losses in mid-morning trade, pressured by persistent global trade uncertainties and continued foreign fund outflows, even as investor focus remained on the ongoing quarterly earnings season.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest losses in mid-morning trade, pressured by persistent global trade uncertainties and continued foreign fund outflows, even as investor focus remained on the ongoing quarterly earnings season. The Nifty traded below the 25,500 level. IT stocks witnessed selling pressure for the second straight trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 333.19 points or 0.40% to 82,912.99. The Nifty 50 index lost 122.45 points or 0.48% to 25,462.55. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.17% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.24%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,028 shares rose and 2,859 shares fell. A total of 197 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 1,06,41,960 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:30 IST on Tuesday (20 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.12 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 1.41% to 38,354. The index dropped 1.87% in the two consecutive trading sessions. LTIMindtree (down 6.71%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.86%), Wipro (down 1.65%), HCL Technologies (down 1.35%), Coforge (down 1.3%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 1.06%), Mphasis (down 0.91%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.9%), Persistent Systems (down 0.69%) and Infosys (down 0.58%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Atishay hit a lower circuit of 10% after its standalone net profit slipped 10.90% to Rs 1.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2.11 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 1.51% to Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Oberoi Realty dropped 6.89% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 18.10% to Rs 622.64 crore, despite a 5.77% rise in net sales to Rs 1,492.64 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Global Markets: Asian stocks traded lower on Tuesday as a resurgence of trade-war concerns hit risk sentiment and sparked selling in U.S. assets. U.S. President Donald Trump's push to take control of Greenland by threatening additional tariffs—a move that risks fueling trade tensions with Europe—has led to uncertainty in the markets, with investors scurrying for safe-haven assets, including the Swiss franc and gold. The tensions have revived talk of the 'Sell America' trade that emerged in the aftermath of his sweeping "Liberation Day" levies last April, where investors sell U.S. stocks, dollars, and Treasuries. That trade appeared to be gathering momentum in Asian hours on Tuesday. Trump's threats triggered a sharp pushback in Europe, and his remarks have raised questions on the outlook of trade deals struck since then with Europe. All eyes will now be on Davos, where Trump is expected to meet global business leaders on Wednesday, as the U.S. president's presence looms large over the annual gathering of the global elite in Switzerland. Meanwhile, Japan's Nikkei saw some selling as investors looked ahead to next month's election. Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi is seeking voter backing for increased spending, tax cuts, and a new security strategy that is expected to accelerate a defence buildup. U.S. cash equity markets were closed on Monday for Martin Luther King Jr. Day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Avana Electrosystems powers a strong debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-avana-electrosystems-powers-a-strong-debut/1665904</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665904</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 77.50, a premium of 31.36% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 77.50, a premium of 31.36% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently down 1.94% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 81.35 and a low of Rs 73.65. About 31.62 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Avana Electrosystems' IPO was subscribed 122.64 times. The issue opened for bidding on 12 January 2026 and it closed on 14 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 56 to Rs 59 per share. The IPO comprised 59,70,000 equity shares, including a fresh issue of 51,76,000 equity shares and offer for sale (OFS) of 7,94,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for capital expenditure towards civil construction, internal electric work and internal plumbing to set up an integrated manufacturing unit, to meet working capital requirements of the company and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Avana Electrosystems on 9 January 2026, raised Rs 9.97 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 16.90 lakh shares at Rs 59 per share to 5 anchor investors. Avana Electrosystems is a manufacturer of customised control and relay panels ranging from 11 kV to 220 kV for power system monitoring, control, and protection applications, including transmission lines, power transformers, bus bars, capacitor banks, and more, for both indoor and outdoor use. The company also manufactures MV and LV panels, protection relays, and substation automation systems. These panels are used across various sectors and industries to facilitate the transmission and distribution of electrical power. As of 30 November 2025, the company had 137 permanent employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 35.75 crore and net profit of Rs 5.61 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AvanaElectrosystemsLtd_22125535_96394.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Edelweiss MF announces IDCW & Monthly Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/edelweiss-mf-announces-idcw-monthly-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1665896</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665896</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Edelweiss Mutual Fund has announced 22 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes.

Edelweiss Mutual Fund has announced 22 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes. The amount IDCW (Rs. per unit) will be: Edelweiss Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option & Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs. 0.18 each Edelweiss Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option & Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs. 0.21 each. Edelweiss Equity Savings Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option & Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs. 0.08 each.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon India MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-india-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1665891</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665891</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 22 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 22 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Nippon India Small Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 2.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 3.00 Nippon India Banking & Financial Services Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 5.50 Direct Plan – IDCW: 8.00

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oberoi Realty slides after Q3 PAT declines 18% QoQ to Rs 623-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oberoi-realty-slides-after-q3-pat-declines-18-qoq-to-rs-623-cr/1665890</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665890</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit rose marginally by 0.68%, while total revenue increased 5.77% in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit rose marginally by 0.68%, while total revenue increased 5.77% in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 835.63 crore in Q3 FY26, up 3.12% from Rs 810.28 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The company reported exceptional items amounting to Rs 23.06 crore during the quarter. On a nine-month basis, consolidated net profit rose 0.65% YoY to Rs 1,804.15 crore, while revenue increased 2.97% YoY to Rs 4,259.23 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Vikas Oberoi, chairman & managing director, Oberoi Realty, said, “India’s economic environment remained stable during the quarter, supported by steady domestic demand and broad-based activity across key sectors. In this context, our residential, commercial, and retail businesses delivered a steady performance, aligned with our focus on disciplined execution. Residential demand held steady, with the luxury segment continuing to draw interest from buyers seeking larger homes in established locations, along with a growing base of HNIs and ultra HNIs. Our commercial assets maintained consistent leasing activity, indicating sustained occupier interest. The festive season also contributed to healthy footfalls and engagement at both Oberoi Mall and Sky City Mall. In 2026, we will continue to actively pursue attractive land opportunities, and we remain optimistic about the year ahead, supported by a strong development pipeline, prudent capital management, and our unwavering focus on creating future ready projects aligned with long-term market demand.” Oberoi Realty is a real estate development company headquartered in Mumbai. It focuses on premium developments in the residential, office space, retail, hospitality and social infrastructure verticals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OberoiRealty_76593607717_38025.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tips Music soars after Q3 PAT climbs 33% YoY to Rs 59-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tips-music-soars-after-q3-pat-climbs-33-yoy-to-rs-59-cr/1665889</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665889</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 33.01% YoY to Rs 78.62 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 33.01% YoY to Rs 78.62 crore during the quarter. During the quarter, operating EBITDA stood at Rs 74.5 crore, registering the growth of 34% compared with Rs 55.6 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Operating EBITDA margin improved to 79.0% in Q3 FY26 as against 71.6% in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, 108 songs were released, including 70 film songs and 38 non-film songs. Among them, the songs "Sheher Ghumawa" and "Halki Halki Nami” stood out. YouTube subscriber count grew to 145.3 million. Kumar Taurani, chairman & managing director said, “During the quarter, 108 songs were released, including 70 film tracks and 38 non-film tracks. The cumulative YouTube channels subscriber base has grown significantly to 145.3 million. Our catalogue maintained significant momentum on Instagram; "Soldier Soldier Meethi Baatien" generated 2.7 billion views, while "Tere Liye" song reached 2.1 billion during the quarter. “Meri Kahani” song became the personal anthem for many to express their young version versus today, it was used by CMD Kumar Taurani, Virat Kohli, Ajay Devgan etc on Instagram. We are happy to announce our partnership with B4U TV as our broadcast partner, enabling wider reach for our rich catalog among television audiences globally.” Meanwhile, the company’s board has declared a third interim dividend of Rs 5 per equity share of face value of Re 1 each. The record has been fixed as 23 January 2026. It will be paid on or before 13 February 2026. Founded in 1988 by Taurani Brothers, TIPS Music is one of India's leading publicly-listed music companies. The company is engaged in the business of creation, acquisition and monetization of audio-video music content, in India and overseas, through digital licensing on various medium.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TipsIndustries_17137674547_8022.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CII's Business Confidence Index climbs to five-quarter high in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ciis-business-confidence-index-climbs-to-five-quarter-high-in-q3-fy26/1665887</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665887</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CII’s Business Confidence Index, rose for the third consecutive quarter to 66.5 in Q3FY26, the highest level in five quarters.

CII’s Business Confidence Index, rose for the third consecutive quarter to 66.5 in Q3FY26, the highest level in five quarters. The improvement is driven by optimism around demand, profitability, and investment conditions, it noted. Domestic demand remains the key driver, with two-thirds of firms reporting higher demand in Q2FY26 and 72 per cent expecting further growth in Q3FY26, aided by GST rate cuts and festive consumption. Investment and hiring intentions remain robust. Driven by bold reform initiatives, India has firmly established itself as the world’s fastest-growing major economy, demonstrating remarkable resilience amid global uncertainty shaped by geopolitical tensions, trade weaponisation, and a slowing world economy. Amidst this, business confidence among Indian industry is high, as corroborated by the latest Business Outlook Survey of the Confederation of Indian Industry (CII). “The steady rise in business confidence shows industry’s ability to navigate external headwinds, anchored by resilient domestic demand and a robust reform agenda,” noted Mr Chandrajit Banerjee, Director General, CII. He further added that industry anticipates the growth momentum to strengthen further in the months ahead.”

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-aditya-birla-lifestyle-brands-ltd-counter/1665884</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665884</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Fashion & Retail Ltd, Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd, Kajaria Ceramics Ltd, Deepak Nitrite Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 20 January 2026.

Aditya Birla Fashion & Retail Ltd, Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd, Kajaria Ceramics Ltd, Deepak Nitrite Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 20 January 2026. Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd witnessed volume of 345.93 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 611.33 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 56586 shares. The stock dropped 0.78% to Rs.114.85. Volumes stood at 49217 shares in the last session. Aditya Birla Fashion & Retail Ltd notched up volume of 110.03 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 49.98 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.20 lakh shares. The stock slipped 5.65% to Rs.67.98. Volumes stood at 4.02 lakh shares in the last session. Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd notched up volume of 1.01 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 24.38 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4137 shares. The stock slipped 0.41% to Rs.1,683.25. Volumes stood at 2686 shares in the last session. Kajaria Ceramics Ltd clocked volume of 52230 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.2 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 8423 shares. The stock lost 1.08% to Rs.982.05. Volumes stood at 5318 shares in the last session. Deepak Nitrite Ltd recorded volume of 42969 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.13 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 8383 shares. The stock gained 4.87% to Rs.1,610.55. Volumes stood at 4005 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdityaBirlaLifestyleBrandsLtd_11691661_92996.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1665886</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665886</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Ankur Kagrana has been appointed as the Chief Risk Officer and key personnel of the ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Limited (the AMC) with effect from January 20, 2026. Details of Mr. Ankur Kagrana Age: 44 years Designation: Chief Risk Officer Qualification: Bachelor of Commerce and Chartered Accountant

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MSME loan applications worth &#8377;52,300 crore sanctioned by PSBs between April and December: Finance Ministry ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/msme-loan-applications-worth-837752300-crore-sanctioned-by-psbs-between-april-and-december-finance-ministry/1665883</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665883</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Public sector banks under the digital credit underwriting programmes sanctioned over 3.96 lakh MSME loan applications amounting to over Rs 52,300 crore between April 1 and December 31, 2025, the finance ministry said on Monday.

Public sector banks under the digital credit underwriting programmes sanctioned over 3.96 lakh MSME loan applications amounting to over Rs 52,300 crore between April 1 and December 31, 2025, the finance ministry said on Monday. The Public Sector Banks (PSBs) had launched the Credit Assessment Model (CAM) based on digital footprints for Micro, Small & Medium Enterprises (MSMEs) in 2025. This credit assessment model leverages the digitally fetched and verifiable data available in the ecosystem and devises automated journeys for MSME Loan appraisal using objective decisioning for all loan applications and model-based limit assessment for both Existing to Bank (ETB) as well as New to Bank (NTB) MSME borrowers, a finance ministry statement said.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/loans-710849__340_debt_markets.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ola Electric Mobility slips on top-level management change ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ola-electric-mobility-slips-on-top-level-management-change/1665882</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665882</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said Deepak Rastogi has been appointed chief financial officer with effect from 20 January 2026.

In a regulatory filing, the company said Deepak Rastogi has been appointed chief financial officer with effect from 20 January 2026. He succeeds Harish Abichandani, who resigned from the post citing personal reasons, effective at the close of business on 19 January 2026. The company added that its board approved Rastogi's appointment at a meeting held on January 19. With over three decades of experience spanning finance, strategy and governance roles, Rastogi will also be designated as a key managerial personnel and will be part of Ola Electric's senior management team from January 20. Ola Electric Mobility is a leading Indian electric vehicle (EV) manufacturer engaged in the integrated development of EV technology and components, including battery cells. Its manufacturing facility, the Ola Futurefactory in Tamil Nadu, produces EVs and key components and is positioned as one of India’s major EV hubs. On a consolidated basis, Ola Electric reported a net loss of Rs 418 crore in Q2 September 2025, compared with a net loss of Rs 495 crore a year earlier. Net sales fell 43.16% YoY to Rs 690 crore in the quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlaElectricMobilityLtd_81720871_75559.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rabi area rises more than 3% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rabi-area-rises-more-than-3-on-year/1665881</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665881</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total area sown under rabi crops in current winter season has increased by 3.30% on year to 652.33 lakh hectares as on January 16 this year, data released by the Ministry of Agriculture and Farmers Welfare showed.

The total area sown under rabi crops in current winter season has increased by 3.30% on year to 652.33 lakh hectares as on January 16 this year, data released by the Ministry of Agriculture and Farmers Welfare showed. The area under major crop wheat has gained 1.86% on year to 334.17 lakh hectares.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/agriculture-1551091__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Samco Mutual Fund announces change in Exit Load Structure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/samco-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-exit-load-structure/1665879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665879</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Samco Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following scheme stands revised with effect from January 20, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Exit Load Revised Exit Load Samco Midcap Fund 10% of units can be redeemed at any time without an exit load.

Samco Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following scheme stands revised with effect from January 20, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Exit Load Revised Exit Load Samco Midcap Fund 10% of units can be redeemed at any time without an exit load. • Any redemption in excess of 10% of units will incur 1% exit load in the first 12 months. • No exit load, if redeemed after 12 months from the date of allotment of unit. 1.00% If the investment is redeemed or switched out on or before 30 days from the date of allotment of units. No Exit Load will be charged if investment is redeemed or switched out after 30 days from the date of allotment of units.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI Governor highlights continued relevance of Urban Cooperative Banks in credit delivery to underserved areas]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-governor-highlights-continued-relevance-of-urban-cooperative-banks-in-credit-delivery-to-underserved-areas/1665878</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665878</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As part of the Reserve Bank of India’s continued engagement with regulated entities, the RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra held a meeting yesterday in Mumbai with the Chairpersons and Managing Directors & Chief Executive Officers (MDs & CEOs) of select Urban Cooperative Banks (UCBs).

As part of the Reserve Bank of India’s continued engagement with regulated entities, the RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra held a meeting yesterday in Mumbai with the Chairpersons and Managing Directors & Chief Executive Officers (MDs & CEOs) of select Urban Cooperative Banks (UCBs). The previous such meeting was held on March 19, 2025. The participants included representatives from the National Urban Cooperative Finance and Development Corporation Limited and the National Federation of Urban Co-operative Banks & Credit Societies Limited. The meeting was also attended by Deputy Governors and other senior officers of the Reserve Bank. In his remarks, the Governor highlighted the continued relevance of UCBs in credit delivery particularly to the underserved areas and in expanding financial inclusion. The Governor also briefly touched upon the various policy initiatives that have been undertaken by Reserve Bank relating to the co-operative banking sector since the previous interaction, and expressed confidence that these enablers will help the sector to become stronger and grow in a healthy manner. He underscored the importance of maintaining high standards of governance, robust underwriting practices and diligent oversight over asset quality. Further, he emphasised the necessity of adopting customer-centric approach, following ethical practices, and timely grievance resolution to maintain customer trust in the sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Atishay hits the floor as Q3 PAT slides 11% YoY to Rs 2 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/atishay-hits-the-floor-as-q3-pat-slides-11-yoy-to-rs-2-cr/1665876</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665876</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 1.51% to Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15.22 crore in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations rose 1.51% to Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 2.51 crore, down 11.92%, compared with Rs 2.85 crore posted in same quarter last year. Total expenses increased 4.19% YoY to Rs 13.41 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Purchase and other operating expenditure were at Rs 8.83 crore (up 18.04%) and employee benefits expenses were at Rs 2.46 crore (down 9.22% YoY) during the period under review. Separately, on 20 January 2026, the company said it secured an order worth Rs 3.77 crore from the Department of Prohibition, Excise and Registration, Government of Bihar, for the digitisation of registration records across registration offices in the state. Atishay is primarily engaged in the business of information technology, database management, software development, e-governance, and fintech services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Atishay_41228080877_45928.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India-UAE Comprehensive Strategic Partnership has continued to strengthen over past decade]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-uae-comprehensive-strategic-partnership-has-continued-to-strengthen-over-past-decade/1665877</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665877</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[At the invitation of the Prime Minister of India, Narendra Modi, President of the United Arab Emirates, His Highness Sheikh Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, paid an official visit to India on 19 January 2026.

At the invitation of the Prime Minister of India, Narendra Modi, President of the United Arab Emirates, His Highness Sheikh Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, paid an official visit to India on 19 January 2026. This was the fifth visit of His Highness Sheikh Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan to India in the last ten years and his third official visit to India as the President of the UAE. Prime Minister Narendra Modi and President His Highness Sheikh Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan reviewed the full scope of bilateral cooperation between the two countries. They agreed that the India-UAE Comprehensive Strategic Partnership has continued to strengthen over the past decade.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-people-shaking-hands-picture-id643974044_Analyst-Meet.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty below 25,500 level; realty shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-below-25500-level-realty-shares-decline/1665874</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665874</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in morning trade, pressured by persistent global trade uncertainties and continued foreign fund outflows, even as investor focus remained on the ongoing quarterly earnings season.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in morning trade, pressured by persistent global trade uncertainties and continued foreign fund outflows, even as investor focus remained on the ongoing quarterly earnings season. The Nifty traded below the 25,500 level. Realty stocks witnessed selling pressure for the second consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 282.95 points or 0.34% to 82,963.23. The Nifty 50 index lost 112.50 points or 0.44% to 25,475.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.07%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 991 shares rose and 2,698 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. Result Today: AU Small Finance Bank (down 1.20%), Canara Robeco Asset Management Company (down 1.20%), CreditAccess Grameen (down 2.31%), Cyient DLM (down 1.49%), DCM Shriram (down 0.81%), Gujarat Gas (rose 0.54%), IndiaMART InterMESH (down 1.40%), ITC Hotels (down 0.49%), Jammu & Kashmir Bank (down 0.39%), Mastek (up 0.89%), Newgen Software Technologies (down 1.33%), Persistent Systems (down 0.95%), PTC India Financial Services (down 1.47%), Rallis India (down 0.83%), Shoppers Stop (down 1.34%), Supreme Petrochem (up 2.02%), SRF (down 0.03%), United Spirits (down 0.15%), Vardhman Special Steels (down 0.83%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 2.15% to 818. The index dropped 4.1% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Oberoi Realty (down 5.2%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 3.59%), Sobha (down 3.16%), Lodha Developers (down 2.55%), Anant Raj (down 1.75%), SignatureGlobal India (down 1.13%), DLF (down 1.09%), Godrej Properties (down 1.01%), Brigade Enterprises (down 0.7%) and Phoenix Mills (down 0.22%) fell. Stocks in Spotlight: LTIMindtree dropped 6.10% after the company reported a 30.73% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 970.6 crore despite a 3.72% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q2 September 2025. Ceat declined 1.28%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 60.40% to Rs 155.77 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 97.11 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 25.97% to Rs 4,157.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>