<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd Spurts 2.93%, BSE Metal index Gains 1.63%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-ltd-spurts-293-bse-metal-index-gains-163/1667535</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667535</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd gained 2.93% today to trade at Rs 719.3.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd gained 2.93% today to trade at Rs 719.3. The BSE Metal index is up 1.63% to quote at 38493.31. The index is up 7.95 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Adani Enterprises Ltd increased 2.5% and APL Apollo Tubes Ltd added 2.2% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 39.01 % over last one year compared to the 8.05% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Zinc Ltd has added 12.96% over last one month compared to 7.95% gain in BSE Metal index and 4.24% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1.93 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 10.49 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 731.1 on 27 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 378.65 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd Slides 4.08%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-slides-408/1667536</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667536</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd fell 4.08% today to trade at Rs 3397.9.

Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd fell 4.08% today to trade at Rs 3397.9. The BSE Auto index is down 0.49% to quote at 59264.82. The index is down 3.81 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Ashok Leyland Ltd decreased 2.02% and Apollo Tyres Ltd lost 1.47% on the day. The BSE Auto index went up 19.79 % over last one year compared to the 8.05% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd has lost 6.17% over last one month compared to 3.81% fall in BSE Auto index and 4.24% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 13282 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 86335 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 3840 on 05 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 2360.45 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR stays pressured beyond Rs 91 per dollar mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-stays-pressured-beyond-rs-91-per-dollar-mark/1667533</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667533</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee edge higher but continue to stay pressured beyond Rs 91 per dollar mark in opening trades on Tuesday.

The Indian rupee edge higher but continue to stay pressured beyond Rs 91 per dollar mark in opening trades on Tuesday. Weakness in dollar and lower international crude oil prices contribute to upside in the local unit. Indian shares look set to open on a positive note Tuesday as traders return to their desks after a long holiday weekend, supporting the unit. INR opened at Rs 91.82 per dollar and hit a low of 91.90 so far during the day. On Friday, the counter ended at 91.90. Indian stock and forex markets were closed on Monday on account of Republic Day. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty tumbled over 2 percent last week. Investors also look ahead to the Union Budget presentation on Sunday, February 1 for clarity on taxation, reforms and policy priorities that could catalyze the next phase of economic growth.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-charts-picture-id165649635_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves see sharp spike]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-see-sharp-spike/1667531</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667531</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s foreign exchange reserves rose sharply by USD 14.167 billion to USD 701.360 billion in the week ended 16 January, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s latest Weekly Statistical Supplement.

India’s foreign exchange reserves rose sharply by USD 14.167 billion to USD 701.360 billion in the week ended 16 January, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s latest Weekly Statistical Supplement. The increase was driven by a strong rise in both foreign currency assets and gold reserves.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-1-1236488_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at strong operning for equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-strong-operning-for-equities/1667517</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667517</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 76.50 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 76.50 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 4,113.38 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 4,102.56 crore in the Indian equity market on 23 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 40,704.39 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asian shares traded mixed on Tuesday as concerns regarding tariffs resurfaced post US President Donald Trump threatening to increase levies on South Korean goods. Trump said on Truth Social that South Korea's legislature has not approved Seoul’s trade deal with Washington, and that tariffs on the country will climb to 25%, from 15%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index advanced 0.50%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 0.64%. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.43%, supported by jumps of about 3%, 2% and 1% in Apple, Meta Platforms and Microsoft, respectively, ahead of their earnings reports later in the week. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, erasing early gains as persistent foreign institutional investor selling weighed heavily on sentiment and sparked a broad-based selloff in the latter half of the session. The Sensex and Nifty opened marginally higher, supported by positive cues from Asian markets and easing geopolitical concerns linked to Greenland. However, sentiment turned decisively weaker post noon, with aggressive profit-booking and sustained selling pressure dragging the indices into the red. The Nifty closed below the 25,050 level, with all NSE sectoral indices ending in the red. Realty and PSU bank stocks led the losses amid heavy selling pressure. Foreign fund outflows remained the key overhang, with FIIs extending their net selling streak to 13 consecutive sessions in January, a trend that has steadily dented market capitalisation and investor confidence. Pressure on domestic shares intensified as the Indian rupee slid to a fresh all-time low against the US dollar, amplifying risk aversion. A subdued earnings season added to the gloom, as weak December-quarter results from several heavyweight companies triggered sharp, stock-specific declines. Rising crude oil prices further stoked concerns over inflation and external balances, capping any recovery attempts. The focus is now shifting to the Union Budget, which will take place on February 1. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 769.67 points or 0.94% to 81,537.70. The Nifty 50 index lost 241.25 points or 0.95% to 25,048.65.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Karur Vysya Bank reappoints B Ramesh Babu as MD & CEO]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/karur-vysya-bank-reappoints-b-ramesh-babu-as-md-ceo/1667516</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667516</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[His current term is scheduled to end on July 28, 2026.

His current term is scheduled to end on July 28, 2026. The board has recommended his reappointment for a third term of two years, effective 29 July, 2026. The appointment will be subject to the approval of the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) and the shareholders of the bank. Karur Vysya Bank provides services such as personal, corporate, and agricultural banking and services to NRIs and SMBs. The bank reported a 39.1% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 689.96 crore on an 11.8% increase in total income to Rs 3,303.13 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Karur Vysya Bank rose 0.66% to end at Rs 265.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KarurVysyaBank_85916324533_2722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: BPCL, MCX, UltraTech Cement, Kotak Mahindra Bank, Zydus Lifesciences]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-bpcl-mcx-ultratech-cement-kotak-mahindra-bank-zydus-lifesciences/1667515</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667515</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 27 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 27 January 2026. Key Events to Watch: Global cues remained in focus as G-7 finance ministers are scheduled to discuss supply chain issues related to rare earths and the Ukraine situation on Tuesday. European Council President António Luís Santos da Costa and European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen will co-chair the 16th India–EU Summit, focusing on strengthening strategic and economic ties. In domestic developments, India Energy Week begins in Goa, highlighting energy transition, oil & gas, and renewables. Meanwhile, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) will conduct state government bond auctions, which could influence bond market sentiment. Result Today: Asian Paints, Tata Consumer Products, Aditya Vision, Bikaji Foods International, CG Power and Industrial Solutions, Vodafone Idea, International Gemmological Institute India, Mahindra Logistics, Marico, Motilal Oswal Financial Services, NESCO, Raymond, Spandana Sphoorty Financial, Vishal Mega Mart, and WeWork India Management will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Kotak Mahindra Bank reported a 4.28% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 3,446.14 crore on 4.3% increase in total income to Rs 16,741.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ultratech Cement reported a 26.92% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,725.40 crore on 22.78% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 21,829.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) reported a 62.29% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 7,545.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 4,649.20 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Godrej Consumer Products has reported flat growth in consolidated net profit at Rs 497.91 crore in Q3 FY26, even as net sales increased 8.8% year-on-year to Rs 4,079.47 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) reported a 67.56% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 32.39 crore on a 16.09% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,167.06 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Multi Commodity Exchange of India (MCX) reported a 150.63% year-on-year (YoY) surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 401.12 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 160.04 crore in Q3 FY25. Income from operations jumped 120.85% YoY to Rs 665.62 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Jayaswal Neco Industries said that it has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) at Davos 2026 with the Government of Maharashtra for setting up a two-million-tonne-per-annum steel plant in Gadchiroli, Maharashtra, with an investment of Rs 12,262 crore. Zydus Lifesciences said that the US FDA conducted an inspection at the group’s Unit-2 manufacturing plant in Ankleshwar, Gujarat. The inspection was carried out from January 19 to 23 and concluded with three observations. There were no data integrity-related observations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>