<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sun Pharma Q3 PAT jumps 16% YoY to Rs 3,369 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sun-pharma-q3-pat-jumps-16-yoy-to-rs-3369-cr/1669701</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669701</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax were at Rs 4,227.16 crore in Q3 FY26, up 21.59% as against Rs 3,476.4 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax were at Rs 4,227.16 crore in Q3 FY26, up 21.59% as against Rs 3,476.4 crore in Q3 FY25. Formulation sales in India were Rs 49,98.59 crore, registering a growth of 16.2%. India Formulation sales accounted for 32.3% of total consolidated sales. Formulation sales in the US were $477 million, marginally up by 0.6%. Innovative Medicines continued to grow offsetting the decline in generics business. US sales accounted for approximately 27.5% of total consolidated sales. Emerging Markets formulations sales were $337 million, up by 21.6% and accounted for 19.4% of total consolidated sales. Formulation sales in Rest of World (RoW) markets were $296 million, up by 14.5% and accounted for 17.1% of total consolidated sales. Global Innovative Medicines sales were $423 million for Q3 FY26. This included a milestone income of $55 million. Ex-milestone, Global Innovative Medicines sales were up 13.2% and accounted for 21.2% of sales. For Q3 FY26, external sales of API were Rs 541.2 crore, down by 4.7%. Sun Pharma’s R&D efforts span both innovative and generic businesses, and the company continues to invest in building a robust pipeline for various markets. Sun’s innovative R&D pipeline includes five novel entities in the clinical stage. The company has a comprehensive product offering in the US market, consisting of 550 approved ANDAs, while 116 ANDA filings await US FDA approval, including 28 tentative approvals. During the quarter, two ANDAs were filed, and two ANDAs received approval. Sun’s portfolio includes 57 approved NDAs, while 14 NDAs are currently pending approval from the US FDA. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs 11 per equity share of Re 1 each for the financial year 2025–26. As intimated on 20 January 2026, the record date for determining entitlement to the interim dividend is 05 February 2026. The interim dividend shall be paid on or before 16 February 2026. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries is engaged in the business of manufacturing, developing and marketing a wide range of branded and generic formulations and Active Pharma Ingredients (APIs). The company and its subsidiaries has various manufacturing facilities spread across the world with trading and other incidental and related activities extending to global market. It is the largest pharmaceutical company in India. Shares of Sun Pharmaceutical rose 0.36% to Rs 1,595 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SunPharmaInds_69091260890_4325.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashoka Buildcon Q3 PAT skyrockets 223% YoY to Rs 2,111 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashoka-buildcon-q3-pat-skyrockets-223-yoy-to-rs-2111-cr/1669700</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669700</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations fell 23.47% YoY to Rs 1,827.33 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

However, revenue from operations fell 23.47% YoY to Rs 1,827.33 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax were at Rs 2,609 crore in Q3 FY26, up 750.80% as against Rs 306.65 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses declined 22.92% YoY to Rs 1,633.86 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 470.37 crore (down 33.56% YoY), while employee benefit expenses were at Rs 98.78 crore (down 13.58% YoY), and finance cost stood at Rs 200.22 crore (down 35.97% YoY). On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit surged 68% year-on-year to Rs 101.8 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations declined 18.35% to Rs 1,463.04 crore compared with Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 157.4 crore in Q3 FY26, down 16% compared with Rs 187.1 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 10.6% in Q3 FY26 from 10.3% posted in the same quarter last year. On a standalone basis, the company’s debt stands at Rs 1,046 crore, comprising Rs 79 crore in equipment loans, Rs 667 crore in working capital loans, and Rs 300 crore in non-convertible debentures (NCDs). As of 31 December 2025, the company’s total order book stood at Rs 15,927 crore, before exceptional gains. Road EPC projects accounted for Rs 7,025 crore, or 44.1% of the total, while Road HAM contributed Rs 1,705 crore (10.7%). Building EPC orders were Rs 528 crore (3.3%), railways Rs 1,562 crore (9.8%), and Power T&D projects Rs 5,108 crore (32.1%). Ashoka Buildcon is engaged in the construction & maintenance of roads and supporting services to land support and operation of toll roads. Shares of Ashoka Buildcon added 3.72% to end at Rs 149.99 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokaBuildcon_9945804621_25513.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Subros Q3 PAT jumps 6% YoY to Rs 35 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/subros-q3-pat-jumps-6-yoy-to-rs-35-cr/1669690</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669690</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 15.43% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 947.68 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 15.43% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 947.68 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 2.40 crore in the third quarter of FY26, down 2.40% YoY. During the quarter, EBITDA jumped 8.12% YoY to Rs 87.19 crore while EBITDA margin stood at 9.23%. The company approved a capacity addition at its Karsanpura manufacturing facility in Gujarat, including the proposed installation of a new local electric compressor line and the expansion of local ICE compressor capacity at the plant in Karsanpura, Ahmedabad district. Subros was incorporated in 1985 as a joint venture public limited company with Suri family of India (36.79% ownership), Denso Corporation, Japan (20% ownership) & Suzuki Motor Corporation, Japan (11.96% ownership). It is engaged in the business of manufacturing and supplying Auto Air Conditioning products for all major Automakers in Passenger and Commercial Vehicle Space. It has a technical collaboration with Denso Corporation. Shares of Subros shed 0.57% to settle at Rs 809.45 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Subros_9340235386_1121.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Relaxo Footwears Q3 PAT tumbles 20% YoY to Rs 27 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/relaxo-footwears-q3-pat-tumbles-20-yoy-to-rs-27-cr/1669687</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669687</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 35.92 crore, down 19.5% compared with Rs 44.61 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 35.92 crore, down 19.5% compared with Rs 44.61 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Total expenses rose 2.22% YoY to Rs 643.07 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The cost of material consumed, including packing material, was at Rs 229.54 crore (up 1.08% YoY), and employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 110.24 crore (up 14.83% YoY) during the quarter. EBITDA declined by 16.8% to Rs 69 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 83 crore in Q3 FY25. The EBITDA margin declined to 10.4% in Q3 FY26, impacted by higher sales promotion spending and one-time costs of Rs 5.7 crore related to the new labour code. Commenting on the results and performance, Ramesh Kumar Dua, chairman and managing director, said, “During the quarter, the company reported stable revenue, after a sequential decline observed in revenue over the last few quarters. This positive development is attributed to the company’s continuous efforts in sales transformation. The organized retail (EBO stores), e-commerce, and large-format retail stores reported a strong performance, while the general trade channel witnessed a positive momentum. Looking ahead, the company will maintain a balanced approach to topline growth and margins. The teams will closely monitor market conditions and the competitive landscape to develop strategies accordingly that ensure positive performance in the upcoming quarters.” Relaxo Footwears is India’s largest footwear manufacturer, primarily engaged in the production of non-leather footwear, including rubber and EVA slippers, sandals, sports shoes, canvas shoes, and school shoes. Shares of Relaxo Footwears jumped 6.11% to settle at Rs 393.15 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RelaxoFootwear_23765230776_5056.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Auto Q3 PAT rises 19% YoY to Rs 2,503 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-auto-q3-pat-rises-19-yoy-to-rs-2503-cr/1669678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669678</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s PAT was reported after adjusting for a one-time exceptional impact arising from the reassessment of employee benefit obligations, following the revised definition of wages under the new Labour Codes notified in November 2025.

The company’s PAT was reported after adjusting for a one-time exceptional impact arising from the reassessment of employee benefit obligations, following the revised definition of wages under the new Labour Codes notified in November 2025. The company’s revenue growth was driven by record quarterly volumes and a richer product mix, underpinned by double-digit growth across all businesses—domestic motorcycles, electric two-wheelers, three-wheelers and exports. This performance was supported by buoyant festive demand and GST-led momentum in the domestic market, alongside a sustained resurgence in exports. Profit before tax was at Rs 3,326.64 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of 18.74% from Rs 2,801.45 crore posted in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, EBITDA rose to Rs 3,161 crore, up 22% year-on-year, scaling a new peak as margins expanded to 20.8%, reflecting dynamic P&L management. Margins improved by 30 bps sequentially, with currency tailwinds and PU benefits more than offsetting the decision to absorb cost inflation during a strong festive season, as well as the margin drag from the highest-ever quarterly sales of electric two-wheelers. The firm added that domestic motorcycles turned in its biggest quarter on 125cc+ with double-digit revenue growth YoY, buoyed by sports segment. "Improved traction on the Pulsar portfolio, led by product refreshes/upgrades and amplified by impactful activation which drove quarterly retail volumes to a historic high and the competitive performance of the strategically important 125cc+ segment," it added. Domestic volumes rose 3% to 7,31,037 units in Q3 FY26 as compared with 7,07,105 units sold in the corresponding quarter last year. Export volumes jumped 18% to 6,10,215 units in Q3 FY26 as compared with 5,17,367 units sold in the corresponding quarter last year. Commercial vehicles posted record retails, crossing 100,000 units for the tenth straight quarter, while electric three-wheelers achieved peak billings and retails, exiting the quarter in a leadership position. Chetak delivered a strong rebound, with volumes up 70% QoQ, aided by resolution of sourcing constraints, rapid production ramp-up and a 500 bps QoQ market-share gain. The company approved an additional investment of up to Rs 12 crore in the equity share capital of Clean Max Godavari for an open-access group captive power purchase arrangement for its Akurdi and Chakan (Plant 2) manufacturing facilities in Pune. Shares of Bajaj Auto rose 0.90% to end at Rs 9,592.90 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajAuto_20897586_28074.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HBL Engineering bags Rs 575-cr order from ICF for KAVACH supply]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hbl-engineering-bags-rs-575-cr-order-from-icf-for-kavach-supply/1669677</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669677</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is to be executed over the next 12 months.

The project is to be executed over the next 12 months. HBL Engineering (formerly known as HBL Power Systems) manufactures different types of batteries, including lead acid, NiCad, silver zinc, lithium, and railway & defense electronics and other products. The company reported a more than fourfold jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 387.27 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 87.26 crore in the same quarter last year. Revenue from operations surged 134.7% YoY to Rs 1,222.90 crore in Q2 September 2025. Shares of HBL Engineering rose 1.87% to settle at Rs 783.20 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HBLPowerSystem_94746576490_2401.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NTPC Q3 PAT jumps 8% YoY to Rs 5,597 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ntpc-q3-pat-jumps-8-yoy-to-rs-5597-cr/1669672</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669672</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The revenue from power generation activity stood at Rs 44,657.81 in Q3 FY26, up 1.29% YoY.

The revenue from power generation activity stood at Rs 44,657.81 in Q3 FY26, up 1.29% YoY. During the period under review, the company recorded Rs 4,894.80 crore as other income, up 17.82% YoY. Profit before tax and regulatory deferral account balances declined 2.67% YoY to Rs 7,385.27 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 7,587.90 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expense rose 2.77% year on year to Rs 39,533.23 crore during the quarter. Employee benefits expense was at Rs 1,756.72 crore (up 8.23% YoY), while other expenses stood at Rs 5,297.09 crore (up 34.48% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved a second interim dividend for FY26 at 27.5%, or Rs 2.75 per share on a face value of Rs 10. The dividend is scheduled for payment and dispatch on 25 February 2026. NTPC, along with its subsidiaries/associates & JVs, is primarily involved in the generation and sale of bulk power to state power utilities. Other business of the group includes providing consultancy, project management & supervision, energy trading, oil & gas exploration, and coal mining. Shares of NTPC rose 0.81% to settle at Rs 3,014.70 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NTPC_90569510917_12001.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Garware Hi-Tech Q3 PAT slides 8% YoY to Rs 56 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/garware-hi-tech-q3-pat-slides-8-yoy-to-rs-56-cr/1669668</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669668</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax dropped 9.75% YoY to Rs 73.11 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax dropped 9.75% YoY to Rs 73.11 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA stood at Rs 86.7 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the de-growth of 7.4%, compared with the Rs 93.7 crore posted in the corresponding quarter last year. EBITDA margin reduced to 18.9% in Q3 FY26 from 20.1% in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, cash profit was at Rs 69 crore, down 0.5% year on year. Dr. S. B. Garware, chairman and managing director of Garware Hi-Tech Films, said, “Global trade conditions continue to evolve amid tariff recalibrations and geopolitical realignments, and the company remains steadfast in its focus on long-term value creation through disciplined execution and strategic clarity. Our strategic vision is anchored in building a resilient, innovation-led organization capable of adapting to global transitions while capitalizing on emerging opportunities.” Monika Garware, vice chairperson and joint managing director of Garware Hi-Tech Films, added, “The company continued to make steady progress during the third quarter. Despite tariff-related impacts, revenues remained largely stable. More recently, we announced plans to establish a wholly owned subsidiary in the UAE to strengthen our export footprint across the MENA region and other international markets. As part of our D2C journey, we launched Garware Home Solutions with the opening of our first showroom in Mumbai. In addition, we set up two first-of-their-kind Global Application Studios in the Middle East, marking an important step in expanding our D2C initiatives and deepening customer engagement in the region. Our focus remains on disciplined execution and prudent risk management as we continue to pursue sustainable, long-term growth.” Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the establishment of a wholly owned subsidiary in the UAE to strengthen its export capabilities and expand its footprint across the Middle East, North Africa (MENA), and other international markets. Domestically, it launched Garware Home Solutions, a high-margin D2C business in architectural films, opening its first studio in Mumbai. Additionally, the company set up two first-of-their-kind Global Application Studios in the MENA region to enhance its international presence. Garware Hi-Tech Films is one of the largest manufacturers of sun control window films for architectural & automotive applications, paint protection films, and high-end BOPET films for label and industrial applications. Shares of Garware Hi-Tech Films rose 0.81% to settle at Rs 3,014.70 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GarwarePolyest_69101031050_189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[The New India Assurance Q3 PAT rises 9% YoY to Rs 380 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/the-new-india-assurance-q3-pat-rises-9-yoy-to-rs-380-cr/1669658</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669658</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income increased 14.2% YoY to Rs 12,234.97 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total income increased 14.2% YoY to Rs 12,234.97 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Consolidated profit before tax (PBT) surged 247% YoY to Rs 372.22 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 107.26 crore a year ago. For the quarter ended 31 December 2025, gross written premium stood at Rs 11,762.83 crore, up 8.32% YoY. Net written premium was at Rs 9,716.72 crore in the third quarter of FY25, registering a growth of 8.38% compared to the same period a year ago. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit rose 5.1% to Rs 371.59 crore on a 14.1% rise in total income to Rs 12,178.85 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 214.8% YoY to Rs 366.54 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 116.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Commenting on the Q3 result, Girija Subramanian, CMD, said, “Our Global Gross Written Premium for the nine-month period grew by 10.5%. Notably, our Domestic Gross Direct Premium growth significantly outpaced the industry average, resulting in our market share improving to 13.4%, compared to 12.8% in the corresponding previous year. The Q3FY26 incurred claim ratio stood at 90.77%, a significant improvement over the 94.49% reported in Q3FY25. The company recognized provisions of approximately Rs 2,500 Cr toward wage arrears and retirement benefits following government-approved wage revisions, partly offset by robust investment income from its equity portfolio. Despite these one-time costs, the company reported Profit Before Tax (PBT) growth of 62% for the nine-month period and 215% for the quarter. The company maintains a strong balance sheet, with improvements in net worth and general reserves, and a solvency ratio of 1.81 times, well above the regulatory requirement of 1.50 times.” The New India Assurance Company is India's largest non-life insurance company. Shares of The New India Assurance Company rose 1.23% to settle at Rs 148.70 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewIndiaAssuranceCompanyLtd_27148328361_12214.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Grid Q3 PAT jumps 8% YoY to Rs 4,185 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-grid-q3-pat-jumps-8-yoy-to-rs-4185-cr/1669647</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669647</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 12,395.09 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 12,395.09 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax and regulatory deferral account balances rose 6.7% YoY to Rs 5,238.79 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,909.32 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses rose 7.11% YoY to Rs 7,314.07 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Employee expenses stood at Rs 659.28 crore (up 10.48% YoY), and finance cost was at Rs 2,190.50 crore (up 14.24% YoY) during the period under review. On the segmental front, revenue from transmission business stood at Rs 11,801.23 crore (up 5.93% YoY), revenue from consultancy business stood at Rs 496.51 crore (up 106.27% YoY), and revenue from telecom business stood at Rs 298.79 crore (up 8.91% YoY) during the quarter. Meanwhile, the company’s board has recommended a second interim dividend of Rs 3.25 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the purpose of dividend payment has been fixed as Monday, 9 February 2026, and the second interim dividend will be paid to the members on Friday, 27 February 2026. Further, the Board cleared a proposal to borrow up to Rs 32,000 crore in FY26 through instruments including domestic bonds, term loans, external commercial borrowings, foreign currency bonds, multilateral funding, or supplier credit. Separately, Power Grid Corporation of India has approved an investment of Rs 173.14 crore for a power transmission project in Kerala, as per a regulatory filing on January 31. The project involves the augmentation of a third 500 MVA interconnecting transformer at the Thrissur 400/220 kV VSC HVDC station and is scheduled for commissioning by 21 August 2027. The Power Grid Corporation of India is a Maharatna CPSU and India’s largest electric power transmission company. Shares of Power Grid Corporation of India fell 1.61% to settle at Rs 256.35 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerGridCorpn_89479008350_5455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godfrey Phillips India posts steady Q3 FY26; PAT rises 8.7% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godfrey-phillips-india-posts-steady-q3-fy26-pat-rises-87-yoy/1669630</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669630</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a sequential basis, profit increased 12.6% from Rs 305 crore in Q2 FY26.

On a sequential basis, profit increased 12.6% from Rs 305 crore in Q2 FY26. Gross sales value for the quarter stood at Rs 4,737 crore, marking a 19.7% YoY increase and a 19.2% rise over the Q2 FY26 quarter. Net revenue rose 15.1% YoY to Rs 1,829 crore, compared with Rs 1,589 crore a year ago. Sequentially, net revenue jumped 41.9% from Rs 1,289 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA from operations came in at Rs 380 crore, up 5.3% YoY from Rs 361 crore in Q3 FY25. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, EBITDA increased 21.0% from Rs 314 crore. EBITDA margin stood at 8.0% in Q3 FY26, lower than 9.1% in the year-ago quarter and broadly unchanged from 7.9% in Q2 FY26. Cost of goods sold increased 16.6% YoY and 61.6% QoQ to Rs 1,115 crore, reflecting higher sales volumes. As a result, gross profit rose 12.8% YoY and 19.2% sequentially to Rs 714 crore. Gross margin stood at 15.1%, compared with 16.0% in Q3 FY25 and 15.1% in Q2 FY26. On the cost front, employee benefit expenses rose sharply by 36.8% YoY to Rs 119 crore, while other expenses increased 16.2% YoY to Rs 215 crore during the quarter. Godfrey Phillips India is engaged in manufacturing of cigarettes and tobacco products and trading of cigarettes, tobacco products and other retail products. Shares of Godfrey Phillips India rose 0.43% to settle at Rs 2035 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodfreyPhillips_19522234394_657.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITI MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/iti-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1669642</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669642</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITI Mutual Fund has announced 03 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following scheme.

ITI Mutual Fund has announced 03 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following scheme. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: ITI Balanced Advantage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.12 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.12 ITI Consumption Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.60 ITI Banking and Financial Services Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Flexi Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.60 ITI Focused Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Large Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI ELSS Tax Saver Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Multi Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Mid Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Small Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.60 ITI Value Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1669592</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669592</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced that, with effect from January 27, 2026, the Board of Directors of UTI Trustee Company Private Limited (Trustee to UTI Mutual Fund) has been reconstituted pursuant to the appointment of Mr.

UTI Mutual Fund has announced that, with effect from January 27, 2026, the Board of Directors of UTI Trustee Company Private Limited (Trustee to UTI Mutual Fund) has been reconstituted pursuant to the appointment of Mr. Ameet Pratapsinh Hariani as an Additional Director (Independent Category). Name: Mr. Ameet Pratapsinh Hariani Age: 65 years Designation: Additional Director (Independentategory) Qualification: B.Com, LLB, LLM

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1669561</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669561</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced that notice is hereby given to all investors and unit holders that, consequent to the appointment of Mr.

UTI Mutual Fund has announced that notice is hereby given to all investors and unit holders that, consequent to the appointment of Mr. Vetri Subramaniam as Managing Director & Chief Executive Officer of UTI Asset Management Company Limited, with effect from February 01, 2026, the following details shall form part of the Statement of Additional Information (SAI) of UTI Mutual Fund under the section titled “Details of AMC Directors.” Name: Mr. Vetri Subramaniam Age: 55 years Designation: Managing Director & Chief Executive Officer Qualification: 1. B. Com 2.Post Graduate Diploma in Management - IIM Bangalore

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Meesho posts wider losses despite strong revenue growth in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/meesho-posts-wider-losses-despite-strong-revenue-growth-in-q3-fy26/1669516</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669516</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter.

Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter. The company reported pre-tax loss of Rs 478.59 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a profit of Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenditure increased 43.99% YoY to Rs 4,060.20 crore in Q3 FY26, significantly outpacing revenue growth. Employee expenses rose 20.64% YoY to Rs 235.17 crore. Interest costs surged 141.61% YoY to Rs 3.89 crore, while depreciation declined 7.06% YoY to Rs 10.92 crore. Meesho's Annual Transacting Users surged 34% YoY to 251 million with net merchandise value (NMV) standing at Rs 10,995 crore, up 26% YoY. Over 9MFY26, it increased 37% YoY to Rs 30,189 crore. The company witnessed 690 million orders placed on its platform in the quarter under review, up 36% YoY. The contribution margin as a percentage of NMV stood at 2.3%, down 104 bps QoQ and 198 bps YoY due to accelerated Valmo scale-up following 3PL industry consolidation. "This is expected to normalise in the coming quarters," the company filing said. On a last twelve month basis, users transacted 9.78 times per year on average, growing 9% year-on-year, reflecting increasing purchase frequency. On a last twelve months basis, free cash flow stood at Rs 56 crore, supported by growth in NMV. As of 31 December 2025, Meesho's cash balance stood at Rs 7,277 crore, including Rs 4,088 crore raised through initial public offering in Dec FY26. Adjusted EBITDA marketplace margin for Q3FY26 was at -4.2% (Rs -460 crore) due to lower contribution margin and accelerated user growth and engineering investments. Adjusted EBITDA for New Initiatives was at Rs 19 crore, up 44% QoQ and 30% YoY with continuous improvement in user adoption for financial services platform. In a letter to the shareholders, Founder & CEO Vidit Aatrey said that the company has increased its investment into Advertising & Sales Promotion to 2.4% of NMV in Q3 FY26 from 1.3% of NMV in Q3 FY25. The company expects significant improvement in Adjusted EBITDA margin in the next two quarters returning to Q1 FY26 levels; driven by logistics cost recovery and operating leverage on user growth and technology investments made in FY26. The company said: "This marks our first quarter reporting as a public company and demonstrates our operating philosophy in action: continued growth in ATUs towards our mission of democratising internet commerce, and when forced to choose between near-term financial optimisation and long-term flywheel health, we chose the latter. We held order fulfillment charges stable, and increased user acquisition. Each decision positions us for stronger platform profitability in the long-term. These investments met our return thresholds; measured through payback periods, expected IRR against hurdle rates, and impact on long-term Free Cash Flow. 251 million ATUs, 9.78 purchase frequency, and 37% NMV growth for 9M FY26 validate such decisions made 12-18 months ago. Results lag strategy by several quarters in platform businesses. The growth we are capturing today compounds Meesho into a leadership position in value-led e-commerce over the next decade." Meesho is India’s largest e-commerce platform by annual transacting users and placed orders. Shares of Meesho rose 3.39% to settle at Rs 173.95 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MeeshoLtd_15936426_77963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MPS acquires US-based Unbound Medicine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mps-acquires-us-based-unbound-medicine/1669418</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669418</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The acquisition will be executed through MPS North America LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of MPS.

The acquisition will be executed through MPS North America LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of MPS. The transaction is expected to be completed on or before 10 February 2026, subject to the fulfilment of customary closing conditions, the company said in a regulatory filing. The acquisition will be carried out for a cash consideration of $16.50 million, subject to customary adjustments. Founded in 1999, Unbound Medicine provides digital medical reference tools, clinical decision-support solutions and healthcare learning platforms. Its services are delivered through proprietary mobile and web-based platforms and follow a subscription-led institutional business model. The company serves medical schools, hospital systems and healthcare associations across the United States and Canada. MPS said the acquisition aligns with its strategy of building platform-led, recurring-revenue businesses. The transaction is expected to support revenue diversification, enable cross-selling opportunities and strengthen the company’s presence in the North American market. MPS provides learning and platform solutions combining content, technology and artificial intelligence. The company is focused on scaling operations and strengthening its position in the global learning and knowledge services market. On a consolidated basis, net profit of MPS rose 57.32% to Rs 55.44 crore while net sales rose 9.42% to Rs 194.44 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. Shares of MPS rose 3.46% to settle at Rs 1884.80 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MPS_88654356883_18868.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>