<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:26:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with small gains in early trade; IT shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-small-gains-in-early-trade-it-shares-tumble/1671048</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671048</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded near the flatline with some positive points in early trade as investors turned cautious and booked profits after the sharp rally seen in the previous session.

The domestic equity indices traded near the flatline with some positive points in early trade as investors turned cautious and booked profits after the sharp rally seen in the previous session. Early pre-opening trends suggested profit-taking at higher levels, especially in index heavyweights, following Tuesday’s blockbuster surge triggered by the India and US trade deal. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark. Metal, auto and consumer durables shares advanced while IT, realty and media shares declined. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, rose 36.12 points or 0.04% to 83,757.87. The Nifty 50 index added 45.85 points or 0.18% to 25,773.40. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.03% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index added 0.01%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,966 shares rose and 1,134 shares fell. A total of 170 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 5,236.28 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,014.24 crore in the Indian equity market on 03 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: NBCC (India) rose 0.45%. The company said it has received six work orders from the Institute of Cost Accountants of India (ICMAI) and the Department of Fisheries, Uttarakhand, aggregating to Rs 271.32 crore. Toss The Coin added 1.83% after it has entered into a Master CMO Retainer Service Agreement along with a Statement of Work (SOW) with Definian Data, LLC, a US-based company headquartered at 135 S. LaSalle, Suite 2225, Chicago, Illinois, USA. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel will start its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday in the backdrop of growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation and more recently the long-awaited India-US trade deal ending prolonged uncertainty on the external front. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.13% to 6.730 compared with previous session close of 6.721. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.5050 compared with its close of 90.3200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement added 3.54% to Rs 159,247. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.05% to 97.43. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.02% to 4.271. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 46 cents or 0.68% to $67.79 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market mostly fell Wednesday, tracking Wall Street losses after a sell-off in U.S. technology stocks weighed on sentiment. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back as investors dumped technology stocks and moved into shares more broadly linked to improvements in the economy. The broad market index fell 0.84% and closed at 6,917.81. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 166.67 points, or 0.34%, to end at 49,240.99. Earlier, the 30-stock index rose as much as 0.5% to touch 49,653.13, a new record. The Nasdaq Composite shed 1.43%, settling at 23,255.19.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PG Electroplast Ltd Spikes 2.53%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pg-electroplast-ltd-spikes-253/1671043</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671043</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PG Electroplast Ltd rose 2.53% today to trade at Rs 576.45.

PG Electroplast Ltd rose 2.53% today to trade at Rs 576.45. The BSE Consumer Durables index is up 0.84% to quote at 57116.95. The index is down 6.73 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Amber Enterprises India Ltd increased 1.28% and Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Ltd added 1.07% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went down 5.25 % over last one year compared to the 5.94% surge in benchmark SENSEX. PG Electroplast Ltd has lost 8.59% over last one month compared to 6.73% fall in BSE Consumer Durables index and 2.56% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 10210 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 1.95 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 1008 on 23 Apr 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 471.15 on 14 Aug 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PGElectro_22594665328_38220.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd Slips 6.21%, BSE Information Technology index Shed 3.24%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/persistent-systems-ltd-slips-621-bse-information-technology-index-shed-324/1671044</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671044</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd fell 6.21% today to trade at Rs 5889.4.

Persistent Systems Ltd fell 6.21% today to trade at Rs 5889.4. The BSE Information Technology index is down 3.24% to quote at 35947.26. The index is down 1.86 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, HCL Technologies Ltd decreased 6.02% and Infosys Ltd lost 5.82% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 14.8 % over last one year compared to the 5.94% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Persistent Systems Ltd has lost 4.99% over last one month compared to 1.86% fall in BSE Information Technology index and 2.56% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 5588 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 18119 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 6597 on 23 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 4163.8 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PersistentSys_70071143_18286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Time Technoplast rises after subsidiary inks exclusive pact with Bulgarian battery maker Monbat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/time-technoplast-rises-after-subsidiary-inks-exclusive-pact-with-bulgarian-battery-maker-monbat/1671049</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671049</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PowerBuild Batteries is a leading Indian manufacturer of industrial and stationary lead-acid batteries.

PowerBuild Batteries is a leading Indian manufacturer of industrial and stationary lead-acid batteries. It serves diverse sectors including renewable energy, railways, UPS, invertors and power. Monbat AD, which is listed on Bulgarian Stock Exchange Sofia and is a part of the Prista Oil Group, has six decades of experience in manufacturing and recycling lead-acid, advanced VRLA, and lithium-ion batteries across facilities in Europe and Africa. Monbat serves global customers in automotive, data centre, UPS, telecom, renewable energy, and industrial infrastructure sectors. Under this arrangement, PowerBuild will exclusively distribute maintenance-free, advanced valve regulated lead-acid (VRLA) stationary and reserve power battery solutions from Monbat in India, catering to the rapidly expanding requirements of data centres, IT infrastructure, BFSI institutions, and other mission-critical industrial applications. India is witnessing a structural expansion in digital infrastructure also driven by the latest Union Budget announcement to promote localization of data centres in India, accelerating capacity creation and long-term investments in this sector. Current data centre capacity of 1.2-1.5 GW is expected to expand by an additional 3.0-3.5 GW over the next 7-10 years. This growth is supported by cumulative investments of 2.3-2.5 lakh crore. Alongside data centres, the BFSI sector’s expanding digital and disaster recovery infrastructure continues to generate sustained demand for high-reliability reserve power systems. Based on the above, Time Technoplast’s internal estimates project, these segments together can create a market opportunity for advanced VRLA batteries of approximately Rs 3,500-4,000 crore over the next decade. Through this collaboration, PowerBuild gains access to Monbat’s complete portfolio of Eurobat- compliant, high-reliability batteries engineered for mission-critical environments, including hyperscale and colocation data centres, financial data rooms, and disaster recovery facilities. PowerBuild will also provide pan-India technical support, including installation, commissioning and after-sales service. Time Technoplast is a global manufacturer of polymer products with operations across multiple countries. Its portfolio spans industrial packaging solutions, lifestyle products, automotive components, infrastructure / construction related products, material handling solutions & composite cylinders. The company's board will meet on 12 February 2026 to consider and approve the financial results for the quarter and the nine months ended on 31 December 2026. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Time Technoplast rose 17.04% to Rs 115.44 crore while net sales rose 10.3% to Rs 1,511.11 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimeTechnoplast_46114320009_27753.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Mankind Pharma, Godrej Agrovet, Bajaj Finance, Rubicon Research]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-mankind-pharma-godrej-agrovet-bajaj-finance-rubicon-research/1671050</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671050</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 04 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 04 February 2026. Result Today: Archean Chemical Industries, Apollo Tyres, Aptus Value Housing Finance India, Aurionpro Solutions, Automotive Axles, Avalon Technologies, Bajaj Finserv, Bajaj Holdings & Investment, Carysil, CCL Products (India), Century Plyboards (India), Cera Sanitaryware, Cummins India, Devyani International, Emami, Emcure Pharmaceuticals, Eureka Forbes, Force Motors, Gallantt Ispat, Greenply Industries, Hexaware Technologies, Inventurus Knowledge Solutions, Jain Irrigation Systems, Jaiprakash Power Ventures, JSW Cement, Jubilant Ingrevia, Kalpataru Projects International, Lloyds Engineering Works, Global Health, Metropolis Healthcare, NHPC, Parag Milk Foods, Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels, Pokarna, Quality Power Electrical Equipments, Redington, RITES, Rane (Madras), Keystone Realtors, Saatvik Green Energy, Sammaan Capital, Shipping Corporation of India Land and Assets, Tata Power Company, Transport Corporation of India, TeamLease Services, Tube Investments of India, Timken India, Tamilnad Mercantile Bank, Trent, Welspun Enterprises, Westlife Foodworld, Wonderla Holidays and Xpro India will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Bajaj Finance reported 6.33% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,977.85 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 4,246.54 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 17.63% YoY to Rs 21,213.89 crore in Q3 FY26. Mankind Pharma reported a 7.6% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 409 crore, driven by an 11.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3,567 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. Godrej Agrovet posted a 3% year-on-year growth in consolidated net profit to Rs 115 crore, while revenue increased 11% to Rs 2,718 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Rubucon Research reported 91.2% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 72.8 crore on 51.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 475.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Aditya Birla Capital’s consolidated net profit jumped 33.48% to Rs 945.02 crore on 27.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 11952.09 crore in Q3 FY36 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints after flat start for equities; RBI MPC to commence three-day policy meet]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-after-flat-start-for-equities-rbi-mpc-to-commence-three-day-policy-meet/1671028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671028</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 5.50 points, suggesting a flat start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 5.50 points, suggesting a flat start for the Nifty 50 today. The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel will start its three-day meting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday in the backdrop of growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation and more recently the long-awaited India-US trade deal ending prolonged uncertainty on the external front. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 5,236.28 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,014.24 crore in the Indian equity market on 03 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 2,815.48 so far in February (till 03 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia market mostly fell Wednesday, tracking Wall Street losses after a sell-off in U.S. technology stocks weighed on sentiment. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back as investors dumped technology stocks and moved into shares more broadly linked to improvements in the economy. The broad market index fell 0.84% and closed at 6,917.81. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 166.67 points, or 0.34%, to end at 49,240.99. Earlier, the 30-stock index rose as much as 0.5% to touch 49,653.13, a new record. The Nasdaq Composite shed 1.43%, settling at 23,255.19. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks ended sharply higher on Tuesday, rising for a second straight session on strong buying interest. Sentiment improved after India and the United States announced a long-awaited trade deal, easing tariff worries that had clouded markets for months. Supportive global cues and softer crude oil prices added to the momentum. The Nifty closed above the 25,700 mark. All NSE sectoral indices finished in positive territory, led by realty, pharma and consumer durables stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 2,072.67 points or 2.54% to 83,739.13. The Nifty 50 index added 639.15 points or 2.55% to 25,727.55. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.74% while the Nifty gained 3.63%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Toss The Coin bags Rs 81 lakh marketing services contract ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/toss-the-coin-bags-rs-81-lakh-marketing-services-contract/1670990</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670990</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the agreement covers a comprehensive suite of marketing services.

According to an exchange filing, the agreement covers a comprehensive suite of marketing services. The scope of work includes strategic enhancements, sales and marketing alignment, content and distribution expansion and operational add-ons. The total value of the order is approximately Rs 81.40 lakh (USD 90,000) and the contract is expected to be executed over a period of one year. The company clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in Definian Data. It further confirmed that the transaction does not fall under the category of related-party transactions, in compliance with applicable regulatory norms. Toss The Coin is a marketing consulting firm that provides customized marketing solutions, with a strong focus on B2B technology companies. Its services include go-to-market (GTM) strategy development, branding, content creation, website design, social media marketing, and customer success management. On the financial front, the company reported a strong performance for FY25, with consolidated net profit rising 14.5% year-on-year to Rs 1.26 crore, while total revenue surged 78% YoY to Rs 8.65 crore, compared to FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TOSSTHECOINLIMITED_24890768_93482.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>