<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:28:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI Governor highlights the important role of NBFCs and HFCs in facilitating credit flow]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-governor-highlights-the-important-role-of-nbfcs-and-hfcs-in-facilitating-credit-flow/1663350</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663350</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra yesterday held a meeting in Mumbai with the Managing Directors and Chief Executive Officers (MDs & CEOs) of select Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs), including Government NBFCs, Housing Finance Companies (HFCs) and Microfinance Institutions.

The Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra yesterday held a meeting in Mumbai with the Managing Directors and Chief Executive Officers (MDs & CEOs) of select Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs), including Government NBFCs, Housing Finance Companies (HFCs) and Microfinance Institutions. The participating entities together account for about 53 per cent of NBFC sector assets. Industry participation included the representatives of Self-Regulatory Organisations, Sa-Dhan, the Micro Finance Institutions Network and the Finance Industry Development Council. The meeting was also attended by Deputy Governors apart from other senior officers of the Reserve Bank. The RBI Governor highlighted the important role of NBFCs and HFCs in facilitating credit flow. He underlined the need for sound underwriting standards and close monitoring of asset quality. He further emphasised the criticality of customer-centricity, ethical conduct and responsible lending along with prompt grievance redressal for preserving confidence in the sector and supporting its orderly and sustainable development. During the discussion, participants shared feedback on policy issues and operational matters relating to the NBFC sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 26,150 mark; media shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-26150-mark-media-shares-decline/1663347</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663347</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded modest losses in the mid-morning trade as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S.

The key equity indices traded modest losses in the mid-morning trade as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S. tariffs against a steady stream of quarterly earnings reports that have kept hopes of an earnings recovery alive. The Nifty traded below 26,150 mark. Media shares slipped after advancing for previous four consecutive trading sessions. At 11:29 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 405.63 points or 0.46% to 85,056.28. The Nifty 50 index declined 104 points or 0.40% to 26,146.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.33% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.37%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,554 shares rose and 2,268 shares fell. A total of 216 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s services sector continued to expand in December 2025, but at the slowest pace in 11 months. The HSBC India Services PMI fell to 58.0 in December from 59.8 in November, indicating a moderation in activity while remaining well above the 50-point expansion threshold. Slower growth was driven by easing new business inflows and stalled hiring, while business confidence slipped to its lowest level in over three years. On the positive side, new export orders rose, supporting international demand, and inflationary pressures remained subdued, allowing firms to maintain competitive pricing. The composite PMI, which combines both services and manufacturing activity, also eased to 57.8, reflecting continued overall expansion of the economy but at a moderated pace. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index shed 0.86% to 1,459.40. The index added 2.52% in the previous four consecutive trading session. Saregama India (down 4.67%), Tips Music (down 1.73%), Sun TV Network (down 1.3%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 1.02%), D B Corp (down 0.6%) and Nazara Technologies (down 0.14%) declined. On the other hand, Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 0.56%), Prime Focus (up 0.35%) and Hathway Cable & Datacom (up 0.32%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: MOIL added 1.92% after the company said that it has achieved a record manganese ore production of 4.77 lakh tonnes in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of about 3.7% over the corresponding period last year (CPLY). AXIS Bank rose 0.44%. The company reported a 12.3% increase in average total deposits to Rs 11,97,400 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 10,66,400 crore in Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets opened mixed Tuesday, building on a record-breaking rally in global stocks as investors continued to assess ongoing geopolitical tensions following the U.S.′ attack on Venezuela and capture of ousted leader Nicolas Maduro. U.S. big oil got a boost from the country's military raid at the weekend that captured Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Crude oil eased back after rising $1 a barrel overnight as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Overall, however, the events had a limited effect on risk sentiment, with equities driven more by momentum and currencies focused on macroeconomic data. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. Trump plans to meet with executives from U.S. oil companies later this week to discuss boosting Venezuelan oil production, media reports stated. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose even after the U.S.′ attack on Venezuela, as crude oil prices advanced and investors bet the action would not lead to broader geopolitical conflict. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 594.79 points, or 1.23%, to close at 48,977.18. The 30-stock index also hit a new all-time high in the session. The S&P 500 advanced 0.64% and ended at 6,902.05. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.69%, settling at 23,395.82.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concept-with-oil-rig-in-the-gulf-picture-id597_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dev Information Tech jumps after bagging Rs 26 lakh order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dev-information-tech-jumps-after-bagging-rs-26-lakh-order/1663346</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663346</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order is for the supply of AutoCAD along with specialised toolsets under a fixed-cost contract.

The order is for the supply of AutoCAD along with specialised toolsets under a fixed-cost contract. The scope includes industry-specific productivity tools, compliance and auditability, and operational readiness and support. The company said the order will be executed over a period of around two months. The services will be delivered for Goa Shipyard, a Government of India undertaking under the Ministry of Defence. Dev Information Technology clarified that the order has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related-party transactions. Earlier on 1 January 2026, the firm announced that it had secured an order worth Rs 1.90 crore from Gujarat’s Directorate of Food and Civil Supplies. The two-month contract involves providing an RDBMS platform for multiple digital service portals, including e-Rasan, My Ration and DBT applications. Dev Information Technology is an IT services company providing cloud services, digital transformation, enterprise applications, and managed IT services. The company's consolidated net profit climbed 786.3% to Rs 71.88 crore on a 35% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 48.51 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DevInformationTechnologyLtd_93091952440_70312.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index softens under 98 mark in Asia]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-softens-under-98-mark-in-asia/1663345</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663345</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar index is easing after hitting near four-week high as the markets focus on economic updates and strength in equities caps upside for the US currency.

The US dollar index is easing after hitting near four-week high as the markets focus on economic updates and strength in equities caps upside for the US currency. A report released by the Institute for Supply Management on Monday showed its reading on US manufacturing activity decreased in the month of December. The ISM said its manufacturing PMI edged down to 47.9 in December after slipping to 48.2 in November, with a reading below 50 indicating contraction. The inflationary pressures were also tepid with prices index component of the PMI coming in at 58.5 in December, unchanged from November. The US dollar index slipped under 98 mark following this and currently quotes at 97.94, down marginally on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Abbott India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-abbott-india-ltd-counter/1663344</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663344</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lodha Developers Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd, Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd, Delhivery Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 06 January 2026.

Lodha Developers Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd, Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd, Delhivery Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 06 January 2026. Abbott India Ltd notched up volume of 7249 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 15.24 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 476 shares. The stock gained 0.79% to Rs.28,400.00. Volumes stood at 145 shares in the last session. Lodha Developers Ltd recorded volume of 4.4 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 11.05 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 39790 shares. The stock slipped 1.20% to Rs.1,106.90. Volumes stood at 1.31 lakh shares in the last session. Poly Medicure Ltd registered volume of 43001 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.93 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7250 shares. The stock gained 5.41% to Rs.1,816.80. Volumes stood at 7959 shares in the last session. Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd saw volume of 90157 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 3.73 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 24161 shares. The stock slipped 3.16% to Rs.556.00. Volumes stood at 31059 shares in the last session. Delhivery Ltd clocked volume of 1.7 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 2.99 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 56985 shares. The stock gained 0.15% to Rs.412.95. Volumes stood at 38922 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AbbottIndia_90273760573_90.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MOIL edges higher after manganese ore production rises 3.7% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/moil-edges-higher-after-manganese-ore-production-rises-37-yoy-in-q3/1663339</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663339</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA["This is the highest-ever production achieved by the company in any third quarter since its inception," MOIL stated.

"This is the highest-ever production achieved by the company in any third quarter since its inception," MOIL stated. The public sector undertaking’s 9M FY26 production of manganese ore aggregated to 14.21 lakh tonnes, up 6.8% YoY. "The sustained improvement in production performance is a result of focused mine planning, operational discipline, enhanced mechanization, and the dedicated efforts of MOIL’s workforce across all operating units," the company said in a statement. MOIL is a Schedule 'A' Miniratna Category-I public sector undertaking (PSU) that is engaged in the business of mining and supplying manganese. At present, the company operates its underground and opencast mines located in the Nagpur and Bhandara districts of Maharashtra and Balaghat district of Madhya Pradesh. The company's net profit jumped 40.99% to Rs 70.44 crore on a 19.24% increase in revenue to Rs 348.05 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MOIL_19199606417_13863.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Railways utilises over 80% of CAPEX in first three quarters of current fiscal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-railways-utilises-over-80-of-capex-in-first-three-quarters-of-current-fiscal/1663338</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663338</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Railways has maintained a strong trend in the utilization of allocated Gross Budgetary Support (GBS) outlays for 2025-26.

Indian Railways has maintained a strong trend in the utilization of allocated Gross Budgetary Support (GBS) outlays for 2025-26. As of the end of December 2025, Indian Railways has spent 80.54 per cent, i.e., Rs 2,03,138 crore of the total GBS of ₹2,52,200 crore. This represents a 6.54 per cent increase in GBS utilization compared to the same period last year (December 2024). The expenditure has primarily focused on safety measures, capacity enhancement, infrastructure modernization, and passenger amenities. In the category of safety-related works, 84 per cent of the allocated funds have been utilized. For capacity augmentation, out of Rs 1,09,238 crore allocated, Rs 76,048 crore (69 per cent) has been expended. Customer amenities have seen 80 per cent utilization, with expenditure amounting to Rs 9,575 crore till December 2025. The results of consistent capital expenditure (CAPEX) over the last decade are evident in 164 Vande Bharat train services, 30 Amrit Bharat train services, the implementation of the Kavach automatic train protection system, over 99 per cent electrification of the broad-gauge network, and extensive works covering new lines, gauge conversion, track doubling, traffic facilities, investments in PSUs, and metropolitan transport systems. These trends indicate that the Ministry of Railways’ GBS expenditure plan is on track, with infrastructural works being executed expeditiously.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Emmvee Photovoltaic Power soars after global brokerage initiates Buy call]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/emmvee-photovoltaic-power-soars-after-global-brokerage-initiates-buy-call/1663337</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663337</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The brokerage expects India’s solar installations to grow rapidly on the back of lower tariffs, rising power demand and policy support for domestic manufacturers.

The brokerage expects India’s solar installations to grow rapidly on the back of lower tariffs, rising power demand and policy support for domestic manufacturers. Emmvee was highlighted for its early move into high-efficiency TOPCon technology and aggressive capacity expansion, with cell and module capacities seen rising sharply by FY27. While near-term margin risks remain due to potential oversupply, the brokerage expects profitability to stabilise over time, supporting strong earnings growth. Bengaluru-based Emmvee Photovoltaic Power is a renewable energy company. It manufactures of Solar PV modules and systems. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 577.3% to Rs 237.86 crore on an 181.1% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1,131 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EmmveePhotovoltaicPowerLtd_42839158_72748.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AXIS Bank’s average total deposits rise 12% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-banks-average-total-deposits-rise-12-yoy-in-q3/1663336</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663336</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a sequential basis, the bank’s average total deposits increased 5.1%.

On a sequential basis, the bank’s average total deposits increased 5.1%. Average CASA deposits stood at Rs 4,48,200 crore as of 31 December 2025, registering a 3.3% quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) growth and an 8.9% YoY growth. The bank’s gross advances (end balance) rose 14.1% YoY to Rs 11,70,500 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 10,25,900 crore in Q3 FY25. On a QoQ basis, gross advances increased 3.7%. Total deposits (end balance) increased 15% YoY and 4.8% QoQ to Rs 12,60,800 crore in Q3 FY26. Axis Bank is the third-largest private sector bank in India. As of 30th September 2025, the bank's distribution network comprised 5,976 domestic branches and 13,177 ATMs. The bank reported a 26.42% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 5,089.64 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 6,917.57 crore in Q2 FY25. Total income increased 1.22% YoY to Rs 37,594.81 crore in Q2 FY26. The bank’s net interest income (NII) stood at Rs 13,745 crore in Q2 FY26, up 1% QoQ and 2% YoY basis. Net Interest Margin (NIM) for Q2 FY26 stood at 3.73%. The counter rose 0.17% to Rs 1,288 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AxisBank_99376846491_5554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aptech bags Rs 4-cr training order from state government body]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aptech-bags-rs-4-cr-training-order-from-state-government-body/1663334</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663334</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract is required to be executed during the financial year 2025–26.

The contract is required to be executed during the financial year 2025–26. Aptech is primarily engaged in the business of education, training, and assessment solution services. It is a global learning solutions company that has commenced its education and training business for over the last three decades. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 17.5% to Rs 6.46 crore on a 6.6% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 134.88 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Aptech shed 0.26% to Rs 91.63 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Aptech_92953066796_8039.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade with minor cuts; oil & gas shares decline for 2th day in row]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-minor-cuts-oil-gas-shares-decline-for-2th-day-in-row/1663333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663333</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in the in the morning trade as investors weighed the risks of new U.S.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in the in the morning trade as investors weighed the risks of new U.S. tariffs against a steady stream of quarterly earnings reports that have kept hopes of an earnings recovery alive. The Nifty traded below the 26,250 mark, while oil and gas shares extended losses for a second consecutive session. At 10:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 188.50 points or 0.22% to 85,251.12. The Nifty 50 index fell 25.95 points or 0.10% to 26,224.35. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.19%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,604 shares rose and 1,984 shares fell. A total of 243 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index fell 1.51% to 12,029.60. The index declined 2.51% in the two consecutive trading session. Reliance Industries (down 2.71%), Gujarat Gas (down 1.68%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 1.5%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 1.31%) and Mahanagar Gas (down 1.21%), Aegis Logistics (down 0.94%), Indian Oil Corporation (down 0.79%), Gujarat State Petronet (down 0.64%), GAIL (India) (down 0.31%) and Castrol India (down 0.29%) declined. On the other hand, Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (up 1.05%) ,Indraprastha Gas (up 0.27%) and Petronet LNG (up 0.12%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Awfis Space Solutions shed 0.36%. The company announced the resignation of Ravi Dugar from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) and key managerial personnel of the company to pursue better career opportunities. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (PV) declined 2.02% after Jaguar Land Rover (JLR)’s Q3 volumes were impacted by a cyber-incident and US tariffs, leading to sharp year-on-year and sequential declines in both wholesale and retail sales. DCX Systems fell 1.60%. The company said it has secured an order worth Rs 11.33 crore from Rafael Advanced Defence Systems, Israel, for the manufacture and supply of cable and wire harness assemblies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trent slumps after Q3 business update signals slower momentum]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trent-slumps-after-q3-business-update-signals-slower-momentum/1663331</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663331</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Standalone revenue from the sale of products, excluding GST, rose 17% YoY to Rs 5,220 crore in Q3 FY26.

Standalone revenue from the sale of products, excluding GST, rose 17% YoY to Rs 5,220 crore in Q3 FY26. This compares with Rs 4,466 crore in the year-ago quarter. For the nine months ended December 2025, revenue increased 18% YoY to Rs 14,604 crore from Rs 12,368 crore. However, investors focused on the growth trajectory. Revenue growth was flat sequentially and matched the 17% YoY growth reported in Q2 FY26. This was slower than the growth seen in Q3 FY25, Q4 FY25 and Q1 FY26, raising concerns over moderation. Store expansion remained strong. As of 31 December 2025, Trent operated 278 Westside stores and 854 Zudio stores, including four in the UAE. It also ran 32 stores across other lifestyle concepts. During Q3 FY26, the company added a net 17 Westside stores and 48 Zudio stores. Net additions for the nine-month period stood at 30 Westside stores and 89 Zudio stores. Despite consistent execution and aggressive expansion, the lack of sequential acceleration appeared to trigger selling in the stock. Trent is part of the Tata Group and operates a portfolio of retail concepts. The primary customer propositions of Trent include Westside, one of India's leading chains of fashion retail stores, Zudio, a one stop destination for great fashion at great value and Star, which operates in the competitive food, grocery and daily needs segment. In Q2 FY26, Trent's consolidated revenue from operations rose 16% year-on-year to Rs 4818 crore and EBITDA increased 14% to Rs 575 crore, while profit after tax grew 11% to Rs 373 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Trent_20841567073_345.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663332</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663332</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has that Mr.

UTI Mutual Fund has that Mr. Kapil Udaiwal, President & Head - Human Resources,UTI Asset Management Company Limited effective from January 1, 2026: Details of Mr. Kapil Udaiwal Age: 48 years Designation: President & Head - Human Resources Qualification: B.Sc., Master in Labour Laws & Labour Welfare, PGDM (PM & HR)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suraj Estate's One Business Bay project clocks gross bookings of Rs 200 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suraj-estates-one-business-bay-project-clocks-gross-bookings-of-rs-200-crore/1663330</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663330</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has achieved a sale of an area of 40,000 square feet within 45 days of the launch of the project, which translates to a GDV of Rs 200 crore out of the total esmated project GDV of Rs 1,200 crore.

The company has achieved a sale of an area of 40,000 square feet within 45 days of the launch of the project, which translates to a GDV of Rs 200 crore out of the total esmated project GDV of Rs 1,200 crore. One Business Bay project, with a sale area of 2.09 lakhs square feet, is being developed on freehold land parcels admeasuring 0.75 acres and is well-connected to Senapati Bapat Marg. Designed by Architect Hafeez Contractor, One Business Bay has been designed as a complete ecosystem that can accommodate 182 premium business office units. Encouraged by early traction at One Business Bay, the company is selectively evaluating similar opportunities for commercial projects within the South-Central Mumbai micro-market. Rahul Thomas, whole-time director, Suraj Estate Developers, said: “The initial soles momentum at One Business Bay validates our decision to expand into the commercial segment. Our continued focus on commercial real estate is a natural progression, backed by decades of development experience in South Central Mumbai and a strong understanding of this micro-market.” Suraj Estate Developers develops real estate across the residential and commercial sectors in South Central Mumbai region. The company has a residential portfolio located in the markets of Mahim, Dadar, Prabhadevi and Parel. On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 4% year-on-year to Rs 33.1 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 31.8 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 144.6 crore, up 33% YoY from Rs 109.1 crore in Q2 FY25. The scrip rose 0.23% to currently trade at Rs 258.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Suraj-Estate-Developers-Ltd_43877842_76563.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Awfis Space Solutions CFO Ravi Dugar resigns]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/awfis-space-solutions-cfo-ravi-dugar-resigns/1663327</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663327</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s board has appointed Sumit Rochlani as Chief Financial Officer (CFO), key managerial personnel, and senior managerial personnel, with effect from 3 February 2026.

The company’s board has appointed Sumit Rochlani as Chief Financial Officer (CFO), key managerial personnel, and senior managerial personnel, with effect from 3 February 2026. Rochlani brings over 14 years of experience in finance and is a Chartered Accountant, having qualified from the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India (ICAI) in 2009. He has expertise across audit, controllership, financial planning & analysis (FP&A), corporate finance, and indirect taxation. Awfis Space Solutions is India's largest and first listed flexible workspace solutions provider of modern workspaces. The company enables small and large corporates to seamlessly book and utilize workspaces as per their requirements and convenience. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 58.7% to Rs 15.97 crore, despite a 25.5% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 366.86 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Awfis Space Solutions shed 0.73% to Rs 483.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AWFISSpaceSolutionsLtd_53289943_77804.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Motors PV skid as cyber incident & tariffs dent JLR Q3 volumes ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-motors-pv-skid-as-cyber-incident-tariffs-dent-jlr-q3-volumes/1663325</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663325</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[JLR is a wholly owned subsidiary of the company.

JLR is a wholly owned subsidiary of the company. Wholesale volumes for the third quarter were 59,200 units (excluding the Chery Jaguar Land Rover China JV (‘CJLR’) ), down 43.3% YoY and down 10.6% QoQ. wholesale declined across all the regions, with the UK down 0.9%, North America down 64.4%, Europe down 47.6%, China down 46.0 %, MENA down 8.5% and Overseas down 50.4%. The overall mix of Range Rover, Range Rover Sport and Defender models accounted for 74.3% of total wholesale volumes in Q3 FY26, up from 70.3% in Q3 FY25 and down from 76.7% in the prior quarter. Retail sales stood at 79,600 units (including CJLR ) in Q3 FY26, marking a decline of 25.1% YoY and 6.7% QoQ. Retail volumes were lower across all key markets in Q3 FY26, comprising the UK which was down 13.3%, North America down 37.7%, Europe down 26.9%, China down 18.4%, MENA down 18.7% and Overseas down 14.1%. The company said that production returned to normal levels only by mid-November post the cyber incident. Due to this and also the time required to distribute vehicles globally once produced, wholesale and retail volumes reduced on a quarter-on-quarter and year-on-year basis. In addition, the planned wind down of legacy Jaguar models ahead of the launch of new Jaguar, and incremental US tariffs impacting JLR’s US exports, continued to impact volumes. JLR is scheduled to report its full financial results for Q3 FY26 in February 2026. Tata Motors Group is a leading global automobile manufacturer. Part of the illustrious multinational conglomerate, the Tata Group, it offers a wide and diverse portfolio of cars, sports utility vehicles, trucks, buses, and defense vehicles to the world.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataMotors_19446492084_560.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Ports records 9% YoY growth in Dec'25 cargo volumes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-ports-records-9-yoy-growth-in-dec25-cargo-volumes/1663307</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663307</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[During the month, logistics rail volumes stood at 59,037 TEUs, remaining flat compared with the year-ago period.

During the month, logistics rail volumes stood at 59,037 TEUs, remaining flat compared with the year-ago period. Volumes under the General Purpose Wagon Investment Scheme (GPWIS) declined 7% YoY to 1.8 MMT. For the year-to-date (YTD) period ended 31 December 2025, APSEZ handled 367.3 MMT of cargo, registering an 11% YoY increase. Container volumes continued to outperform, rising 21% YoY during the period. Logistics rail volumes for the YTD period increased 11% YoY to 528,872 TEUs, while GPWIS volumes stood at 16.1 MMT, broadly flat on a YoY basis. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) is the largest private port operator in India. APSEZ operates a portfolio of 15 domestic ports/terminals with an international presence at 4 global ports/terminals. Along with its port operations, it has its wide logistics network and offers various port-based marine services to its owned ports/terminals as well as other ports. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) has reported a 29% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,120 crore on a 30% rise in revenue to Rs 9,167 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The counter slipped 1.02% to Rs 1,477.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniPorts_15044199473_21281.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DCX Systems bags Rs 11-cr defence order from Rafael]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dcx-systems-bags-rs-11-cr-defence-order-from-rafael/1663290</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663290</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DCX Systems is a leading Indian defense manufacturing player for the manufacturing and supply of electronic systems, cable & wire harness assemblies, and printed circuit board assemblies.

DCX Systems is a leading Indian defense manufacturing player for the manufacturing and supply of electronic systems, cable & wire harness assemblies, and printed circuit board assemblies. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 9.04 crore in Q2 FY26 as against a net profit of Rs 5.22 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 1.4% YoY to Rs 192.85 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of DCX Systems fell 1.34% to Rs 191.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DCXSystemsLtd_25003026_76686.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Government of India announces the sale of two dated securities for a notified amount of &#8377;29,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/government-of-india-announces-the-sale-of-two-dated-securities-for-a-notified-amount-of-837729000-crore/1663287</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663287</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of (i) “6.68% Government Security 2040” for a notified amount of ₹16,000 crore and (ii) “6.90% Government Security 2065” for a notified amount of ₹13,000 crore.

The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of (i) “6.68% Government Security 2040” for a notified amount of ₹16,000 crore and (ii) “6.90% Government Security 2065” for a notified amount of ₹13,000 crore. The auction will be conducted using multiple price method. Both competitive and non-competitive bids for the auction should be submitted in electronic format on the Reserve Bank of India Core Banking Solution (e-Kuber system) on January 09, 2026 (Friday). GoI will have the option to retain additional subscription up to ₹2,000 crore against each security.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drift lower in early trade; VIX jumps 1.89%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drift-lower-in-early-trade-vix-jumps-189/1663286</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663286</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses in early trade, reflecting mixed sectoral performance and cautious investor sentiment.

The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses in early trade, reflecting mixed sectoral performance and cautious investor sentiment. The Nifty traded below the 26,200 level. Metal, PSU bank and financial services shares advanced while oil & gas, media and FMCG shares declined. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 356.30 points or 0.42% to 85,078.23. The Nifty 50 index fell 79.35 points or 0.30% to 26,170.95. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.16%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,364 shares rose and 1,633 shares fell. A total of 187 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 1.89% to 10.21. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 36.25 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,764.07 crore in the Indian equity market on 05 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Dabur India fell 2.54%. The company said that it expects consolidated revenue to grow in the mid-single digits with operating profit and Profit after Tax to grow ahead of revenue in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, early signs of demand recovery were witnessed, aided by GST rate revisions. Post trade stabilisation, consumer sentiment improved in urban and rural areas. Rural demand continued to outperform urban demand this quarter as well. Kotak Mahindra Bank rose 0.90%. The bank’s average total deposits climbed 14.7% to Rs 5,26,025 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 5,10,138 crore as of 31st December 2024. Average advances jumped 16.2% YoY to Rs 465,879 crore as of 31st December 2025. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.02% to 6.635 compared with previous session close of 6.633. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1450 compared with its close of 90.3000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement added 0.18% to Rs 138,387. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.10% to 98.22. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.26% to 4.179. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 18 cents or 0.29% to $61.58 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets opened mixed Tuesday, building on a record-breaking rally in global stocks as investors continued to assess ongoing geopolitical tensions following the U.S.′ attack on Venezuela and capture of ousted leader Nicolas Maduro. U.S. big oil got a boost from the country's military raid at the weekend that captured Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Crude oil eased back after rising $1 a barrel overnight as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Overall, however, the events had a limited effect on risk sentiment, with equities driven more by momentum and currencies focused on macroeconomic data. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. Trump plans to meet with executives from U.S. oil companies later this week to discuss boosting Venezuelan oil production, media reports stated. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose even after the U.S.′ attack on Venezuela, as crude oil prices advanced and investors bet the action would not lead to broader geopolitical conflict. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 594.79 points, or 1.23%, to close at 48,977.18. The 30-stock index also hit a new all-time high in the session. The S&P 500 advanced 0.64% and ended at 6,902.05. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.69%, settling at 23,395.82.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>