<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:49:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR recovers amid dollar weakness overseas; positive start to markets support]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-recovers-amid-dollar-weakness-overseas-positive-start-to-markets-support/1679405</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679405</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee recovered slightly in opening trades but remained largely range bound.

The Indian rupee recovered slightly in opening trades but remained largely range bound. INR opened at Rs 90.94 per dollar and climbed to a high of 90.88 so far during the day. Dollar weakness and positive local shares also supported the local unit. The dollar index slipped below 97.8 on Wednesday, giving back some of the previous session’s gains after President Donald Trump offered no indication of altering his tariff policies in his State of the Union address. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty slumped by 1.3 percent and 1.1 percent, respectively on Tuesday, with uncertainties over the India-U.S. trade deal, U.S.-Iran tensions and worries over AI-related disruptions weighing on markets. Foreign investors net sold shares worth Rs 103 crore on Tuesday while domestic institutional investors net bought shares to the extent of Rs 3,161 crore, according to provisional exchange data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HG Infra rises after emerging L1 bidder for Rs 1,582-cr NHAI project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hg-infra-rises-after-emerging-l1-bidder-for-rs-1582-cr-nhai-project/1679400</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679400</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves construction from Gobindpur (NH-55) to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza (NH-16), covering a length of 40.33 km in Odisha under NH(O).

The project involves construction from Gobindpur (NH-55) to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza (NH-16), covering a length of 40.33 km in Odisha under NH(O). The estimated project cost is Rs 1,827.33 crore, while HG Infra’s bid stands at Rs 1,582.11 crore, excluding applicable GST. The project is to be completed within 910 days. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity. The company stated that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding authority. It further clarified that the order does not fall under related party transactions. H.G. Infra Engineering is an Indian road infrastructure company engaged in the business of Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) services and maintenance of roads, bridges, flyovers, and other infrastructure contract works. The company reported an 18.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 94.28 crore on a 12.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,421.16 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HGInfraEngineeringLtd_52714149365_71631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin gets USFDA nod for Brivaracetam Oral Solution]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-gets-usfda-nod-for-brivaracetam-oral-solution/1679385</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679385</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Brivaracetam Oral Solution is bioequivalent to Briviact Oral Solution, 10 mg/mL, of UCB, Inc.

Brivaracetam Oral Solution is bioequivalent to Briviact Oral Solution, 10 mg/mL, of UCB, Inc. and is indicated for the treatment of partial-onset seizures in patients aged one month and older. Following the regulatory approval, the company has initiated the launch of Brivaracetam Oral Solution in the United States market. According to IQVIA MAT data for December 2025, Brivaracetam Oral Solution (RLD Briviact) recorded estimated annual sales of $135 million in the US. The approval strengthens Lupin’s portfolio in the central nervous system (CNS) segment and reinforces its presence in the US generics market. Lupin is a global pharmaceutical leader headquartered in Mumbai, India, with products distributed in over 100 markets. It specializes in pharmaceutical products, including branded and generic formulations, complex generics, biotechnology products, and active pharmaceutical ingredients. The pharmaceutical company reported a 37.46% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,175.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 855.16 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter rose 0.48% to Rs 2,263.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Biocon gets US FDA nod for chronic weight management drug Liraglutide ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/biocon-gets-us-fda-nod-for-chronic-weight-management-drug-liraglutide/1679399</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679399</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Liraglutide is a drug-device combination formulation used in the treatment of chronic weight management, indicated as an adjunct to a reduced-calorie diet and increased physical activity.

Liraglutide is a drug-device combination formulation used in the treatment of chronic weight management, indicated as an adjunct to a reduced-calorie diet and increased physical activity. GLP-1 receptor agonists have emerged as one of the fastest growing therapeutic classes globally, driven by the rising prevalence of obesity and metabolic disorders, strong clinical outcomes, and increasing physician adoption. According to IQVIA MAT December 2025 the total addressable market opportunity for GLP-1 in weight loss in the U.S. was US $127 million. Siddharth Mittal, chief executive officer and managing director, Biocon, said: “This timely approval of gSaxenda in the United States marks a defining milestone for Biocon, validating our scientific depth, our vertically integrated development and manufacturing platform, and our ability to bring complex drug products to markets around the world. GLP-1 therapies represent a significant growth driver for the company, with the U.S. being an important market in this strategy.” Biocon is a global biopharma company dedicated to improving affordable access to therapies for chronic conditions such as diabetes, cancer, and autoimmune diseases. The company's consolidated net profit surged to Rs 143.80 crore in the quarter ended December 2025 as against Rs 25.10 crore during the previous quarter ended December 2024. Sales rose 9.28% to Rs 4,123 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip rose 0.35% to currently trade at Rs 391.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Biocon_44501850463_14801.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market opens higher in early trade; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-opens-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-strong/1679383</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679383</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with substantial gains in the early trade.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with substantial gains in the early trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,550 mark. Barring the Nifty Chemical index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the green, with the IT, metal and oil & gas indices gaining the most. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 515.93 points or 0.62% to 82,741.85. The Nifty 50 index gained 146.40 points or 0.58% to 25,571.05. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.44% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.43%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,050 shares rose and 872 shares fell. A total of 169 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 102.53 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,161.22 crore in the Indian equity market on 24 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: HG Infra Engineering rallied 3.38% after the company was declared the lowest bidder (L1) by NHAI for a project worth Rs 1,582 crore. The project involves the construction of a six-lane, access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road (Package-III) from Gobindpur (NH-55) to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza (NH-16) in Odisha under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) slipped 3.70%. The company said that the Government of India will sell up to 26.13 crore equity shares (2% stake) on 25–26 February, with an option to additionally sell up to 26.13 crore shares (2% stake) through the offer-for-sale (OFS) route on BSE and NSE. The floor price has been fixed at Rs 104 per share. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) shed 0.25%. The company has received a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 270.22 crore from Central Railway. The order pertains to the design, supply, erection, testing, and commissioning of a 220/132/55 kV traction substation and associated works for the Daund–Solapur section. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper declined 0.12% to 6.677 compared with previous session close of 6.699. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9275 compared with its close of 90.9500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement gained 0.35% to Rs 160,534. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.07% to 97.70. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.25% to 4.043. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 55 cents or 0.78% to $71.32 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian markets edged higher with South Korea and Japan stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd Surges 1.98%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-ltd-surges-198/1679379</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679379</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd gained 1.98% today to trade at Rs 709.2.

Vedanta Ltd gained 1.98% today to trade at Rs 709.2. The BSE Metal index is up 0.77% to quote at 40172.06. The index is up 6.06 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd increased 1.91% and National Aluminium Company Ltd added 1.32% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 43.04 % over last one year compared to the 10.63% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Vedanta Ltd has added 3.62% over last one month compared to 6.06% gain in BSE Metal index and 1.22% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 49763 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 13.13 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 770 on 29 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 362.2 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests positive start for key indices]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-positive-start-for-key-indices/1679368</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679368</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 19.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 19.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 102.53 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,161.22 crore in the Indian equity market on 24 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have bought shares worth Rs 1,369.93 crore in the cash market so far in February (till 23 February 2026). This is in contrast to their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian markets edged higher with South Korea and Japan stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker. Domestic Market: Indian benchmark indices suffered a major setback on Tuesday, as a brutal sell-off in the information technology sector dragged the market into the deep red. The expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE intensified volatility. The primary catalyst for the decline was a massive rout in IT heavyweights, triggered by fears of AI-led disruption after Anthropic’s "Claude Code" tool raised concerns about the long-term viability of the traditional labor-arbitrage model. Adding to the gloom were renewed global trade anxieties following U.S. President Donald Trump’s threats of universal tariffs and escalating geopolitical tensions that led the Brent crude towards the $72-per-barrel mark. By the closing bell, the carnage had wiped out over Rs 4 lakh crore in investor wealth, leaving only a few defensive sectors like metals and FMCG in positive territory. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 479.95 points or 0.58% to 83,294.66. The Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: HG Infra, IRFC, RVNL, Schaeffler India, Dr Reddys Lab, Waaree Energies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-hg-infra-irfc-rvnl-schaeffler-india-dr-reddys-lab-waaree-energies/1679365</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679365</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[New listing: In the SME segment, Yashhtej Industries (India) is scheduled to debut on the bourses today.

New listing: In the SME segment, Yashhtej Industries (India) is scheduled to debut on the bourses today. The company’s IPO was subscribed 1.35 times. The issue price was fixed at Rs 110 per share. Stocks to Watch: HG Infra Engineering has been declared the lowest bidder (L1) by NHAI for a project worth Rs 1,582 crore. The project involves the construction of a six-lane, access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road (Package-III) from Gobindpur (NH-55) to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza (NH-16) in Odisha under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) said that the Government of India will sell up to 26.13 crore equity shares (2% stake) on 25–26 February, with an option to additionally sell up to 26.13 crore shares (2% stake) through the offer-for-sale (OFS) route on BSE and NSE. The floor price has been fixed at Rs 104 per share. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) has received a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 270.22 crore from Central Railway. The order pertains to the design, supply, erection, testing, and commissioning of a 220/132/55 kV traction substation and associated works for the Daund–Solapur section. Waaree Energies announced that its subsidiary, Waaree Forever Energies, has received a Letter of Award from Solar Energy Corporation of India for the development of a 300 MW wind power project in Dwarka, Gujarat. Hindalco Industries said that Novelis has entered into a subscription agreement with AV Minerals, its sole shareholder and a wholly owned subsidiary of the company. AV Minerals will purchase 13.33 lakh Novelis common shares for $200 million at a price of $150 per share. Lupin has received approval from the US FDA for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for Brivaracetam Oral Solution 10 mg/mL. The product is bioequivalent to Briviact Oral Solution and is indicated for the treatment of partial-onset seizures. The reference-listed drug had estimated annual US sales of $135 million. Hexaware Technologies has expanded its collaboration with Amazon Web Services (AWS) to deliver AI-enabled software development lifecycle (SDLC) capabilities, building on its Strategic Collaboration Agreement (SCA) with AWS. Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories has received a letter from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) stating that it has concluded its investigation and does not intend to recommend enforcement action against the company at this time. The investigation related to allegations of improper payments to healthcare professionals in Ukraine and potential violations of US anti-corruption laws, including the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act (FCPA). Power Grid Corporation of India said that the Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs has increased the permissible equity investment limit per subsidiary to Rs 7,500 crore from Rs 5,000 crore, while retaining the cap at 15% of the company’s net worth. 5Paisa Capital said that its board has approved raising up to Rs 475 crore through a rights issue of equity shares. Schaeffler India reported a net profit of Rs 322.3 crore for Q4, up 35.9% from Rs 237.2 crore in the same period last year. Revenue for the quarter increased 27.5% to Rs 2,724 crore from Rs 2,136 crore a year ago. Biocon has received approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for its drug-device combination, Liraglutide, indicated for weight management. Federal Bank has launched revamped current account variants named ‘Fed Prime’ and ‘Shreni CA Premium.’

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rail Vikas Nigam bags Rs 270-cr EPC order from Central Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rail-vikas-nigam-bags-rs-270-cr-epc-order-from-central-railway/1679355</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679355</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order pertains to the design, supply, erection, testing and commissioning of a 220/132/55 KV traction substation, sectioning posts (SPs) and sub-sectioning posts (SSPs) in the 2x25 KV traction system (Scott-connected transformer) for the Daund–Solapur section.

The order pertains to the design, supply, erection, testing and commissioning of a 220/132/55 KV traction substation, sectioning posts (SPs) and sub-sectioning posts (SSPs) in the 2x25 KV traction system (Scott-connected transformer) for the Daund–Solapur section. The project is aimed at meeting the 3,000 MT loading target. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is to be executed within a period of 24 months. The total cost of the work stands at Rs 270,22,24,735.83, inclusive of applicable taxes. RVNL clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity. The company also confirmed that the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Rail Vikas Nigam is engaged in executing a wide range of railway infrastructure projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, cable-stayed bridges, and institutional buildings. The company reported a 3.65% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 322.83 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 311.44 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 2.56% YoY to Rs 4,684.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of Rail Vikas Nigam rose 0.74% to end at Rs 321.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>