<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:19:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee recovers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-recovers/1663448</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663448</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 90.2550 per Dollar on Tuesday (06 January 2025), versus its previous close of 90.4025 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil near one-week high, OPEC+ to keep oil production steady ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-near-one-week-high-opec-to-keep-oil-production-steady/1663447</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663447</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures are consolidating around one week high on firm equities.

WTI crude oil futures are consolidating around one week high on firm equities. The counter currently trades at $58.61 per barrel, up half a percent on the day after a volatile prior session that ended nearly 2% higher. Prices spiked yesterday as markets reassessed the real supply impact of recent US actions toward Venezuela. Despite holding the world’s largest proven oil reserves, Venezuela contributes less than 1% to global output, limiting the potential for meaningful disruptions to international supply. The bearish tone was reinforced by Saudi Arabia’s decision to cut crude selling prices to Asia for a third consecutive month, underscoring weak demand conditions. Meanwhile, OPEC+ stuck to its plan to pause output increases in Q1 amid lingering concerns over surplus. The producer group confirmed on Sunday that it will keep oil production steady through the first quarter of 2026, as eight key producers reaffirmed their commitment to market stability.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-rig-back-light-picture-id494545396_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD lingers around two-week low as dollar firms on safe haven demand ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-lingers-around-two-week-low-as-dollar-firms-on-safe-haven-demand/1663445</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663445</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[EUR/USD pair continues to stay around a two week low even amid a slight revival after hitting a Dec 11 low in the previous session.

EUR/USD pair continues to stay around a two week low even amid a slight revival after hitting a Dec 11 low in the previous session. The pair is quoting at $1.1745, down 0.18% on the day. Dollar strength overseas amid geo-political tensions is weighing on the counter. Investors weighed the implications of the US attack on Venezuela. Besides, data today showed a downward revision of December's Eurozone Services PMI. Eurozone HCOB Services Purchasing Managers' Index (PMI) has been revised down to 52.4, from the previous estimation of 52.6, and a reading of 53.1 in November.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper stays well supported amid firm stock markets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-stays-well-supported-amid-firm-stock-markets/1663444</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663444</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper stayed above $6 per pound amid mining worries and firm equities.

COMEX Copper stayed above $6 per pound amid mining worries and firm equities. A strike that began on January 2 at the Mantoverde copper mine in Chile propped up the metal by around 5% in last session and the counter currently trades up 0.55% at $6.01 per pound. Meanwhile, Asian stocks extended their upmove as investors looked ahead to the release of key US economic data for direction. China's Shanghai Composite index soared 1.50% to hit highest level in more than a decade. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index surged 1.38% while Japanese Nikkei average climbed 1.32% to hit another record high. European stocks were mixed but overall mood in risky assets was supported after the US stocks regained ground following the slump seen during holiday-interrupted previous week. The major US averages edged higher, with the Dow marking another new record closing high.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/blue-stock-chart-growth-picture-id174673054_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI Supervisory Data Quality Index for commercial banks shows modest improvement ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-supervisory-data-quality-index-for-commercial-banks-shows-modest-improvement/1663441</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663441</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released an update giving an assessment of its Supervisory Data Quality Index (sDQI) that measures data quality in terms of the Accuracy, Timeliness, Completeness and Consistency in the submission of returns.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released an update giving an assessment of its Supervisory Data Quality Index (sDQI) that measures data quality in terms of the Accuracy, Timeliness, Completeness and Consistency in the submission of returns. The sDQI score of Scheduled Commercial Banks (SCBs) has improved in September 2025 as compared to June 2025. The index edged up to 90.7 in Sep-25 compared to 89.9 in previous quarter. Timeliness saw an impressive spurt with the corresponding index for the competent soaring from 90.5 in Jun-25 to 93.5 in Sep-25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/debt-loan-credit-money-financial-problem-concept-picture-id_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s automotive exports well positioned to scale further through continued value-chain integration]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-automotive-exports-well-positioned-to-scale-further-through-continued-value-chain-integration/1663440</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663440</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NITI Aayog has come up with the fifth edition of “Trade Watch Quarterly” update, offering a comprehensive assessment of India’s trade performance amid evolving global conditions, with a special focus on the structure and competitiveness of India’s automotive exports.

NITI Aayog has come up with the fifth edition of “Trade Watch Quarterly” update, offering a comprehensive assessment of India’s trade performance amid evolving global conditions, with a special focus on the structure and competitiveness of India’s automotive exports. It noted that is India’s automotive exports, a sector with rising global relevance, strong domestic production capabilities, and expanding international market presence. India has achieved notable gains in auto components and in vehicle segments such as motorcycles and tractors, reflecting growing manufacturing depth and competitiveness. With increasing integration into global value chains and a broad export footprint across advanced and emerging markets, the sector is well positioned to scale further through continued value-chain integration, improved logistics, and closer alignment with global demand. The report also stated that though India has done well in specific segments of the automotive export market, there are significant opportunities to increase market share in the $2.2 trillion global automotive export market, which is growing. The analysis, based on mapping of global automotive exports, India’s exports, and stakeholder consultations, suggests specific policy steps to enhance competitiveness, global positioning, two-way trade, and to reorient production toward high-demand segments. Further, suggestions include strengthening quality standards, certification systems, technology adoption and market diversification alongside fostering forward linkages in global automotive supply chains.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stack-of-four-black-car-tires-isolated-on-white-picture-id1_rubber.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures scale ahead of 122 mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-scale-ahead-of-122-mark/1663439</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663439</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures fell 0.16% at 90.25.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures fell 0.16% at 90.25. EUR/INR edged up to 105.82. GBP/INR and JPY/INR added around 0.3% to end at 122.05 and 57.85 respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty slip for second day as tariff worries, FII selling weigh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-slip-for-second-day-as-tariff-worries-fii-selling-weigh/1663435</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663435</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks ended lower for a second straight session on Tuesday as risk sentiment weakened across markets.

Domestic equity benchmarks ended lower for a second straight session on Tuesday as risk sentiment weakened across markets. Sentiment was hit by renewed tariff concerns after US President Donald Trump warned of higher tariffs on India if it failed to curb purchases of Russian oil. Foreign institutional investors also turned net sellers, adding to liquidity pressure. Geopolitical tensions further weighed on sentiment following the arrest of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro, while volatility edged higher. The Nifty 50 settled below the 26,200 mark, dragged down by private bank stocks. In contrast, healthcare and pharmaceutical shares saw buying interest. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 376.28 points or 0.44% to 85,063.34. The Nifty 50 index dropped 71.60 points or 0.27% to 26,178.70. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.81% while the Nifty fell 0.56%. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.24% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.39%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1659 shares rose and 2520 shares fell. A total of 169 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, down 0.04% to 10.02. Economy: India’s services sector growth slowed in December, with the HSBC India Services PMI Business Activity Index easing to 58.0 from 59.8 in November, marking the weakest expansion since January while still indicating solid growth. The Composite PMI Output Index also softened to 57.8 from 59.7 in November but remained well above its long-run average, pointing to continued overall economic expansion at a moderated pace. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper declined 0.12% to 6.625 compared with the previous session close of 6.633. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1800 compared with its close of 90.3000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.06% to Rs 138,200. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.05% to 98.37. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.26% to 4.179. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 13 cents or 21% to $61.89 a barrel. Crude oil eased slightly as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Global Markets: Most European market advanced on Tuesday as investors track geopolitical developments following the U.S.'s ouster of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Asian indices ended higher, building on a record-breaking rally in global stocks as investors continued to assess ongoing geopolitical tensions following the U.S. attack on Venezuela and capture of ousted leader Nicolas Maduro. U.S. big oil got a boost from the country's military raid at the weekend that captured Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Crude oil eased back after rising $1 a barrel overnight as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Overall, however, the events had a limited effect on risk sentiment, with equities driven more by momentum and currencies focused on macroeconomic data. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. Trump plans to meet with executives from U.S. oil companies later this week to discuss boosting Venezuelan oil production, media reports stated. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose even after the U.S. attack on Venezuela, as crude oil prices advanced and investors bet the action would not lead to broader geopolitical conflict. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 594.79 points, or 1.23%, to close at 48,977.18. The 30-stock index also hit a new all-time high in the session. The S&P 500 advanced 0.64% and ended at 6,902.05. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.69%, settling at 23,395.82. Stocks in Spotlight: Reliance Industries dropped 4.42% despite the company strongly denying reports that Russian Urals crude shipments were headed to its Jamnagar refinery. Reliance said it has not received any Russian crude for nearly three weeks and expects none in January, reiterating that it halted the use of Russian oil at its export-oriented unit in November 2025 amid rising geopolitical and regulatory risks, including US tariff threats under Donald Trump. The company also flagged inaccuracies in vessel tracking data and said it is shifting to diversified, non-Russian crude sourcing to avoid sanctions risks and maintain access to global markets. Trent fell 8.62% after its Q3 FY26 business update showed steady but slowing momentum. While standalone revenue rose 17% YoY to Rs 5,220 crore and nine-month revenue increased 18% YoY, investors were concerned about flat sequential growth and a moderation compared with the stronger growth seen in recent quarters. HDFC Bank fell 1.56% despite reporting double-digit loan growth in the December quarter. While advances rose 12% YoY and deposits grew 11.5%, investor concerns centred on the loan-deposit ratio, which increased to nearly 99%, well above management’s near-term target of below 90%. The elevated ratio has renewed worries over deposit constraints and raised questions about the bank’s ability to sustain above-industry growth in the coming financial year. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (PV) declined 1.23% after Jaguar Land Rover (JLR)’s Q3 volumes were impacted by a cyber-incident and US tariffs, leading to sharp year-on-year and sequential declines in both wholesale and retail sales. IndusInd Bank rose 1.70%. The bank reported a 3.8% decline in deposits to Rs 3,94,022 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 4,09,438 crore as of 31st December 2024. LG Electronics India advanced 1.66% after signing an Advance Pricing Agreement with the Central Board of Direct Taxes, eliminating Rs 487.74 crore of tax and royalty-related contingent liabilities and bringing long-term clarity on transfer pricing. GM Breweries fell 4.32%. The company reported a 91.22% surge in standalone net profit of Rs 42.01 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 21.97 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased 21.89% YoY to Rs 202.14 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. KSH International rallied 3.34% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 129.02% to Rs 29.59 crore on a 50.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 712.14 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. MOIL added 3.59% after the company said that it has achieved a record manganese ore production of 4.77 lakh tonnes in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of about 3.7% over the corresponding period last year (CPLY). Dev Information Technology rose 1.78% after the company announced that it had secured an order worth about Rs 26 lakh from Core Technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1663431</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663431</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,281.90, a premium of 103.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,178.70 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,281.90, a premium of 103.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,178.70 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index fell 71.60 points or 0.27% to 26,178.70. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.04% to 10.02. Reliance Industries, Trent and HDFC Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices decline for 2nd day; pharma index rallies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-decline-for-2nd-day-pharma-index-rallies/1663430</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663430</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today for a second straight session as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today for a second straight session as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S. tariffs against a steady stream of quarterly business updates that continued to support hopes of an earnings recovery. The Nifty settled below the 26,200 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 376.28 points or 0.44% to 85,063.34. The Nifty 50 index dropped 71.60 points or 0.27% to 26,178.70. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.81% while the Nifty fell 0.56%. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.24% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.39%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, down 0.04% to 10.02. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Healthcare index (up 1.85%), the Nifty Pharma index (up 1.69%) and the Nifty Financial services index (up 0.64%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Media index (down 1.05%), the Nifty Realty index (down 0.33%) and the Nifty Private Bank index (down 0.02%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: India’s services sector growth slowed in December, with HSBC India Services PMI Business Activity Index easing to 58 from 59.8 in November, marking the weakest expansion since January while still indicating solid growth. The Composite PMI Output Index also softened to 57.8 in November but remained well above its long-run average, pointing to continued overall economic expansion at a moderated pace. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper declined 0.12% to 6.625 compared with the previous session close of 6.633. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1800 compared with its close of 90.3000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.06% to Rs 138,200. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.05% to 98.37. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.26% to 4.179. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 13 cents or 21% to $61.89 a barrel. Crude oil eased slightly as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Global Markets: Most European market advanced on Tuesday as investors track geopolitical developments following the U.S.′ ouster of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Asia-Pacific markets ended higher, building on a record-breaking rally in global stocks as investors continued to assess ongoing geopolitical tensions following the U.S. attack on Venezuela and capture of ousted leader Nicolas Maduro. U.S. big oil got a boost from the country's military raid at the weekend that captured Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Crude oil eased back after rising $1 a barrel overnight as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Overall, however, the events had a limited effect on risk sentiment, with equities driven more by momentum and currencies focused on macroeconomic data. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. Trump plans to meet with executives from U.S. oil companies later this week to discuss boosting Venezuelan oil production, media reports stated. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose even after the U.S. attack on Venezuela, as crude oil prices advanced and investors bet the action would not lead to broader geopolitical conflict. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 594.79 points, or 1.23%, to close at 48,977.18. The 30-stock index also hit a new all-time high in the session. The S&P 500 advanced 0.64% and ended at 6,902.05. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.69%, settling at 23,395.82.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Pharma Index gains 1.69%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-pharma-index-gains-169/1663428</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663428</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Pharma index closed up 1.69% at 23126.85 today.

Nifty Pharma index closed up 1.69% at 23126.85 today. The index has gained 1.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Divis Laboratories Ltd added 4.38%, Ipca Laboratories Ltd rose 4.01% and Lupin Ltd gained 3.17%. The Nifty Pharma index has soared 0.00% over last one year compared to the 10.85% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Infrastructure index has dropped 1.18% and Nifty Media index is down 1.05% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 0.27% to close at 26178.7 while the SENSEX has dropped 0.44% to close at 85063.34 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 376 pts lower; Nifty ends below 26,200 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-376-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-26200-level/1663427</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663427</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today for a second straight session as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today for a second straight session as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S. tariffs against a steady stream of quarterly business updates that continued to support hopes of an earnings recovery. The Nifty settled below the 26,200 level. Oil & gas, media and realty shares declined while pharma, IT and PSU bank shares advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 376.28 points or 0.44% to 85,063.34. The Nifty 50 index dropped 71.60 points or 0.27% to 26,178.70. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.81% while the Nifty fell 0.56%. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.24% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.39%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,668 shares rose and 2,511 shares fell. A total of 189 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s services sector growth slowed in December, with HSBC India Services PMI Business Activity Index easing to 58 from 59.8 in November, marking the weakest expansion since January while still indicating solid growth. The Composite PMI Output Index also softened to 57.8 in November but remained well above its long-run average, pointing to continued overall economic expansion at a moderated pace. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index declined 1.75% to 12,000.60. The index declined 2.51% in the two consecutive trading session. Reliance Industries (down 4.54%), Mahanagar Gas (down 4.29%), GAIL (India) (down 2.34%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 2.06%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 1.84%), Adani Total Gas (down 1.19%), Castrol India (down 0.65%), Gujarat State Petronet (down 0.64%), Indian Oil Corporation (down 0.56%) and Gujarat Gas (down 0.54%) declined. On the other hand, Petronet LNG (up 2.31%), Aegis Logistics (up 1.84%) and Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (up 1.62%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: GM Breweries fell 5.20%. The company reported a 91.22% surge in standalone net profit of Rs 42.01 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 21.97 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased 21.89% YoY to Rs 202.14 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Dabur India fell 0.05%. The company said that it expects consolidated revenue to grow in the mid-single digits with operating profit and Profit after Tax to grow ahead of revenue in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, early signs of demand recovery were witnessed, aided by GST rate revisions. Post trade stabilization, consumer sentiment improved in urban and rural areas. Rural demand continued to outperform urban demand this quarter as well. KSH International rallied 3.16% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 129.02% to Rs 29.59 crore on a 50.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 712.14 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. MOIL added 3.44% after the company said that it has achieved a record manganese ore production of 4.77 lakh tonnes in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of about 3.7% over the corresponding period last year (CPLY). Dev Information Technology rose 1.78% after the company announced that it had secured an order worth about Rs 26 lakh from Core Technologies. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (PV) declined 1.30% after Jaguar Land Rover (JLR)’s Q3 volumes were impacted by a cyber-incident and US tariffs, leading to sharp year-on-year and sequential declines in both wholesale and retail sales. IndusInd Bank rose 2%. The bank reported a 3.8% decline in deposits to Rs 3,94,022 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 4,09,438 crore as of 31st December 2024. LG Electronics India advanced 1.66% after the company signed Advance Pricing Agreement (APA) with the Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT), leading to a reduction in its net tax exposure. Global Markets: The Dow Jones index futures were down 103 points, indicating a weak opening for U.S. stocks. European shares traded higher on Tuesday as investors track geopolitical developments following the U.S.′ ouster of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. France’s harmonized inflation rate, adjusted for comparison with other euro zone countries, stood at 0.7% year-on-year in December, slightly below the expected 0.8%. Asia-Pacific markets ended higher, building on a record-breaking rally in global stocks as investors continued to assess ongoing geopolitical tensions following the U.S. attack on Venezuela and capture of ousted leader Nicolas Maduro. U.S. big oil got a boost from the country's military raid at the weekend that captured Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Crude oil eased back after rising $1 a barrel overnight as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Overall, however, the events had a limited effect on risk sentiment, with equities driven more by momentum and currencies focused on macroeconomic data. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. Trump plans to meet with executives from U.S. oil companies later this week to discuss boosting Venezuelan oil production, media reports stated. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose even after the U.S. attack on Venezuela, as crude oil prices advanced and investors bet the action would not lead to broader geopolitical conflict. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 594.79 points, or 1.23%, to close at 48,977.18. The 30-stock index also hit a new all-time high in the session. The S&P 500 advanced 0.64% and ended at 6,902.05. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.69%, settling at 23,395.82.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-mutual-funds-picture-id157281690_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SABTNL gains after board approves multiple corporate actions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sabtnl-gains-after-board-approves-multiple-corporate-actions/1663426</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663426</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The board of directors approved a stock split of the existing 1 equity share with a face value of Rs 10 each into 10 equity shares with a face value of Rs 1 each, fully paid.

The board of directors approved a stock split of the existing 1 equity share with a face value of Rs 10 each into 10 equity shares with a face value of Rs 1 each, fully paid. The board appointed Srivatsava Sunkara as chairperson with effect from 6 January 2026. He has experience in Artificial Intelligence (AI) and the development of Large Language Models (LLMs), with proven expertise in transforming organizational operations to enhance efficiency and foster innovation. Additionally, the board accepted the resignation of Kiran Kumar Inampudi with effect from January 6, 2026. However, he will continue to be actively associated with the company as an Executive Director. Further, the board has approved the acceptance of loans from the promoter up to Rs 100 crore, including the option to convert such loans into equity shares of the company. Furthermore, the borrowing powers of the company were enhanced, with the total outstanding borrowings capped at Rs 500 crore. Sri Adhikari Brothers Television Network (SABTNL) is a media company and operates in the field of content production and syndication of content to various broadcasters, aggregators and satellite networks. <> In Q2 FY26, the company reported a standalone net profit of Rs 14.10 crore, nearly 83 times higher than the Rs 0.17 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations surged 244.44% YoY to Rs 4.34 crore during the quarter ended 30th September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SriAdhikBros_57175738493_6113.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Satin Creditcare gains after board approves Rs 100-cr NCD issue]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/satin-creditcare-gains-after-board-approves-rs-100-cr-ncd-issue/1663432</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663432</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the board, at its meeting held on 5 January 2026, approved the issuance of 1,00,000 senior, secured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, and transferable NCDs, each with a face value of Rs 10,000, aggregating to Rs 100 crore.

According to an exchange filing, the board, at its meeting held on 5 January 2026, approved the issuance of 1,00,000 senior, secured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, and transferable NCDs, each with a face value of Rs 10,000, aggregating to Rs 100 crore. The issue includes a green shoe option of up to Rs 50 crore, as may be agreed, on a private placement basis. The debentures are proposed to be listed on the BSE, with 13 January 2026 set as the deemed date of allotment. The NCDs will have a tenure of 30 months and are scheduled to mature on 13 July 2028. The debentures will carry an interest rate of 10.15% per annum, payable on a monthly basis. In the event of a payment default, the company will pay additional interest of 2% per annum over the applicable coupon rate until the default is cured. The NCDs will be secured by a first-ranking exclusive charge on identified loan receivables of the company through a deed of hypothecation, along with any other security as may be agreed. The security cover will be maintained at a minimum of 1.05 times the outstanding debenture amount until full redemption. The debentures will be redeemed on a pari passu basis by payment of the outstanding principal on the final redemption date, in accordance with the debenture trust deed. Satin Creditcare Network is a leading microfinance institution (MFI) in the country. The company offers a bouquet of financial products in the non-MFI segment, comprising loans to MSMEs and affordable housing loans. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 19% to Rs 53.16 crore on a 20.6% rise in total income to Rs 792.80 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SatinCreditcare_84494064_16093.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trent Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trent-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1663402</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663402</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kaynes Technology India Ltd, CSB Bank Ltd, Supreme Petrochem Ltd and V-Mart Retail Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 January 2026.

Kaynes Technology India Ltd, CSB Bank Ltd, Supreme Petrochem Ltd and V-Mart Retail Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 January 2026. Trent Ltd lost 9.20% to Rs 4022 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.96 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 56516 shares in the past one month. Kaynes Technology India Ltd tumbled 5.69% to Rs 3771.1. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.9 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.75 lakh shares in the past one month. CSB Bank Ltd crashed 5.60% to Rs 529.05. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2.98 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 71599 shares in the past one month. Supreme Petrochem Ltd corrected 5.39% to Rs 610.7. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6390 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3201 shares in the past one month. V-Mart Retail Ltd fell 4.81% to Rs 699.95. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 43903 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11924 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Trent_20841567073_345.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Allcargo Terminals’ CFS volumes jump 18% YoY in December ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/allcargo-terminals-cfs-volumes-jump-18-yoy-in-december/1663401</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663401</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company handled 61.2 thousand TEUs during the month, marking an 18% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared with December 2024 and a 10.66% rise from November 2025.

The company handled 61.2 thousand TEUs during the month, marking an 18% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared with December 2024 and a 10.66% rise from November 2025. Allcargo Terminals, demerged from Allcargo Logistics in August 2023, operates as an independent listed entity. It runs one of India’s largest Container Freight Stations (CFS) and Inland Container Depots (ICD) networks across major ports like Nhava Sheva, Mundra, Chennai, and Kolkata. The company leverages its digital platform, myCFS, to offer seamless, contactless logistics services and aims to expand into multimodal logistics parks and terminal ventures. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Allcargo Terminals rose 1.2% to Rs 11.30 crore and net sales increased 6.3% to Rs 207.16 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter rose 0.51% to Rs 27.84 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AllcargoTerminalsLtd_35103494_76341.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Reliance denies reports of Russian crude shipments to Jamnagar refinery]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/reliance-denies-reports-of-russian-crude-shipments-to-jamnagar-refinery/1663400</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663400</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company was responding to reports suggesting that shipments of Russian oil were approaching the Jamnagar complex.

The company was responding to reports suggesting that shipments of Russian oil were approaching the Jamnagar complex. Reliance said its refinery has not received any Russian crude cargo for nearly three weeks and is not expecting any deliveries in January. Reliance clarified that it had already committed in November 2025 to halting the use of Russian crude at its export-oriented unit, citing rising geopolitical and regulatory risks. These include the threat of higher US tariffs linked to purchases of Russian oil. The company also pointed to inaccuracies in satellite-based vessel tracking data, stating that automated signals and intermediary-linked trades do not reflect its actual procurement plans. It said it is distancing itself from potential secondary sanctions and moving towards a more diversified crude sourcing strategy. The issue remains sensitive as Russian oil imports have drawn scrutiny from the US. In August 2025, US President Donald Trump imposed 25% penalty tariffs on Indian imports over New Delhi’s purchases of Russian oil. Reliance, once India’s largest buyer of Russian crude, said it is now sourcing non-Russian oil for exports to ensure sanctions compliance and continued access to key global markets. Reliance Industries is India's largest private sector company. Its activities span hydrocarbon exploration and production, petroleum refining and marketing, petrochemicals, advanced materials and composites, renewables (solar and hydrogen), retail and digital services. The company‘s consolidated net profit jumped 9.54% to Rs 18,165 crore on 9.94% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2,58,898 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Reliance Industries are currently down 4.49% at Rs 1506.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RelianceInds_29114129325_476.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AWL Agri Business registers muted volume growth in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/awl-agri-business-registers-muted-volume-growth-in-q3/1663403</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663403</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to the company’s exchange filing, standalone volumes in Q3 FY26 were largely flat compared with Q3 FY25, while revenues grew 5% year on year, indicating modest price or mix-led growth.

According to the company’s exchange filing, standalone volumes in Q3 FY26 were largely flat compared with Q3 FY25, while revenues grew 5% year on year, indicating modest price or mix-led growth. At the segment level, the Edible Oil business delivered relatively better performance, with volumes rising 3% and value increasing 6%. The Food & FMCG segment reported a marginal 1% decline in volumes but managed to post a 1% increase in value, reflecting stable realizations. In contrast, the Industry Essentials division underperformed, with volumes contracting 7% and value declining 1% during the quarter. AWL Agri Business stated that growth during the quarter was primarily led by uptick in both Edible Oil and Food & FMCG segment. However, the overall volumes were dragged by de-growth in castor and de-oiled cakes classified under the Industry Essentials segment. Festive demand was relatively subdued during the quarter as trade continued to operate with lean inventory levels. The Food & FMCG business has shown a gradual recovery over recent quarters with improved offtake, on the back of multiple interventions and improvements in the rice business. While the overall rice business (ex-G2G) marginally declined in low single digits, the branded domestic rice business grew in strong double digits. Wheat Flour consumer pack business remained flat during the quarter, as demand continues to remain subdued this year. However, wheat flour & refined flour business catering to HORECA segment recorded strong double-digit growth during the quarter. Food & FMCG products other than rice & wheat business, contributing over one-third of the segment, recorded a strong growth exceeding 30% YoY in Q3 FY26. Alternate channels (E-com, Q-com, MT) continued the strong growth momentum during the quarter, growing at 42% YoY in volumes. The channel recorded a revenue of INR 4,800 crore in the last twelve months. The strong momentum in channel was led by record 65% YoY volume growth in Quick Commerce. Most of the products on e-commerce recorded a solid growth, with atta & rice registering a growth exceeding 40% YoY. With the increasing relevance and competition across e-commerce platforms (including quick commerce), marketing spends towards the channel are being gradually rationalized in favor of alternate channel. HoReCa and Branded exports (edible oil & foods) too recorded a strong double digit volume growth during the quarter. The company continues to focus on both these channels as they represent huge potential in the coming years. AWL Agri Business is engaged in manufacturing of wide range of products, including edible oils, non-edible oil, de-oiled cake (DOC), vanaspati, specialty fats, food & FMCG products such as wheat, besan, atta, rice, and oleo chemicals, among others. Singapore-based Wilmar Group is the largest stakeholder in the company. The company had reported 21% drop in net profit to Rs 245 crore despite a 22% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 17,605 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip shed 0.79% to currently trade at Rs 232 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniWilmarLtd_38707947_20696.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Systematix Corporate Services Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/systematix-corporate-services-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663399</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663399</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vivimed Labs Ltd, Indian Metals & Ferro Alloys Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 January 2026.

Vivimed Labs Ltd, Indian Metals & Ferro Alloys Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 January 2026. Systematix Corporate Services Ltd lost 19.33% to Rs 110 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.09 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.94 lakh shares in the past one month. Vivimed Labs Ltd tumbled 9.94% to Rs 12.23. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 7.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10049 shares in the past one month. Indian Metals & Ferro Alloys Ltd crashed 9.55% to Rs 1317. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 81090 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9187 shares in the past one month. Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd corrected 9.15% to Rs 48.15. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 110 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 544 shares in the past one month. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup pared 8.97% to Rs 4.77. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 143 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2097 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SystematixCorp_19909031607_3845.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold storms higher on Venezuela upheaval and flight to safety]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-storms-higher-on-venezuela-upheaval-and-flight-to-safety/1663395</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663395</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices surged toward $4490 per ounce in Asia electronic trading on Tuesday, marking a third consecutive session of gains as investors flocked to safe-haven assets amid escalating political turmoil in Venezuela.

Gold prices surged toward $4490 per ounce in Asia electronic trading on Tuesday, marking a third consecutive session of gains as investors flocked to safe-haven assets amid escalating political turmoil in Venezuela. Bullion jumped more than $100 on Monday following a US military operation over the weekend that resulted in the capture of President Nicolas Maduro, sharply lifting geopolitical risk sentiment. President Donald Trump further intensified concerns after stating that the US would temporarily run Venezuela and warning of a second strike if the interim government failed to meet Washington’s demands. Attention has now shifted to key US labor market indicators, with the December jobs report due on Friday expected to offer fresh insight into the Federal Reserve’s policy trajectory. In the domestic market, MCX February gold futures rose 0.4% to ₹138625 per 10 grams, mirroring the strong momentum in international prices.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>