<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:46:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cartrade Tech Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cartrade-tech-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679312</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679312</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SpiceJet Ltd, Le Travenues Technology Ltd, L&T Technology Services Ltd and Affle 3i Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 February 2026.

SpiceJet Ltd, Le Travenues Technology Ltd, L&T Technology Services Ltd and Affle 3i Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 February 2026. Cartrade Tech Ltd crashed 10.03% to Rs 1800 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 24200 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 32887 shares in the past one month. SpiceJet Ltd lost 8.64% to Rs 14.48. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 221.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 120.74 lakh shares in the past one month. Le Travenues Technology Ltd tumbled 8.38% to Rs 164.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.83 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.5 lakh shares in the past one month. L&T Technology Services Ltd shed 8.22% to Rs 3155.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11675 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12715 shares in the past one month. Affle 3i Ltd pared 7.16% to Rs 1401. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 15556 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 34500 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cartrade--Tech-Ltd_25528484_65036.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold retreats toward $5150 support after four-day rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-retreats-toward-5150-support-after-four-day-rally/1679311</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679311</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices slipped below $5200 per ounce on Tuesday, ending a four-session rally as investors locked in profits after prices touched four-year highs.

Gold prices slipped below $5200 per ounce on Tuesday, ending a four-session rally as investors locked in profits after prices touched four-year highs. A firmer U.S. dollar, up around 0.2%, added pressure by making bullion more expensive for overseas buyers. However, renewed trade uncertainty and rising geopolitical risks helped limit losses, keeping gold supported near lower levels. Fresh U.S. tariff threats and lingering global tensions sustained safe-haven demand. Meanwhile, markets also monitored developments around upcoming U.S.–Iran nuclear talks in Geneva. On the domestic front, MCX April gold futures traded lower by about 0.5% at Rs 160886 per 10 grams, with near-term support seen around Rs 159500–160000 and resistance near Rs 162000 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alembic Pharma gets USFDA nod for antifungal ANDA]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alembic-pharma-gets-usfda-nod-for-antifungal-anda/1679309</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679309</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug product (RLD), Jublia Topical Solution, 10%, of Bausch Health Americas, Inc.

The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug product (RLD), Jublia Topical Solution, 10%, of Bausch Health Americas, Inc. (Bausch). The said drug is indicated for the topical treatment of onychomycosis of the toenail(s) due to Trichophyton rubrum and Trichophyton mentagrophytes. According to IQVIA, Efinaconazole Topical Solution, 10%, has an estimated market size of $500 million for twelve months ending December 2025. The company has a cumulative total of 234 ANDA approvals (215 final approvals and 19 tentative approvals) from USFDA. Alembic Pharmaceuticals, a vertically integrated research and development company, is engaged in the manufacture and marketing of generic pharmaceutical products across global markets. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 3.9% to Rs 132.97 crore despite a 10.8% jump in net sales to Rs 1,876.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter fell 1.31% to Rs 757 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlembicPharma_46538273359_40294.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indoco Remedies rises on USFDA approval for Brivaracetam oral solution]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indoco-remedies-rises-on-usfda-approval-for-brivaracetam-oral-solution/1679306</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679306</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approval allows the company to market a generic version of Briviact 10 mg/mL oral solution, the reference listed drug (RLD) of UCB, Inc.

The approval allows the company to market a generic version of Briviact 10 mg/mL oral solution, the reference listed drug (RLD) of UCB, Inc. The company said its Brivaracetam Oral Solution has been determined to be bioequivalent and therapeutically equivalent to the RLD. The product will be manufactured at Indoco Remedies’ facility located at L-14, Verna Industrial Area, Verna, Goa – 403722, India. Brivaracetam Oral Solution (10 mg/mL) is a prescription antiepileptic drug indicated for the treatment of partial-onset seizures in patients aged one month and older. Aditi Panandikar, managing director (MD) said, “The ANDA approval for Brivaracetam is a significant milestone for us as we continue to strengthen our presence in the Regulated Markets. We are committed to offering innovative and affordable healthcare to patients worldwide.” Indoco Remedies is engaged in the manufacturing and marketing of Formulations and Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients. The Company caters to both Domestic and International markets. The company’s consolidated net loss of Rs 23.64 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 27.30 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 7.9% year on year to Rs 434.34 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndocoRemedies_30015747980_12579.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AKI India Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aki-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679305</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679305</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Yatra Online Ltd, Cropster Agro Ltd, EFC (I) Ltd and Shekhawati Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 February 2026.

Yatra Online Ltd, Cropster Agro Ltd, EFC (I) Ltd and Shekhawati Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 February 2026. AKI India Ltd crashed 17.05% to Rs 5.01 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 79751 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4724 shares in the past one month. Yatra Online Ltd tumbled 14.32% to Rs 122.65. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.95 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.19 lakh shares in the past one month. Cropster Agro Ltd lost 13.73% to Rs 11.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 59614 shares in the past one month. EFC (I) Ltd shed 9.97% to Rs 238.75. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15.91 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 78569 shares in the past one month. Shekhawati Industries Ltd plummeted 9.85% to Rs 12.35. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5313 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16482 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AKIIndiaLtd_33238188821_72485.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with major losses; auto shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-major-losses-auto-shares-decline/1679304</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679304</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with deep cuts in the mid-afternoon trade dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with deep cuts in the mid-afternoon trade dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters. Investor sentiment was dented after Trump has threatened foreign nations that if they side with the US Supreme Court's judgment, they may face higher tariffs on goods imported into the US, while the expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE added to the volatility in the market. Nifty traded below 25,450 mark. Auto shares declined after advancing in the past two consecutive trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 1096.28 points or 1.32% to 82,197.91. The Nifty 50 index tanked 298.58 points or 1.15% to 25,414.65. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.81% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index dropped 1.06%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,165 shares rose and 2,940 shares fell. A total of 187 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 2.99% to 14.59. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index fell 0.75% to 27,867.55. The index rose 1.23% in the past two consecutive trading session. Uno Minda (down 1.81%), Eicher Motors (down 1.37%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 1.31%), Bajaj Auto (down 1.17%), Exide Industries (down 1.15%), Mahindra & Mahindra (down 1.01%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 0.86%), Bosch (down 0.79%), Ashok Leyland (down 0.77%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 0.71%) declined. On the other hand, Bharat Forge (up 0.44%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 0.33%) and Hero MotoCorp (up 0.21%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.24% to 6.683 compared with the previous session close of 6.699. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9625 compared with its close of 90.8950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement slipped 0.56% to Rs 160,696. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.13% to 97.77. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.35% to 4.040. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 11 cents or 0.15% to $71.60 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Caplin Point Laboratories slipped 1.40%. The company announced that its subsidiary, Caplin Steriles, has received final approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for Sodium Phosphates Injection USP. KEC International added 0.60%. The company announced that it has secured new orders worth Rs 1,002 crore across its Transmission & Distribution (T&D) and Cables & Conductors businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Aegis Logistics Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-aegis-logistics-ltd-counter/1679303</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679303</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd, R R Kabel Ltd, Central Bank of India, DOMS Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 24 February 2026.

Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd, R R Kabel Ltd, Central Bank of India, DOMS Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 24 February 2026. Aegis Logistics Ltd clocked volume of 107.14 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 58.67 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.83 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.54% to Rs.698.60. Volumes stood at 2.41 lakh shares in the last session. Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd registered volume of 266.87 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 13.43 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 19.87 lakh shares. The stock rose 2.84% to Rs.109.57. Volumes stood at 48.31 lakh shares in the last session. R R Kabel Ltd clocked volume of 6.13 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.32 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.15 lakh shares. The stock gained 2.43% to Rs.1,485.90. Volumes stood at 1.91 lakh shares in the last session. Central Bank of India registered volume of 283.61 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.53 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 62.59 lakh shares. The stock rose 1.82% to Rs.39.21. Volumes stood at 107.23 lakh shares in the last session. DOMS Industries Ltd recorded volume of 1.3 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.24 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 30766 shares. The stock gained 2.62% to Rs.2,358.30. Volumes stood at 20764 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisLogistics_61348536029_9.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude oil hovers near seven-month highs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-oil-hovers-near-seven-month-highs/1679302</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679302</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil prices rose on Tuesday, hovering near seven-month highs as traders assessed potential supply disruptions linked to escalating geopolitical risks.

Oil prices rose on Tuesday, hovering near seven-month highs as traders assessed potential supply disruptions linked to escalating geopolitical risks. Brent crude gained 0.6% to $71.94 a barrel, while U.S. crude climbed 0.6% to $66.72. Market attention is centered on the upcoming round of U.S.–Iran nuclear talks in Geneva, with uncertainty over Iran’s nuclear program keeping risk premiums elevated. At the same time, renewed U.S. tariff warnings have added to broader market volatility. On the domestic front, MCX March crude oil futures edged higher by 0.3% to Rs 6064 per barrel, tracking firm global cues as supply-side concerns continue to support prices.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concept-with-oil-rig-in-the-gulf-picture-id597_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Caplin Point’s arm Caplin Steriles gets USFDA nod for Sodium Phosphates Injection]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/caplin-points-arm-caplin-steriles-gets-usfda-nod-for-sodium-phosphates-injection/1679300</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679300</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approval covers Sodium Phosphates Injection USP in strengths of 15mM P/5mL, 45mM P/15mL and 150mM P/50mL (3mM P/mL) single-dose vials.

The approval covers Sodium Phosphates Injection USP in strengths of 15mM P/5mL, 45mM P/15mL and 150mM P/50mL (3mM P/mL) single-dose vials. The product is a generic therapeutic equivalent of the Reference Listed Drug (RLD), approved under NDA 018892 and marketed by Hospira, Inc., USA. Sodium Phosphates Injection is indicated as a source of phosphorus for addition to large volume intravenous fluids to prevent or treat hypophosphatemia in patients with limited or no oral intake. It is also used in the preparation of customised parenteral nutrition formulations when standard electrolyte or nutrient solutions are inadequate to meet patient requirements. According to IQVIA (IMS Health) data, the approved strengths of Sodium Phosphates Injection recorded total US sales of approximately $67 million for the 12-month period ended December 2025. Caplin Point Laboratories is a pharmaceutical company with a unique business model catering predominantly to emerging markets of Latin America and Africa. The company also has a growing presence in the regulated markets such as US through its subsidiary Caplin Steriles and Caplin Steriles USA Inc. The company's consolidated net profit rose 17.9% to Rs 163.88 crore while net sales increase 10.1% to Rs 542.77 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter declined 1.49% to Rs 1,706.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CaplinPointLab_88809258160_4464.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KEC International bags Rs 1,002-cr new orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kec-international-bags-rs-1002-cr-new-orders/1679299</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679299</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The T&D business bagged orders for 220/132 kV transmission lines, substations, and EHV cabling (composite order) in India, along with an additional order for a 400 kV transmission line in the international market.

The T&D business bagged orders for 220/132 kV transmission lines, substations, and EHV cabling (composite order) in India, along with an additional order for a 400 kV transmission line in the international market. The company has also secured orders for the supply of towers, hardware, and poles in the Americas. The cables & conductors segment secured orders for the supply of various types of cables and conductors in India as well as overseas markets. Vimal Kejriwal, MD & CEO, KEC International, commented, “We are pleased with the new order wins, especially the orders in our T&D business. These orders have significantly strengthened our T&D order book, led by the significant composite order secured in India T&D. The addition of this order has further diversified our customer mix in the India T&D order book. With these wins, our year-to-date order intake stands at approximately Rs 21,300 crore.” The company is a global EPC player with operations across power transmission and distribution, civil infrastructure, transportation, renewables, oil and gas pipelines, and cables. KEC’s consolidated net profit jumped 88.21% to Rs 160.75 crore in Q2 FY26, while revenue from operations rose 19.13% to Rs 6,091.56 crore. Its year-to-date order intake has crossed Rs 17,000 crore, up about 17% from last year. Shares of KEC International shed 0.87% to Rs 578.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KECIntl_17426819343_27273.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Wipro Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wipro-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1679289</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679289</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Wipro Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Wipro Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 199.99, down 2.87% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.Wipro Ltd has lost around 14.83% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Wipro Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 22.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 31550.5, down 5.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 169.08 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 178.22 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 199.57, down 3.04% on the day. Wipro Ltd tumbled 31.35% in last one year as compared to a 12.75% rally in NIFTY and a 23.43% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 17.97 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Wipro_36546468_614.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mphasis Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mphasis-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1679290</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679290</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mphasis Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Mphasis Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2221.8, down 3.81% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.Mphasis Ltd has eased around 20.82% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Mphasis Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 22.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 31550.5, down 5.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 8.64 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.22 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2220.9, down 3.67% on the day. Mphasis Ltd tumbled 9.42% in last one year as compared to a 12.75% rally in NIFTY and a 23.43% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 30.9 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Mphasis_88855176_3361.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Infosys Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/infosys-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1679291</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679291</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Infosys Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Infosys Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1271.3, down 4.23% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.Infosys Ltd has lost around 24.45% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Infosys Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 22.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 31550.5, down 5.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 163.97 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 145.45 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1273, down 4.04% on the day. Infosys Ltd tumbled 28.08% in last one year as compared to a 12.75% rally in NIFTY and a 23.43% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 18.8 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Infosys_56909713360_2806.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HCL Technologies Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hcl-technologies-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1679292</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679292</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HCL Technologies Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

HCL Technologies Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1330.9, down 6.68% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.HCL Technologies Ltd has eased around 22.63% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which HCL Technologies Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 22.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 31550.5, down 5.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 61.34 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 31.78 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1332, down 6.55% on the day. HCL Technologies Ltd tumbled 18.65% in last one year as compared to a 12.75% rally in NIFTY and a 23.43% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 31.54 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HCLTechnologies_63631997_5656.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LTIMindtree Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ltimindtree-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1679293</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679293</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[LTIMindtree Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

LTIMindtree Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 4504.5, down 6.77% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.LTIMindtree Ltd has lost around 24.17% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which LTIMindtree Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 22.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 31550.5, down 5.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.24 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.11 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 4499, down 6.9% on the day. LTIMindtree Ltd tumbled 9.24% in last one year as compared to a 12.75% rally in NIFTY and a 23.43% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 28 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LTIMindtreeLtd_76198734_18105.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tech-mahindra-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1679294</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679294</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Tech Mahindra Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1343.2, down 6.78% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.Tech Mahindra Ltd has lost around 23.03% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Tech Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 22.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 31550.5, down 5.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 42.06 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 23.51 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1343.7, down 7.04% on the day. Tech Mahindra Ltd tumbled 15.73% in last one year as compared to a 12.75% rally in NIFTY and a 23.43% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 33.61 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TechMahindra_28047796713_17215.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/persistent-systems-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1679295</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679295</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Persistent Systems Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 4603.5, down 7.51% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.Persistent Systems Ltd has lost around 25.94% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Persistent Systems Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 22.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 31550.5, down 5.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 18.23 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.74 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 4606.5, down 7.6% on the day. Persistent Systems Ltd tumbled 16.42% in last one year as compared to a 12.75% rally in NIFTY and a 23.43% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 49.93 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PersistentSys_70071143_18286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hathway-cable-datacom-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1679296</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679296</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 10.75, down 2.01% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd has gained around 5.08% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 5.6% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1429.6, down 1.6% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 13.45 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 27.25 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 26.88 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HathwayCable_63160375018_20659.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[D B Corp Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/d-b-corp-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1679297</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679297</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[D B Corp Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

D B Corp Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 219.8, down 2.8% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.13% on the day, quoting at 25422.6. The Sensex is at 82225.5, down 1.28%.D B Corp Ltd has lost around 8.55% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which D B Corp Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 5.6% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1429.6, down 1.6% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 25596 shares today, compared to the daily average of 60990 shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 12.49 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DBCorp_72647549474_28589.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market under pressure Nifty trades around 25,400 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-under-pressure-nifty-trades-around-25400-level/1679298</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679298</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks tumbled in the afternoon trade dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters.

The key equity benchmarks tumbled in the afternoon trade dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters. Investor sentiment was dented after Trump has threatened foreign nations that if they side with the US Supreme Court's judgment, they may face higher tariffs on goods imported into the US. Nifty traded around 25,400 level. Barring Pharma index all the sectoral indices on the NSE were traded in red with IT, realty and media shares were top laggards. At 13:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 1125.97 points or 1.34% to 82,172.95. The Nifty 50 index tanked 312.25 points or 1.21% to 25,403.15. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 1.07% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index dropped 1.26%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,099 shares rose and 2,924 shares fell. A total of 194 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 2.94% to 14.59. Gainers & Losers: Hindustan Unilever (up 1%), JSW Steel (up 0.63%), Power Grid Corporation of India (up 0.61%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 0.58%) and CIpla (up 0.54%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Tech Mahindra (down 6.74%), HCL Technologies (down 6.69%), Eternal (down 5.15%), Infosys (down 4.23%) and Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) (down 3.77%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Silver Touch Technologies declined 1.82%. The company announced that it has been selected by the FSSAI for a strategic digital transformation engagement. Shilpa Medicare fell 1.82%. The company said that its subsidiary Shilpa Biologicals and SteinCares have entered into a strategic licensing agreement to commercialize a biosimilar across Latin America. Under the agreement, SteinCares will hold exclusive rights to register, commercialize, and distribute the biosimilar across the region while Shilpa Biologicals will complete product development and provide long-term commercial manufacturing from its facility in Dharwad, India. Brahmaputra Infrastructure hit an upper limit of 5% after it has emerged as the L-1 bidder for a National Highway project awarded by the Ministry of Road Transport & Highways (MoRTH), Government of India. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) fell 3.69%. The company said its Heavy Civil Infrastructure (HCI) and Heavy Engineering (HE) verticals have jointly secured a ‘significant’ order from the Department of Atomic Energy for the LIGO India Observatory in Maharashtra. Samvardhana Motherson International shed 0.08%. The company announced that it has launched a manufacturing facility in Sanand, Gujarat, dedicated to producing cutting-edge exterior lighting systems. The facility has been set up under a strategic joint venture with Marelli, namely Marelli Motherson Automotive Lighting India (MMLI). The joint venture strengthens the group’s capabilities in automotive component manufacturing. MMLI is a 50:50 partnership between Samvardhana Motherson International and Marelli Europe S.p.A. Signpost India rose 0.81%. after securing exclusive outdoor advertising rights from the Kolkata Municipal Corporation under the ‘Kolkata Streetscape Renaissance’ project in a Rs 450-crore, 10-year public-private partnership contract. Waaree Energies added 2.59% after the company announced that it has received an order to supply 500 MW of solar modules from a renowned domestic solar power developer and independent power producer (IPP). Global Markets: European market declined as investors assess the new global trading landscape after U.S. President Donald Trump’s latest tariff move. Asian markets traded mixed on Tuesday as investors weighed renewed tariff threats from U.S. President Donald Trump and concerns that artificial intelligence could disrupt software companies. Trump posted on Truth Social Monday that any country that wants to “play games” with the Supreme Court decision “will be met with a much higher tariff.” The comments followed a Supreme Court decision Friday striking down tariffs enacted under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act. In response, Trump said he would impose a 15% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act. Investors in Asia were also assessing China’s loan prime rate (LPR) decision. China’s central bank on Tuesday kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged at 3% for the one-year LPR and 3.5% for the five-year LPR. Overnight on Wall Street, U.S. equities tumbled on Monday as investors grappled with persistent fears around artificial intelligence disruptions to various industries and President Donald Trump’s decision to raise his global tariffs. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 821.91 points, or 1.66%, to close at 48,804.06, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.13% and ended at 22,627.27. The S&P 500 shed 1.04% and closed at 6,837.75, putting it into the red once again for 2026. The 30-stock Dow was dragged down by IBM shares, which declined 13% on the heels of Anthropic outlining new programming capabilities for its Claude Code product. Software stocks such as Microsoft and CrowdStrike were under pressure yet again as AI disruption worries hovered over the market. However, software hasn’t been the only sector to be hit due to AI fears recently: Stocks linked to trucking and logistics, commercial real estate and financial services have similarly suffered losses this month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>