<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Regency Ceramics Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/regency-ceramics-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662035</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662035</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Creative Eye Ltd, Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd, Teamo Productions HQ Ltd and Adroit Infotech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 December 2025.

Creative Eye Ltd, Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd, Teamo Productions HQ Ltd and Adroit Infotech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 December 2025. Regency Ceramics Ltd tumbled 10.57% to Rs 43 at 14:00 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 90 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3235 shares in the past one month. Creative Eye Ltd crashed 9.85% to Rs 7.14. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 7110 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10039 shares in the past one month. Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd lost 9.74% to Rs 22.6. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 35 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 24.76 lakh shares in the past one month. Teamo Productions HQ Ltd shed 9.30% to Rs 0.78. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9.09 lakh shares in the past one month. Adroit Infotech Ltd slipped 7.30% to Rs 9.9. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.54 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12373 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RegencyCeramics_1874361855_831.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concord Control rises after subsidiary bags order from Indian Railways ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concord-control-rises-after-subsidiary-bags-order-from-indian-railways/1662034</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662034</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order covers the supply, installation and commissioning of locomotive wireless control systems, a safety-critical solution that enhances real-time communication, operational coordination, and control in locomotive operations.

The order covers the supply, installation and commissioning of locomotive wireless control systems, a safety-critical solution that enhances real-time communication, operational coordination, and control in locomotive operations. The contract further strengthens Concord’s execution pipeline, reinforcing its growing engagement with Indian Railways across multiple safety and control applications. With this addition, the company’s order book as on date is Rs. 450-plus crore. Gaurav Lath, joint managing director of Concord Control Systems, said: “This order strengthens Concord’s position as a leader in India’s railway technology journey. It shows the trust Indian Railways has in our capabilities in railway safety and electronic systems, and fits well with the country’s focus on safer and better rail infrastructure.” Concord Control Systems is a manufacturer of embedded electronic systems and critical electronic solutions, specializing in railway safety and control technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ConcordControlSystemsLtd_63232532_77868.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Choice Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/choice-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1662032</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662032</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Choice Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Choice Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Manish Jain has been appointed as Deputy Chief Executive Officer and shall be a Key Personnel of Choice AMC Private Limited with effect from Tuesday December 23, 2025. Details of Mr. Manish Jain Age: 37 years Designation: Deputy Chief Executive Officer Qualification: BE (GEC Bilaspur), M.Tecch (IIT Madras), MBA Finance (Purdue University)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at MMTC Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-mmtc-ltd-counter/1662026</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662026</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, Karur Vysya Bank Ltd, Indian Railway Catering & Tourism Corporation Ltd, Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 December 2025.

Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, Karur Vysya Bank Ltd, Indian Railway Catering & Tourism Corporation Ltd, Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 December 2025. MMTC Ltd witnessed volume of 589.56 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 32.74 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 18.01 lakh shares. The stock increased 10.79% to Rs.63.74. Volumes stood at 32.15 lakh shares in the last session. Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd recorded volume of 836.5 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.46 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 73.02 lakh shares. The stock gained 11.43% to Rs.385.20. Volumes stood at 125.11 lakh shares in the last session. Karur Vysya Bank Ltd recorded volume of 110.01 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.25 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 11.89 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.92% to Rs.267.40. Volumes stood at 13.85 lakh shares in the last session. Indian Railway Catering & Tourism Corporation Ltd saw volume of 61.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.21 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7.50 lakh shares. The stock increased 4.00% to Rs.706.85. Volumes stood at 11.44 lakh shares in the last session. Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd notched up volume of 1228.93 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.66 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 160.48 lakh shares. The stock rose 8.68% to Rs.132.03. Volumes stood at 275.8 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MMTC_69316024395_2292.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops over 426 pts; auto shares slide]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-over-426-pts-auto-shares-slide/1662028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662028</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 26,050 mark. Auto shares extended losses for the second consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 426.32 points or 0.50% to 84,979.27. The Nifty 50 index lost 116.10 points or 0.44% to 26,026.65. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.11% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.22%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,721 shares rose and 2,403 shares fell. A total of 184 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index rose 0.49% to 27,750. The index jumped 1.54% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Uno Minda (down 1.53%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 1.11%), Hero MotoCorp (down 1.04%), Ashok Leyland (down 0.95%), Bajaj Auto (down 0.86%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 0.78%), TVS Motor Company (down 0.52%), Mahindra & Mahindra (down 0.42%), Exide Industries (down 0.31%) and Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 0.26%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was up 0.41% to 6.565 as compared with the previous close of 6.538. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8425 compared with its close of 89.7100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 0.89% to Rs 1,39,329. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.08% to 98.03. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.56% to 4.153. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 7 cents or 0.11% to $62.31 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Dilip Buildcon rose 3.80% after the company announced that it has secured a letter of award (LOA) for a significant road construction project in Bihar. Astra Microwave Products rose 2.38% after the company announced the execution of a memorandum of undertaking with state-run Bharat Electronics.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bondada Engg gains after bagging EPC order worth Rs 391-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bondada-engg-gains-after-bagging-epc-order-worth-rs-391-cr/1662030</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662030</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of NTPC Green Energy fell 0.32% to Rs 92.95 on the BSE.

Shares of NTPC Green Energy fell 0.32% to Rs 92.95 on the BSE. The order involves the design, engineering, site development, manufacture, inspection at NTPC Green Energy’s works, supply, insurance, transportation, storage, erection, installation, testing, and commissioning of a 300 MW solar power project. The order is valued at Rs 391.38 crore. The order will be executed under engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) mode, along with operations & maintenance (O&M) services for a period of three years. The company said that the award further enhances order book visibility and medium-term revenue growth prospects. Bondada Engineering provides engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) services and operations and maintenance (O&M) services to companies operating in the telecom, renewable energy and Indian railways sectors. NTPC Green Energy (NGEL) is a renewable energy company that focuses on undertaking projects through organic and inorganic routes.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BondadaEngineeringLtd_97234508_91662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil in demand as $58 mark holds up]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-oil-in-demand-as-58-mark-holds-up/1662022</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662022</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures are witnessing sustained upmove, staying near two-week high above $58 per barrel amid positive cues from equities.

WTI Crude oil futures are witnessing sustained upmove, staying near two-week high above $58 per barrel amid positive cues from equities. The US stocks hovered around record high amidst sustained uptick in technology stocks. The US actions against Venezuelan tankers spark fresh supply fears for oil and new worries are emerging now after the US attacks on Nigeria. Falling rig count is also supporting sentiments after oil prices tested near four-year low. Oil is currently trading up 0.34% at $58.55 per barrel. MCX Crude oil futures are trading at Rs 5283 per barrel, 0.21% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/steel-long-pipes-in-crude-oil-factory-during-sunset-picture_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sayaji Hotels rallies on inking 15-year deal for Takve Khurd luxury hotel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sayaji-hotels-rallies-on-inking-15-year-deal-for-takve-khurd-luxury-hotel/1662021</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662021</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agreement allows for renewal on mutually agreed terms for subsequent five-year periods.

The agreement allows for renewal on mutually agreed terms for subsequent five-year periods. The hotel, to be branded under the “SAYAJI” name, will feature 49 room keys, 71 villas with bedroom and hall, two banquet halls, a banquet lawn, a coffee shop cum restaurant, a specialty restaurant, an open rooftop restaurant, gym, spa, swimming pool, guest and service lifts, back-of-house areas, reception, offices, and ancillary equipment including two cars and an air-conditioning plant. The handover of the property is scheduled on or before 31 December 2027. The transaction is not a related party deal. No other disclosures have been reported. Sayaji Hotels is primarily engaged in the business of owning, operating & managing hotels. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 9.85 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 1.30 crore posted in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 12.6% YoY to Rs 31.67 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SayajiHotels_94949064653_2719.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baroda-bnp-paribas-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1662023</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662023</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 29 December 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes.

Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 29 December 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.12 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.14 per unit Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.40 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.43 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Arbitrage Fund – Direct Plan – Quarterly IDCW Option: Rs 0.19 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[The Wealth Company Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/the-wealth-company-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-scheme/1662020</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662020</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Wealth Company Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following scheme, With effect from 29 December 2025.

The Wealth Company Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following scheme, With effect from 29 December 2025. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager New Fund Manager The Wealth Company Gold ETF Mr. Rouhak Shah Mr. Niranjan Das

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Seshaasai Tech bags contract from large PSU Bank for debit card procurement and personalization]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/seshaasai-tech-bags-contract-from-large-psu-bank-for-debit-card-procurement-and-personalization/1662025</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662025</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract, which has been awarded to Seshaasai among other successful bidders, is for a three year period from December 2025 to December 2028.

The contract, which has been awarded to Seshaasai among other successful bidders, is for a three year period from December 2025 to December 2028. The company’s revenues under this engagement will accrue in line with actual allocations and volumes executed. This development marks a continuation of Seshaasai’s long-standing relationship with the bank, with the company having consistently supplied cards and related services since 2020. The new contract also entails enhanced business, with higher card volumes compared to the previous cycles and expansion in scope, as the bank introduces new-age and premium payment solutions, including metal cards, biometric cards, dynamic CVV cards, and non-card wearable form factors, aimed at enhancing customer experience, security, and product differentiation. Pragnyat Lalwani, managing director, Seshaasai Technologies, said: “We are pleased to continue our long standing-association with one of the country’s large public sector banks through this contract. The growth projected by the bank and inclusion of innovative and advanced payment form factors reflects the evolving needs of the banking ecosystem, and we remain committed to supporting our customers with secure, scalable and future-ready solutions as their portfolios continue to grow.” Seshaasai Technologies is a technology-led, multi-location solutions provider with a strong focus on the banking, financial services, and insurance (BFSI) sector. The company specializes in secure payment solutions, omnichannel communication, and fulfilment services, offering innovative, scalable technologies tailored to the evolving needs of its clients. The scrip shed 0.22% to currently trade at Rs 273.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SeshaasaiTechnologiesLtd_54031367_94321.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NIFTEM-Kundli Empanelled as PIA under PM VIKAS to Skill 2,110 Minority Youth in Food Processing Across Four States]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/niftem-kundli-empanelled-as-pia-under-pm-vikas-to-skill-2110-minority-youth-in-food-processing-across-four-states/1662019</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662019</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Institute of Food Technology Entrepreneurship and Management (NIFTEM) Kundli has been selected as a Project Implementing Agency (PIA) by the Ministry of Minority Affairs to implement the scheme PM VIKAS.

National Institute of Food Technology Entrepreneurship and Management (NIFTEM) Kundli has been selected as a Project Implementing Agency (PIA) by the Ministry of Minority Affairs to implement the scheme PM VIKAS. In this regard, an MoU was signed with the Ministry by the Institute. The scheme is aimed at developing the capacity of youth from minority communities through targeted interventions by providing skill training support in need-based courses and ensuring employment /livelihood opportunities for them. NIFTEM Kundli is one of the few Institutes of National Importance (INI) selected as PIA for the scheme. Under this project, NIFTEM-K will train a total of 2,110 beneficiaries from the minority community under three categories - Multi Skill Technician (Food Processing), Millet Products Processor and Assistant Baking Technician across seven locations in four states of Jharkhand, Bihar, Punjab and Haryana. This intervention seeks to enhance the employability of minority communities and create better livelihood opportunities by providing market and credit linkages to integrate them into the economic mainstream. The project will provide NSQF (National Skills Qualification Framework) compliant skill training to the beneficiaries through NCVET (National Council of Vocational Education and Training) approved courses, and will facilitate placement of eligible skilled beneficiaries in some form of employment (wage employment, self-employment or apprenticeship), including opportunities in the organized sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/wallet-2668577__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades tad below 26,050; broader mrkt outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-tad-below-26050-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1662018</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662018</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest losses in early-afternoon trade as investors stayed cautious ahead of upcoming corporate earnings announcements.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest losses in early-afternoon trade as investors stayed cautious ahead of upcoming corporate earnings announcements. The Nifty traded tad below the 26,050 mark. IT, pharma and auto shares declined, while consumer durables, metal and FMCG shares advanced. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 348.85 points or 0.41% to 85,059.85. The Nifty 50 index dropped 92.60 points or 0.35% to 26,049.50. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.01%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,841 shares rose and 2,228 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Titan Company (up 2.13%), Hindalco Industries (up 0.77%), Nestle India (up 0.78%), UltraTech Cement (up 0.69%) and NTPC (up 0.64%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (down 1.34%), Asian Paints (down 1.25%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.09%), Bajaj Finance (down 1.15%) and Tata Consultancy Services (down 1%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Vikran Engineering rose 3.78% after securing an order worth Rs 459.20 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy for the engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) of a 400 MW AC solar power project at Chitrakoot-1 in Uttar Pradesh. Strides Pharma Science slipped 2.07% after its step-down subsidiary, Strides Pharma Inc. USA (SPI), has received four observations from the USFDA following a routine inspection of its formulations facility in Chestnut Ridge, New York. Apollo Micro Systems climbed 1.88% after the company received orders amounting to Rs 100.24 crore from a private company for the supply of Unmanned Aerial Systems. NMDC advanced 1.90% after the company has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Colorado School of Mines, USA to establish a framework for research collaboration in mining, mineral processing, metallurgy and AI/ML in mining. Ola Electric Mobility jumped 2.71% after its subsidiary, Ola Electric Technology has secured incentives worth Rs 366.78 crore under the Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for automobile and auto components (PL I-Auto) for FY25. Global Markets: European markets remained closed on Friday on account of the Boxing Day holiday, while Asian markets traded mixed, with several regional exchanges also shut for the holiday. Silver prices continued rising and hit another high after notching a record Wednesday. Spot silver rose more than 4% on Friday to reach an all-time high of $74.89 per ounce. Silver has rallied over 159% year to date. Metal prices have soared this year amid shaky investor sentiment on riskier assets, as fears of an AI bubble and uncertainty over U.S. Fed rate cuts mount. Meanwhile, core consumer prices in Tokyo rose 2.3% in December from a year earlier, according to government data Friday. The core CPI, which strips out volatile fresh food costs, remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target, reinforcing the case for more interest rate hikes. The latest reading was below the 2.8% increase in November. Tokyo’s inflation numbers are widely considered to be a leading indicator of nationwide trends. The Australia and Hong Kong markets were closed for the holiday. U.S. equity futures ticked slightly higher in early Asian hours, after the S&P 500 closed at a new record for the second straight day on Wednesday stateside. The broad market index advanced 0.32%, ending the session at 6,932.05. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 288.75 points, or 0.60%, and also posted a closing record of 48,731.16. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.22% and settled at 23,613.31.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Bank of India eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-bank-of-india-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1662017</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662017</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Bank of India dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Union Bank of India dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 150.6, down 0.11% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 26048.65. The Sensex is at 85057.2, down 0.41%.Union Bank of India has eased around 2.39% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty PSU Bank index of which Union Bank of India is a constituent, has eased around 2.34% in last one month and is currently quoting at 8309.5, down 0.08% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 17.17 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 110.76 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 150.65, down 0.19% on the day. Union Bank of India jumped 27.77% in last one year as compared to a 9.39% rally in NIFTY and a 26.36% spurt in the Nifty PSU Bank index. The PE of the stock is 6.41 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnionBankI_88937846814_5493.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dilip Buildcon edges higher after bagging road construction contract in Bihar]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dilip-buildcon-edges-higher-after-bagging-road-construction-contract-in-bihar/1662016</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662016</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Valued at Rs 3,400 crore, the contract was awarded by Adani Road Transport (ARTL).

Valued at Rs 3,400 crore, the contract was awarded by Adani Road Transport (ARTL). The employer of the project is Bihar State Road Development Corporation. The project involves the engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) of the Ganga Path, which will connect the Sultanganj-Bhagalpur-Sabour Road. Executed on a back-to-back basis, the scope of work covers everything from the initial design and engineering to the final testing and commissioning of the roadway. The project spans a total construction length of 41.090 kilometers. The project is scheduled for completition within a 42-month timeframe. In a separate regulatory filing, Dilip Buildcon announced that it has been selected as the successful bidder for a major power transmission project in Karnataka. Valued at Rs 1,850 crore, the contract was awarded by REC Power Development and Consultancy (RECPDCL). The project involves establishing a 400/220/33 kV sub-station at Mekhali in the Belagavi District, along with the construction of associated 400 kV and 220 kV transmission lines. Dilip Buildcon will execute this project on a build, own, operate, and transfer (BOOT) basis. Under the terms of the agreement, the company will acquire 100% equity in a special purpose vehicle (SPV) to serve as the transmission service provider for a period of 35 years following the commercial operation date. The project was secured through a tariff-based competitive bidding (TBCB) process and will operate under a transmission service agreement (TSA). The construction and commissioning are expected to be completed within 24 months. Dilip Buildcon is presently in the business of development of infrastructure facilities on an Engineering Procurement and Construction basis (EPC) and undertakes contracts from various government and other parties and special purpose vehicles promoted by the company. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 22.8% to Rs 181.49 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 235.24 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations fell 22.9% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1925.89 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DilipBuildconLtd_92563827065_36662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd spurts 0.19%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eicher-motors-ltd-spurts-019-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1662008</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662008</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Eicher Motors Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 7326.5, up 0.19% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 26039.75. The Sensex is at 85032.85, down 0.44%. Eicher Motors Ltd has gained around 4.68% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Eicher Motors Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.5% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27885.65, down 0.51% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 84760 shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.32 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 7327.5, up 0.28% on the day. Eicher Motors Ltd is up 50.23% in last one year as compared to a 9.35% jump in NIFTY and a 20.1% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 42.72 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EicherMotors_60312767308_151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd spurts 0.11%, up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-grid-corporation-of-india-ltd-spurts-011-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1662009</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662009</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 268.35, up 0.11% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 26039.75. The Sensex is at 85032.85, down 0.44%. Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has dropped around 1.95% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 1.59% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35095.1, up 0.26% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 9.45 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 93.2 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 268.65, up 0.09% on the day. Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is down 13.27% in last one year as compared to a 9.35% gain in NIFTY and a 0.42% gain in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 16.15 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerGridCorpn_89479008350_5455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ABB India Ltd soars 0.02%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/abb-india-ltd-soars-002-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1662010</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662010</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ABB India Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

ABB India Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5216, up 0.02% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 26039.75. The Sensex is at 85032.85, down 0.44%. ABB India Ltd has slipped around 0.47% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which ABB India Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 1.59% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35095.1, up 0.26% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 31540 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.38 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5214.5, down 0.09% on the day. ABB India Ltd is down 23.82% in last one year as compared to a 9.35% spurt in NIFTY and a 0.42% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 62.5 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABB_25842664874_242.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund announces change in scheme name]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aditya-birla-sun-life-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-scheme-name/1662007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662007</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has announced change in scheme name under the following schemes, With effect from December 29, 2025 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in the name of the Scheme: Existing Name(s) Revised Name(s) Aditya Birla Sun Life US Treasury 1-3 Year Bond ETFs Fund of Funds Aditya Birla Sun Life US Treasury 1-3 Year Bonds ETFs Passive FOF Aditya Birla Sun Life US Treasury 3-10 Year Bond ETFs Fund of Funds Aditya Birla Sun Life US Treasury 3-10 Year Bonds ETFs Passive FOF

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/aktienkurse-analog-und-digital-picture-id672450302_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade in negative terrain; pharma shares under pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-in-negative-terrain-pharma-shares-under-pressure/1662005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662005</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in early afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in early afternoon trade. Market witnessed subdued volatility and concentrated option open interest signaling limited near-term movement. Investors will keep track on FII outcome, domestic and global economic data, and global cues. Nifty hovered below 26,100 level. Pharma shares tumbled for third straight session. At 12:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 308.73 points or 0.36% to 85,104.61. The Nifty 50 index dropped 79.30 points or 0.30% to 26,063.35. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.19% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.04%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,848 shares rose and 2,140 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 0.48% to 9.15. The Nifty 30 December 2025 futures were trading at 26,081.50, at a premium of 18.15 points as compared with the spot at 26,063.35. The Nifty option chain for the 30 December 2025 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 285 lakh contracts at the 26,100 strike price. Maximum put OI of 196.4 lakh contracts was seen at 26,000 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index declined 0.39% to 22,668.10. The index declined 1.13% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (down 1.66%), Piramal Pharma (down 1.29%), Ajanta Pharma (down 0.79%), Alkem Laboratories (down 0.75%), Ipca Laboratories (down 0.67%), Zydus Lifesciences (down 0.65%), Torrent Pharmaceuticals (down 0.61%), Mankind Pharma (down 0.53%), Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (down 0.5%) and Lupin (down 0.1%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: NTPC rose 0.95%. The company announced the commercial operation of the remaining 13 MW of its 23 MW Solapur Solar PV Project in Maharashtra, taking the project to full capacity. Apollo Micro Systems climbed 2.17% after the company received orders amounting to Rs 100.24 crore from a private company for the supply of Unmanned Aerial Systems. Panacea Biotec surged 14.66% after it has received an award from the United Nations International Children’s Emergency Fund (UNICEF) for the supply of its WHO pre-qualified pentavalent vaccine, Easyfive-TT, for 2023–2027.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>