<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:31:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baazar Style Retail tumbles on Rs 332 crore warrant deal with Cupid]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baazar-style-retail-tumbles-on-rs-332-crore-warrant-deal-with-cupid/1666273</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666273</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Investors appeared wary of potential dilution from the proposed issuance.

Investors appeared wary of potential dilution from the proposed issuance. Cupid’s shares also came under pressure. The stock slipped 7.69% to Rs 372.30 as markets assessed the impact of the transaction. In an exchange filing, Baazar Style Retail said its board approved the fundraise at a meeting held on 20 January 2026. The company plans to issue 1.01 crore fully convertible equity warrants. The issue price has been fixed at Rs 328.25 per warrant. The total size of the preferential issue is Rs 331.53 crore. Each warrant will be convertible into one equity share with a face value of Rs 5. The conversion can be done in one or more tranches. The exercise window is 18 months from the date of allotment. The transaction is subject to shareholder approval and other regulatory clearances. While the fundraise will add to the company’s capital base, the sharp fall in the stock reflects near-term concerns around dilution. Baazar Style Retail is a value fashion and lifestyle retailer with a strong footprint in eastern India. The company has a dominant presence in Odisha and West Bengal and operates 214 stores. It is expanding rapidly through a focused cluster-based strategy, targeting Tier 2 and Tier 3 cities to take affordable, quality fashion deeper into emerging India. On a consolidated basis, Baazar Style Retail reported net profit of Rs 51.49 crore in Q2 September 2025 as against net loss of Rs 8.94 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales rose 70.99% YoY to Rs 531.69 crore in Q2 September 2025. Cupid is an Indian manufacturer of condoms, personal lubricants, IVD kits and a range of FMCG and personal care products. The company has recently expanded its portfolio to include fragrances, personal hygiene products and wellness items as part of its growth strategy. The company has a strong international presence, exporting to more than 110 countries, and is the first globally to receive WHO and UNFPA pre-qualification for both male and female condoms. Cupid's board will meet on 29 January 2026, to consider a bonus issue along with the company’s financial results for the third quarter. The company had reported a sharp improvement in performance in Q2 FY26, with consolidated net profit rising 140.47% YoY to Rs 24.12 crore from Rs 10.03 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations more than doubled, climbing 103.22% YoY to Rs 84.44 crore for the quarter ended September 30, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cupid_16723626520_5185.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shoppers Stop tanks as Q3 PAT slides 74% YoY to Rs 13 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shoppers-stop-tanks-as-q3-pat-slides-74-yoy-to-rs-13-cr/1666272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666272</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations marginally rose 0.71% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,320.85 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operations marginally rose 0.71% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,320.85 crore in Q3 FY26. The company posted a GAAP EBITDA of Rs 234 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 262 crore in Q3 FY25. Non-GAAP EBITDA for the December 2025 quarter stood at Rs 70 crore, reflecting a 36% YoY decline. The GAAP gross margin came in at 39.4% in Q3 FY26, slightly lower than the 40.7% recorded in Q3 FY25. The average transaction value (ATV) and average selling price (ASP) both rose 7% year-on-year in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, premium brands contributed 69% of total sales, up 6% year-on-year, with like-for-like (LFL) growth also at 6%. In Q3 FY26, core business sales stood at Rs 1,516 crore, remaining flat year-on-year. Beauty segment sales rose 14% to Rs 395 crore, while INTUNE sales grew 22% to Rs 77 crore. Shoppers Stop’s First Citizen loyalty program remained a key driver of sales, contributing 84% of total revenue during the quarter. The member base expanded to 13.3 million, supported by strong enrollments across tiers and a record addition of Premium Black Card members. The Black Card segment’s contribution rose to 21% of total sales, reflecting higher engagement from premium customers. The Beauty category sustained strong performance, led by growth in fragrances and continued expansion of global luxury brands. During the quarter, the company launched eight Estée Lauder Brands SIS stores and strengthened customer engagement through initiatives such as makeovers, masterclasses, and curated beauty events. The Beauty Distribution business scaled further, delivering 58% year-on-year growth. The Private Brands portfolio delivered steady performance, aided by focused product launches. FRATINI Girls, a new apparel line for young girls, received a positive initial response across eight stores, with plans to expand to 60 stores. The INTUNE value fashion format grew year-on-year, though performance was impacted by subdued discretionary demand. The company continues to strengthen the format through targeted investments in existing stores while maintaining disciplined capital allocation. During Q3 FY26, Shoppers Stop expanded its retail network with the opening of three department stores, three INTUNE stores, and one HomeStop store. Capital expenditure for the quarter stood at Rs 35 crore, taking year-to-date capex to Rs 89 crore. Working capital was reduced during the quarter, while net debt remained stable at Rs 90 crore. Kavindra Mishra, Managing Director & CEO, Shoppers Stop Ltd, said, “Q3 was marked by external factors such as festive calendar shifts and uneven consumption trends, which weighed on overall sales. However, we continued to make steady progress on our strategic priorities. Premium brands grew on a like-for-like basis and now account for 69% of our total sales, reinforcing the direction of our portfolio shift. The re-launch of our Juhu store as one of India’s most premium experiential retail destinations reflects our long-term commitment to differentiated customer experiences. Categories such as Beauty, Handbags and Watches continue to scale well, and our Beauty Distribution business has delivered strong year-on-year growth. While discretionary demand remained subdued for INTUNE, we are taking a calibrated approach to strengthening the format through focused investments and measured expansion. As macro conditions improve, we believe our investments in premium offerings, personalization and omnichannel capabilities position us well for sustainable growth.” Shoppers Stop is the nation's leading premier retailer of fashion and beauty brands.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShoppersSt_15063296637_19961.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen stuck near 158 per dollar amid fiscal concerns]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-stuck-near-158-per-dollar-amid-fiscal-concerns/1666270</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666270</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen hovered around 158 per dollar, struggling for direction as Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s proposed cut to the 8% food sales tax revived worries over Japan’s fiscal outlook, with funding details still unclear.

The Japanese yen hovered around 158 per dollar, struggling for direction as Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s proposed cut to the 8% food sales tax revived worries over Japan’s fiscal outlook, with funding details still unclear. Political uncertainty deepened after the announcement of a Feb. 8 snap election, while markets looked ahead to the Bank of Japan’s policy meeting, where rates are expected to remain unchanged following December’s hike. Although traders remained alert to the risk of yen intervention amid inflation concerns, losses were partly offset by a softer US dollar as escalating US–Europe tensions over Greenland undermined confidence in American assets. The dollar index traded at 98.4 against the basket of 6 other currencies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slides 646 pts; private bank shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slides-646-pts-private-bank-shares-decline/1666268</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666268</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in mid-morning trade as persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings, and lingering concerns over global trade and geopolitics weighed on investor sentiment.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in mid-morning trade as persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings, and lingering concerns over global trade and geopolitics weighed on investor sentiment. The Nifty traded below the 25,050 mark. Private bank stocks witnessed selling pressure for the third consecutive trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 645.67 points or 0.79% to 81,527.66. The Nifty 50 index lost 199.65 points or 0.79% to 25,035.10. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tumbled 1.66% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.70%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 872 shares rose and 3,114 shares fell. A total of 156 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 9.05% to 13.88. The Indian rupee fell to a record low of 91.19 against the US dollar on Wednesday, pressured by a stronger greenback as fresh tariff threats from US President Donald Trump over Greenland fueled global risk aversion. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 4,79,53,080 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:30 IST on Wednesday (21 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.54 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Private Bank index declined 1.44% to 27,995.55. The index dropped 2.42% in the three consecutive trading sessions. ICICI Bank (down 2.34%), IDFC First Bank (down 2.33%), Axis Bank (down 1.41%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (down 1.3%) and HDFC Bank (down 1.22%), Federal Bank (down 0.86%), IndusInd Bank (down 0.75%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Supreme Petrochem declined 1.47% after the company’s standalone net profit fell 57.74% to Rs 30.15 crore on 10% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,264.69 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Persistent Systems declined 4.32% after the company reported a 6.79% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 439.4 crore despite of 5.52% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3778.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. IndiaMart InterMESH jumped 3% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 55.62% to Rs 188.3 crore on 13.35% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 401.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asian market traded lower on Wednesday, while gold jumped to a record high level after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on countries resisting the transfer of Greenland to the United States. Spot gold prices rose over 1% to an all-time high of $4,813 per ounce as investors rushed into safe haven assets. On Saturday, Trump said that exports from eight European countries would face tariffs of 10% from Feb. 1, rising to 25% by June 1 if talks fail to deliver U.S. control of mineral-rich Greenland. He also threatened to slap 200% tariffs on French wine and champagne, following reports that President Emmanuel Macron was unwilling to join his proposed “Board of Peace.” Trump further criticized the U.K., calling its plan to transfer sovereignty of the Chagos Islands, which is home to a joint U.K.-U.S. military base, to Mauritius an “act of great stupidity,” citing the move as further justification for acquiring Greenland on national security grounds. European leaders have labeled President Donald Trump’s latest tariff threats “unacceptable” and are reportedly weighing retaliatory measures. France is said to be urging the European Union to deploy its strongest economic response tool, the so-called Anti-Coercion Instrument. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 870.74 points, or 1.76%, to end the session at 48,488.59. The S&P 500 dipped 2.06% to settle at 6,796.86. The Nasdaq Composite slid 2.39%, closing at 22,954.32. It was the worst session since October for all three major averages. U.S. Treasury yields spiked and the U.S. dollar declined as Trump’s threat caused a flight from U.S. assets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikram Solar slumps after Q3 PAT drops 25% QoQ to Rs 96-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikram-solar-slumps-after-q3-pat-drops-25-qoq-to-rs-96-cr/1666269</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666269</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit surged 405.47% while revenue from operations jumped 7.79% in Q3 FY26.

On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit surged 405.47% while revenue from operations jumped 7.79% in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax soared 402.2% to Rs 148.45 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 29.56 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Exceptional items during the quarter included labour code charges amounting to Rs 5.61 crore. EBITDA rose sharply to Rs 205 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 142% increase from Rs 85 crore reported in the year-ago period. The EBITDA margin expanded significantly to 19% in Q3 FY26 from 8% in Q3 FY25. Order book stood at 10.6 GW as of 31st December 2025. Domestic operations accounted for 84% of total revenue, while exports contributed the remaining 16%. In Q3 FY26, module sales jumped 35% YoY to 796 MW. Capacity utilization stands at 90% in during the quarter. Gyanesh Chaudhary, chairman & managing director, Vikram Solar, said, “During this quarter, we delivered a resilient and disciplined performance, anchored by strong execution volumes and continued improvements in operating efficiency. Revenues grew 8% yearon-year, reflecting the steady scale-up of our manufacturing operations and our ability to execute consistently in a dynamic market environment. The broader solar industry continues to be firmly positioned for long-term growth, supported by robust demand fundamentals, enabling policy frameworks, and a growing shift toward high-efficiency and technologically advanced solutions. Our order book remains robust at 10.6 GW, providing strong medium-term revenue visibility across utility-scale, C&I, and other customer segments. During the quarter, we successfully commenced operations at our 5 GW Vallam manufacturing facility, which is ramping up as planned and meaningfully strengthens our ability to deliver high-quality, large-scale solutions to both domestic and global customers. In parallel, our Gangaikondan cell and module projects continue to progress in line with our roadmap, reinforcing our focus on backward integration, cost competitiveness, and long-term resilience of the value chain. During the quarter, we successfully transitioned our entire portfolio to high-efficiency N-Type modules, with our HYPERSOL series delivering power outputs of up to 640 Wp. This marks an important step in aligning Indian manufacturing with international standards on efficiency, form factor, and long-term bankability.” Vikram Solar is one of the leading Indian solar module manufacturers, specializing in efficient photovoltaic (PV) module manufacturing, with an international presence across 39 countries. The company is one of the largest PV module manufacturers in India with cumulative production capacity of 9.5 GW.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vikram-Solar-Ltd_64374838_68162.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Persistent Systems drops after Q3 PAT slides 7% QoQ to Rs 439 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/persistent-systems-drops-after-q3-pat-slides-7-qoq-to-rs-439-cr/1666234</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666234</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 17.82% and 23.38% respectively in Q3 FY26.

On a year on year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 17.82% and 23.38% respectively in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items stood at Rs 654.01 crore, up 6.03% QoQ and 35.68% YoY. The exceptional item comprised the impact of new labour code charges amounting to Rs 89.02 crore during the quarter. Excluding the one-time impact of the new labour code charges, EBIT came in at Rs 631.78 crore, registering an 8.2% sequential growth and a 38.6% year-on-year increase. In dollar terms, the company has recorded revenue of $422.5 million (up 4% QoQ). In constant currency terms, the revenue is higher 4.1% sequentially. The order booking for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025, was $674.5 million in Total Contract Value (TCV) and $501.9 million in Annual Contract Value (ACV). Sandeep Kalra, chief executive officer and executive director, Persistent: “We delivered sustained performance, achieving our 23rd sequential quarter of revenue growth with 4.0% quarter-on-quarter and 17.3% year-on-year growth. This was accompanied by an EBIT margin of 16.7%, excluding a one-time impact of 2.3% arising from the New Labour Codes. In line with this performance, we are declaring an interim dividend of Rs 22 per share. Our performance reflects a deeper role in strategic client programs and sustained demand for data, cloud, and digital engineering across our core industries. This momentum is reinforced by our inclusion among India’s Most Valuable Brands by Kantar BrandZ. We are also applying Agentic AI within our own operations, as a ‘customer zero’ to improve productivity and speed adoption at scale, an approach further validated by our recognition as a Microsoft Frontier Firm.” Meanwhile, the company’s board declared an interim dividend of Rs 22 per equity share of face value Rs 5 each for FY26. The record date for dividend has been fixed as on Tuesday 27 January 2026. In addition, to achieve entity rationalization and operational efficiency within the group, the Board of Directors approved the transfer of 100% shareholding in Persistent Systems Germany GmbH and Persistent Systems France S.A.S. from Persistent Systems, India, to Aepona Group, Ireland, subject to the execution of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) in due course. Persistent Systems is a global services and solutions company delivering AI-led, platform-driven digital engineering and enterprise modernization to businesses across industries. Persistent offers a comprehensive suite of services, including software engineering, product development, data and analytics, CX transformation, cloud computing, and intelligent automation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PersistentSys_70071143_18286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Supreme Petrochem slides after Q3 PAT drops 58% YoY to Rs 30 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/supreme-petrochem-slides-after-q3-pat-drops-58-yoy-to-rs-30-cr/1666211</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666211</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Supreme Petrochem declined 1.47% to Rs 500 after the company’s standalone net profit fell 57.74% to Rs 30.15 crore on 10% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,264.69 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SupremePetroch_63985677359_3608.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at CreditAccess Grameen Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-creditaccess-grameen-ltd-counter/1666188</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666188</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Adani Green Energy Ltd, SRF Ltd, Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd, SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 21 January 2026.

Adani Green Energy Ltd, SRF Ltd, Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd, SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 21 January 2026. CreditAccess Grameen Ltd registered volume of 6.03 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 86.69 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6951 shares. The stock gained 8.71% to Rs.1,348.30. Volumes stood at 11155 shares in the last session. Adani Green Energy Ltd registered volume of 11.18 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.95 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.61 lakh shares. The stock slipped 0.76% to Rs.876.60. Volumes stood at 1.34 lakh shares in the last session. SRF Ltd recorded volume of 32422 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.08 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5329 shares. The stock dropped 4.33% to Rs.2,748.70. Volumes stood at 10714 shares in the last session. Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd notched up volume of 6.71 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 4.12 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.63 lakh shares. The stock gained 2.43% to Rs.101.30. Volumes stood at 1.86 lakh shares in the last session. SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd witnessed volume of 1.13 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 3.87 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 29136 shares. The stock increased 0.23% to Rs.2,053.15. Volumes stood at 6908 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CreditAccessGrameenLtd_17343154102_37419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KPI Green Energy Q3 PAT jumps 48% YoY to Rs 126 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kpi-green-energy-q3-pat-jumps-48-yoy-to-rs-126-cr/1666186</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666186</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 676 crore, up 45% year-on-year from Rs 466 crore in Q3 FY25, driven by accelerated project execution and strong performance across key business segments.

Total revenue for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 676 crore, up 45% year-on-year from Rs 466 crore in Q3 FY25, driven by accelerated project execution and strong performance across key business segments. EBITDA rose to Rs 251 crore in Q3 FY26, up 73% year-on-year from Rs 145 crore in Q3 FY25, supported by improved operational efficiency and scale-driven benefits. The board has declared a third interim dividend of 4%, or Rs 0.20 per equity share (face value Rs 5 each), for FY26. The record date for determining shareholder entitlement has been fixed as 28 January 2026. KPI Green Energy is part of KP Group. They develop, build, own, manage, and maintain renewable power facilities (solar and wind solar hybrid power project) as an Independent Power Producer (IPP) and as a service provider to Captive Power Producers (CPPs) under the ‘Solarism’ brand. Shares of KPI Green Energy tanked 3.51% to currently trade at Rs 427 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/K.P.I.GlobalInfrastructureLtd._85264125_73584.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DXY lingers near 2-week low amid escalating EU-US trade tensions ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dxy-lingers-near-2-week-low-amid-escalating-eu-us-trade-tensions/1666185</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666185</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index is extending slide for the third straight day to its lowest level in almost two-weeks.

The dollar index is extending slide for the third straight day to its lowest level in almost two-weeks. Escalating tensions between US and EU over trade tariffs are weighing on sentiments. President Donald Trump, attending the World Economic Forum in Davos, reportedly remained firm on his plan to acquire Greenland. US President Donald Trump said there is “no going back” on his ambitions regarding Greenland, alongside earlier threats to impose new 10% tariffs on eight European Union (EU) countries, fuelling concerns over slower economic growth. DXY, that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 98.39, marginally down on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IndiaMART InterMESH gains after Q3 PAT jumps 56% YoY to Rs 188 scr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indiamart-intermesh-gains-after-q3-pat-jumps-56-yoy-to-rs-188-scr/1666184</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666184</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 55.35% YoY to Rs 247 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 55.35% YoY to Rs 247 crore during the quarter. EBITDA fell 3% YoY to Rs 134 crore, while the EBITDA margin stood at 33% for the period. Collection from customer jumped 17% YoY to Rs 426 crore in Q3 FY26. This was primarily driven by IndiaMART’s standalone collections of Rs 390 crore, reflecting a 14% YoY growth, along with Rs 33 crore in collections from its subsidiary, Busy Infotech. Deferred Revenue as on December 31, 2025 increased to Rs 1,775 crore representing a YoY growth of 19%. This primarily includes IndiaMART Standalone Deferred Revenue of Rs 1,654 crore and Busy Infotech Deferred Revenue of Rs.112 crore. Cash Flow from Operations for the quarter was Rs 129 crore. Cash and Investments balance stood at Rs 3,051 crore as on December 31, 2025. On a standalone net profit jumped 65.01% to Rs 206.1 crore on 9.13% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 368 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. IndiaMART registered Unique business enquiries of 28 million in Q3FY26. Supplier Storefronts grew to 8.7 million, an increase of 6% YoY and paying suppliers at the end of the quarter were 2,21,000. Dinesh Agarwal, chief executive officer, said, “We are focused on delivering sustained growth by strengthening our platform, enhancing quality, and improving experience and engagement for both buyers and suppliers, while reinforcing trust across the marketplace. These initiatives are supported by the rapid adoption of AI-enabled technologies. Underpinned by a robust business model and strong cash generation, we remain well positioned to drive sustainable, long-term value creation for all stakeholders.” IndiaMART InterMESH is India's largest online B2B marketplace for business products and services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndiaMARTInterMESH_51321124_68842.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s financial journey has unfolded like a quiet revolution over past decade, says SEBI Investor Survey]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-financial-journey-has-unfolded-like-a-quiet-revolution-over-past-decade-says-sebi-investor-survey/1666182</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666182</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SEBI Investor Survey 2025 has stated that over the past decade, India’s financial journey has unfolded like a quiet revolution—steady at first, then unmistakably transformative.

SEBI Investor Survey 2025 has stated that over the past decade, India’s financial journey has unfolded like a quiet revolution—steady at first, then unmistakably transformative. The scale of this transformation becomes clear when we trace its arc: BSE equity market capitalization, once around Rs 101 lakh crore in FY2014–15, has surged to nearly Rs 4701 lakh crore by October 2025, it noted. During the same period, mutual fund assets under management expanded from Rs 12 lakh crore in 2015 to Rs 79 lakh crore in September 2025. These numbers illustrate more than financial growth—they reflect the growing confidence of everyday investors who are now discovering markets as an accessible path to long-term wealth. Digital platforms have changed the way investors engage, simplifying onboarding, shortening settlement cycles, and expanding reach across the country. The survey findings indicate that approximately 63% of Indian households demonstrate awareness of at least one securities market product. However, this translates into actual investment activity for only 9.5% of households, creating a substantial gap of over 53 percentage points. Of the 33.72 crore households in the country, 53.5% are aware of securities market products but do not invest, while 37% are not aware of such products at all.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CreditAccess Grameen jumps on sharp Q3 profit rebound]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/creditaccess-grameen-jumps-on-sharp-q3-profit-rebound/1666183</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666183</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net profit swung to Rs 252.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 99.5 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net profit swung to Rs 252.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 99.5 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit after tax more than doubled, rising 100.4% from Rs 125.8 crore in Q2 FY26. Net interest income grew 13.4% YoY to Rs 976.9 crore and remained almost flat QoQ. Non-interest income rose 21.2% YoY to Rs 55 crore and increased 2.8% over the previous quarter. Profit before tax stood at Rs 337.9 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 128.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, PBT almost doubled, rising 99.8% from Rs 169.2 crore in Q2 FY26. Pre-provision operating profit came in at Rs 680.5 crore in Q3 FY26, up 9.2% YoY but down 2.1% QoQ. Employee expenses increased 27.2% to Rs 226.9 crore while other expenses rose 20% to Rs 108.2 crore. Depreciation and amortisation rose 5.5% YoY to Rs 16.4 crore. Impairment costs fell sharply by 54.4% YoY to Rs 342.6 crore, aiding the bottom-line recovery. On the balance sheet front, assets under management rose 7.1% YoY to Rs 26,566 crore, while disbursements grew 13.4% YoY to Rs 5,767 crore. The lender added 2.06 lakh new borrowers during the quarter, with 39% being new-to-credit customers. Portfolio share of unique borrowers improved to 43% in Q3 FY26 from 41% in Q2 FY26. Asset quality continued to strengthen, with PAR 0+ declining to 4.4% from 4.7% in the previous quarter. Collection efficiency improved to 95.5% in December 2025 from 94.5% in September 2025. Declining new PAR accretion led to reduction in credit cost by 54.4% YoY to Rs 342.6 crore. Operationally, the branch network expanded 7.9% YoY to 2,222 branches, while employee strength increased 12.2% YoY to 21,701. Retail finance portfolio share rose to 14.1% in December 2025 from 11.1% in September 2025. Liquidity remained strong at Rs 2,397.4 crore, equivalent to 8.4% of total assets, while the capital adequacy ratio stood at a healthy 26.4%. CreditAccess Grameen is a Bengaluru-based microfinance institution focused on providing micro-loans to women customers in rural India. The company operates across more than 450 districts in 16 states and one union territory through a widespread branch-led model, with a strategic focus on disciplined growth, improving asset quality and sustainable profitability.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CreditAccessGrameenLtd_17343154102_37419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Arbitrage Fund announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-arbitrage-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1666181</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666181</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced 23 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option of Kotak Arbitrage Fund.

Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced 23 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option of Kotak Arbitrage Fund. The amount of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs 0.0659 Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs 0.0743

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India has accelerated its growth during periods of global slowdown and supply-chain disruptions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-has-accelerated-its-growth-during-periods-of-global-slowdown-and-supply-chain-disruptions/1666174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666174</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[At the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting 2026 in Davos, Union Minister for New and Renewable Energy Pralhad Joshi underscored that the real challenge of the global energy transition lies in building infrastructure that is resilient, scalable and investment-ready.

At the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting 2026 in Davos, Union Minister for New and Renewable Energy Pralhad Joshi underscored that the real challenge of the global energy transition lies in building infrastructure that is resilient, scalable and investment-ready. The Union Minister highlighted India’s experience of combining scale with system resilience, noting that the country has achieved 267 GW of non-fossil fuel capacity as of December 2025 and is firmly on track to meet its 2030 targets. This is backed by robust policies, strong domestic manufacturing, grid modernisation, energy storage solutions and emerging frameworks for geothermal and nuclear energy. He emphasised the need for patient capital, blended finance and deeper collaboration among governments, the private sector and multilateral development banks to enable a sustainable and inclusive global energy transition. The Minister noted that even during periods of global slowdown and supply-chain disruptions, India has accelerated its growth by building resilience and expanding capabilities with a long-term vision.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-growth-1-1057028_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty tad below 25,100 level; consumer durables shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-tad-below-25100-level-consumer-durables-shares-decline/1666171</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666171</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in morning trade as persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings, and lingering concerns over global trade and geopolitics weighed on investor sentiment.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in morning trade as persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings, and lingering concerns over global trade and geopolitics weighed on investor sentiment. The Nifty traded a tad below the 25,100 level. Consumer durables stocks witnessed selling pressure for the ninth consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 462.47 points or 0.56% to 81,718. The Nifty 50 index lost 144 points or 0.57% to 25,098.10. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.13% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.02%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,075 shares rose and 2,705 shares fell. A total of 180 shares were unchanged. The Indian rupee fell to a record low of 91.19 against the US dollar on Wednesday, pressured by a stronger greenback as fresh tariff threats from US President Donald Trump over Greenland fueled global risk aversion. Result Today: Anant Raj (up 2.60%), Bajaj Consumer Care (down 0.02%), Bank of India (up 0.40%), Dalmia Bharat (up 0.10%), Dr Reddys Laboratories (up 0.96%), Gallantt Ispat (down 0.63%), Gravita India (down 0.64%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 0.09%), Jindal Stainless (down 0.86%), KEI Industries (down 2.64%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 2.44%), PNB Housing Finance (down 1.58%), Rajratan Global Wire (up 6.56%), Sagar Cements (down 0.50%), Supreme Industries (down 0.96%), Tata Communications (down 0.59%), Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem (down 1.14%), Thangamayil Jewellery (up 5.77%), UTI Asset Management Company (down 2.22%), and Eternal (up 1.07%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. New Listing: Shares of Amagi Media Labs were currently trading at Rs 347.10 at 10:10 IST on the BSE, representing a discount of 3.85% as compared with the issue price of Rs 361. The stock debuted at Rs 317, a discount of 12.19% to the issue price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 349.90 and a low of 317. On the BSE, over 7.82 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index fell 0.56% to 35,129.90. The index dropped 8.37% in the nine consecutive trading sessions. Kalyan Jewellers India (down 6.89%), Havells India (down 3.37%), Dixon Technologies (India) (down 2.49%), Blue Star (down 2.48%), Voltas (down 2.34%), Cera Sanitaryware (down 2.09%), Amber Enterprises India (down 1.96%), Whirlpool of India (down 1.38%), Century Plyboards (India) (down 1.29%) and PG Electroplast (down 1.25%) fell. Stocks in Spotlight: AU Small Finance Bank (SFB) fell 2.31%. The company reported a 26.34% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 667.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 528.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25. SRF declined 4.03%. The company reported a 59.60% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 432.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 271.08 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations rose 6.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 3,712.53 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India and EU are on cusp of historic FTA, says European Commission President]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-and-eu-are-on-cusp-of-historic-fta-says-european-commission-president/1666170</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666170</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[European Commission President Ursula Von Der Leyen has said that India and the European Union (EU) are on the cusp of signing a Free Trade Agreement (FTA), describing it as the mother of all agreements.

European Commission President Ursula Von Der Leyen has said that India and the European Union (EU) are on the cusp of signing a Free Trade Agreement (FTA), describing it as the mother of all agreements. In her address at the World Economic Forum (WEF), she said that after Davos, the next weekend, she will travel to India. There is still work to do. But we are on the cusp of a historic trade agreement. Some call it the mother of all deals, she said. One that would create a market of 2 billion people, accounting for almost a quarter of global GDP. And, crucially, that would provide a first-mover advantage for Europe with one of the world's fastest growing and most dynamic continents. Europe wants to do business with the growth centres of today and the economic powerhouses of this century. From Latin America to the Indo Pacific and far beyond, Europe will always choose the world. And the world is ready to choose Europe, she further noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aditya-birla-sun-life-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1666176</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666176</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has announced 23 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has announced 23 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The quantum of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Aditya Birla Sun Life Balanced Advantage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.154 Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.176 Aditya Birla Sun Life Arbitrage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.065 Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.067 Aditya Birla Sun Life Banking&Financial Services Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.504 Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 2.042 Aditya Birla Sun Life PSU Equity Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.610 Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.874 Aditya Birla Sun Life Special Opportunities Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.314 Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.415 Aditya Birla Sun Life Multi Asset Allocation Fund Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.899 Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.977

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Spirits Q3 PAT climbs 12% YoY to Rs 529 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-spirits-q3-pat-climbs-12-yoy-to-rs-529-cr/1666155</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666155</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding net excise duty) jumped 7.31% to Rs 3,683 crore in Q3 December 2025, driven by solid performance in the top-half of the portfolio, partly offset by the adverse policy led impact in Maharashtra and lapping the one-time retail pipeline fill in Andhra Pradesh in prior year comparative.

Revenue from operations (excluding net excise duty) jumped 7.31% to Rs 3,683 crore in Q3 December 2025, driven by solid performance in the top-half of the portfolio, partly offset by the adverse policy led impact in Maharashtra and lapping the one-time retail pipeline fill in Andhra Pradesh in prior year comparative. Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 5.31% year on year (YoY) to Rs 654 crore in Q3 FY26. In Q3 FY26, EBITDA stood at Rs 618 crore, up 5.1% over Q3 FY25, while the reported EBITDA margin at 16.8% contracted 35 bps year-on-year, largely due to higher A&P expenses. Interest cost for the quarter stood at Rs 19 crore, down 5.0% year-on-year. During the third quarter, the Prestige & Above segment accounted for 90.0% of net sales, up 80 bps year-on-year, with segment net sales rising 8.2%. In contrast, the Popular segment contributed 8.7% of net sales, down 110 bps over the same period last year, while segment net sales declined 4.6% year-on-year. The A&P reinvestment rate stood at 14.0% of net sales, reflecting targeted and consistent investment behind key trademarks and a higher growth mix at the premium end of the portfolio. Gross profit grew 12.6% year-on-year, while the reported gross margin expanded 219 bps to 46.9%, driven by premiumisation-led mix improvement, ongoing management productivity and the flow-through of prior-year headline pricing. Praveen Someshwar, CEO & MD, commenting on the Q3FY26 performance, said, “We have delivered a resilient quarter overall while navigating policy headwinds in one of our most salient markets. Strong momentum in Rest of India and at the top-end of our portfolio bodes well. We continue to make robust investments in our trademarks and execution capabilities to sustain the longterm value for all our stakeholders.” The board approved an interim dividend of Rs 6 per equity share (face value Rs 2) for FY26. The record date to determine shareholder entitlement has been fixed as 27 January 2026, and the dividend will be paid on or after 16 February 2026. United Spirits is one of the leading beverage alcohol companies in India. It is a subsidiary of Diageo Plc. Shares of United Spirits fell 2.89% to currently trade at Rs 1,280.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnitedSpirits_20574926747_8036.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sundaram MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sundaram-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1666156</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666156</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced 23 January 2026 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes.

Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced 23 January 2026 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) will be: Sundaram Dividend Yield Fund - Regular Plan - IDCW Option: 2.566 Sundaram Dividend Yield Fund - Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 4.275 Sundaram Value Fund - Regular Plan - IDCW Option: 1.228 Sundaram Value Fund - Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 1.489 Sundaram Focused Fund - Regular Plan - IDCW Option: 3.194 Sundaram Focused Fund - Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 3.461

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>