<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:38:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee slips]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-slips/1671567</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671567</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.5500 per Dollar on Wednesday (04 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.3675 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trent Q3 PAT climbs 36% YoY to Rs 640 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trent-q3-pat-climbs-36-yoy-to-rs-640-cr/1671562</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671562</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 829.80 crore, up 34.19% compared with Rs 618.36 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 829.80 crore, up 34.19% compared with Rs 618.36 crore in Q3 FY25. Exceptional items during the quarter amounted to Rs 25.79 crore and were related to labour code charges. Adjusted PAT jumped 41% YoY to Rs 660 crore during the quarter. Operating EBITDA climbed 23% YoY to Rs 822 crore. In Q3FY26, the company opened 17 Westside and 48 Zudio stores (including 1 store in the UAE). As of 31st December 2025, the company operated with a footprint of over 15 million sqft. across its fashion brands. The company said that it believes that, given its approach to merchandise sourcing, price architecture, distribution, and disciplined inventory provisioning, the full-year results are more representative of the underlying health of the business. The gross margin profile of Westside and Zudio remained stable. Operating EBIT margin for Q3 FY26 stood at 13.8%, compared with 13.2% in Q3 FY25. On consolidated basis, net profit jumped 2.73% to Rs 510.11 crore on 14.79% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5345.06 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company clarified that its consolidated revenue excludes sales from the Trent Hypermarket business due to accounting standards, though its share of profit from the venture is included under the equity method. The Star business consists of 79 stores including the addition of 6 stores and closure of 5 stores during the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company said it is pursuing multiple initiatives, including technology-led interventions, to enhance differentiation and improve customer convenience. Noel N Tata, chairman, Trent said, “On a higher base, our fashion business registered category leading growth during the quarter. The customer sentiment is gradually improving and our business outlook for the medium term continues to remain positive. Our focus continues to be on portfolio growth, elevating products and enhancing store experience for our customers. We have consistently delivered a differentiated consumer proposition that appeals to a wider audience across diverse markets. We believe an unwavering focus on being relevant to our customers and building resilience with our business model choices will continue to hold us in good stead. We are excited and remain committed to building out a sizable pure play direct-to-customer business across customer segments in the context of the market size and opportunity. In our Star business, we continue to apply Trent’s playbook and the contribution of our own brands is now trending over 74% of revenues. We recognize that the expansion program for Star stores has been slower vis-à-vis our expectations and we are looking to accelerate this agenda in the coming periods. The opportunity in the food space for the Star proposition is exciting at the same time it is intensely competitive and we are calibrating our store portfolio to be more future-ready. We remain convinced that this business is well poised to deliver growing consumer value in the years ahead.” As of 31st December 2025, the company’s store portfolio included 278 Westside, 854 Zudio (including 4 stores in the UAE) and 32 stores across other lifestyle concepts. Trent is part of the Tata Group and operates a portfolio of retail concepts. The primary customer propositions of Trent include Westside, one of India's leading chains of fashion retail stores, Zudio, a one stop destination for great fashion at great value and Star, which operates in the competitive food, grocery and daily needs segment. The counter rallied 4.98% to end at Rs 4013.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Trent_20841567073_345.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper turns around after rising more than 4% yesterday]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-turns-around-after-rising-more-than-4-yesterday/1671557</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671557</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper eased after massive gains in last session amid cautious moves as equities saw stressed moves.

COMEX Copper eased after massive gains in last session amid cautious moves as equities saw stressed moves. Shanghai Composite index rose 0.85% as buying support stayed in place. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index edged up mildly. Japanese Nikkei 225 index eased 0.78% on AI worries. European stocks saw mixed moves. The US stocks tanked from near-record levels overnight as concerns posed by AI advances hurt of technology stocks. Copper currently trades at $6.03 per pound, down 0.87% on the day after a 4.50% spike in last session. Broad outlook is supportive as global manufacturing witnessed a modest but encouraging start to 2026. The headline global manufacturing PMI rose from 50.4 to a three-month high of 50.9, signalling a sustained, albeit subdued, improvement of business conditions for a sixth straight month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Outstanding corporate bonds have grown at roughly 12% CAGR over last decade]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/outstanding-corporate-bonds-have-grown-at-roughly-12-cagr-over-last-decade/1671555</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671555</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tuhin Kanta Pandey, Chairman, SEBI, has highlighted in a latest speech how corporate bond markets can support India’s next phase of growth.

Tuhin Kanta Pandey, Chairman, SEBI, has highlighted in a latest speech how corporate bond markets can support India’s next phase of growth. The corporate bond market has become increasingly important. In FY25, issuers raised about Rs 10 trillion through debt issuances; between April - December 2025, they have raised about Rs 6.8 trillion. Over the last decade, outstanding corporate bonds have grown at roughly 12% CAGR, from about Rs 17.5 trillion in FY15 to Rs 58 trillion at end of December 2025. These amount to around 60% of bank credit to industry and services. Even so, corporate bonds outstanding amount to only about 16% of our GDP. By comparison, this figure for South Korea is around 79%, for Malaysia - 54%, and China- 38%, he noted. SEBI has already taken measures for deepening the primary and secondary bond markets and building the foundation for a larger, more liquid corporate bond market. The next phase depends on issuers, investors, intermediaries, stock exchanges, and regulators moving together.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JPY/INR futures fall to 58 levels ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jpyinr-futures-fall-to-58-levels/1671554</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671554</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures climbed 0.22% at 90.55.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures climbed 0.22% at 90.55. GBP/INR and EUR/INR added 0.65% and 0.44% to settle at 124.21 and 107.13 respectively. Meanwhile, JPY/INR futures slipped by 0.24% to end at 58.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR reverses sharp rally as sentiments turn cautious amid absence of formal documentation for US-India trade deal ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-reverses-sharp-rally-as-sentiments-turn-cautious-amid-absence-of-formal-documentation-for-us-india-trade-deal/1671543</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671543</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.43 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday, after a sharp rally in the previous trading session following India-US trade deal announcement and possible dollar buying by corporates and importers.

The Indian rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.43 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday, after a sharp rally in the previous trading session following India-US trade deal announcement and possible dollar buying by corporates and importers. However, caution still remains as there is no signed or officially released trade agreement yet, no framework text or final documentation. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 90.35 and touched an early high of 90.26 and a low of 90.54 against the greenback. Meanwhile, Indian shares ended a choppy session little changed on Wednesday as fears over AI-led disruption countered investor optimism surrounding the U.S.-India trade deal. The benchmark BSE Sensex swung between gains and losses before ending the session up 78.56 points, or 0.09 percent, at 83,817.69. The broader NSE Nifty index rose 48.45 points, or 0.19 percent, to 25,776. In the meantime, the Reserve Bank of India will hold its Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) meeting from today to Friday. The first MPC decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra for 2026 will be announced on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI conducts USD/INR swap auction for US$10 billion, bid to cover ratio hits 2.5 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-conducts-usdinr-swap-auction-for-us10-billion-bid-to-cover-ratio-hits-25/1671544</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671544</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The RBI conducted a USD/INR buy/sell swap auction for a notified amount of USD 10 billion, as previously announced in its January 23, 2026 announcement.

The RBI conducted a USD/INR buy/sell swap auction for a notified amount of USD 10 billion, as previously announced in its January 23, 2026 announcement. For USD 10 billion, total bids were received for USD 25.03 billion. The Cut-off premium was 748 paisa while weighted average premium for accepted bids was 751.66 paisa. Partial allotment as percent of competitive bids at cut off premium was 71.89%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-exchange-911613__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India joins BRICS centre for industrial competencies to support manufacturing and MSME sector]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-joins-brics-centre-for-industrial-competencies-to-support-manufacturing-and-msme-sector/1671508</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671508</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India has joined the BRICS Centre for Industrial Competencies (BCIC) at an event organised by the Department for Promotion of Industry and Internal Trade (DPIIT), Ministry of Commerce & Industry.

India has joined the BRICS Centre for Industrial Competencies (BCIC) at an event organised by the Department for Promotion of Industry and Internal Trade (DPIIT), Ministry of Commerce & Industry. The BCIC, launched in partnership with the United Nations Industrial Development Organization (UNIDO), serves as a one-stop centre providing integrated support services to manufacturing companies and Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs) across BRICS countries, with a focus on strengthening Industry 4.0 competencies. Following this, a Trust Fund Agreement was signed between DPIIT and UNIDO. The National Productivity Council (NPC) has been designated as the India Centre for BRICS Industrial Competencies. Under the policy guidance of DPIIT and with technical support from UNIDO, NPC will spearhead India’s engagement with BCIC and contribute to capacity building, productivity enhancement and adoption of advanced manufacturing practices.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/auto-mechanic-service-and-repair-picture-id652660470_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty, Sensex extend rally despite global tech rout]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-sensex-extend-rally-despite-global-tech-rout/1671506</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671506</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks eked out modest gains on Tuesday, extending their rally to a third straight session.

The key equity benchmarks eked out modest gains on Tuesday, extending their rally to a third straight session. Sentiment remained supported by the landmark India-US trade agreement, which helped ease external uncertainty. Gains, however, were capped as rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran kept risk appetite in check. The Nifty 50 closed above the 25,750 level, led by buying in consumer durables, energy and auto stocks, while IT shares lagged amid a global technology selloff. The S&P BSE Sensex added 78.56 points or 0.09% to 83,817.69. The Nifty 50 index rose 48.45 points or 0.19% to 25,776. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.83% while the Nifty jumped 3.82%. Adani Ports & SEZ (up 2.25%), Reliance Industries (up 1.27%) and ICICI Bank (up 1.18%) boosted the Nifty today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index advanced 0.61% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.54%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,726 shares rose and 1,477 shares fell. A total of 168 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 4.98% to 12.25. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India's rate-setting panel kicked off its three-day monetary policy meeting today. The outcome of the meeting of the six-member Monetary Policy Committee, chaired by RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra, is scheduled to be announced on Friday. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Services PMI rose to 58.5 in January from 58.0 in December. The flash score was 59.3. A score above 50.0 indicates expansion. The composite output index rose to 58.4 in January from December's 11-month low of 57.8, indicating that the latest sharp rate of expansion in the Indian private sector was boosted by stronger growth at goods producers as well as service providers. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.19% to 6.708 compared with previous session close of 6.721. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.4475 compared with its close of 90.3200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 3.25% to Rs 158,811. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.20% to 97.57. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.19% to 4.280. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 38 cents or 0.56% to $67.71 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently up by 136 points, signaling a strong opening for US stocks today. European stocks traded higher on Wednesday as Euro zone inflation cooled to 1.7% in January, flash data from statistics agency Eurostat showed Wednesday. Core inflation, which excludes more volatile energy, food, alcohol and tobacco prices, stood at 2.2% in January, a touch down from the 2.3% seen in the year to December. The latest data shows the key inflation rate has now dipped below the European Central Bank’s 2% target. It’s likely to steer clear of any more rate cuts for the foreseeable future. Asian indices ended higher, bucking the weak lead from Wall Street where a sell-off in U.S. technology stocks dampened sentiment, while gold extended its gains for a second straight session. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back as investors dumped technology stocks and moved into shares more broadly linked to improvements in the economy. The broad market index fell 0.84% and closed at 6,917.81. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 166.67 points, or 0.34%, to end at 49,240.99. Earlier, the 30-stock index rose as much as 0.5% to touch 49,653.13, a new record. The Nasdaq Composite shed 1.43%, settling at 23,255.19. Stocks in Spotlight: IT stocks came under sharp pressure on Wednesday amid a global technology selloff after AI firm Anthropic unveiled new automation tools, stoking fears of AI-led disruption to traditional, licence-driven business models. The Nifty IT index tanked 5.87% to 36,345.65. The index rallied 1.41% in the previous trading session. Infosys slipped 7.37% and Tata Consultancy Services fell 6.99%. Coforge declined 6.02%, while LTIMindtree slipped 5.84%. Persistent Systems dropped 4.76% and Mphasis lost 4.59%. HCL Technologies shed 4.58%, Tech Mahindra declined 4.52%, Oracle Financial Services Software fell 4.06%, while Wipro ended 3.79% lower. Bajaj Finserv (BFS) rose 0.30%. The company reported a 0.08% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 2,229.15 crore on 29.93% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 39,708.06 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Finance shed 0.12%. The company reported a 6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,977.85 crore despite 17.63% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 21,213.89 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Teamlease Services rallied 5.32% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 46.75% to Rs 41.72 crore on 3.14% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 3,012.95 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Kansai Nerolac Paints fell 2.61% after its standalone net profit tanked 75.08% to Rs 131.20 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 526.49 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 3.53% to Rs 1,907.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,842.16 crore posted in the same quarter last year. Sheela Foam surged 14.53% after the company’s consolidated net profit soared 211.97% to Rs 52.13 crore on 11.1% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1,074.43 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ADF Foods surged 8.80% after the company reported 55.7% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 29.2 crore on a 29.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 191 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The Anup Engineering dropped 6.52% after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 15.5% year-on-year to Rs 25.53 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 30.21 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 20.5% YoY to Rs 206.92 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 171.74 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Century Plyboards (India) declined 5% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 8.37% to Rs 65.05 crore on a 2.57% drop in total income to Rs 495.53 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit and revenue rose 10.55%, while total income increased 18.29% in Q3 FY26. Emami advanced 1.06% after the company reported 14.5% increase in consolidated to Rs 319.48 crore on a 9.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,151.81 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1671505</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671505</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,830, a premium of 54 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,776 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,830, a premium of 54 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,776 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index rose 48.45 points or 0.19% to 25,776. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 4.98% to 12.25. Infosys, Tata Consultancy Services and Hindustan Aeronautics were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty settles above 25.750 mark; broader mrkt outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-settles-above-25750-mark-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1671503</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671503</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with small gains today, extending rally for a third consecutive session after initial intraday weakness was absorbed by robust buying.

The key equity benchmarks ended with small gains today, extending rally for a third consecutive session after initial intraday weakness was absorbed by robust buying. Investor sentiment was underpinned by the landmark India-US trade agreement, which reduced external uncertainty and bolstered confidence in near-term economic and corporate growth prospects. Market recovery also reflects tactical buying by funds anticipating positive spillovers from trade and policy developments.The Nifty settled above the 25,750 mark. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex added 78.56 points or 0.09% to 83,817.69. The Nifty 50 index rose 48.45 points or 0.19% to 25,776. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.83% while the Nifty jumped 3.82%. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index advanced 0.61% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.54%. The market breadth was strong. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 4.98% to 12.25. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 2.66%), the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 2.08%) and the Nifty Auto index (up 1.18%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 5.87%), the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.34%) and the Nifty Healthcare index (up 0.13%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel began its three-day meeting for the upcoming bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday, against the backdrop of a growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation, and the recently concluded India–US trade deal that has eased prolonged external uncertainty. The decision of the RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Services PMI rose to 58.5 in January from 58.0 in December. The flash score was 59.3. A score above 50.0 indicates expansion. Both output and new orders grew at faster rates in January, and the upturn in the latter was driven by demand buoyancy, new business gains, and tech investment. The growth in sales was attributed to greater client interest in their services and a stronger online presence. New export orders grew at the fastest pace in three months, linked to new business gains from clients in Indonesia, Kenya, Malaysia, Oman, Qatar, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Vietnam. In line with rising new orders, Indian service providers resumed hiring activity in January, though the pace of job creation was only marginal. On the price front, input price inflation accelerated to a 4-month high in January, and selling price inflation was the strongest in three months. Looking ahead, business confidence strengthened amid optimistic forecasts for efficiency gains, marketing efforts, and new client wins. The composite output index rose to 58.4 in January from December's 11-month low of 57.8, indicating that the latest sharp rate of expansion in the Indian private sector was boosted by stronger growth at goods producers as well as service providers. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.19% to 6.708 compared with previous session close of 6.721. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.4475 compared with its close of 90.3200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 3.25% to Rs 158,811. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.20% to 97.57. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.19% to 4.280. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 38 cents or 0.56% to $67.71 a barrel. Global Markets: European stocks traded higher on Wednesday as Euro zone inflation cooled to 1.7% in January, flash data from statistics agency Eurostat showed Wednesday. Core inflation, which excludes more volatile energy, food, alcohol and tobacco prices, stood at 2.2% in January, a touch down from the 2.3% seen in the year to December. The latest data shows the key inflation rate has now dipped below the European Central Bank’s 2% target. It’s likely to steer clear of any more rate cuts for the foreseeable future. Asian markets ended higher, breaking ranks with Wall Street after a sell-off in U.S. technology stocks weighed on sentiment, while gold extended gains for a second day. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back as investors dumped technology stocks and moved into shares more broadly linked to improvements in the economy. The broad market index fell 0.84% and closed at 6,917.81. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 166.67 points, or 0.34%, to end at 49,240.99. Earlier, the 30-stock index rose as much as 0.5% to touch 49,653.13, a new record. The Nasdaq Composite shed 1.43%, settling at 23,255.19.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index falls 5.87%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-falls-587/1671484</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671484</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index ended down 5.87% at 36345.65 today.

Nifty IT index ended down 5.87% at 36345.65 today. The index has slipped 4.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Infosys Ltd shed 7.26%, Tata Consultancy Services Ltd dropped 7.01% and Coforge Ltd fell 5.74%. The Nifty IT index has fallen 15.00% over last one year compared to the 8.58% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Energy index gained 2.00% and Nifty Commodities index increased 1.90% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.19% to close at 25776 while the SENSEX recorded a gain of 0.09% to close at 83817.69 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market extend gains for 3rd day; IT shares tanks; VIX slumps 4.98%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-extend-gains-for-3rd-day-it-shares-tanks-vix-slumps-498/1671482</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671482</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with small gains today, extending gains for a third consecutive session after initial intraday weakness was absorbed by robust buying.

The key equity benchmarks ended with small gains today, extending gains for a third consecutive session after initial intraday weakness was absorbed by robust buying. Investor sentiment was underpinned by the landmark India-US trade agreement, which reduced external uncertainty and bolstered confidence in near-term economic and corporate growth prospects. Market recovery also reflects tactical buying by funds anticipating positive spillovers from trade and policy developments. The Nifty settled above the 25,750 mark. IT and pharma shares declined while consumer durables, oil & gas and metal shares advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 78.56 points or 0.09% to 83,817.69. The Nifty 50 index rose 48.45 points or 0.19% to 25,776. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.83% while the Nifty jumped 3.82%. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index advanced 0.61% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.54%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,639 shares rose and 1,493 shares fell. A total of 173 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 4.98% to 12.25. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel has started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy, against the backdrop of the growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation, and the recently concluded India-US trade deal, which ended prolonged external uncertainty. The decision of the RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) is scheduled to be announced on Friday. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Services PMI rose to 58.5 in January from 58.0 in December. The flash score was 59.3. A score above 50.0 indicates expansion. Both output and new orders grew at faster rates in January, and the upturn in the latter was driven by demand buoyancy, new business gains, and tech investment. The growth in sales was attributed to greater client interest in their services and a stronger online presence. New export orders grew at the fastest pace in three months, linked to new business gains from clients in Indonesia, Kenya, Malaysia, Oman, Qatar, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Vietnam. In line with rising new orders, Indian service providers resumed hiring activity in January, though the pace of job creation was only marginal. On the price front, input price inflation accelerated to a 4-month high in January, and selling price inflation was the strongest in three months. Looking ahead, business confidence strengthened amid optimistic forecasts for efficiency gains, marketing efforts, and new client wins. The composite output index rose to 58.4 in January from December's 11-month low of 57.8, indicating that the latest sharp rate of expansion in the Indian private sector was boosted by stronger growth at goods producers as well as service providers. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index tanked 5.87% to 36,345.65. The index rallied 1.41% in the previous trading session. IT stocks came under sharp pressure on Wednesday amid a global technology selloff after AI firm Anthropic unveiled new automation tools, stoking fears of AI-led disruption to traditional, licence-driven business models. Infosys (down 7.37%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 6.99%), Coforge (down 6.02%), LTIMindtree (down 5.84%) and Persistent Systems (down 4.76%), HCL Technologies (down 4.62%), Mphasis (down 4.59%), Tech Mahindra (down 4.52%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 4.06%) and Wipro (down 3.79%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Teamlease Services rallied 3.24% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 46.75% to Rs 41.72 crore on 3.14% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 3,012.95 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Finserv (BFS) rose 0.21%. The company reported a 0.08% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 2,229.15 crore on 29.93% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 39,708.06 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Rubicon Research rallied 6.13% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 91.2% to Rs 72.79 crore on 51.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 475.52 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Finance shed 0.08%. The company reported a 6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,977.85 crore despite 17.63% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 21,213.89 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Kansai Nerolac Paints tanked 2.81% after its standalone net profit tanked 75.08% to Rs 131.20 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 526.49 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 3.53% to Rs 1,907.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,842.16 crore posted in the same quarter last year. Sheela Foam surged 13.93% after the company’s consolidated net profit soared 211.97% to Rs 52.13 crore on 11.1% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1,074.43 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ADF Foods surged 10.03% after the company reported 55.7% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 29.2 crore on a 29.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 191 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The Anup Engineering dropped 6.34% after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 15.5% year-on-year to Rs 25.53 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 30.21 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 20.5% YoY to Rs 206.92 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 171.74 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Century Plyboards (India) declined 5% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 8.37% to Rs 65.05 crore on a 2.57% drop in total income to Rs 495.53 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit and revenue rose 10.55%, while total income increased 18.29% in Q3 FY26. Emami advanced 2.57% after the company reported 14.5% increase in consolidated to Rs 319.48 crore on a 9.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,151.81 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. RITES added 0.54%. The company reported 5.2% rise in consolidated to Rs 115.10 crore on a 5.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 608.59 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The company’s board has declared third interim dividend of Rs 1.90 per share for the financial year 2025-26. Global Markets: European stocks traded higher on Wednesday as investors digested more quarterly earnings ahead of the release of keenly anticipated regional inflation data. Asian markets ended higher, breaking ranks with Wall Street after a sell-off in U.S. technology stocks weighed on sentiment, while gold extended gains for a second day. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back as investors dumped technology stocks and moved into shares more broadly linked to improvements in the economy. The broad market index fell 0.84% and closed at 6,917.81. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 166.67 points, or 0.34%, to end at 49,240.99. Earlier, the 30-stock index rose as much as 0.5% to touch 49,653.13, a new record. The Nasdaq Composite shed 1.43%, settling at 23,255.19.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Q3 PAT climbs 14% YoY to Rs 341 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-q3-pat-climbs-14-yoy-to-rs-341-cr/1671475</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671475</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income (NII) rose 13.3% YoY to Rs 646.14 crore in Q3 FY26, while net interest margin (NIM) stood at 4.04% for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Net interest income (NII) rose 13.3% YoY to Rs 646.14 crore in Q3 FY26, while net interest margin (NIM) stood at 4.04% for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Operating profit (OP) increased 14.8% YoY to Rs 468.22 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 407.71 crore in Q3 FY25. On the asset quality front, gross non-performing assets (NPAs) amounted to Rs 474.45 crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 584.45 crore as of 31 December 2024. The gross NPA ratio was 0.91% as of 31 December 2025 as against 1.32% as of 31 December 2024. The net NPA ratio was 0.20% as of 31 December 2025, as against 0.41% as of 31 December 2024. Total deposits of the bank stood at Rs 56,707 crore as of 31 December 2025, recording a growth of 12.53% YoY. Gross advances of the bank stood at Rs 50,763 crore as of 31 December 2025, up by 16.30% YoY. CASA deposits rose 14.93% year-on-year to Rs 15,847 crore, reflecting stable granular funding. Provision coverage ratio (PCR) stood at 96.08% as of 31 December 2025. CRAR stood at 30.08 as of 31 December 2025, as against 29.35% as of 31 December 2024. Tamilnad Mercantile Bank is one of the renowned old private sector banks. Shares of Tamilnad Mercantile Bank rose 4.60% to close at Rs 624.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TamilnadMercantileBankLtd_18937215_12426.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Teamlease Services jumps after Q3 PAT surges 47% YoY to Rs 42 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/teamlease-services-jumps-after-q3-pat-surges-47-yoy-to-rs-42-cr/1671473</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671473</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax jumped 71.81% YoY to Rs 49.07 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before exceptional items and tax jumped 71.81% YoY to Rs 49.07 crore in Q3 FY26. Exceptional items in Q3 FY26 include Rs 5.68 crore linked to labour code compliance. EBITDA stood at Rs 42.5 crore, registering the growth of 22% compared with Rs 38.4 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 1.41% in Q3 FY26 as against 1.2% in Q3 FY25. Revenue from specialized staffing segment jumped 7% YoY to Rs 7,165 crore, with the GCC segment remaining a key growth driver for the company, contributing over 65% of total revenue through both volume and stability. Revenue from Degree Apprenticeship stood at Rs 46,000 crore(down 3% YoY), while General staffing stood at Rs 2,82,000 crore (down 6% YoY) during the period under review. The company’s headcount dropped 5% YoY to 335,165 in Q3 FY26. Ashok Reddy, executive vice chairman & whole-time director, TeamLease Services, said, “Our initiatives on digitization and cost optimization have been consistently contributing to operating leverage. Despite general slowness in the economy, our new logo acquisition is stable, including the GCC wins. Our YTD EBITDA grew 24% YoY setting a strong base for the future. Full impact of BFSI headcount loss will be absorbed by Q1FY27.” Team Lease Services provides to its clients a gamut of HR services that include staffing services, temporary recruitment, permanent recruitment, payroll process outsourcing, regulatory compliance services, vocational training / education and assessments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TeamLeaseServ_51614750130_24915.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro stays mildly supported ahead of key data updates]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-stays-mildly-supported-ahead-of-key-data-updates/1671472</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671472</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro stayed mildly supported today as recovery from a one and half week low stayed in place ahead of some key data releases.

Euro stayed mildly supported today as recovery from a one and half week low stayed in place ahead of some key data releases. Flash inflation and final composite Purchasing Managers' survey results from the euro area. Tomorrow, the European Central Bank (ECB) will also announce its monetary policy decision will be keenly watched for further cues. EUR/USD is currently quoting at $1.1839, up 0.03% on the day. European stocks are mixed. EUR/INR futures are quoting at 107.17, up 0.49%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/concept-money-tree-on-grass-picture-id462171033_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil edges above $64 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-oil-edges-above-64-per-barrel/1671471</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671471</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures edged above $64 per barrel on Wednesday, extending the prior session’s advance as geopolitical risk re-entered the market following the US downing of an Iranian drone in the Arabian Sea.

WTI crude oil futures edged above $64 per barrel on Wednesday, extending the prior session’s advance as geopolitical risk re-entered the market following the US downing of an Iranian drone in the Arabian Sea. Crude markets posted their first monthly gain in six months in January 2026, with WTI rising roughly 14% to $65.74 per barrel, its strongest monthly performance since mid-2023. The recovery followed an extended period of weakness driven by surplus supply, tepid demand growth, and elevated OPEC+ output, before risk events and short-term supply concerns prompted a reassessment of near-term price dynamics. Additional support came from API data indicating a sharp 11.1 million barrel draw in US crude inventories, while OPEC+ expects demand to firm gradually from March or April and will decide in early March on resuming monthly production increases.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concept-with-oil-rig-in-the-gulf-picture-id597_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lloyds Metals jumps after Q3 PAT climbs 169% YoY to Rs 1,047 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lloyds-metals-jumps-after-q3-pat-climbs-169-yoy-to-rs-1047-cr/1671499</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671499</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 189.38% to Rs 1,516.57 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 524.07 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 189.38% to Rs 1,516.57 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 524.07 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 1,856.4 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 235% YoY growth. The EBITDA margin improved to 36.01% in Q3 FY26 from 32.75% in Q3 FY25. On a nine-month basis, the company reported an 81.18% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 2,261.35 crore in 9M FY26, compared with Rs 1,248.09 crore in 9M FY25. Revenue from operations surged 100.66% YoY to Rs 11,092.95 crore during the period. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the incorporation of a wholly owned subsidiary in Maharashtra, with an estimated aggregate capital outlay of over Rs 252 crore, to be invested in tranches. The subsidiary is envisioned as a mission-driven institutional platform focused on structured skilling, leadership, entrepreneurship, and employment-linked programs aligned with regional development objectives and global workforce standards. In furtherance of its earlier disclosures dated 25 April 2023 and 22 January 2024, the board also approved the development of a second slurry pipeline project, to be implemented in phases along with the requisite financing arrangements. The proposed pipeline route will run from Hedri–Konsari–Chandrapur–Jalna–Maharashtra Port, with Phase I covering Hedri to Chandrapur and Phase II extending to Maharashtra Port. The project aims to enable reliable and cost-efficient delivery of iron ore to multiple steel hubs. Additionally, the board approved the designation of Ashit Patni, Chief Marketing Officer, as Senior Managerial Personnel (SMP) of the company, effective 3 February 2026, based on the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee. The board further approved a proposal for Lloyds Global Resources FZCO (LGRF), a wholly owned subsidiary, to acquire up to a 95% equity stake in Lloyds Asia Resources Pte., Singapore, for an aggregate consideration of up to $5 million, to be invested in one or more tranches. The entity will serve as a regional investment and operating platform for mining and mineral investments in Papua New Guinea and other Asian jurisdictions. Separately, the board approved proposals for LGRF to acquire a 100% equity stake in TP Phoenix (Pty), a South Africa-based company, and to hold a 100% equity stake in a newly incorporated entity, Lloyds Global Resources South Africa. These entities will serve as strategic investment and operating platforms for the Lloyds Group’s African operations. Each acquisition will involve an aggregate consideration of up to $1 million, to be invested in tranches. In line with earlier intimations dated 25 April 2023 and 8 December 2023, the board approved the capacity expansion of Pellet Plant–1 and Pellet Plant–2 at Konsari from 4 MTPA each to 5 MTPA each, through debottlenecking and process optimisation. The expansion aligns with the company’s strategy to strengthen its presence across the steel-making value chain, enables efficient utilisation of iron ore reserves, and facilitates value addition through forward integration with existing sponge iron facilities. It is also expected to support the company’s long-term growth objectives while contributing to improved margins and enhanced profitability. Lloyds Metals and Energy (LMEL) is the leading player in the iron and steel-making industry.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsMetals_76757705405_2629.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Century Plyboards drops after Q3 PAT slides 8% QoQ to Rs 65 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/century-plyboards-drops-after-q3-pat-slides-8-qoq-to-rs-65-cr/1671469</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671469</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit and revenue rose 10.55%, while total income increased 18.29% in Q3 FY26.

On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit and revenue rose 10.55%, while total income increased 18.29% in Q3 FY26. The company reported profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 92.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 79.93 crore a year ago. The quarter included exceptional items of Rs 7.61 crore, attributable to a one-time increase in employee benefit provisions following the implementation of the new Labour Codes effective 21 November 2025. On the segmental front, revenue from plywood and allied products stood at Rs 710.19 crore (up 14.9% YoY), medium-density fiberboard was Rs 325.82 (up 19.09% YoY), laminate and allied products was at Rs 182.99 crore (up 9.62% YoY), particle board stood at Rs 65.36 crore (up 83.44% YoY), and container freight station services was at Rs 42.12 crore (up 35.83% YoY) during the period under review. During the quarter, total expenses increased 18.49% YoY to Rs 1,259.40 crore. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 672.78 crore (up 9.73% YoY), employee benefits expense was Rs 207.80 crore (up 17.57% YoY), and finance costs stood at Rs 31.25 crore (up 74.58% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the company plans to set up a new plywood and MDF manufacturing unit in Uttar Pradesh, with the board considering the proposal on 4 February 2026, to tap rising demand and raw material availability. The project will expand plywood capacity by 90,000 CBM per year in phases from an existing 400,800 CBM (93% utilization) and add 330,000 CBM per year to MDF capacity from 561,000 CBM (85% utilization). Century Plyboards (India) is a manufacturer and distributor of building products. Its portfolio of products comprises plywood, blockboard, decorative veneer and timber, particle boards, flush doors, medium-density fiberboards (MDF), decorative laminates, pre-laminated boards, and fiber cement boards.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CenturyPly_30255229715_15783.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Finserv Q3 PAT inches up YoY to Rs 2,229 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-finserv-q3-pat-inches-up-yoy-to-rs-2229-cr/1671468</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671468</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[During the quarter, the company and its subsidiaries accounted for one-time charge of Rs 379 crore towards new labour codes released on 21 November 2025.

During the quarter, the company and its subsidiaries accounted for one-time charge of Rs 379 crore towards new labour codes released on 21 November 2025. Net impact on consolidated profit of BFS is Rs 540 crore for accelerated ECL provision and Rs 167 crore for new labour codes. Profit after tax, before accelerated ECL provision, one-time charge of New Labour Code and jumped 32% YoY to Rs 2,229 crore during the quarter. Bajaj Finserv is the holding company for the various financial services businesses under the Bajaj group. It participates in the financing business through its 51.32% holding in Bajaj Finance Limited (BFL) and in the life, general and health insurance businesses through its 74% holding in two unlisted subsidiaries, Bajaj General Insurance (Bajaj General) and Bajaj Life Insurance (Bajaj Life). BFL holds 86.70% stake in Bajaj Housing Finance (BHFL). Bajaj Finance profit after tax for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 3,978 crore, down 6% YoY. Loan losses and provisions in Q3 FY26 was Rs 3,625 crore during the quarter Loan losses and provisions before the accelerated ECL provision of Rs 1,406 crore was Rs 2,219 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,043 crore in Q3 FY25, an increase of 9%. Assets Under Management (AUM) as on 31 December 2025 were Rs 484,477 crore compared with Rs 398,043 crore as on 31 December 2024, registering the growth of 22%. Gross non-performing assets (GNNPA) and Net NPA (NNPA) as on 31st December 2025 stood at 1.21% and 0.47% respectively as against 1.12% and 0.48% as on 31st December 2024. Provisioning coverage ratio on stage 3 assets was 61%. Capital adequacy ratio (CRAR) (including Tier-II capital) as on 31st December 2025 stood at 21.45%. The Tier-I capital was at 20.60%. Bajaj Finserv is the holding company for the various financial services businesses under the Bajaj group. It serves millions of customers by providing solutions for asset acquisition through financing, asset protection through general insurance, family and income protection in the form of life and health insurance, and retirement and savings solutions. The counter rose 0.44% to Rs 2021.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajFinservLtd_81833438_28075.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>