<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen rebounds as Takaichi victory sparks fiscal stimulus optimism]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-rebounds-as-takaichi-victory-sparks-fiscal-stimulus-optimism/1673959</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673959</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen rebounded sharply in Asian trading on Monday, climbing 0.5% to 156.43 per dollar after hitting two-week lows.

The Japanese yen rebounded sharply in Asian trading on Monday, climbing 0.5% to 156.43 per dollar after hitting two-week lows. The move came following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s decisive victory in Sunday’s snap election, giving her a strong mandate to pursue expansionary fiscal policies.re betting that increased fiscal stimulus, including potential tax cuts, could support the stock market, even as concerns over Japan’s rising debt persist. The election outcome also adds pressure on Japanese government bonds, with markets weighing the impact of looser fiscal policy on the broader financial landscape.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Somi Conveyor Beltings Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/somi-conveyor-beltings-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1673958</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673958</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jay Bharat Maruti Ltd, Tainwala Chemicals & Plastics (India) Ltd, Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd and Vaibhav Global Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 February 2026.

Jay Bharat Maruti Ltd, Tainwala Chemicals & Plastics (India) Ltd, Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd and Vaibhav Global Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 February 2026. Somi Conveyor Beltings Ltd spiked 19.99% to Rs 120.16 at 11:38 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 9332 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3204 shares in the past one month. Jay Bharat Maruti Ltd soared 19.99% to Rs 100.9. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 2.67 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14156 shares in the past one month. Tainwala Chemicals & Plastics (India) Ltd surged 18.41% to Rs 201.6. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 2149 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 767 shares in the past one month. Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd rose 15.52% to Rs 20.91. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 34.89 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11.56 lakh shares in the past one month. Vaibhav Global Ltd gained 15.32% to Rs 261.95. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.29 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 48969 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SomiConvBelt_32874889803_28239.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashiana Housing gains on strong booking conversions at Gurugram project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashiana-housing-gains-on-strong-booking-conversions-at-gurugram-project/1673957</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673957</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said it has converted 242 expressions of interest into bookings at its "Ashiana Aaroham" Phase 1 and Phase 2 project, covering around 5.03 lakh sq ft with an estimated sale value of Rs 767.23 crore.

The company said it has converted 242 expressions of interest into bookings at its "Ashiana Aaroham" Phase 1 and Phase 2 project, covering around 5.03 lakh sq ft with an estimated sale value of Rs 767.23 crore. Invitations for EOIs began on 7 December 2025, while the conversion into bookings started on 7 February 2026, and is currently ongoing. "Ashiana Aaroham" is a kid-centric housing project in Gurugram, Haryana, comprising 364 units of 3 BHK and 4 BHK apartments. Following these conversions, the company said the total value of area booked during the current financial year has crossed Rs 2,000 crore. Ashiana Housing is a real estate developers, mostly working in the field of development of residential group housing projects. The company's board will consider Q3 results on on 10 February 2026. On a consolidated basis, the company reported net profit of Rs 27.54 crore in Q2 September 2025 as against net loss of Rs 7.55 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales soared 204.67% YoY to Rs 165.77 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshianaHousing_80521790060_2769.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ganesha-ecosphere-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1673954</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673954</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Goldiam International Ltd, Shipping Corporation of India Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd and Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 February 2026.

Goldiam International Ltd, Shipping Corporation of India Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd and Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 February 2026. Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd spiked 14.65% to Rs 785 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 38521 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2968 shares in the past one month. Goldiam International Ltd surged 13.86% to Rs 415.55. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.85 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 55231 shares in the past one month. Shipping Corporation of India Ltd soared 12.92% to Rs 250.35. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 20.56 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.89 lakh shares in the past one month. Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd advanced 11.28% to Rs 422.65. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 24.83 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5.95 lakh shares in the past one month. Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd added 10.34% to Rs 386.85. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 6.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8178 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GaneshaEcosphe_40248392277_2278.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hi-Tech Pipes gains after Sikandrabad units commences commercial production]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hi-tech-pipes-gains-after-sikandrabad-units-commences-commercial-production/1673953</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673953</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Sikandrabad facility hosts a production capacity of 0.12 million tons.

The Sikandrabad facility hosts a production capacity of 0.12 million tons. It would specialise in the production on ERW pipes and hollow sections. With the commencement of commercial production at Sikandrabad, and supported by recently commissioned capacities at other locations, the company has raised its total installed annual capacity to 1.05 million tons. Ajay Kumar Bansal, chairman and managing director, Hi-Tech Pipes, said: “With this commissioning, we have reached the important milestone of 1 million ton of installed capacity, reflecting our disciplined execution and long-term strategic vision. As we move ahead, we are actively gearing up for the next phase of expansion, targeting an additional 1 million tons of capacity.” Hi-Tech Pipes had announced its earnings for the December quarter on Saturday (07 February 2026). The company has reported 14.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.38 crore despite a 24.6% increase in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,069.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 1,046.63 crore, up 25.7% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 23.20 crore, down by 14.3% from Rs 27.06 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Hi-Tech Pipes is one of the leading steel tubes and pipes manufacturers in India. It provides innovative products for nearly four decades with a strong presence in steel pipes, hollow sections, tubes, cold rolled coils & strips, road crash barriers, solar mounting structures, GP/GC Sheets, color coated coils and a variety of other galvanised products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HiTechPipes_75760192686_23653.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade higher; media shares surge]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-higher-media-shares-surge/1673952</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673952</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks continued to trade with significant gains in the early afternoon trade as investors sentiment remained optimistic following the recently signed India- US trade deal agreement and positive global cues.

The domestic equity benchmarks continued to trade with significant gains in the early afternoon trade as investors sentiment remained optimistic following the recently signed India- US trade deal agreement and positive global cues. Market participants will track earnings reports, schedule to announce later today. Nifty scaled above 25,850 mark and Sensex crossed 84,050 mark. Media shares jumped after declining in the past two trading sessions. At 11:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 499.51 points or 0.60% to 84,079.91. The Nifty 50 index added 170.65 points or 0.66% to 25,863.05. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 1.22% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.01%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,948 shares rose and 1,083 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Fractal Analytics received bids for 7,31,600 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.04 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. Aye Finance received bids for 10,91,096 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.02 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index rallied 3.43% to 1,438.45. The index rose 0.26% in the previous two consecutive trading sessions. Prime Focus (up 9.21%), Saregama India (up 6.85%), Network 18 Media & Investments (up 5.06%), Sun TV Network (up 3.97%) and Hathway Cable & Datacom (up 3.3%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 3.23%), Nazara Technologies (up 2.61%), Tips Music (up 2.23%), PVR Inox (up 2.07%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: JK Tyre & Industries rallied 6.39% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 294.96% to Rs 207.75 crore on a 14.95% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 4,222.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sterlite Technologies rallied 5.36% after the company announced key decisions taken at its board meeting, including a sizeable promoter-led capital raise. The board approved the issuance of up to 45.3 crore convertible warrants to promoter Twin Star Overseas on a preferential basis at Rs 110 per warrant, aggregating Rs 498.3 crore. Each warrant is convertible into one equity share within 18 months from the date of allotment. As on December 2025, total promoter shareholding in the company stood at 44.44%. Global Markets: Asian markets advanced on Monday, led by a surge in Japanese stocks following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s historic landslide election victory. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party captured a two-thirds supermajority in the 465-seat lower house, public broadcaster NHK reported. A decisive win for Takaichi could be the “best outcome” for markets over the medium term, as strategic investments and tax reform bolster equities, said Sree Kochugovindan, media report said. Japanese stocks have hit several highs over the past few months, driven by the so-called 'Takaichi trade' as markets expect the prime minister’s economic policies — seen as growth‑focused continuation of Abenomics — to boost equities, while weakening the yen as she pushes for a looser monetary policy and higher government spending. U.S. President Donald Trump congratulated Takaichi on her victory in a TruthSocial post. Last Friday in the U.S., stocks surged as tech names recovered following several days of heavy selling in the sector and bitcoin rebounded following a rout that took the popular cryptocurrency down more than 50% from its high in October last year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 1,206.95 points, or 2.47%, closing at 50,115.67. Friday marked the first time the Dow exceeded the 50,000 level. The S&P 500 jumped 1.97% and ended at 6,932.30, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 2.18% to 23,031.21. With those moves, the S&P 500 climbed back into the green for 2026. Even with Friday’s rise, the S&P 500 posted a 0.1% decline for the week, while the Nasdaq fell 1.8% on the week. The 30-stock Dow rose 2.5% week to date, benefiting from some rotation into some economically cyclical stocks even as the overall market was weighed down by tech selling.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ganesha Ecosphere jumps after sharp QoQ turnaround in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ganesha-ecosphere-jumps-after-sharp-qoq-turnaround-in-q3-fy26/1673950</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673950</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a sequential basis, Ganesha Ecosphere returned to profitability in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit at Rs 4.75 crore compared with a loss of Rs 0.50 crore in Q2 FY26.

On a sequential basis, Ganesha Ecosphere returned to profitability in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit at Rs 4.75 crore compared with a loss of Rs 0.50 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations eased 1.7% QoQ to Rs 357.22 crore. Profit before tax soared to Rs 8.16 crore from Rs 0.59 crore in the previous quarter, while EBITDA rose 37.7% QoQ to Rs 30.7 crore. EBITDA margin stood at 8.6% in Q3 FY26 as against 6.1% in Q2FY26 and 14.2% in Q3FY25. On a year-on-year basis, consolidated net profit declined 84% YoY from Rs 29.71 crore in Q3 FY25, while revenue from operations fell 10.2% YoY from Rs 397.80 crore. Profit before tax dropped 77.9% YoY from Rs 36.92 crore in the year-ago quarter, and EBITDA declined 45.7% YoY to Rs 30.7 crore from Rs 56.5 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, cost of materials consumed declined 10% QoQ to Rs 215.96 crore, while on a year-on-year basis it was down 8%. Employee benefit expenses rose 8.77% QoQ to Rs 25.67 crore and increased 12.39% YoY. Ganesha Ecosphere is a leading PET waste recycling company in India and is mainly engaged in the manufacturing of Recycled Polyester Staple Fibre (RPSF), Spun Yarn and Dyed Texturised Yarn.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GaneshaEcosphe_40248392277_2278.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shipping Corp climbs after Q3 PAT surges 436% YoY to Rs 405 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shipping-corp-climbs-after-q3-pat-surges-436-yoy-to-rs-405-cr/1673949</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673949</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations increased 22.5% year-on-year to Rs 1,611.67 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations increased 22.5% year-on-year to Rs 1,611.67 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 426.93 crore in Q3 FY26, up 409.89%, compared to Rs 83.73 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Total expenses declined 1.88% year on year to Rs 1,253.28 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of service rendered stood at Rs 728.80 crore (down 3.99% YoY), employee benefit expense was at Rs 154.15 crore (down 5.43% YoY), and finance cost stood at Rs 48.39 crore (down 24.3% YoY) during the period under review. On the segmental front, revenue from liners stood at Rs 205.81 crore (down 26.78% YoY), revenue from bulk carriers stood at Rs 237.51 crore (up 61.73% YoY), revenue from tankers stood at Rs 1,096.91 crore (up 34.25% YoY), and revenue from technical & offshore stood at Rs 79.36 crore (up 24.56% YoY) during the quarter. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved a second interim dividend of Rs 3.5 per equity share (35%) for FY26 and fixed 17 February 2026 as the record date. The dividend will be paid within 30 days of declaration. Shipping Corporation of India is engaged in the business of transporting goods and passengers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SCI_79641479387_2347.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kalyan Jewellers rallies after Q3 PAT jumps 90% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kalyan-jewellers-rallies-after-q3-pat-jumps-90-yoy/1673947</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673947</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 601.4 crore, up 104.83% as against Rs 293.6 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 601.4 crore, up 104.83% as against Rs 293.6 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) rose 74.53% year-on-year to Rs 750.5 crore in Q3 FY26. The EBITDA margin also improved, reaching 7.3% compared to 5.9% in the same period last year. The company’s consolidated revenue climbed approximately 42% YoY, driven by robust festive demand, strong same-store sales growth (SSSG), and sharp traction in its digital platform, Candere. The company’s India operations witnessed revenue growth of approximately 42% during Q3 FY26 as compared to Q3 FY25, driven primarily by strong festive demand. Demand after Diwali remained resilient despite volatility in gold prices, with growth broad-based across both plain gold and studded jewellery segments. The quarter recorded healthy same-store-sales-growth of approximately 27%. International operations recorded revenue growth of approximately 36% YoY during the quarter. In the Middle East, revenue rose approximately 28% in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25, largely driven by strong same-store sales growth. International markets contributed approximately 11% to the company’s consolidated revenue during the quarter. The company’s digital-first jewellery platform, Candere, recorded a revenue growth of approximately 147% during the quarter as compared to the same period during the last year. During the quarter, the company launched 21 Kalyan showroom. Kalyan Jewellers India is a leading international retail jewellery chain, into the manufacture and retailing of primarily gold and precious stone studded jewelleries.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KalyanJewellersIndia_46056464.1248805_42402.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at EID Parry (India) Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-eid-parry-india-ltd-counter/1673944</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673944</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[AU Small Finance Bank Ltd, Blue Star Ltd, City Union Bank Ltd, SRF Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 09 February 2026.

AU Small Finance Bank Ltd, Blue Star Ltd, City Union Bank Ltd, SRF Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 09 February 2026. EID Parry (India) Ltd recorded volume of 1.55 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 18.31 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 8441 shares. The stock gained 2.88% to Rs.906.15. Volumes stood at 4413 shares in the last session. AU Small Finance Bank Ltd registered volume of 9.47 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 12.41 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 76267 shares. The stock rose 0.45% to Rs.995.15. Volumes stood at 22647 shares in the last session. Blue Star Ltd clocked volume of 1.7 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.13 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 33156 shares. The stock gained 2.36% to Rs.1,925.85. Volumes stood at 6209 shares in the last session. City Union Bank Ltd clocked volume of 8.03 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 4.58 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.75 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.48% to Rs.291.60. Volumes stood at 57698 shares in the last session. SRF Ltd saw volume of 55262 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 4.52 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 12231 shares. The stock increased 1.76% to Rs.2,954.00. Volumes stood at 908 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EIDParry_79775166468_148.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index speculators further reduce net short position]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-speculators-further-reduce-net-short-position/1673943</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673943</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index speculators further reduced net short position, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

US dollar index speculators further reduced net short position, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of US dollar index futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 852 contracts in the data reported through February 03, 2026, showing a decrease of 3553 net short positions compared to the previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-726884__340_forex.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI to replace flat-rate deposit insurance premium with a risk-based framework ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-to-replace-flat-rate-deposit-insurance-premium-with-a-risk-based-framework/1673933</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673933</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has said it will replace the flat-rate deposit insurance premium with a risk-based framework from April this year.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has said it will replace the flat-rate deposit insurance premium with a risk-based framework from April this year. RBI announced that the framework, which replaces the flat-rate premium system in place since 1962, will be reviewed at least once every three years. Currently, banks pay a uniform premium of 12 paise per Rs 100 of assessable deposits. Under the new framework, banks will be classified into four risk categories—A, B, C and D— with category A representing the lowest risk. Premium rates will range from 8 paise to 12 paise per Rs 100 of assessable deposits, offering a discount of up to 33.3% to the strongest banks. RBI noted that the risk categorisation will be based on the latest available audited financial year-end data and supervisory ratings. Banks will be required to pay the insurance premium in advance for the first half of FY27 by May 31, based on assessable deposits as of March 31.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/euro-seem-money-finance_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,800 level; PSU Bank shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25800-level-psu-bank-shares-rally/1673924</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673924</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the morning trade as investors sentiment remained optimistic following the recently signed India- US trade deal agreement.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the morning trade as investors sentiment remained optimistic following the recently signed India- US trade deal agreement. market participants will track earnings reports, schedule to announced later today. Nifty traded above 25,800 level. PSU Bank shares jumped after declining in the past trading session. At 10:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 346.07 points or 0.41% to 83,934.31. The Nifty 50 index added 120.90 points or 0.47% to 25,813.70. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 1.05% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 1.54%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,785 shares rose and 1,054 shares fell. A total of 220 shares were unchanged. Earnings to Watch: Zydus Lifesciences(up 0.93%), Aurobindo Pharma(down 0.39%), All Time Plastics(up 3.30%), Amber Enterprises India(up 3.19%), Bajaj Electricals(up 2.95%), Bata India(up 2.33%), Enviro Infra Engineers(up 5.08%), PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery(up 2.92%), GlaxoSmithKline Pharmaceuticals(up 1.33%), Happiest Minds Technologies(up 2.04%), Navin Fluorine International(up 2.02%), P N Gadgil Jewellers(up 4.76%), The Ramco Cements(up 2.44%), Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company(up 2.12%), Trident(up 3.18%), and Vadilal Industries (up 0.87%)will release quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index jumped 3.23% to 9,162.80. The index declined 0.51% in past trading session. State Bank of India (up 5.48%), Bank of India (up 3.31%), Indian Bank (up 3.01%), UCO Bank (up 1.86%) and Central Bank of India (up 1.81%) Union Bank of India (up 1.67%), Punjab & Sind Bank (up 1.59%), Bank of Baroda (up 1.23%), Canara Bank (up 1.21%) and Indian Overseas Bank (up 1.18%) advanced. Stock in Spotlight: Atul Auto surged 10.04% after the company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 98.06% to Rs 15.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7.75 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JK Tyre Inds jumps after Q3 PAT climbs 295% YoY to Rs 208 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jk-tyre-inds-jumps-after-q3-pat-climbs-295-yoy-to-rs-208-cr/1673912</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673912</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company reported profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 358.10 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 97.94 crore recorded in the same period a year ago.

The company reported profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 358.10 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 97.94 crore recorded in the same period a year ago. The firm reported exceptional loss items of Rs 104.02 crore during the quarter. Consolidated EBITDA stood at Rs 583 crore in Q3 FY26, up 74.03% YoY. EBITDA margin stood at 13.8% during the period under review. The company said domestic business recorded healthy double-digit growth of 16% YoY, driven by a 12% rise in the replacement segment and a strong 27% growth in the OEM segment. Exports remained resilient despite geopolitical uncertainties impacting global markets. Raghupati Singhania, chairman & managing director (CMD), said that "JK Tyre delivered a robust performance in Q3, on the back of healthy automobile demand supported by GST-led reforms, festive season momentum, and positive rural sentiments. Strong traction across both OEM and replacement segments once again underscores customers’ enduring trust in the JK Tyre brand. During the quarter, the company successfully completed the merger of Cavendish Industries (CIL) with JK Tyre, following the receipt of all statutory approvals. Acquired in 2016 from Kesoram Industries, CIL has undergone a remarkable transformation under JK Tyre’s leadership. Through sustained technical, financial, and managerial support, capacity utilization was scaled from around 30% to over 95%, making this JK Tyre’s yet another successful turnaround, after Vikrant Tyres and JK Tornel, Mexico. JK Tyre’s international subsidiary, JK Tornel (Mexico), also delivered a significant improvement in financial performance during the quarter, further strengthening the company’s consolidated results. We enter Q4 with strong confidence, supported by healthy demand across segments and favorable macro tailwinds such as positive consumer sentiment and lower interest rates. We remain optimistic that this momentum will extend into FY27.” JK Tyre & Industries develops, manufactures, markets, and distributes automotive tires, tubes, flaps, and retreads. The company sells its tires to vehicle manufacturers for fitment in original equipment and in replacement markets worldwide.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JKTyreIndust_68453937147_304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s fisheries sector progressing toward financial formalization]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-fisheries-sector-progressing-toward-financial-formalization/1673911</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673911</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian fisheries sector is recognized as the “Sunrise Sector” has evolved from a primarily subsistence-driven activity into a dynamic engine of economic growth, government noted in a latest update.

The Indian fisheries sector is recognized as the “Sunrise Sector” has evolved from a primarily subsistence-driven activity into a dynamic engine of economic growth, government noted in a latest update. With a contribution of 1.12% to India’s Gross Value Added (GVA), the sector plays a pivotal role in delivering nutritional security, providing affordable protein, and sustaining the livelihoods of nearly 30 million people. India today stands as the world’s second largest fish producer and largest aquaculture producer, accounting for approximately 8% of global fish production. Over the past decade, the sector has achieved remarkable expansion fish production reached an all-time high of 197 lakh tonnes in FY 2024–25, nearly doubling from 95.79 lakh tonnes in 2013–14. This growth has been structurally reshaped by the rising dominance of inland fisheries, contributing over 75% of total production. The sector’s gradual transition from capture-based fisheries to culture-based aquaculture has further strengthened production stability. In FY 2024–25, exports touched Rs 62,408 crore (USD 7.45 billion), with frozen shrimp as the major commodity and the United States and China as key markets. The sector contributes 7.26% to agricultural GVA. The government has set an ambitious target to increase national fish production to 220 lakh tonnes by FY 2025-26. The journey of credit flow to the sector has been digitized with real time tracking of loan request. All the 12 nationalized banks have been on boarded on the NFDP for easy and direct loan request to banks. The nationalized banks have been very supportive of the scheme and doing fabulous job in processing the loan requests. With strengthened digital financing rails, de-risked lending instruments, and customized institutional partnerships now in place, India’s fisheries sector is progressing toward financial formalization and sustainable expansion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/fish-2-1373013_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sterlite Tech jumps after board clears promoter warrant issue]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sterlite-tech-jumps-after-board-clears-promoter-warrant-issue/1673889</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673889</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The board approved the issuance of up to 45.3 crore convertible warrants to promoter Twin Star Overseas on a preferential basis at Rs 110 per warrant, aggregating Rs 498.3 crore.

The board approved the issuance of up to 45.3 crore convertible warrants to promoter Twin Star Overseas on a preferential basis at Rs 110 per warrant, aggregating Rs 498.3 crore. Each warrant is convertible into one equity share within 18 months from the date of allotment. On a fully diluted basis, Twin Star Overseas’ shareholding is expected to increase to 47.75% from 42.9%, subject to full conversion of the warrants and shareholder approval. As on December 2025, total promoter shareholding in the company stood at 44.44%. Separately, the board also approved amendments to the Articles of Association to enable the issuance of convertible and non convertible securities. To seek shareholder approval for these proposals, the company has scheduled an extraordinary general meeting on 4 March 2026. The stock gained as investors reacted positively to the planned capital infusion and promoter participation. Sterlite Technologies is a global leader in advanced connectivity solutions, providing end-to-end solutions for building AI-ready infrastructure, FTTx, rural, enterprise and data centre networks. data centre & cloud companies, telecom operators, internet service providers and large enterprises collaborate with the company to build their future-ready digital infrastructure. On a consolidated basis, Sterlite Technologies reported net loss of Rs 17 crore in Q3 December 2025 as against net loss of Rs 24 crore in Q3 December 2024. Net sales rose 25.95% YoY to Rs 1257 crore in Q3 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SterliteTech_57490273283_21331.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KRN Heat Exchanger surges after PAT increases over 65% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/krn-heat-exchanger-surges-after-pat-increases-over-65-yoy-in-q3/1673890</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673890</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 129.61 crore, up 33.32% YoY.

Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 129.61 crore, up 33.32% YoY. While EBITDA improved by 96.54% to Rs 31.08 crore, EBITDA margin expanded by 610 basis points to 20.28% in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 25.87 crore, up by 35.19% from Rs 19.13 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Santosh Kumar, chairman & managing director of KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration, said: “During the quarter and across the nine-month period, we have seen steady progress in our core business, driven by consistent execution and improving order visibility. Demand from both domestic and export customers has remained healthy, and our teams have responded well by maintaining delivery timelines and quality standards. Over the past nine months, our focus has been on building depth—stronger customer relationships, higher value products, and tighter control over operations. This has helped us grow in a balanced manner while improving the overall quality of earnings. With a stable order pipeline, expanding export engagements, and continued emphasis on operational efficiency, we believe the business is well positioned to grow steadily and strengthen its revenue base in the coming periods.” KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration specializes in manufacturing aluminium and copper fin and tube heat exchangers, including water coils, condenser coils, and evaporator coils. Their products are widely used by OEMs in the HVAC&R industry for heating, ventilation, air conditioning, and refrigeration applications.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KRNHeatExchangerandRefrigerationLtd_36100110_92755.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SMS Pharma edges higher after Q3 PAT rises nearly 29% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sms-pharma-edges-higher-after-q3-pat-rises-nearly-29-yoy/1673888</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673888</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 166.80 crore, up 19.0% YoY.

Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 166.80 crore, up 19.0% YoY. PBIDT improved by 34.1% to Rs 47.40 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 35.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 31.16 crore, up by 38.9% from Rs 22.44 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. SMS Pharmaceuticals is a diversified and integrated pharmaceutical company specializing in APIs and intermediates for global customers. The company operates two state-of-the-art manufacturing facilities in Hyderabad and Vizag.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SMSPharma_56135329409_25807.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ram Ratna Wires climbs after Q3 PAT surges 73% YoY to Rs 31 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ram-ratna-wires-climbs-after-q3-pat-surges-73-yoy-to-rs-31-cr/1673873</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673873</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 97.87% YoY to Rs 47.45 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 97.87% YoY to Rs 47.45 crore during the quarter. The company reported exceptional loss of Rs 3.56 crore in Q3 FY26, related to labour code compliance. EBITDA stood at Rs 72 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 84.9% compared with Rs 39 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 5.6% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.4% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter 92% of revenue contributed from domestic region while 8% revenue came from exports. Mahendrakumar Kabra, MD said, “We are delighted to report yet another quarter of exceptional performance, led by rising demandfor copper tubes driven by the growth in the HVAC industry. This segment has seen its contributionto revenues increase from 17% last year to 27% this quarter, driving profitability and underscoringour focus on expanding domestic capacity and reducing import reliance. To further strengthen thissegment, Inner Grooved Tube (IGT) manufacturing is currently in progress and at the evaluation stage. At the same time, copper winding wires continue to benefit from India’s electrification push andthe rapid expansion of power transmission and distribution infrastructure, resulting in robustgrowth across our portfolio. Our consolidated revenue for this quarter grew by 43.8% year-on-year,with Operating EBITDA rising 84.9% and Profit After Tax improving 72.5%, reflecting operationalexcellence and disciplined execution. Looking ahead, strong demand momentum supported by industry tailwinds and capacity additionswill continue to drive growth. In addition, developments in our joint venture and subsidiary areadvancing well and will further enhance our growth trajectory. We remain committed to deliveringsustainable value for all our stakeholders.” Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the change in designation of Rajeev Maheshwari from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) of the company to senior vice president (Accounts & Taxation) with effect from April 01, 2026, consequent to this change Maheshwari will cease to be the CFO of the Company from the closure of business hours on March 31, 2026. Additionally, the board approved the appointment of Iqbal Singh Saggu, as senior vice president (Finance) and CFO with effect from April 01, 2026. Iqbal Singh Saggu is a qualified chartered accountant with over 23 years of experience in handling treasury department, plant & finance operations, strategic planning, capital structuring, and regulatory compliance with expertise in driving profitability and optimizing capital. Ram Ratna Wires (RRWL) is a prominent part of RR Global, a leading conglomerate in the electrical and copper industry. The company manufactures super enameled copper winding wires in India that offers a wide range of sizes under its brand, RR Shramik.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RamRatnaWires_52194664867_4453.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pace Digitek Q3 PAT jumps 8% YoY to Rs 76 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pace-digitek-q3-pat-jumps-8-yoy-to-rs-76-cr/1673872</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673872</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 16.8% YoY to Rs 114.25 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 16.8% YoY to Rs 114.25 crore in Q3 FY26. Total expenses rose 15.01% to Rs 539.90 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 469.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 91.98 crore (down 20.8% YoY), engineering, procurement, and construction project expenses stood at Rs 201.23 (down 22.25% YoY), finance cost was at Rs 9.27 crore (down 58.34% YoY), while employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 24.91 crore (up 44.49% YoY) during the period under review. Pace Digitek (PDL) is a telecom infrastructure solutions provider offering manufacturing, installation, commissioning, and operation & maintenance (O&M) services for telecom towers and optical fiber networks. Shares of Pace Digitek shed 0.70% to Rs 190.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PACEDIGITEKLIMITED_26475505_94643.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>