<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Titagarh Rail Systems Q3 PAT drops 23% YoY to Rs 48 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/titagarh-rail-systems-q3-pat-drops-23-yoy-to-rs-48-cr/1677290</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677290</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax from continuing operations stood at Rs 65.15 crore in Q3 FY26, down 26.40% year on year. Total expenses fell 7.13% to Rs 770.34 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. During the quarter, cost of raw materials & components consumed stood at Rs 643.33 crore, down 7.83% YoY, while employee benefits expense was at Rs 30.61 crore, up 40.41% YoY. On segmental front, revenue from freight rail systems stood at Rs 665.70 crore (down 21.93% YoY) and revenue from passenger rail systems stood at Rs 166.36 crore (up 236.82% YoY), during the quarter. Titagarh Rail Systems is mainly engaged in the manufacturing and selling of Freight Wagons, Passenger Coaches, Metro Trains, Train Electricals, Steel Castings, Specialised Equipments & Bridges, Ships, etc. The Company caters to both domestic and export market. Shares of Titagarh Rail Systems slipped 1.65% to end at Rs 765.05 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TitagarhWagons_2675196128_19939.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ola Electric Q3 revenue drops 55% YoY; net loss narrows to Rs 487 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ola-electric-q3-revenue-drops-55-yoy-net-loss-narrows-to-rs-487-crore/1677281</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677281</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Deliveries stood at 32,680 units in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% YoY from 84,029 units and down 37.9% QoQ from 52,666 units.

Deliveries stood at 32,680 units in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% YoY from 84,029 units and down 37.9% QoQ from 52,666 units. Premium deliveries fell 79.3% YoY to 6,065 units and declined 54.8% QoQ. Mass segment deliveries dropped 51.4% YoY and 32.2% QoQ to 26,612 units. However, cells produced rose sharply to 72,418 units, up 90.2% QoQ from 38,080 units. On a consolidated basis, revenue from operations stood at Rs 470 crore, declining 55.0% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and 31.9% QoQ from Rs 690 crore. Automotive and cell sales dropped 53.1% YoY and 35.5% QoQ to Rs 433 crore. Production-linked incentive income declined 69.4% YoY, though increased 94.7% QoQ to Rs 37 crore. Gross profit came in at Rs 161 crore, down 17.0% YoY and 24.4% QoQ. However, gross margin improved to 34.3%, compared with 30.9% in Q2 FY26 and 18.6% in Q3 FY25. Total operating expenses stood at Rs 432 crore, down 33.9% YoY, but up 3.8% QoQ. R&D expenses rose 124.1% YoY and 8.3% QoQ to Rs 65 crore. SG&A expenses declined 38.1% YoY and 4.4% QoQ, while other operating expenses fell 42.2% YoY but increased 5.6% QoQ. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss stood at Rs 323 crore, widening from Rs 258 crore in Q2 FY26 but improving from Rs 494 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA margin was -68.7%, compared with -37.4% in Q2 FY26 and -47.3% a year ago. Net loss for the quarter stood at Rs 487 crore, widening from Rs 418 crore in Q2 FY26 but narrowing compared with Rs 564 crore in Q3 FY25. Cash flow from operations remained negative at Rs 575 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a negative Rs 255 crore in Q2 FY26 and negative Rs 851 crore in Q3 FY25. Free cash flow stood at negative Rs 781 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with negative Rs 405 crore in Q2 FY26 and negative Rs 1,076 crore in Q3 FY25. In the automotive segment, revenue from operations stood at Rs 467 crore, down 55.3% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and lower by 32.1% QoQ from Rs 688 crore. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss stood at Rs 167 crore, improving significantly from a loss of Rs 373 crore in Q3 FY25 but widening from a loss of Rs 102 crore in Q2 FY26. Adjusted EBITDA margin was -35.8%, broadly in line with -35.7% YoY, but weaker than -14.8% in Q2 FY26. In the cell segment, revenue from operations stood at Rs 9 crore, up from Rs 3 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 4 crore in Q2 FY26, reflecting scaling up of cell operations. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss widened to Rs 39 crore, compared with losses of Rs 8 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 27 crore in Q2 FY26. Adjusted EBITDA margin deteriorated sharply to -228.5%, versus -29.6% YoY and -100.0% QoQ. Ola Electric spokesperson said, "Q3 FY26 marks a structural reset for Ola Electric. We chose to fix the fundamentals by restoring service execution, resetting our cost structure, and deepening vertical integration. The result is a leaner operating model with materially lower breakeven and industry-leading gross margins. With service metrics stabilising and our Gigafactory transitioning into commercial scale deployment, we are positioned to enter the next phase of growth with significantly improved operating leverage." Ola Electric Mobility is India's leading electric vehicle (EV) manufacturer. It specialises in the vertical integration of technology and manufacturing for EVs and their components, including battery cells.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlaElectricMobilityLtd_81720871_75559.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crisil Q4 PAT rises 7.5% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crisil-q4-pat-rises-75-yoy/1677252</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677252</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, the company's income from operations for Q4 2025 was up 18.5% to Rs 1,081.6 crore, compared with Rs 912.9 crore in Q4 2024.

On a consolidated basis, the company's income from operations for Q4 2025 was up 18.5% to Rs 1,081.6 crore, compared with Rs 912.9 crore in Q4 2024. Profit before tax for Q4 2025 was up 10.9% to Rs 326.5 crore, compared with Rs 294.5 crore in Q4 2024. Profit after tax was up 7.5% to Rs 241.5 crore, compared with Rs 224.7 crore in Q4 2024. Crisil's consolidated income from operations in FY 2025, was up 11.9% to Rs 3,649 crore, compared with Rs 3,259.8 crore in FY 2024. Consolidated total income, rose 12.1% to Rs 3,755.6 crore, compared with Rs 3,349.4 crore in FY 2024. Profit before tax was up 12.4% to Rs 1,041 crore, compared with Rs 926.5 crore in FY 2024. Profit after tax was up 12% to Rs 766 crore, compared with Rs 684.1 crore in FY 2024. The above results include impact of new labour codes of Rs 16.8 crore for the fourth quarter and year ended 31 December 2025. Crisil Ratings maintained its leadership in corporate bond ratings. Its revenue grew 14.3% on year in Q4 2025, and 15.7% in FY 2025. Overall, the Ratings segment revenue grew 14.4% in Q4 2025 and 18.4% in FY 2025. The research, analytics and solutions segment revenue grew 20.1% in Q4 2025 and 9.4% in FY 2025. The board has recommended a final dividend of Rs 28 per share (of Re 1 face value), taking the total dividend for the year to Rs 61 per share. Amish Mehta, managing director & CEO, Crisil, "We saw strong revenue and EBITA growth compared with last year, driven by consistent financial delivery and operational resilience across our businesses. While a dynamic macroeconomic backdrop persists, we are committed to delivering sustainable growth through continuous investments in creating new products and solutions, expanding our client footprint, and developing future-ready talent. We focus on creating domain-led GenAI solutions that drive competitiveness by enhancing client experiences and insights and augmenting operational efficiencies. Notably, Crisil is marching towards its 40th year of making markets function better, driven by deep institutional intelligence and rich experience honed by economic cycles, reforms and shocks, and as a steadfast ally in the Viksit Bharat quest." Crisil is a global, insights-driven analytics company. Headquartered in India, Crisil is majority owned by S&P Global. Founded in 1987 as India’s first credit rating agency, its services spans across businesses: Crisil Ratings, Crisil Intelligence, Crisil Coalition Greenwich and Crisil Integral IQ. Crisil’s global workforce operates in the Americas, Asia-Pacific, Europe, Australia and the Middle East.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CRISIL_25806077903_3265.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>