<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:00:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd Surges 19.6%, BSE Information Technology index Gains 1.95%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/iris-regtech-solutions-ltd-surges-196-bse-information-technology-index-gains-195/1665111</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665111</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd gained 19.6% today to trade at Rs 338.9.

IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd gained 19.6% today to trade at Rs 338.9. The BSE Information Technology index is up 1.95% to quote at 37245.14. The index is up 1.05 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Infosys Ltd increased 3.82% and Mphasis Ltd added 3% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 13 % over last one year compared to the 8.6% surge in benchmark SENSEX. IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd has added 12.03% over last one month compared to 1.05% gain in BSE Information Technology index and 1.05% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 846 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 573.65 on 14 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 229.1 on 23 May 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IRISBusinessServicesLtd_95899652988_69022.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd Slips 1.63%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kalyan-jewellers-india-ltd-slips-163/1665112</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665112</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd fell 1.63% today to trade at Rs 472.8.

Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd fell 1.63% today to trade at Rs 472.8. The BSE Consumer Durables index is down 0.33% to quote at 60652.42. The index is up 1.05 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd decreased 0.58% and Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Ltd lost 0.24% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went up 0.3 % over last one year compared to the 8.6% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd has lost 0.35% over last one month compared to 1.05% gain in BSE Consumer Durables index and 1.05% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 23233 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 2.27 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 617.3 on 24 Jul 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 399.2 on 11 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KalyanJewellersIndia_46056464.1248805_42402.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ZEN Technologies gains after bagging Rs 404-cr orders from Ministry of Defence]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zen-technologies-gains-after-bagging-rs-404-cr-orders-from-ministry-of-defence/1665108</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665108</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the orders pertain to the supply of Anti-Drone Systems / Counter Unmanned Aerial Systems (C-UAS) as well as training simulators and equipment.

According to an exchange filing, the orders pertain to the supply of Anti-Drone Systems / Counter Unmanned Aerial Systems (C-UAS) as well as training simulators and equipment. The total order value includes Rs 332 crore for the supply of Anti-Drone Systems / Counter Unmanned Aerial Systems (C-UAS) and Rs 72 crore for training simulators and equipment. The orders are expected to be executed within one year. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity and that the contracts do not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. Zen Technologies provides defence training and anti-drone solutions. It builds training systems for imparting defense training and measuring combat readiness of security forces. With a dedicated R&D (recognized by the Ministry of Science and Technology, Government of India) and production facility in Hyderabad, the company has applied for over 180+ patents and shipped more than 1,000 training systems around the world. On a consolidated basis, the company’s net profit stood at Rs 59.4 crore in Q2 FY26, down 5.2% year-on-year from Rs 62.7 crore in Q2 FY25, though it rose 24.4% sequentially from Rs 47.8 crore in Q1 FY26. Total revenue came in at Rs 198.9 crore, declining 20.6% YoY from Rs 250.3 crore a year earlier, but up 10.5% QoQ from Rs 180 crore in Q1 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZenTechnologies_28090860091_21203.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests possible red start for equities; Taiwan to invest $250 billion in U.S. chipmaking industry]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-possible-red-start-for-equities-taiwan-to-invest-250-billion-in-us-chipmaking-industry/1665095</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665095</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 14.50 points, hinting towards a possible red opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 14.50 points, hinting towards a possible red opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 4,781.24 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,217.28 crore in the Indian equity market on 14 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 21,706.27 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market broadly traded mixed on Friday even as major chip stocks edged higher. Shares of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. rose in trade after the company delivered another record quarter, saying it expects to boost capital spending in 2026 to between $52 billion and $56 billion. Investors across the region were also watching chip-related stocks after the U.S. reached a trade deal with Taiwan. Under the agreement, Taiwanese semiconductor companies commited to invest at least $250 billion in U.S. production capacity in exchange for lower “reciprocal” tariffs. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.60%, while the S&P 500 rose 0.26% and the Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.25%. U.S. bank stocks also advanced after the latest raft of quarterly earnings. Goldman Sachs advanced more than 4% after its fourth-quarter profit topped widely reported earnings estimates. Morgan Stanley surged nearly 6% after its wealth management unit contributed to top- and bottom-line beats in the fourth quarter. The rally also came on the back of solid economic data. Jobless claims data for the week ending Jan. 10 came in at 198,000, lower than the 215,000 expected by economists polled by Dow Jones. Domestic Market: Benchmark equity indices closed lower for a second straight session on Wednesday as profit booking, foreign institutional selling, and F&O contract expiry on the BSE weighed on sentiment. Investors tracked progress on the India-US trade agreement, ongoing Q3 earnings results, and global geopolitical developments, while remaining cautious ahead of a US Supreme Court ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump’s tariff measures. The Nifty slipped below the 25,700 level. IT and automobile stocks led the declines, while metal stocks and PSU banks attracted buying interest. The S&P BSE Sensex slipped 244.98 points or 0.29% to 83,382.71. The Nifty 50 index lost 66.70 points or 0.26% to 25,665.60. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.60% while the Nifty fell 0.48%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Infosys, HDB Financial Services, Waaree Renewable, Jio Financial Services, HDFC Life Insurance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-infosys-hdb-financial-services-waaree-renewable-jio-financial-services-hdfc-life-insurance/1665085</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665085</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 16 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 16 January 2026. Result Today: Reliance Industries, Wipro, Tech Mahindra, Tata Technologies, Bajaj Healthcare, Central Bank of India, Federal Bank, Geojit Financial Services, JB Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals, Jindal Saw, JSW Infrastructure, Kesoram Industries, L&T Finance, Polycab India, Poonawalla Fincorp, Sobha, and Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts will release their quarterly results today. Maharashtra elections result 2026 Updates: The state election commission will announce the results of the high-stakes elections to Maharashtra's 29 municipal corporations, including Mumbai's Brihanmumbai Municipal Corporation (BMC), on Friday. Elections for 2,869 seats across 893 wards in Maharashtra took place on 15 January, and the counting of votes will begin at 10 am today. Some of the key municipal corporations to watch are Mumbai, Pune, Thane, Pimpri-Chinchwad, Kalyan-Dombivli, Mira-Bhayandar, Ulhasnagar and Navi Mumbai, among others. Stocks to Watch: Infosys reported a 9.6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,654 crore on a 2.22% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 45,479 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY25. HDB Financial Services reported a 36.33% jump in net profit to Rs 643.9 crore on 12.78% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 4,673.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Waaree Renewable’s consolidated net profit jumped 122.22% to Rs 120 crore on 136.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 851 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Jio Financial Services’ consolidated net profit declined 8.8% to Rs 269 crore despite a 100.7% jump in total income to Rs 901 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. HDFC Life Insurance reported a 0.8% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 418 crore despite a 9% rise in net premium income to Rs 18,351 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. L&T Technology Services reported a 7.9% decline in net profit to Rs 303 crore on 1.9% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 2,924 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. TVS Supply Chain informed that it has appointed Vikas Chadha as its Global CEO, effective 22 January 2026. Transrail Lighting said that it received orders worth Rs 527 crore from the MENA region, Africa, and India, taking its cumulative order inflows for FY26 to Rs 5,637 crore. Railtel Corporation informed that it has received a letter of acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 88 crore from Central Railway.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITCONS E-Solutions bags Rs 7-cr contract from Bank of Maharashtra]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itcons-e-solutions-bags-rs-7-cr-contract-from-bank-of-maharashtra/1665084</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665084</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, under the agreement, the company will provide 63 resources manpower outsourcing services for a period of three years.

According to an exchange filing, under the agreement, the company will provide 63 resources manpower outsourcing services for a period of three years. The total value of the contract stands at Rs 6,68,65,225.42. The contract is scheduled to commence on 1 February 2026 and will remain in force until 31 January 2029, unless extended further by mutual consent of both parties. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity and that the contract does not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. ITCONS E-Solutions is engaged in the business of recruitment and staffing services. On a full-year basis, the company’s net profit surged 70.2% to Rs 3.25 crore on a 96.4% soar in net sales to Rs 55.98 crore in FY25 over FY24. The counter tumbled 19.20% to Rs 316 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITCONSESolutionsLtd_70007426_78414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>