<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:25:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PNB records 8% YoY growth in domestic deposits in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pnb-records-8-yoy-growth-in-domestic-deposits-in-q3/1663070</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663070</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank's domestic advances stood at Rs 11,67,801 crore on 31 December 2025, up 10.15% YoY and up 4.47% QoQ.

The bank's domestic advances stood at Rs 11,67,801 crore on 31 December 2025, up 10.15% YoY and up 4.47% QoQ. The bank’s global advances increased 10.98% YoY to Rs 12,32,245 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 11,10,292 crore a year earlier and rose 5.36% QoQ from Rs 11,69,592 crore as of 30 September 2025. As of 31 December 2025, the bank’s global deposits stood at Rs 16,60,385 crore, registering a growth of 8.54% YoY and 2.68% QoQ. The bank's global business stood at Rs 28,92,630 crore as of 31 December 2025, recording a growth of 9.57% YoY and 3.80% QoQ. The global credit-deposit ratio advanced to 74.21% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 72.58% recorded a year earlier on 31 December 2024. Punjab National Bank is engaged in treasury operations, corporate/wholesale banking, retail banking, digital banking, and others. As of 30th September 2025, the bank has 10,228 domestic branches and 2 international branches. Out of the total number of branches, the bank has 63.3% of branches in rural & semi-urban areas. The bank’s standalone net profit climbed 13.95% to Rs 4,903.73 crore on a 5.13% jump in total income to Rs 36,213.62 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Jammu & Kashmir Bank rallied 1.17% to close at Rs 125.40 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663069</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663069</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon Mutual Fund has announced that Notice is hereby given that Mr.

Nippon Mutual Fund has announced that Notice is hereby given that Mr. Ajay Patel, Deputy Head - Operations has ceased from the services of Nippon Life India Asset Management Limited due to superannuation with effect from the close of business hours on January 02, 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TRUST Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trust-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663068</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TRUST Mutual Fund has announced that NOTICE is hereby given that Mr.

TRUST Mutual Fund has announced that NOTICE is hereby given that Mr. Ameet Hariani has resigned as an Independent Director on the Board of TRUST AMC Trustee Private Limited with effect from December 31, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[J&K Bank gross advances grow 17% YoY in Q3FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jk-bank-gross-advances-grow-17-yoy-in-q3fy26/1663066</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663066</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total business stood at Rs 2,72,109.27 crore as of 31 December 2025, up 13.34%, compared with Rs 2,40,080.49 crore as of 31 December 2024.

Total business stood at Rs 2,72,109.27 crore as of 31 December 2025, up 13.34%, compared with Rs 2,40,080.49 crore as of 31 December 2024. CASA deposits rose 1.25% YoY to Rs 68,736.27 crore as of 31 December 2025. CASA ratio reduced to 44.10% as of 31 December 2025 as against 48.17% as of 31 December 2024. Total deposits increased 10.58% to Rs 1,55,861.35 crore as of 31 Decemeber 2025, compared with Rs 1,40,947.14 crore as of 31 December 2024. Gross investment declined 2.07% to Rs 40,535.76 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 41,394.29 crore as of 31 December 2024. J&K Bank offers banking services under the three major divisions as support services, depository services, and third-party services. The bank reported a 1.91% jump in net profit to Rs 494.11 crore on a 2.04% decline in total income to Rs 3,446.71 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q1 FY26. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit declined 10.31%, and revenue rose 0.79% in Q2 FY26. Shares of Jammu & Kashmir Bank rallied 1.29% to close at Rs 102.35 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JKBank_38858702295_7311.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663067</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663067</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced that Ms.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced that Ms. Roshi Jain, Senior Fund Manager - Equities has resigned from the services of HDFC Asset Management Company Limited (“HDFC AMC”) and accordingly, has ceased to be a Key Personnel of HDFC AMC with effect from close of business hours of December 31, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NIBE bags Rs 293-cr defence order from Indian Army]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nibe-bags-rs-293-cr-defence-order-from-indian-army/1663062</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663062</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the manufacturing and supply of ground equipment, accessories, ESP and ammunition for a Universal Rocket Launcher System capable of integrating multiple rocket types, including long-range rockets with strike capabilities of 150 km and 300 km.

The order involves the manufacturing and supply of ground equipment, accessories, ESP and ammunition for a Universal Rocket Launcher System capable of integrating multiple rocket types, including long-range rockets with strike capabilities of 150 km and 300 km. As per the contract terms, the company is required to furnish a performance-cum-warranty bank guarantee equivalent to 10% of the total contract value within 30 days of signing the agreement. The contract will be executed in tranches over a period of 12 months. The total consideration of Rs 292.69 crore is inclusive of all taxes and duties. The company clarified that the order has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related-party transactions. Further, the promoters or promoter group entities do not have any interest in the awarding authority. NIBE operates in manufacturing critical components for the defence sector, electric vehicles (E-Vehicles), and software development. The company is engaged in fabrication and machining of components used in the defence sector, as well as assembly of components for E-vehicles. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 8.44 crore in Q2FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 9.12 crore posted in Q2FY25. Revenue from operations fell 46.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 73.37 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of NIBE rallied 9.21% to close at Rs 1,240.25 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KavitaFabrics_98715753806_43224.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Torrent Pharma credit rating unchanged as India Ratings reaffirms AA+]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/torrent-pharma-credit-rating-unchanged-as-india-ratings-reaffirms-aa/1663060</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663060</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Torrent Pharmaceuticals said India Ratings and Research has reaffirmed the credit rating of the company’s existing banking facilities, issuer rating and non-convertible debentures at IND AA+ with a stable outlook.

Torrent Pharmaceuticals said India Ratings and Research has reaffirmed the credit rating of the company’s existing banking facilities, issuer rating and non-convertible debentures at IND AA+ with a stable outlook. The rating agency has also assigned a short-term rating of IND A1+ to Torrent Pharma's proposed commercial paper programme, indicating a strong degree of safety with respect to timely servicing of financial obligations. The company's securities transfer and stakeholders relationship committee will meet on 5 January 2026 to consider the issuance of secured non-convertible debentures through a private placement, within the borrowing limits already approved by the board in July 2025. Torrent Pharma is the flagship company of the Torrent Group. It is ranked 7th in the Indian Pharmaceuticals Market and is amongst the Top 5 in the therapeutics segments of Cardiovascular (CV), Gastro Intestinal (GI), Central Nervous System (CNS) and Cosmo-Dermatology. It is a specialty-focused company with 76% of its revenues in India from chronic & sub-chronic therapies. It has presence in 50+ countries and is ranked No. 1 amongst the Indian pharma companies in Brazil and Germany. Torrent has 8 manufacturing facilities, of which 5 are USFDA approved. On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit rose 30.46% to Rs 591 crore while net sales rose 14.66% to Rs 3246 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. Shares of Torrent Pharmaceuticals rose 0.96% to settle at Rs 3884.85 on Friday, 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TorrentPharma_35676110126_3616.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>