<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:44:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AWL Agri Business records 35% YoY fall in Q3 PAT; registers EBITDA of Rs 685 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/awl-agri-business-records-35-yoy-fall-in-q3-pat-registers-ebitda-of-rs-685-crore/1670691</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670691</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations increased by 10% YoY to Rs 18,603 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by an underlying volume growth of 3%.

Revenue from operations increased by 10% YoY to Rs 18,603 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by an underlying volume growth of 3%. Growth was primarily driven by healthy volume offtake in the Edible Oil segment. On the segmental front, Edible Oil revenue was Rs 15,025 crore (up 12% YoY), Food & FMCG revenue was Rs 1,648 crore (up 9% YoY) and Industry Essentials revenue was Rs 1,930 crore (up 1% YoY) for the period under review. EBITDA declined by 20% to Rs 685 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 858 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax and exceptional item for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 389 crore, down by 29% from Rs 546 crore in Q3 FY25. The company recorded an exceptional charge of Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY26 on account of the implementation of the new labour codes. Shrikant Kanhere, MD & CEO, AWL Agri Business, said: “Despite a challenging macro demand environment, AWL Agri Business maintained modest single-digit volume growth in Q3 FY26, led by resilient performance in edible oils and a continued rebound in our Food & FMCG portfolio. We remain focused on strengthening our integrated value chain and go-to-market capabilities while scaling alternate, digital and quick-commerce channels. We continue to enhance distribution efficiency and reach to support sustainable and profitable growth. As part of the Wilmar Group, we align with our parent’s strategic emphasis on resilient core operations and long-term value creation, even when headline results face transient challenges." AWL Agri Business is one of India’s largest Food & FMCG companies, offering a diverse portfolio of essential kitchen staples, including edible oils, wheat flour, rice, pulses, and sugar. The scrip rose 0.87% to currently trade at Rs 214.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniWilmarLtd_38707947_20696.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel Corp Q3 PAT slides 4% YoY to Rs 62 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-corp-q3-pat-slides-4-yoy-to-rs-62-cr/1670667</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670667</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 18.99% YoY to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26.

However, revenue from operations rose 18.99% YoY to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 85 crore in Q3 FY26, down 5.21%, compared with Rs 89.68 crore posted in same quarter last year. Total expenses jumped 20.22% to Rs 829.86 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 690.25 crore in Q3 FY25. License fees to DoT (Department of telecommunication) stood at Rs 22.47 crore (down 32.90%), expenses on project was at Rs 54514 crore (up 33.34% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 58.56 crore (up 3.79% YoY) during the period under review. Revenue from telecom services increased 3.43% to Rs 349.54 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 337.92 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from project work services was at Rs 563.91 crore, up 31.23% YoY. RailTel was incorporated in 2000, with the objective of creating nationwide broadband and VPN services, telecom, and multimedia network, to modernize the train control operation and safety system of Indian Railways. It is a "Navratna" PSU of the Government of India. At present, RailTel's network passes through around 6,000 stations across the country, covering all major commercial centers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Kasturi Metal Composite makes a calm market entry]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-kasturi-metal-composite-makes-a-calm-market-entry/1670669</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670669</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 64, matching the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 64, matching the issue price. The stock touched a high of Rs 64.50 and a low of Rs 60.80, with around 10.08 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Kasturi Metal Composite's IPO was subscribed 16.57 times. The issue opened for bidding on 27 January 2026 and it closed on 29 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 61 to Rs 64 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 27,52,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter group shareholding diluted to 67.90% from 92.35% pre-issue. The company intends to utilise the net proceeds for funding the capital expenditure towards construction of building, mechanical and electrical works, interior work and procurement of plant and machinery for setting up a new manufacturing facility at Amravati, Maharashtra and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Kasturi Metal Composite on 23 January 2025, raised Rs 5 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 7.82 lakh shares at Rs 64 each to 4 anchor investors. Kasturi Metal Composite specialises in the manufacturing of steel fiber products for industrial applications. Its portfolio includes loose hook-end, glued hook-end, and flat crimped steel fibres, along with steel wool fibre. Operating under the Duraflex, Durabond, and Durocrete brands, the company serves the construction, engineering, automotive, and infrastructure sectors. Its subsidiary, Durafloor Concrete Solution LLP, provides specialised flooring solutions. With over 20 years of experience, the company supplies critical materials for tunnel shotcrete, precast concrete, industrial flooring, road construction, and automotive friction linings, consistently delivering quality and value across diverse industries. As of 31 October 2025, the company has employed 98 permanent full-time employees, including managerial personnel. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 32.04 crore and net profit of Rs 2.47 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KasturiMetalCompositeLtd_79159032_95338.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/garware-hi-tech-films-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1670666</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670666</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Avalon Technologies Ltd, Gokaldas Exports Ltd, Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd and Indo Count Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 03 February 2026.

Avalon Technologies Ltd, Gokaldas Exports Ltd, Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd and Indo Count Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 03 February 2026. Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd surged 20.00% to Rs 3905.2 at 11:42 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 2172 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3137 shares in the past one month. Avalon Technologies Ltd spiked 20.00% to Rs 1029.1. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.88 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14642 shares in the past one month. Gokaldas Exports Ltd soared 20.00% to Rs 696.1. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 76281 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 82565 shares in the past one month. Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd advanced 19.99% to Rs 168.95. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 98568 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35660 shares in the past one month. Indo Count Industries Ltd spurt 19.99% to Rs 286.9. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 68106 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12860 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GarwarePolyest_69101031050_189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zaggle Prepaid gains on inking pact with Dr Batra’s Positive Health Clinic]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zaggle-prepaid-gains-on-inking-pact-with-dr-batras-positive-health-clinic/1670665</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670665</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As per an exchange filing, Zaggle will provide its Zaggle Zoyer Platform to Dr Batra’s Positive Health Clinic.

As per an exchange filing, Zaggle will provide its Zaggle Zoyer Platform to Dr Batra’s Positive Health Clinic. The agreement remains effective until terminated as specified in the terms of the contract. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It also confirmed that the contract does not fall under the category of related-party transactions, in line with regulatory norms. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services (Zaggle) is a leading player in spend management, with a differentiated value proposition and diversified user base. The company operates in the business-to-business-to-customer segment. It is one of the largest numbers of issued prepaid cards in India in partnership with its banking partners. Additionally, the company has a diversified portfolio of software as a service (SaaS) products, including tax and payroll software, and a wide touchpoint reach.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZagglePrepaidOceanServicesLtd_95613182_78337.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dhampur Sugar Mills gains after Q3 PAT jumps 75% YoY to Rs 26 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dhampur-sugar-mills-gains-after-q3-pat-jumps-75-yoy-to-rs-26-cr/1670662</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670662</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 71.4% YoY to Rs 37.21 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 71.4% YoY to Rs 37.21 crore during the quarter. EBITDA stood at Rs 62 crore in Q3 December 2025, registering the growth of 28.9% compared with Rs 48.1 crore posted in Q3 December 2024. EBITDA margin improved to 9.3% in Q3 December 2025 as against 8.2% in Q3 December 2024. Sugar sales jumped 18.97% to 0.69 lakh tons in Q3 FY26 compared with 0.58 lakh tons sold in corresponding quarter last year. Sugar realization increased 5.81% to Rs 40,259 per ton in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 38,048 per ton in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, revenue from ethanol business jumped 12.7% YoY to Rs 110 crore, revenue from power business increased 44.69% to Rs 90 crore, revenue from potable spirits jumped 22.94% YoY to Rs 241.7 crore while revenue from chemicals business stood at Rs 18.3 crore, down 61.47% YoY. Dhampur Sugar Mills is engaged mainly in the manufacturing and selling of sugar, chemicals, ethanol, potable spirits, co-generation and sale of power.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DhampurSugar_83826239460_2626.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Japanese yen recovers amid policy signals and election focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/japanese-yen-recovers-amid-policy-signals-and-election-focus/1670660</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670660</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen moved back above 155 per dollar on Tuesday after two days of losses, even as the US dollar remained underpinned by strong economic data and a more hawkish Federal Reserve outlook.

The Japanese yen moved back above 155 per dollar on Tuesday after two days of losses, even as the US dollar remained underpinned by strong economic data and a more hawkish Federal Reserve outlook. The dollar index hovered near 97.3 following a sharp rebound earlier in the week. Pressure on the yen has persisted amid domestic political developments, after Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi signaled that a weaker currency could benefit exporters. With a snap lower house election set for February 8 and expectations of expansionary fiscal policies, investors remain cautious. Attention now shifts to Friday’s US jobs report, though its release could be delayed by a partial government shutdown.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brahmaputra Infra rises after JV secures Rs 62-cr LOA ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brahmaputra-infra-rises-after-jv-secures-rs-62-cr-loa/1670659</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670659</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order includes execution of underwater riverbank protection works (Section 1) and above-water riverbank protection works (Section 2) under the Jorhat subproject, covering Sivasagar, Jorhat, and Golaghat districts.

The order includes execution of underwater riverbank protection works (Section 1) and above-water riverbank protection works (Section 2) under the Jorhat subproject, covering Sivasagar, Jorhat, and Golaghat districts. The work falls under Package No. W-AF-03-RPJH, Lot 1, as part of the ADB’s Climate Resilient Brahmaputra Integrated Flood and Riverbank Erosion Risk Management Project in Assam. The total project value is Rs 62.03 crore and the work is scheduled to be completed over a 30-month period. Brahmaputra Infrastructure is a versatile construction company with a significant presence in sectors like highways & roads, buildings, bridges/flyovers, airports, tunnels, and other civil construction works. On a consolidated basis, Brahmaputra Infrastructure reported a net profit of Rs 14.64 crore in Q2 September 2025, a surge of 3,653.85% from Rs 0.39 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales rose 188.89% year-on-year to Rs 90.19 crore during the same period.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrahmaputraInf_89782917235_28067.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[City Union Bank rallies after Q3 PAT rises 16% YoY to Rs 332 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/city-union-bank-rallies-after-q3-pat-rises-16-yoy-to-rs-332-cr/1670658</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670658</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income (NII) rose 28% to Rs 752 crore in the December 2025 quarter, compared to Rs 588 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net interest income (NII) rose 28% to Rs 752 crore in the December 2025 quarter, compared to Rs 588 crore in Q3 FY25. For Q3 FY26, NIM was at 3.89% as against 3.58% in the corresponding period last year. Profit before tax (PBT) grew 15.6% year on year (YoY) to Rs 417.16 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The bank's operating profit before provisions and contingencies jumped 18% to Rs 513 crore in the December 2025 quarter, compared to Rs 436 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The bank made a provision of Rs 468 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 402 crore in the corresponding period last year. On the asset quality front, the gross non-performing assets (GNPA) were at Rs 1,320 crore as of 31 December 2025, down 20.03% as against Rs 1,693 crore as of 31 December 2024. The ratio of gross NPA stood at 2.17% as of 31 December 2025, compared to 3.36% as of 31 December 2024. The ratio of net NPA stood at 0.78% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 1.42% as of 31 December 2024. The bank’s capital adequacy as of 31 December 2025, as per Reserve Bank of India (RBI) guidelines on Basel III norms, is 20.13%, and Tier-1 capital adequacy was 19.18%, well above regulatory requirements. Total deposits of the bank had increased by 21.01% and increased to Rs 70,516 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 58,271 crore in the corresponding period last year. The CASA portion stood at 27% of total deposits. The cost of deposits reduced to 5.57% in Q3 FY26 from 5.71% in Q3 FY25. Total advances increased by 21% for Q3 FY26 to Rs 60,892 crore from Rs 50,409 crore in Q3 FY25. The average credit deposit ratio stood at 84%. The yield on Advances for Q3 FY26 improved to 9.73% compared to 9.66% in Q2 FY26. City Union Bank is an old private sector bank with 902 branches across 18 states and four Union territories. It is a scheduled commercial bank regulated by the Reserve Bank of India. It is professionally managed and governed. City Union Bank has contemporary technology and infrastructure, including ATMs, net banking, mobile banking, e-wallets, and social media banking for personal as well as business banking customers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CityUnionBank_58915157897_7015.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades near 25,800 level; consumer durables share advance for 2nd day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-near-25800-level-consumer-durables-share-advance-for-2nd-day/1670645</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670645</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with significant gains in the early afternoon trade as investors cheered the long-awaited trade agreement between India and the United States.

The key equity benchmarks traded with significant gains in the early afternoon trade as investors cheered the long-awaited trade agreement between India and the United States. The announcement sparked broad-based buying across sectors, enabling domestic markets to recoup losses triggered by the recent Union Budget. The Nifty traded near the 25,800 level. Consumer Durables shares extended gains for two consecutive trading sessions. At 11:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, zoomed 2,379.76 points or 2.91% to 84,046.22. The Nifty 50 index added 709.65 points or 2.83% to 25,798.05. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 2.91% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.91%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,214 shares rose and 709 shares fell. A total of 200 shares were unchanged. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index added 3.49% to 35,598.10. The index added 3.99% in the two consecutive trading session. Dixon Technologies (India) (up 6.37%), Kalyan Jewellers India (up 5.61%), Amber Enterprises India (up 4.54%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (up 3.66%), PG Electroplast (up 3.53%), Titan Company (up 3.43%), Havells India (up 2.91%), Voltas (up 2.82%), Blue Star (up 2.74%) and Century Plyboards (India) (up 2.42%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: RMC Switchgears surged 7.57% after the company announced that it has received orders worth Rs 200.86 crore for development of distribution infrastructure works. Veedol Corporation advanced 1.67% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 16.63% to Rs 43.55 crore on 11.47% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 537.73 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Transrail Lighting rallied 9.93% after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 17.7% to Rs 109.74 crore on a 32.6% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,777.19 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Most Asian indices rose on Tuesday after the U.S. and India trade deal, sparking a sharp risk-on move across the region. Japan's Nikkei 225 jumped nearly 3% and the Topix rose over 2%. South Korea’s Kospi surged about 5%, triggering a buy-side trading curb. U.S. stocks climbed overnight as Wall Street kicked off the new month on a positive note, with investors looking past recent volatility in silver and bitcoin and turning their focus to the upcoming earnings slate. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.05%, the S&P 500 gained 0.54%, and the Nasdaq Composite added 0.56%. Markets are also tracking key economic signals and cues from the Federal Reserve on interest rates, even as efforts continue in Washington to avert a partial government shutdown. Data releases have been disrupted, with the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics postponing the January jobs report and other labour data until federal operations resume.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ather Energy soars after best-ever quarter, losses narrow sharply]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ather-energy-soars-after-best-ever-quarter-losses-narrow-sharply/1670642</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670642</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a standalone basis, the company reported a net loss of Rs 84.60 crore in Q3 December 2025, narrowing sharply from a loss of Rs 197.80 crore in Q3 December 2024 and lower than the Rs 154.10 crore loss in Q2 September 2025.

On a standalone basis, the company reported a net loss of Rs 84.60 crore in Q3 December 2025, narrowing sharply from a loss of Rs 197.80 crore in Q3 December 2024 and lower than the Rs 154.10 crore loss in Q2 September 2025. Net sales jumped 50.20% year-on-year and 6.09% quarter-on-quarter to Rs 953.60 crore in December 2025 quarter. For the quarter ended December 2025, Ather Energy reported total income of Rs 995.7 crore, up 53% YoY, driven by robust volume growth and a rising contribution of non-vehicle revenue, including software subscriptions, charging, accessories, spares, and service, which rose to 14% of revenue. Adjusted Gross Margin (AGM) reached Rs 251.3 crore in Q3 FY26, up 111% YoY, while AGM excluding incentives improved to 23%, up 1,100 bps YoY. This was driven by Ather’s value engineering capabilities and the ability to command strong premiums, reflecting a continued focus on healthier unit economics and structurally stronger margins. EBITDA margin narrowed significantly to (-3%), driven by better unit economics, disciplined cost management, and operating leverage as volumes scaled. Losses continued to shrink, with EBITDA loss down to Rs 29.9 crore, and the quarterly loss narrowing by 45% compared to Q2 FY26, underscoring steady progress toward profitable, sustainable growth. During the quarter, the company reported highest-ever quarterly volumes of 67,851 units, delivering 50% YoY growth. Ather Energy’s market share continued to strengthen in India’s electric two-wheeler market in Q3 FY26, with a pan-India market share of 18.8%. South India remained Ather’s strongest region, retaining leadership with a 24.4% market share. Middle India continued its upward trajectory, with market share almost doubling to 17.4% from 8.8% in Q3 FY25, driven by strong performance across Gujarat, Madhya Pradesh, Maharashtra, and Odisha. In the Rest of India, market share rose to 12.6%, reflecting steady growth across northern and emerging markets. Ather added 76 new Experience Centres (ECs) in Q3, taking its national network to 600 ECs. South India continued to have the deepest presence with 261 ECs, followed by Middle India with 202 ECs and the Rest of India with 137 ECs. Charging infrastructure also expanded steadily, with the Ather Grid network expanding to 4,357 fast-charging points and neighbourhood chargers across India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka. Tarun Mehta, executive director & CEO, Ather Energy, said, "Q3 has been a strong quarter for us. Robust festive demand, healthy volume growth, and improving market share together drove our best quarterly revenue and EBITDA so far. Over the past few quarters, we have stayed very focused on getting the fundamentals right by improving unit economics, margins, and operating leverage, and that effort is now clearly showing in the improvement in EBITDA. What is particularly encouraging is the strength of our ecosystem. AtherStack attach rates remain very high, and customer engagement is deepening even as our sales scale. All of this gives us confidence that the business is structurally prepared for sustainable, long-term growth." Meanwhile, the company's board approved incorporation of a wholly owned subsidiary in Hong Kong to support the Company’s critical procurement functions and enhance supply chain resilience within the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region. Ather Energy is one of India’s leading electric two-wheeler manufacturers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AtherEnergyLtd_32132763_75556.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DSP MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under three schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dsp-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-three-schemes/1670640</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670640</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund has announced 06 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

DSP Mutual Fund has announced 06 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: DSP India T.I.G.E.R Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 4.300000 Direct Plan – IDCW: 2.300000 DSP Global Clean Energy Fund of Fund: Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00000 DSP Focused Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.800000 Direct Plan – IDCW: 3.500000

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1670637</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670637</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 05 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 05 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Nippon India Pharma Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 8.5000 Direct Plan – IDCW: 12.0000 Nippon India Focused Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 2.5000 Direct Plan – IDCW: 3.5000

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Kalpataru Projects International Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-kalpataru-projects-international-ltd-counter/1670633</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670633</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CRISIL Ltd, PCBL Chemical Ltd, Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd, Aarti Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 03 February 2026.

CRISIL Ltd, PCBL Chemical Ltd, Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd, Aarti Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 03 February 2026. Kalpataru Projects International Ltd recorded volume of 1.47 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 29.09 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5053 shares. The stock lost 0.95% to Rs.1,114.60. Volumes stood at 6898 shares in the last session. CRISIL Ltd witnessed volume of 51250 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 22.92 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2236 shares. The stock dropped 0.48% to Rs.4,792.95. Volumes stood at 3597 shares in the last session. PCBL Chemical Ltd notched up volume of 10.6 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 16.44 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 64462 shares. The stock rose 14.40% to Rs.306.25. Volumes stood at 64273 shares in the last session. Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd clocked volume of 1.22 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 14.86 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 8215 shares. The stock gained 0.40% to Rs.1,153.85. Volumes stood at 7831 shares in the last session. Aarti Industries Ltd saw volume of 7.97 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 14.8 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 53808 shares. The stock increased 12.41% to Rs.419.45. Volumes stood at 66330 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KalpataruPower_75778021409_4518.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RMC Switchgears jumps after securing Rs 201-cr distribution infrastructure orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rmc-switchgears-jumps-after-securing-rs-201-cr-distribution-infrastructure-orders/1670631</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670631</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the company received an order from Jaipur Vidyut Vitran Nigam for executing works related to the segregation of 11 kV mixed feeders at the Dholpur Circle of Jaipur Discom in Rajasthan.

According to an exchange filing, the company received an order from Jaipur Vidyut Vitran Nigam for executing works related to the segregation of 11 kV mixed feeders at the Dholpur Circle of Jaipur Discom in Rajasthan. The project is being awarded under the Revamped Reforms-based and Results-linked Distribution Sector Scheme (RDSS) on a turnkey basis, against RFP JVVNL/RDSS/INFRA/FS/TN-610. The order is valued at Rs 116.49 crore, and the work scheduled to commence within 15 days from the date of issuance of the letter of intent (LOI) and to be completed as per the project schedule provided by the project authorities. The company also received another order from Jaipur Vidyut Vitran Nigam for similar distribution infrastructure works involving the segregation of 11 kV mixed-load feeders at the Jhalawar Circle of Jaipur Discom, Rajasthan. This order has been awarded under the RDSS on a turnkey basis against RFP JVVNL/RDSS/INFRA/FS/TN-612. This second order is valued at Rs 84.38 crore, with work expected to begin within 15 days from the date of the LOI and to be completed as per the prescribed project timeline. RMC Switchgears clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. The company also confirmed that both contracts do not fall under the category of related-party transactions, in line with applicable regulatory norms. The company stated that the receipt of these LOIs strengthens its order book and is expected to contribute positively to its revenue visibility and growth prospects. It added that it will update the stock exchanges on any further material developments, as required under regulations. RMC Switchgears is primarily engaged in the business of switchgear engineering and ECI contracts for the power distribution/transmission sector. The company’s net profit surged 87.9% year-on-year to Rs 19.15 crore, while revenue from operations more than doubled—rising 130.1% to Rs 241.09 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RMCSwitchgearsLtd_53131054371_69731.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Helios Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/helios-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1670620</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670620</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Helios Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Helios Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Akshay Thakur has been appointed as Assistant Vice President (AVP) – Research with effect from February 02, 2026. Name: Mr. Akshay Thakur Age: 32 years Designation: Associate Vice President (AVP) – Research Qualification: CFA Charter holder B.com (Mumbai University)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rabi area up around 2.40% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rabi-area-up-around-240-on-year/1670617</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670617</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total area sown under rabi crops in current winter season has edged up by 2.40% on year to 676.84 lakh hectares as on January 30 this year, data released by the Ministry of Agriculture and Farmers Welfare showed.

The total area sown under rabi crops in current winter season has edged up by 2.40% on year to 676.84 lakh hectares as on January 30 this year, data released by the Ministry of Agriculture and Farmers Welfare showed. The area under major crop wheat has gained 1.86% on year to 334.17 lakh hectares.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/agriculture-1551086__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Veedol Corp gains after Q3 PAT climbs 17% YoY to Rs 43 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/veedol-corp-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-17-yoy-to-rs-43-cr/1670615</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670615</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 50.32% YoY to Rs 55.36 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 50.32% YoY to Rs 55.36 crore during the quarter. Total expenses rose 9.53% to Rs 495.28 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 452.17 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 290.55 crore (up 12.92% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 41.77 crore (up 10.88% YoY) and franchisee fees stood at Rs 68.16 crore (up 1.64% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared dividend of Rs 14 per share for FY26. The record date has been set as Friday, 6 February 2026. The dividend will be paid within 30 days of the date of declaration. Veedol Corporation engaged in the business of manufacturing and marketing of lubricants.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TideWaterOil_2608463856_2846.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Government notifies Baggage Rules 2026, allows enhanced general free allowance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/government-notifies-baggage-rules-2026-allows-enhanced-general-free-allowance/1670612</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670612</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Central Government has notified the Baggage Rules, 2026.

The Central Government has notified the Baggage Rules, 2026. New Customs Baggage (Declaration and Processing) Regulations, 2026 and a Master Circular have also been issued. These measures reflect facilitative and revised provisions for international passengers and in line with new economic conditions, rising travel volumes and passenger expectations. The changes have been aimed at in consultation with stakeholders including Ministries, airport operators, and feedback from passengers, etc. These Rules will simplify procedures, enhance transparency, enable electronic and advance declarations and ensure smooth clearance. The revised rules enhance duty-free allowances in line with present-day travel realities, by revising entitlements for different passenger categories. These rules will further offer transfer of residence benefits; special allowances for jewellery; new provisions for temporary import/re-import; duty-free import of one laptop (for passengers above 18 years) and pets; and enhanced passenger facilitation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/people-sign-traveling-blur_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Textile stocks surge after India-US trade deal, Budget measures add tailwinds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/textile-stocks-surge-after-india-us-trade-deal-budget-measures-add-tailwinds/1670609</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670609</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gokaldas Exports Garware Technical Fibres and Indo Count Industries hit their upper circuits of 20%.

Gokaldas Exports Garware Technical Fibres and Indo Count Industries hit their upper circuits of 20%. Welspun Living jumped 17.12%, Vardhman Textiles rose 12%, Arvind gained 10.93%, Trident advanced 10.58%, Raymond Lifestyle climbed 6.80%, and Bombay Dyeing and Manufacturing Company added 4.37%. Under the agreement, Washington will cut reciprocal tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25%, U.S. The deal comes as a relief for textile exporters, many of whom derive 50% to 70% of their revenue from the US. Indian textile exports will now face a lower tariff than competing garment hubs such as Vietnam and Bangladesh, which attract duties of about 20%, boosting India’s relative competitiveness in the US market. Sentiment in the sector was further supported by Budget announcements aimed at strengthening India’s textile ecosystem. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in her Budget 2026-27 speech, announced the setting up of Mega Textile Parks under a challenge mode, with a focus on bringing value addition to technical textiles. To support traditional segments, the government announced the launch of the Mahatma Gandhi Gram Swaraj Initiative, aimed at strengthening khadi, handloom and handicrafts. It also announced initiative to help in global market linkage, branding and will streamline and support training, skilling, quality of process and production. In a boost to exports of textiles, leather and marine products, the Budget extended the export obligation period from six months to 12 months for exporters using duty-free imported inputs, a move expected to ease compliance pressures and improve working capital management for exporters. Sitharaman said the government will roll out an integrated programme for the labour-intensive textile sector with five sub-parts, including a National Fibre Scheme to promote self-reliance in natural fibres such as silk, wool and jute, man-made fibres, and new-age fibres.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concepts-picture-id519261614_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>