<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:21:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEBI extends deadline for implementation distributor incentive framework to March 01]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sebi-extends-deadline-for-implementation-distributor-incentive-framework-to-march-01/1663876</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663876</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a recently released circular, the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has extended the timeline for the implementation of an additional incentives structure for mutual fund distributors for onboarding new individual investors from B-30 cities and new women investors from any city.

In a recently released circular, the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has extended the timeline for the implementation of an additional incentives structure for mutual fund distributors for onboarding new individual investors from B-30 cities and new women investors from any city. Earlier, the new incentive structure, aimed at promoting wider outreach and awareness, was scheduled to be effective from 01 February 2026. The market regulator SEBI has now extended this deadline to 01 March 2026. According to the classification used in the mutual fund industry, B-30 refers to places beyond the top 30 cities. Based on the feedback received from the industry, citing operational difficulties in putting in place the requisite systems and processes for smooth implementation of the additional incentive structure, SEBI has decided to extend the implementation timeline. Accordingly, the new provisions will now come into effect from 01 March 2026, SEBI stated in its circular. Under the new framework, asset management companies (AMCs) will pay these distributors 1% of the first lump-sum investment or the first-year SIP amount, up to Rs 2,000, provided the investor stays invested for at least a year. This commission will come from the 2 basis points AMCs already set aside for investor education and will be paid over and above existing trail commissions. However, no dual incentives would be allowed for the same woman investor from B-30 cities. The additional commission would not apply to ETFs, certain Fund of Funds, and very short-duration schemes like overnight, liquid, ultra-short, and low-duration funds. The mutual fund distributors shall be eligible for additional commission for bringing new individual investors from B-30 cities, at the mutual fund industry level, and new women individual investors from both top 30 and B-30 cities.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee flat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-flat/1663875</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663875</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed flat at 90.0300 per Dollar on Thursday (08 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.0150 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dalal Street buckles as bears extend rout into fourth session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dalal-street-buckles-as-bears-extend-rout-into-fourth-session/1663866</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663866</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bears clawed deeper into Dalal Street as equity benchmarks slid for a fourth straight session on Thursday, with relentless selling dragging the Nifty below the 25,900 level.

Bears clawed deeper into Dalal Street as equity benchmarks slid for a fourth straight session on Thursday, with relentless selling dragging the Nifty below the 25,900 level. Indices reeled under a barrage of headwinds, led by sustained foreign fund outflows and rising global uncertainty. Selling pressure intensified across sectors as investors grew jittery over the prospect of fresh U.S. tariffs and escalating geopolitical tensions. All sectoral indices on the NSE ended in the red, with metals, PSU banks and energy stocks leading the decline. Sentiment weakened further amid political turmoil in Venezuela and a subdued global market backdrop. Heavyweight stocks bore the brunt of the sell-off, pulling benchmarks lower and snuffing out any attempt at a rebound. Traders also braced for a potential growth slowdown in H2 FY26, reinforcing the risk-off mood. On the technical front, indicators flashed caution, pointing to a phase of consolidation as the market struggled to find a clear near-term trigger. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 780.18 points or 0.92% to 84,180.96. The Nifty 50 index dropped 263.90 points or 1.01% to 25,876.85. In four consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 1.84% while the Nifty fell 1.71%. Larsen & Toubro (down 3.35%), TCS (down 2.74%) and Reliance Industries (down 2.25%) were major index drags today. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 1.99% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.97%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,039 shares rose and 3,157 shares fell. A total of 170 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.53% to 10.60. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.27% to 6.629 compared with previous session close of 6.611. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.857 compared with its close of 89.8700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.79% to Rs 136,924. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.01% to 98.74. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.46% to 4.158. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement rose 64 cents or 1.08% to $60.60 a barrel. Global Markets: The Dow Jones index futures were down 145 points, signaling a weak opening for U.S. equities today. European shares declined on Thursday as regional market jitters grow over U.S. President Donald Trump’s threat to annex Greenland. Asian indices ended lower after Wall Street closed lower amid rising geopolitical tensions and comments from U.S. President Donald Trump. U.S. defense stocks fell after Trump said he “will not permit” defense companies to issue dividends or stock buybacks until they address his complaints about the industry, including executive pay packages and production issues. In U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day winning streak, falling 466 points, or 0.94%, to close at 48,996.08. The S&P 500 declined 23.89 points or 0.34% to end at 6,920.93, while the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite edged up 37.10 points or 0.16% to close at 23,584.28. Stocks in Spotlight: DEE Development Engineers surged 6.41% after the company said its total order book stood at Rs 1,302.73 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 1,332.53 crore at the beginning of the month. Order inflows during December came in at Rs 98.11 crore, while execution during the month aggregated Rs 127.91 crore. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) declined 3.35%. The company said it has received a supply order from the Corps of Electronics and Mechanical Engineers (EME) of the Indian Army for overhaul, upgrade, and obsolescence management of the indigenous Pinaka Multi-Rocket Launcher Systems. LG Electronics India fell 1.89% after the expiry of the three-month shareholder lock-in period. Around 1.52 crore shares, or nearly 2% of the company’s outstanding equity, have reportedly become eligible for trading following the end of the lock-in. Market participants noted that the expiry does not necessarily signal immediate selling, as it merely permits these shares to be traded. IDFC First Bank rose 1.94% after the lender revised its savings account interest rates, effective 9 January 2026, lowering returns across several balance slabs. Market participants viewed the move as margin-accretive, as it lowers the bank’s cost of funds. Balaji Amines surged 13.74% after it received an Eligibility Certificate under Maharashtra’s Package Scheme of Incentives, 2013 for its Unit IV expansion in Solapur. The company will get benefits including an Industrial Promotion Subsidy of up to Rs 258 crore, electricity duty exemption and a 100% stamp duty waiver for seven years, boosting visibility on costs and margins. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services fell 4.99%. The company announced that it has entered into an agreement with Cubastion Consulting. Tata Steel fell 1.93%. The company’s India crude steel production stood at 6.34 million tons in Q3 FY26, up 12% QoQ and YoY, primarily aided by higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities. Meesho tanked 4.71% after its general manager- business, Megha Agarwal has tendered her resignation with effect from 7 January 2026. Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) fell 4.08%. The company has signed an MoU with the Government of Chhattisgarh to provide financial assistance of up to Rs 1 lakh crore over the next five years for housing and urban infrastructure development. Avantel fell 0.06%. The company announced that it had received a purchase order valued at Rs 11.19 crore from NewSpace India. Gland Pharma fell 1.19%. The company received an approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) filed for Olopatadine Hydrochloride Ophthalmic Solution USP, 0.7%. Gujarat Pipavav Port declined 1.82% after the company reported a 1.69% drop in container volumes to 174,000 twenty-foot equivalent units (TEU) in Q3 FY26, compared with 177 TEUs recorded in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures slide under 122 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-slide-under-122-mark/1663862</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663862</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures inch up to settle at 90.06.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures inch up to settle at 90.06. EUR/INR and JPY/INR slide by 0.15% to end at 105.24 and 57.70 respectively. Meanwhile, GBP/INR futures end lower by 0.36% at 121.09.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles lower on tariff related worries; Firm dollar and higher oil prices add to further woes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-lower-on-tariff-related-worries-firm-dollar-and-higher-oil-prices-add-to-further-woes/1663859</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663859</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee fell 7 paise to settle at 89.94 (provisional) against the US dollar on Thursday, weighed down by higher crude oil prices, foreign fund outflows, and a stronger greenback.

The Indian rupee fell 7 paise to settle at 89.94 (provisional) against the US dollar on Thursday, weighed down by higher crude oil prices, foreign fund outflows, and a stronger greenback. The apprehension of any further tariffs by the US and weak sentiments at the domestic equity markets further pressured the local unit. Indian shares fell sharply on Thursday, with key benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty extending losses for a fourth consecutive session due to ongoing geopolitical tensions and tariff-related concerns. The benchmark BSE Sensex fell 780.18 points, or 0.92 percent, to 84,180.96, reflecting widespread weakness across sectors after reports emerged that U.S. President Donald Trump has okayed a bipartisan bill that can further add to India's tariff troubles. The bill, if passed, could impose up to 500 percent tariffs on nations that knowingly purchase Russian oil. The broader NSE Nifty index ended down 263.90 points, or 1.01 percent. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 89.96 and traded in the range of 89.73 to 90.13. It eventually settled at 89.94 (provisional), down 7 paise from its previous close.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Transformer & Rectifiers drops after CEO, Mukul Srivastava resigns; Q3 PAT climbs 37% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/transformer-rectifiers-drops-after-ceo-mukul-srivastava-resigns-q3-pat-climbs-37-yoy/1663858</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663858</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Following his exit, the board appointed Satyen J.

Following his exit, the board appointed Satyen J. Mamtora, the company’s managing director (MD), as CEO with effect from 8 January 2026. Satyen J. Mamtora is the MD of TARIL and a second-generation entrepreneur with over three decades of experience in the transformer manufacturing and power equipment sector. He joined TARIL in 1997 as director – marketing and has since played a central role in expanding the company’s market presence, strengthening customer relationships, and guiding its evolution from a regional manufacturer to a globally recognised transformer organisation. Meanwhile, the company announced its Q3 result, reporting 36.93% YoY jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 75.97 crore on 31.71% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 736.76 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 46.2% YoY to Rs 107.79 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA surged 38% YoY to Rs 129.24 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA margin expanded to 17.54% in Q3 FY26 as against 16.76% in Q3 FY25. The unexecuted order book stood at Rs 5,450 crore, up 47.86% YoY and down 0.4% QoQ. Headquartered in Ahmedabad, Transformer & Rectifiers (India) (TARIL) is a leading manufacturer of transformers and reactors. It caters to power generation, transmission, distribution, and industrial sectors on a B2B model. Its product portfolio spans single-phase power transformers up to 500 MVA and 1200 kV, furnace, rectifier, and distribution transformers, as well as specialty units for locomotive traction, solar applications, green hydrogen, and mobile substations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TRIL_80857453502_28340.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty settles below the 25,900 level; metal stocks witness significant sell-off]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-settles-below-the-25900-level-metal-stocks-witness-significant-sell-off/1663860</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663860</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fourth straight session, as investor sentiment remained under pressure from geopolitical tensions, the prospect of additional U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fourth straight session, as investor sentiment remained under pressure from geopolitical tensions, the prospect of additional U.S. tariffs, and mixed corporate earnings, which dampened risk appetite and outweighed isolated pockets of optimism across sectors. The Nifty settled below the 25,900 level. All the sectoral indices ended in the red with metal, oil & gas and PSU bank shares declined. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 780.18 points or 0.92% to 84,180.96. The Nifty 50 index dropped 263.90 points or 1.01% to 25,876.85. In four consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 1.84% while the Nifty fell 1.71%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 1.99% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.97%. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.53% to 10.60. The S&P BSE Private Banks Index (down 0.45%), the S&P BSE BANKEX (down 0.75%) and the S&P BSE Consumer Durables Index (down 0.76%) outperformed the benchmark S&P BSE Sensex. However, the S&P BSE Metal Index (down 3.34%), the S&P BSE Oil & Gas Index (down 3.15%) and the S&P BSE Power Index (down 2.92%) underperformed the benchmark S&P BSE Sensex. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.27% to 6.629 compared with previous session close of 6.611. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.857 compared with its close of 89.8700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.79% to Rs 136,924. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.01% to 98.74. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.46% to 4.158. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement rose 64 cents or 1.08% to $60.60 a barrel. Global Markets: The Dow Jones index futures were down 143 points, signaling a weak opening for U.S. equities today. European shares traded lower on Thursday as regional market jitters grow over U.S. President Donald Trump’s threat to annex Greenland. Asia-Pacific markets ended lower after Wall Street closed lower amid rising geopolitical tensions and comments from U.S. President Donald Trump. U.S. defense stocks fell after Trump said he “will not permit” defense companies to issue dividends or stock buybacks until they address his complaints about the industry, including executive pay packages and production issues. In U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day winning streak, falling 466 points, or 0.94%, to close at 48,996.08. The S&P 500 declined 23.89 points or 0.34% to end at 6,920.93, while the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite edged up 37.10 points or 0.16% to close at 23,584.28.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Startups and AI entrepreneurs are the co-architects of India’s future: PM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/startups-and-ai-entrepreneurs-are-the-co-architects-of-indias-future-pm/1663851</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663851</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi highlighted the importance of artificial intelligence in bringing about transformation in society during a roundtable with Indian AI Start-Ups.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi highlighted the importance of artificial intelligence in bringing about transformation in society during a roundtable with Indian AI Start-Ups. He noted that India will host the India AI Impact Summit next month, through which the country will play a major role in the technology sector. He highlighted that India is making efforts to bring about a transformation with & leveraging AI. Prime Minister emphasised that startups and AI entrepreneurs are the co-architects of India’s future and said that the country has immense capacity for both innovation and large-scale implementation. He added that India should present a unique AI model to the world that reflects the spirit of “Made in India, Made for the World.” Prime Minister further said that the world’s trust in India is the country’s biggest strength. He emphasised the need to ensure that Indian AI models are ethical, unbiased, transparent, and based on data privacy principles. He said startups should also work towards global leadership from India, and noted that India can promote affordable AI, inclusive AI, and frugal innovation globally. He also suggested that Indian AI models should be distinct and should promote local and indigenous content and regional languages.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/world-1195593__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1663847</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663847</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 25,965, a premium of 88.15 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,876.85 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 25,965, a premium of 88.15 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,876.85 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index tanked 263.90 points or 1.01% to 25,876.85. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.53% to 10.60. HDFC Bank, Tata Consultancy Services and ICICI Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index registers a drop of 3.40%, NIFTY Crashes  1.01% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-registers-a-drop-of-340-nifty-crashes-101/1663844</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663844</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index closed down 3.40% at 11132 today.

Nifty Metal index closed down 3.40% at 11132 today. The index has added 10.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Hindustan Zinc Ltd dropped 6.23%, Jindal Stainless Ltd shed 5.75% and Jindal Steel Ltd fell 5.69%. The Nifty Metal index has increased 31.00% over last one year compared to the 9.24% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Energy index has slid 2.89% and Nifty PSE index has dropped 2.48% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 1.01% to close at 25876.85 while the SENSEX has slid 0.92% to close at 84180.96 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id51_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 780 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,900 level; VIX spurts 6.53%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-780-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25900-level-vix-spurts-653/1663843</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663843</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fourth straight session, as investor sentiment remained under pressure from geopolitical tensions, the prospect of additional U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fourth straight session, as investor sentiment remained under pressure from geopolitical tensions, the prospect of additional U.S. tariffs, and mixed corporate earnings, which dampened risk appetite and outweighed isolated pockets of optimism across sectors. The Nifty settled below the 25,900 level. All the sectoral indices ended in the red with metal, oil & gas and PSU bank shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 780.18 points or 0.92% to 84,180.96. The Nifty 50 index dropped 263.90 points or 1.01% to 25,876.85. In four consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 1.84% while the Nifty fell 1.71%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 1.99% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.97%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,035 shares rose and 3,160 shares fell. A total of 171 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.53% to 10.60. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index declined 3.40% to 11,132. The index tanked 3.40% in the two consecutive trading session. Hindustan Zinc (down 6.4%), Jindal Stainless (down 6.07%), Jindal Steel (down 5.79%), Hindustan Copper (down 5.76%) and National Aluminium Company (down 5.53%), NMDC (down 5.35%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 3.79%), Hindalco Industries (down 3.75%), Welspun Corp (down 3.24%) and Vedanta (down 3.07%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services fell 4.29%. The company announced that it has entered into an agreement with Cubastion Consulting. Tata Steel fell 2.15%. The company’s India crude steel production stood at 6.34 million tons in Q3 FY26, up 12% QoQ and YoY, primarily aided by higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities. Meesho tanked 4.62% after its general manager- business, Megha Agarwal has tendered her resignation with effect from 7 January 2026. Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) fell 4.32%. The company has signed an MoU with the Government of Chhattisgarh to provide financial assistance of up to Rs 1 lakh crore over the next five years for housing and urban infrastructure development. Avantel fell 1.14%. The company announced that it had received a purchase order valued at Rs 11.19 crore from NewSpace India. Gland Pharma fell 1.19%. The company received an approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) filed for Olopatadine Hydrochloride Ophthalmic Solution USP, 0.7%. DEE Development Engineers surged 6.41% after the company reported an update on its order book for December 2025, showing steady inflows and execution across its core businesses. The company said its total order book stood at Rs 1,302.73 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 1,332.53 crore at the beginning of the month. Order inflows during December came in at Rs 98.11 crore, while execution during the month aggregated Rs 127.91 crore. Gujarat Pipavav Port declined 1.67% after the company reported a 1.69% drop in container volumes to 174,000 twenty-foot equivalent units (TEU) in Q3 FY26, compared with 177 TEUs recorded in Q3 FY25. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) declined 2.91%. The company said it has received a supply order from the Corps of Electronics and Mechanical Engineers (EME) of the Indian Army for overhaul, upgrade, and obsolescence management of the indigenous Pinaka Multi-Rocket Launcher Systems. Global Markets: The Dow Jones index futures were down 143 points, signaling a weak opening for U.S. equities today. European shares traded lower on Thursday as regional market jitters grow over U.S. President Donald Trump’s threat to annex Greenland. Asia-Pacific markets ended lower after Wall Street closed lower amid rising geopolitical tensions and comments from U.S. President Donald Trump. U.S. defense stocks fell after Trump said he “will not permit” defense companies to issue dividends or stock buybacks until they address his complaints about the industry, including executive pay packages and production issues. In U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day winning streak, falling 466 points, or 0.94%, to close at 48,996.08. The S&P 500 declined 23.89 points or 0.34% to end at 6,920.93, while the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite edged up 37.10 points or 0.16% to close at 23,584.28.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eimco Elecon climbs after Q3 PAT soars to Rs 12 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eimco-elecon-climbs-after-q3-pat-soars-to-rs-12-cr/1663839</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663839</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) soared 92.93% to Rs 16.11 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) soared 92.93% to Rs 16.11 crore during the quarter. Total expenses jumped 31.4% to Rs 52.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 40.26 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 30.18 crore (down 3.95% YoY) while compensation to distributors stood at Rs 7.19 crore (up 37.74% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the proposal for purchase of a parcel of land admeasuring approx. 35,056 square meters situated in Kanjari, District Kheda, Gujarat, on a freehold basis to support the company's future business outlook. Eimco Elecon (India) is principally engaged in the business of manufacturing of equipment for mining and construction sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EimcoEleconI_30262501893_2747.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Angel One client base climbs 21% YoY in Dec’25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/angel-one-client-base-climbs-21-yoy-in-dec25/1663840</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663840</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s client base also increased 1.8% month-on-month (MoM) in December 2025 from 35.08 million in November 2025.

The company’s client base also increased 1.8% month-on-month (MoM) in December 2025 from 35.08 million in November 2025. Gross client acquisition declined 12.8% YoY to 0.68 million in December 2025, compared with 0.78 million in December 2024. Angel One reported an Average Daily Turnover (ADTO), based on notional turnover, of Rs 53,37,400 crore in December 2025, reflecting a 0.2% MoM decline and an 83.9% YoY increase. The ADTO from the Futures & Options (F&O) segment stood at Rs 51,54,200 crore, registering a 0.4% MoM decline and an 82.1% YoY increase. Based on option premium turnover, the ADTO in the cash segment stood at Rs 6,700 crore in December 2025, down 8.2% MoM and 13.8% YoY. The commodity segment reported a higher ADTO of Rs 1,76,500 crore, marking an increase of 6.2% MoM and a sharp 178.2% YoY rise. Angel One is the largest listed retail stockbroking house in India in terms of active clients on NSE. The company provides brokerage and advisory services, margin funding, loans against shares, and distribution of third-party financial products to its clients. The brokerage and allied services are offered through online and digital platforms and a network of authorized persons. The company’s consolidated net profit dropped 49.98% to Rs 211.73 crore on a 20.56% fall in total revenue from operations to Rs 1,204.20 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter slipped 2.44% to Rs 2,412 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AngelBrokingLtd._94973857_38941.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prestige Group to acquire 16.38 acres of land in Chennai’s Padi Area]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prestige-group-to-acquire-1638-acres-of-land-in-chennais-padi-area/1663846</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663846</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The land parcel is strategically located near Anna Nagar, one of Chennai’s most established and prime residential micro-markets, known for its strong social infrastructure, excellent connectivity, and mature residential character.

The land parcel is strategically located near Anna Nagar, one of Chennai’s most established and prime residential micro-markets, known for its strong social infrastructure, excellent connectivity, and mature residential character. The acquisition aligns with Prestige Group’s strategy to strengthen its presence in high-quality urban locations while maintaining a disciplined approach to capital allocation. Prestige Group said it continues to evaluate well-located land acquisition opportunities across key markets to support its future residential and mixed-use development pipeline. Prestige Group is a diversified real estate developers, with a portfolio spanning residential, commercial, retail, hospitality, and integrated townships across major cities. As at June 2025, the Group has delivered 310 projects spanning 202 million square feet and currently has a pipeline of 130 projects across 199 million square feet. The scrip declined 1.91% to currently trade at Rs 1,587.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PrestigeEstates_5830476588_13212.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s import-cut, export-push and domestic manufacturing thrust is aimed at making it the world’s third-largest economy while enhancing self-relian]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-import-cut-export-push-and-domestic-manufacturing-thrust-is-aimed-at-making-it-the-worlds-third-largest-economy-while-enhancing-self-relian/1663836</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663836</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Minister Nitin Gadkari is pushing for a decisive shift in India's economic strategy trim imports, ramp up exports and promote fast-tracking of domestic manufacturing to position India as the world's third-largest economy.

Union Minister Nitin Gadkari is pushing for a decisive shift in India's economic strategy trim imports, ramp up exports and promote fast-tracking of domestic manufacturing to position India as the world's third-largest economy. He pitches that decreasing the dependence on imported products, especially crude oil and high-value components, would strengthen local industries, conserve foreign exchange, and give it much-needed resilience. He cites innovative ideas such as those of converting farm waste to bio-bitumen for road construction as one way to cut imports of crude oil while offering an ecological dividend in the bargain. India pursues trade diversification in view of negotiating free trade agreements, backing exporters for a break-in into new markets. Government efforts to support exporters participation in international fairs and incentives for MSMEs are continuously being pursued to widen India's presence in world trade.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/keyboard-338517__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aptus Pharma jumps 24% in six days]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aptus-pharma-jumps-24-in-six-days/1663834</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663834</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of Aptus Pharma surged 23.89% in ten trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 169.50 on 31 December 2025.

Shares of Aptus Pharma surged 23.89% in ten trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 169.50 on 31 December 2025. The stock hit an all-time high of Rs 210 today. On the BSE, 0.36 lakh shares have been traded so far, compared with an average daily volume of 0.50 lakh shares over the past two weeks. The stock had outperformed the market over the past month, rising 29.63% as against the Sensex's 0.88% drop. The stock had outperformed the market over the three months, rising 137.77% as against the Sensex's 3.15% jump. On the technical front, the stock's daily RSI (relative strength index) stood at 83.352. The RSI oscillates between zero and 100. Traditionally, the RSI is considered overbought when above 70 and oversold when below 30. On the daily chart, the stock was trading above its 50-day, 100-day, and 200-day simple moving average (SMA), placed at 80.80, 77.33, and 42.35, respectively. These levels will act as crucial support zones in the near term. Aptus Pharma is engaged in the business of marketing and distribution of finished pharmaceutical formulations. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 270% to Rs 2.96 crore on a 37.5% jump in net sales to Rs 24.56 crore in FY26 over FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/APTUSPHARMALIMITED_18727309_95582.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pound under pressure amid firm greenback overseas; GBP/INR futures slide under 122 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pound-under-pressure-amid-firm-greenback-overseas-gbpinr-futures-slide-under-122-mark/1663833</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663833</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Firmness in DXY overseas is adding pressure on GBP/USD pair on Thursday for the third straight day.

Firmness in DXY overseas is adding pressure on GBP/USD pair on Thursday for the third straight day. The pair is currently quoting lower by 0.20% at $1.3438. The greenback gained momentum after ISM reported on Wednesday that the US Services PMI rose to 54.4 in December from 52.6 in November. This figure came in stronger than the expectation of 52.3. JOLTS Job Openings came in at 7.146 million in November. Meanwhile, ADP Employment Change showed an increase of 41,000 jobs in December, following a revised decline of 29,000 in November. Investors now turn attention to weekly jobless claims due Thursday and the December employment report on Friday for further cues on possible Federal stance going ahead. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies was quoting at 98.55, up 0.12% on the day. On the NSE, GBP/INR futures are trading at lower by 0.36% at 121.09.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pearl Global Industries Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pearl-global-industries-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1663831</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663831</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Gokaldas Exports Ltd, Avanti Feeds Ltd and Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 08 January 2026.

SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Gokaldas Exports Ltd, Avanti Feeds Ltd and Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 08 January 2026. Pearl Global Industries Ltd lost 10.88% to Rs 1444 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 8623 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3457 shares in the past one month. SignatureGlobal India Ltd tumbled 10.00% to Rs 993.25. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2.51 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12934 shares in the past one month. Gokaldas Exports Ltd crashed 9.03% to Rs 622.3. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.7 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11240 shares in the past one month. Avanti Feeds Ltd dropped 8.40% to Rs 812. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 64997 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 47542 shares in the past one month. Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd fell 8.08% to Rs 279.15. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 9.09 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.6 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PearlGlobalInd_7533044884_27614.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems jumps 13% in ten days]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-jumps-13-in-ten-days/1663832</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663832</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems surged 13.46% in ten trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 79.05 on 24 December 2025.

Shares of R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems surged 13.46% in ten trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 79.05 on 24 December 2025. The stock hit an all-time high of Rs 89.75 today. On the BSE, 0.43 lakh shares have been traded so far, compared with an average daily volume of 0.50 lakh shares over the past two weeks. The stock had outperformed the market over the past month, rising 12.42% as against the Sensex's 0.88% drop. The stock had outperformed the market over the three months, rising 29.22% as against the Sensex's 3.15% jump. The counter had also outperformed the market in the past year, soaring 32.58% as against Sensex's 7.94% rise. On the technical front, the stock's daily RSI (relative strength index) stood at 83.352. The RSI oscillates between zero and 100. Traditionally, the RSI is considered overbought when above 70 and oversold when below 30. On the daily chart, the stock was trading above its 50-day, 100-day, and 200-day simple moving average (SMA), placed at 80.80, 77.33, and 42.35, respectively. These levels will act as crucial support zones in the near term. R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems manufactures micro irrigation systems. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 220.1% to Rs 5.73 crore on a 79.8% jump in net sales to Rs 31.18 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RMDripSprinklersSystemsLtd_34584827303_71578.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/manaksia-aluminium-company-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663826</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663826</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd, Yasho Industries Ltd, N K Industries Ltd and Goyal Aluminiums Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 08 January 2026.

NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd, Yasho Industries Ltd, N K Industries Ltd and Goyal Aluminiums Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 08 January 2026. Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd tumbled 11.13% to Rs 32.67 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 84546 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53611 shares in the past one month. NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd crashed 11.12% to Rs 33.88. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 23035 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19934 shares in the past one month. Yasho Industries Ltd lost 11.01% to Rs 1175.9. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3531 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 718 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd slipped 9.94% to Rs 61.9. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62 shares in the past one month. Goyal Aluminiums Ltd pared 9.82% to Rs 8.82. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.8 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManaksiaAlumi_41111727342_64845.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>