<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:45:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rubicon Research surges after Q3 PAT jumps 91% YoY to Rs 73 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rubicon-research-surges-after-q3-pat-jumps-91-yoy-to-rs-73-cr/1671247</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671247</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 70.42% YoY to Rs 90.58 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 70.42% YoY to Rs 90.58 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA stood at Rs 111.9 crore during the quarter, recording the growth of 59% compared with Rs 70.4 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved 23.5% in Q3 FY26 as against 22.3% in Q3 FY25. Revenue grew 52% year-on-year during the quarter, driven by broad-based performance. The top five products contributed 35% of total revenue in Q3 FY26, up from 30% in Q2 FY26 and 34% in Q1 FY26. Meanwhile, the top 10 products accounted for 53% of revenue, compared with 51% in Q2 FY26 and 56% in Q1 FY26. Reasearch & Development (R&D) expense climbed 100.38% to Rs 52.3 crore, compared with Rs 26.1 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. R&D expenses were 11.0% of operating revenue in Q3 FY26. In dollar terms, the revenue stood at $53 million in Q3 FY26, up 46% YoY. Approximately 98% of the revenue was denominated in US dollars. Meanwhile, the company’s board granted in-principle approval for the merger of KIA Health Tech, wholly owned subsidiary of the company, with Rubicon Research and their shareholders. Rubicon Research is a pharmaceutical formulations company focused on innovation-led research and development, with a growing portfolio of specialty products and drug–device combination offerings aimed at regulated markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RubiconResearchLtd_40373339_34163.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kansai Nerolac slides as Q3 PAT slumps 75% YoY to Rs 131 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kansai-nerolac-slides-as-q3-pat-slumps-75-yoy-to-rs-131-cr/1671246</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671246</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 3.53% to Rs 1,907.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,842.16 crore posted in the same quarter last year.

However, revenue from operations rose 3.53% to Rs 1,907.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,842.16 crore posted in the same quarter last year. EBITDA stood at Rs 247.8 crore, registering a marginally growth of 0.2% over the same quarter of the previous year. Profit before tax (PBT) in Q3 FY26 was Rs 174.28 crore, down 75.25% from Rs 707.28 crore reported in Q3 FY25. For the nine-month period, Kansai Nerolac Paints reported net revenue of Rs 5,865.79 crore, up 1.9% year-on-year. EBITDA stood at Rs 771.10 crore, down 3.2% compared with the same period last year, while PBT (before exceptional items) declined 4.0% to Rs 714.18 crore. PAT (after exceptional items) was recorded at Rs 498.99 crore. On its outlook, the Indian paint industry, valued at around Rs 77,500 crore as of March 2025, is poised for robust growth in the coming years. Expansion in infrastructure, core sectors, automobile, and real estate is expected to sustain demand for both industrial and decorative paints. Rising urbanization, modernization of commercial and residential spaces, and premiumization of paint products are likely to further strengthen the industry’s long-term growth trajectory. Pravin Chaudhari, MD, Kansai Nerolac Paints, said, “That industrial coatings recorded strong growth, driven primarily by the automotive segment. The recent GST rate cuts have boosted demand across various OEM categories. In the decorative segment, demand remained subdued due to a shorter festival season, but the company’s internal initiatives in projects, distribution, waterproofing, and construction chemicals helped sustain growth. Raw material prices remained stable, although the quarter experienced forex volatility and geopolitical uncertainty. Looking ahead, momentum in automotive and performance coatings is expected to continue, while recovery in decorative paints will remain gradual.” Kansai Nerolac is one of the leading paint companies in India and is the leader in Industrial paints. The company has eight strategically located manufacturing units all over India and a strong dealer network across the country. The company manufactures a diversified range of products ranging from decorative paints coatings for homes, offices, hospitals, and hotels to sophisticated industrial coatings for most of the industries.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KansaiNerolac_26092545928_200.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gokaldas Exports Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gokaldas-exports-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1671243</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671243</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sheela Foam Ltd, Kitex Garments Ltd, Indo Count Industries Ltd and Avanti Feeds Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 04 February 2026.

Sheela Foam Ltd, Kitex Garments Ltd, Indo Count Industries Ltd and Avanti Feeds Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 04 February 2026. Gokaldas Exports Ltd surged 17.29% to Rs 816.45 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 15.11 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 86031 shares in the past one month. Sheela Foam Ltd soared 15.73% to Rs 607.1. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3487 shares in the past one month. Kitex Garments Ltd spiked 13.30% to Rs 222.4. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 10.89 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.76 lakh shares in the past one month. Indo Count Industries Ltd exploded 13.09% to Rs 324.45. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 4.81 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17302 shares in the past one month. Avanti Feeds Ltd rose 12.30% to Rs 1078.75. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 5.73 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 75555 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GokaldasExports_17758090823_12966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India steps up mining of rare-earth minerals ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-steps-up-mining-of-rare-earth-minerals/1671242</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671242</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Minister of Coal and Mines, Kishan Reddy, has stated that Atomic Minerals Directorate for Exploration and Research (AMD), a constituent unit of DAE, is carrying out exploration and augmentation of minerals of rare earth group elements along the coastal and inland placer sands as well as in hard rock terrains in several potential geological domains of the country.

Minister of Coal and Mines, Kishan Reddy, has stated that Atomic Minerals Directorate for Exploration and Research (AMD), a constituent unit of DAE, is carrying out exploration and augmentation of minerals of rare earth group elements along the coastal and inland placer sands as well as in hard rock terrains in several potential geological domains of the country. While India has adequate rare-earth resources and capabilities for extraction and refining, commercial mining and processing of these minerals has been limited due to lack of adequate technology, absence of mid-stream and downstream industries in the REE value chain.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/mineral-oil-297487__340_crude_oil.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Kanishk Aluminium India slips on listing day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-kanishk-aluminium-india-slips-on-listing-day/1671211</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671211</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 58.40, a 20% discount to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 58.40, a 20% discount to the issue price. The stock was currently frozen at its lower limit of 5% to the listing price. The stock touched a high of Rs 58.40 and a low of Rs 55.48, with around 19,000 shares changing hands on the counter. Kanishk Aluminium India's IPO was subscribed 1.04 times. The issue opened for bidding on 28 January 2026 and it closed 30 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed at Rs 73 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 40,00,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter group shareholding diluted to 70.24% from 99.99% pre-issue. The company intends to utilise the net proceeds for repayment/prepayment, in full or part, of certain borrowings availed by the company, branding and promotion of Brand Baari by Kanishk and general corporate purposes. Kasturi Metal Composite manufactures a wide range of aluminium extrusion products, including solid and hollow profiles, solar profiles, railings, heat sinks, and aluminium doors and windows, serving industries such as electronics, automotive, solar, furniture, transport, electrical and architecture. Built on a focus on continuous improvement and operational excellence, the company expanded its portfolio in 2024 with the launch of its premium brand, Baari by Kanishk, which offers high-quality aluminium system doors and windows across multiple designs and configurations. As of 30 November 2025, the company had a total workforce of 46 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 29.18 crore and net profit of Rs 2.15 crore for the period ended 31 August 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KANISHKALUMINIUMINDIALIMITED_26909053_95751.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 225 pts; pharma shares decline ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-225-pts-pharma-shares-decline/1671209</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671209</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in the early afternoon as investors engaged in profit-booking following Tuesday’s sharp rally on Dalal Street spurred by the India–US trade deal.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in the early afternoon as investors engaged in profit-booking following Tuesday’s sharp rally on Dalal Street spurred by the India–US trade deal. Market caution was further reinforced by escalating geopolitical tensions between the U.S. and Iran, prompting participants to reassess near-term risk exposure. The Nifty traded below the 25,750 mark. Pharma shares declined after advancing for previous two consecutive trading sessions. At 11:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 224.60 points or 0.27% to 83,518.71. The Nifty 50 index shed 23.45 points or 0.09% to 25,704.10. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index shed 0.12% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.14%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,332 shares rose and 1,527 shares fell. A total of 200 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel will start its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday in the backdrop of growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation and more recently the long-awaited India-US trade deal ending prolonged uncertainty on the external front. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index fell 0.75% to 22,033.70. The index added 2.31% in the previous two consecutive trading session. Mankind Pharma (down 3.58%), Aurobindo Pharma (down 3.4%), Divis Laboratories (down 2.16%), Gland Pharma (down 2.1%) and Ajanta Pharma (down 1.86%), Piramal Pharma (down 1.01%), Torrent Pharmaceuticals (down 0.81%), Alkem Laboratories (down 0.69%), J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals (down 0.5%) and Lupin (down 0.29%) declined. On the other hand, Abbott India (up 1.02%) ,Laurus Labs (up 0.79%) and Cipla (up 0.73%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Axiscades Technologies hit an upper circuit of 5% after its subsidiary Mistral Solutions secured international contracts worth around $1.4 million from Axon Enterprise Inc. and Stratacache Inc., USA. Mahindra & Mahindra advanced 1.42% after the company announced that it has secured its largest-ever export order for 35,000 light commercial vehicles (LCVs) to be delivered to Agrinas Pangan Nusantara, Indonesia, in 2026. DAM Capital Advisors declined 4.55% after the company’s consolidated net profit dropped 61.1% to Rs 20.06 crore on a 32.8% drop in total income to Rs 69.94 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sheela Foam surged 18.50% after the company’s consolidated net profit soared 211.97% to Rs 52.13 crore on 11.1% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1,074.43 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asia market mostly fell Wednesday, tracking Wall Street losses after a sell-off in U.S. technology stocks weighed on sentiment. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back as investors dumped technology stocks and moved into shares more broadly linked to improvements in the economy. The broad market index fell 0.84% and closed at 6,917.81. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 166.67 points, or 0.34%, to end at 49,240.99. Earlier, the 30-stock index rose as much as 0.5% to touch 49,653.13, a new record. The Nasdaq Composite shed 1.43%, settling at 23,255.19.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Msafe Equipments stands tall after a solid listing pop]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-msafe-equipments-stands-tall-after-a-solid-listing-pop/1671188</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671188</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 144, a 17.07% premium to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 144, a 17.07% premium to the issue price. The stock was currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% to the listing price. The stock touched a high of Rs 151.20 and a low of Rs 136.80, with around 30.54 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Msafe Equipments' IPO was subscribed 153.98 times. The issue opened for bidding on 28 January 2026 and it closed on 30 January 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 116 to Rs 123 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 44,00,000 equity shares and offer for sale (OFS) of 10,00,000 equity shares by existing shareholders. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for funding of capital expenditure towards setup of a new manufacturing facility, funding of capital expenditure for manufacturing of equipment’s for rental purpose, utilization towards working capital requirements and for general corporate purpose. Ahead of the IPO, Msafe Equipments on 27 December 2025, raised Rs 1.75 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 1.43 lakh shares at Rs 123 per share to 8 anchor investor. Msafe Equipments manufactures, sells and rents access and height-safety equipment for working at elevated locations, with a product portfolio that includes aluminium and mild steel scaffoldings, aluminium ladders and fibre-reinforced plastic ladders. The company operates three manufacturing facilities in Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh, and is supported by 17 warehouses across key states, enabling efficient sales and rental operations. In FY25, Msafe supplied products across 22 states and three Union Territories, serving clients in construction, HVAC, MEP, electrical, fire safety, interior fit-out and warehousing segments. As of 31 December 2025, Msafe Equipments had a workforce of 350 permanent employees and 66 contractual staff. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 49.01 crore and net profit of Rs 10.50 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MsafeEquipmentsLimited_99194515_95841.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sheela Foam sizzles after reporting three-fold jump in Q3 profit to Rs 52 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sheela-foam-sizzles-after-reporting-three-fold-jump-in-q3-profit-to-rs-52-cr/1671187</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671187</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue growth during the quarter was driven by higher volumes across both mattress and foam segments.

Revenue growth during the quarter was driven by higher volumes across both mattress and foam segments. Mattress registered volume growth of 11% and foam segment grew by 20%. Profit before tax (PBT) surged 198.68% to Rs 65.68 crore during the quarter. Core EBITDA stood at Rs 117 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 39%, compared with Rs 84 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Core EBITDA margin improved 220 bps to 10.9% in Q3 FY26 as against .8.7% in Q3 FY25., Rahul Gautam (chairman & managing director) commenting on the results, he said that the Kurlon acquisition has begun delivering tangible benefits, driving a turnaround at Sheela Foam Limited. The business has entered a phase of double-digit growth, with both the mattress and foam segments recording strong volume expansion. Profitability and cash generation have continued to improve sequentially each quarter, supported by improved performance across all key markets - India, Australia, and Spain. We remain confident in our ability to deliver sustained, profitable growth backed by robust cash generation, thereby creating long-term value for all stakeholders. Sheela Foam is a leading player in India’s mattress and foam products industry and a leader in Polyurethane (PU) Foam. It has a nationwide presence in manufacturing PU Foam with a track record, since 1971. In India, the company markets its products under well-known brands such as Sleepwell and Kurlon.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SheelaFoamLtd_17308322593_26840.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ADF Foods spurts after Q3 PAT rises nearly 56% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adf-foods-spurts-after-q3-pat-rises-nearly-56-yoy/1671244</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671244</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company stated that the revenue growth was driven by traction from new listings and strengthening brand penetration across all key markets.

The company stated that the revenue growth was driven by traction from new listings and strengthening brand penetration across all key markets. EBITDA improved by 40.6% YoY to Rs 37.1 crore while EBITDA margin expanded by 150 basis points to 19.4% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 138.11 crore, up by 37.75% from Rs 100.26 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Bimal Thakkar, chairman & managing director, said: “Despite prevailing tariff challenges, our U.S. business continues to show substantial progress, benefiting from the enhancement of our sales force and strategic distributor level changes implemented at the beginning of CY2025. Our flagship brand Ashoka continues to strengthen its market presence, and our mainstream brand Truly Indian has exceeded expectations with a marked acceleration in its growth trajectory. We have successfully completed pilot runs at our upcoming Surat Greenfield facility, and Phase 1 is on track to become fully operational by Q4 FY26.” ADF is a consumer-focused Company and a leading manufacturer of prepared ethnic foods, offering frozen foods, ready-to-eat (RTE) items, ready-to-cook (RTC) items, sauces, pickles, pastes and dips under its 5 prominent brands.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ADFFoods_70843773898_2416.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Sheela Foam Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-sheela-foam-ltd-counter/1671183</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671183</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Firstsource Solutions Ltd, Mastek Ltd, Whirlpool of India Ltd, Brainbees Solutions Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 04 February 2026.

Firstsource Solutions Ltd, Mastek Ltd, Whirlpool of India Ltd, Brainbees Solutions Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 04 February 2026. Sheela Foam Ltd clocked volume of 1.26 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 32.9 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3832 shares. The stock gained 18.37% to Rs.620.95. Volumes stood at 3964 shares in the last session. Firstsource Solutions Ltd registered volume of 6.53 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 20.67 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 31581 shares. The stock slipped 1.76% to Rs.304.40. Volumes stood at 47586 shares in the last session. Mastek Ltd saw volume of 1.02 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.41 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 10792 shares. The stock dropped 1.69% to Rs.2,065.60. Volumes stood at 5818 shares in the last session. Whirlpool of India Ltd registered volume of 1.48 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 6.68 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 22179 shares. The stock rose 0.01% to Rs.791.00. Volumes stood at 17224 shares in the last session. Brainbees Solutions Ltd saw volume of 4.08 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 6.48 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 63012 shares. The stock dropped 0.41% to Rs.269.15. Volumes stood at 1.26 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SheelaFoamLtd_17308322593_26840.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axiscades Tech hits the roof on $1.4 mn multi-year international order win]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axiscades-tech-hits-the-roof-on-14-mn-multi-year-international-order-win/1671182</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671182</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the contracts are for design, development, and production, with an execution period of over one year.

The company said the contracts are for design, development, and production, with an execution period of over one year. Bengaluru-based Axiscades Technologies is an end-to-end technology and product engineering company operating across aerospace, defence and ESAI domains, with capabilities spanning the full product development lifecycle. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 88.82% year-on-year to Rs 23.13 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 12.25 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 12.97% YoY to Rs 299.06 crore. In dollar terms, revenue stood at $31.6 million, up 9.3% YoY.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AXISCADESEngg_38496178544_21304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shriram Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shriram-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1671153</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671153</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shriram Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Shriram Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Chandrashekhar Kadechkar has been appointed as the Head of Operations & Investor Relations Officer of the Asset Management Company with effect from January 29, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Mr. Chandrashekhar Kadechkar Age: 43 years Designation: Head of Operations & Investor Relations Officer Qualification: Bachelor of Commerce

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra rises on securing largest-ever export order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-mahindra-rises-on-securing-largest-ever-export-order/1671152</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671152</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said it will supply 35,000 units of Scorpio Pik Up vehicles to Agrinas Pangan Nusantara, an Indonesian state-owned enterprise, as part of the Koperasi Desa/Kelurahan Merah Putih (KDKMP) Project.

In an exchange filing, the company said it will supply 35,000 units of Scorpio Pik Up vehicles to Agrinas Pangan Nusantara, an Indonesian state-owned enterprise, as part of the Koperasi Desa/Kelurahan Merah Putih (KDKMP) Project. The vehicles will support logistics operations for cooperatives being established across the country. Under this partnership, Mahindra and Agrinas Pangan Nusantara will work together to equip Koperasi with robust and reliable vehicles to ensure the effective and seamless flow of fresh supplies from farmers directly to the marketplace, thereby bridging the gap between producers and consumers. The collaboration aims to strengthen rural logistics and enable villages to become independent centers of economic growth. Manufactured at the company’s Nashik plant, the Scorpio Pik Up is known for its durability, high payload capacity, and low operating costs, and is designed to operate efficiently across diverse rural terrains, including rough roads and farm tracks. The company said the Mahindra Scorpio Pik Up will bolster the Koperasi ecosystem by enabling first-mile aggregation, transporting produce from farms to cooperatives and facilitating intra-village logistics, thereby ensuring the efficient movement of goods within the cooperative network. Nalinikanth Gollagunta, CEO, Automotive Division, Mahindra & Mahindra, said, “We are looking forward to this association and to supporting Indonesia’s Koperasi through our partnership with Agrinas Pangan Nusantara. By deploying the Scorpio Pik Ups as a part of the Koperasi, we are strengthening a reliable logistics backbone that connects farmers to markets more efficiently. Our Pik Ups are engineered to perform in tough conditions while keeping operating costs to a minimum. The volume committed for this partnership will significantly boost our international operations, adding as much as our total export volumes achieved in FY 25. In line with Mahindra’s Rise philosophy, this collaboration reflects our commitment to enabling prosperity and supporting national priorities.” Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) Group enjoys a leadership position in farm equipment, utility vehicles, information technology, and financial services in India. It is the world's largest tractor company by volume. It has a strong presence in renewable energy, agriculture, logistics, hospitality and real estate. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit surged 17.7% to Rs 4,520.52 crore on a 21.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 33,421.60 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25, reflecting broad-based growth across Auto and Farm segments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Budget introduces structural reforms designed to grant taxpayers greater autonomy, says Revenue Secretary]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/budget-introduces-structural-reforms-designed-to-grant-taxpayers-greater-autonomy-says-revenue-secretary/1671108</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671108</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Budget 2026–27 introduces structural reforms designed to grant taxpayers greater autonomy and reduce their engagement with tax authorities, Revenue Secretary Arvind Shrivastava told industry leaders at a FICCI interactive session on the Union Budget 2026-27.

Union Budget 2026–27 introduces structural reforms designed to grant taxpayers greater autonomy and reduce their engagement with tax authorities, Revenue Secretary Arvind Shrivastava told industry leaders at a FICCI interactive session on the Union Budget 2026-27. Shrivastava said the reforms reflect the government’s conviction that taxpayers prefer compliance over disputes. The fundamental thought behind this is that we believe the general incentive with the taxpayer is to be honest, would rather like to pay his tax dues as long as he can appreciate those to be legitimate, he said. The budget extends the return filing revision period by three months and permits updated returns for four years. On indirect taxation, the government is expanding benefits under the Authorised Economic Operator scheme and shifting customs oversight from transaction-level approvals to entity-based audits. He noted that reforms to data centres and special economic zones aim to create a level playing field where tax structures do not disadvantage domestic industry. Tax treatment has been designed in a manner that is equitable and enables fair competition by ensuring a level playing field.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/euro-seem-money-finance_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under one scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/invesco-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-one-scheme/1671107</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671107</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund has announced 06 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the IDCW option of following scheme.

Invesco Mutual Fund has announced 06 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the IDCW option of following scheme. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) will be: Invesco India Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular IDCW Option & Direct IDCW Option: 0.15

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade sideways; IT shares slumps ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-sideways-it-shares-slumps/1671106</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671106</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the morning trade as sharp selling in IT stocks weighed on sentiment following an overnight technology-led rout in U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the morning trade as sharp selling in IT stocks weighed on sentiment following an overnight technology-led rout in U.S. markets. The weakness was compounded by profit-booking after the previous session’s strong India–US trade deal–driven rally, while escalating geopolitical tensions between the U.S. and Iran further dampened risk appetite and kept investors cautious. The Nifty traded above the 25,700 level, while IT shares tanked after advancing for previous trading session. At 10:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, shed 64.03 points or 0.08% to 83,677.57. The Nifty 50 index added 14.15 points or 0.05% to 25,741.70. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices.The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 0.19% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 0.13%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,439 shares rose and 1,259 shares fell. A total of 188 shares were unchanged. Earnings to Watch: Archean Chemical Industries, Apollo Tyres, Aptus Value Housing Finance India, Aurionpro Solutions, Automotive Axles, Avalon Technologies, Bajaj Finserv, Bajaj Holdings & Investment, Carysil, CCL Products (India), Century Plyboards (India), Cera Sanitaryware, Cummins India, Devyani International, Emami, Emcure Pharmaceuticals, Eureka Forbes, Force Motors, Gallantt Ispat, Greenply Industries, Hexaware Technologies, Inventurus Knowledge Solutions, Jain Irrigation Systems, Jaiprakash Power Ventures, JSW Cement, Jubilant Ingrevia, Kalpataru Projects International, Lloyds Engineering Works, Global Health, Metropolis Healthcare, NHPC, Parag Milk Foods, Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels, Pokarna, Quality Power Electrical Equipments, Redington, RITES, Rane (Madras), Keystone Realtors, Saatvik Green Energy, Sammaan Capital, Shipping Corporation of India Land and Assets, Tata Power Company, Transport Corporation of India, TeamLease Services, Tube Investments of India, Timken India, Tamilnad Mercantile Bank, Trent, Welspun Enterprises, Westlife Foodworld, Wonderla Holidays and Xpro India will announce their quarterly earnings today. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel will start its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday in the backdrop of growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation and more recently the long-awaited India-US trade deal ending prolonged uncertainty on the external front. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index tanked 5.69% to 36,414.25. The index rallied 1.41% in the previous trading session. IT stocks came under sharp pressure on Wednesday amid a global technology selloff after AI firm Anthropic unveiled new automation tools, stoking fears of AI-led disruption to traditional, licence-driven business models. Infosys (down 6.07%), Persistent Systems (down 5.7%), LTIMindtree (down 5.67%), Coforge (down 5.48%) and Tata Consultancy Services (down 5.26%), HCL Technologies (down 4.64%), Mphasis (down 4.59%), Tech Mahindra (down 4.48%), Wipro (down 3.58%) and Oracle Financial Services Software (down 3.23%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Sterling Tools declined 3.11% after the company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 88.5% to Rs 1.56 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 13.60 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 21.1% year-on-year to Rs 205.85 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Time Technoplast added 1.31% after the company's subsidiary PowerBuild Batteries announced a business collaboration and exclusive distribution agreement with Monbat AD, a leading European battery manufacturer based in Bulgaria. Bajaj Finance shed 0.21%. The company reported 6.33% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,977.85 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 4,246.54 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 17.63% YoY to Rs 21,213.89 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Budget offered a comprehensive and integrated policy framework to bolster entire textile value chain]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-budget-offered-a-comprehensive-and-integrated-policy-framework-to-bolster-entire-textile-value-chain/1671102</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671102</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Union Budget 2026-27 offered a comprehensive and integrated policy framework to bolster the entire textile value chain- from fibre to fashion, from village industries to global markets.

The Union Budget 2026-27 offered a comprehensive and integrated policy framework to bolster the entire textile value chain- from fibre to fashion, from village industries to global markets. With the objective of boosting competitiveness, fostering self-reliance and creating jobs, the Government has proposed an Integrated Programme for the textile sector, structured around five sub-components: National Fibre Scheme, Textile Expansion and Employment Scheme, National Handloom and Handicraft Programme, Tex-Eco Initiative and Samarth 2.0: An upgraded skilling programme. The Government has also announced the setting up of Mega Textile Parks in challenge mode, with a focus on providing integrated infrastructure, enabling scale efficiencies, and promoting value addition across the textile value chain. These parks are also expected to support the growth of technical textiles, a high-potential segment with applications in industrial, medical, defence, and infrastructure sectors. Further, to strengthen liquidity access for textile MSMEs, the Government has announced measures to enhance the effectiveness of the Trade Receivables Discounting System (TReDS), through which over Rs 7 lakh crore has already been facilitated. A dedicated Rs 10,000 crore SME Growth Fund has been introduced to support the creation of future “Champion SMEs.” The fund is poised to incentivise enterprises based on select criteria. The textile sector is the second-largest employment generator in India, after agriculture. As per the Economic Survey 2026-27, textiles industry has a 9% share in employment across 8 major industry groups. The recent policy push is towards scale and modernisation - integrated textile parks, support for MMF and technical textiles, investment incentives, and easing of raw-material constraints are all aimed at boosting competitiveness and value addition.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/clothing-1425542_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DAM Capital Advisors tanks after Q3 PAT drops 61% YoY to Rs 20 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dam-capital-advisors-tanks-after-q3-pat-drops-61-yoy-to-rs-20-cr/1671103</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671103</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax was at Rs 26.97 crore in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% as against the Rs 69.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax was at Rs 26.97 crore in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% as against the Rs 69.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 23.8% YoY to Rs 42.97 crore during the quarter. Finance costs stood at Rs 2.23 crore (up 502.7% YoY), and employee benefits expenses came in at Rs 29.75 crore (up 7.71% YoY). On the segmental front, revenue from stockbroking stood at Rs 17.62 crore (down 13.54% YoY), and investment banking stood at Rs 48.46 crore (down 39.69% YoY) during the period under review. Net cash available as of December 31, 2025, stood at Rs 309 crore vs Rs 241 crore as of December 31, 2024. Dharmesh Mehta, managing director & CEO of DAM Capital Advisors, said, "In Q3 FY26, the fundraising environment was very selective and challenging owing to the nervousness in the small- and mid-cap segments and macroeconomic uncertainties, both domestic and global. Despite the headwinds, during the quarter, we executed 5 transactions across products, including 2 IPOs, a QIP, a rights issue, and an M&A advisory mandate, and raised approximately Rs 4,376 crore, taking our cumulative ECM execution to 96 transactions since November 2019. This track record reinforces the strength of our franchise and our ability to deliver consistently across market cycles. We remain disciplined and selective in bringing strong, well-governed companies to the capital markets. This approach has helped us build and sustain a healthy pipeline of 22 IPO mandates, including 13 as left lead banker and 7 sole banker IPOs, along with multiple QIP mandates at various stages, providing strong visibility while keeping our focus firmly on quality of execution rather than chasing volumes. Institutional Equities revenue this quarter (Q3FY26) was stable compared to last quarter (Q2FY26). Weaker market conditions, however, can impact volumes going forward. Volatile market conditions have resulted in delays for a few of our mandates. We are hoping for better market conditions to execute our existing IPO pipeline. Given the inherent volatility and cyclical nature of capital markets, our business is best evaluated over a disciplined three-to-five-year investment horizon.” DAM Capital Advisors is an investment bank providing financial advisory services and capital market solutions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DamCapitalAdvisorsLtd_61485198_12067.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Finance Q3 PAT slumps 6% YoY to Rs 3,978 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-finance-q3-pat-slumps-6-yoy-to-rs-3978-cr/1671105</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671105</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bajaj Finance reported a 6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,977.85 crore despite 17.63% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 21,213.89 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajFin_55786316_3722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen slides past 156 ahead of Japan’s snap election]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-slides-past-156-ahead-of-japans-snap-election/1671096</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671096</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen slipped past 156 per dollar, extending its decline to a fourth straight session as markets brace for Japan’s snap lower house election.

The Japanese yen slipped past 156 per dollar, extending its decline to a fourth straight session as markets brace for Japan’s snap lower house election. Expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s LDP will expand fiscal spending and cut taxes have weighed on the yen and Japanese bonds, reviving concerns over debt-funded growth. Despite this week’s weakness, the yen has still gained over 1% in January, supported by rising global risk aversion that has periodically unwound carry trades. Meanwhile, the US dollar index hovered near 97.2, pausing its recent rally as a partial government shutdown delayed key labor market data, leaving investors cautious about the near-term outlook for the US economy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>