<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godfrey Phillips India posts steady Q3 FY26; PAT rises 8.7% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godfrey-phillips-india-posts-steady-q3-fy26-pat-rises-87-yoy/1669630</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669630</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a sequential basis, profit increased 12.6% from Rs 305 crore in Q2 FY26.

On a sequential basis, profit increased 12.6% from Rs 305 crore in Q2 FY26. Gross sales value for the quarter stood at Rs 4,737 crore, marking a 19.7% YoY increase and a 19.2% rise over the Q2 FY26 quarter. Net revenue rose 15.1% YoY to Rs 1,829 crore, compared with Rs 1,589 crore a year ago. Sequentially, net revenue jumped 41.9% from Rs 1,289 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA from operations came in at Rs 380 crore, up 5.3% YoY from Rs 361 crore in Q3 FY25. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, EBITDA increased 21.0% from Rs 314 crore. EBITDA margin stood at 8.0% in Q3 FY26, lower than 9.1% in the year-ago quarter and broadly unchanged from 7.9% in Q2 FY26. Cost of goods sold increased 16.6% YoY and 61.6% QoQ to Rs 1,115 crore, reflecting higher sales volumes. As a result, gross profit rose 12.8% YoY and 19.2% sequentially to Rs 714 crore. Gross margin stood at 15.1%, compared with 16.0% in Q3 FY25 and 15.1% in Q2 FY26. On the cost front, employee benefit expenses rose sharply by 36.8% YoY to Rs 119 crore, while other expenses increased 16.2% YoY to Rs 215 crore during the quarter. Godfrey Phillips India is engaged in manufacturing of cigarettes and tobacco products and trading of cigarettes, tobacco products and other retail products. Shares of Godfrey Phillips India rose 0.43% to settle at Rs 2035 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodfreyPhillips_19522234394_657.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITI MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/iti-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1669642</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669642</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITI Mutual Fund has announced 03 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following scheme.

ITI Mutual Fund has announced 03 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following scheme. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: ITI Balanced Advantage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.12 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.12 ITI Consumption Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.60 ITI Banking and Financial Services Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Flexi Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.60 ITI Focused Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Large Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI ELSS Tax Saver Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Multi Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Mid Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00 ITI Small Cap Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.60 ITI Value Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.00 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.00

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1669592</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669592</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced that, with effect from January 27, 2026, the Board of Directors of UTI Trustee Company Private Limited (Trustee to UTI Mutual Fund) has been reconstituted pursuant to the appointment of Mr.

UTI Mutual Fund has announced that, with effect from January 27, 2026, the Board of Directors of UTI Trustee Company Private Limited (Trustee to UTI Mutual Fund) has been reconstituted pursuant to the appointment of Mr. Ameet Pratapsinh Hariani as an Additional Director (Independent Category). Name: Mr. Ameet Pratapsinh Hariani Age: 65 years Designation: Additional Director (Independentategory) Qualification: B.Com, LLB, LLM

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1669561</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669561</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced that notice is hereby given to all investors and unit holders that, consequent to the appointment of Mr.

UTI Mutual Fund has announced that notice is hereby given to all investors and unit holders that, consequent to the appointment of Mr. Vetri Subramaniam as Managing Director & Chief Executive Officer of UTI Asset Management Company Limited, with effect from February 01, 2026, the following details shall form part of the Statement of Additional Information (SAI) of UTI Mutual Fund under the section titled “Details of AMC Directors.” Name: Mr. Vetri Subramaniam Age: 55 years Designation: Managing Director & Chief Executive Officer Qualification: 1. B. Com 2.Post Graduate Diploma in Management - IIM Bangalore

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Meesho posts wider losses despite strong revenue growth in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/meesho-posts-wider-losses-despite-strong-revenue-growth-in-q3-fy26/1669516</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669516</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter.

Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter. The company reported pre-tax loss of Rs 478.59 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a profit of Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenditure increased 43.99% YoY to Rs 4,060.20 crore in Q3 FY26, significantly outpacing revenue growth. Employee expenses rose 20.64% YoY to Rs 235.17 crore. Interest costs surged 141.61% YoY to Rs 3.89 crore, while depreciation declined 7.06% YoY to Rs 10.92 crore. Meesho's Annual Transacting Users surged 34% YoY to 251 million with net merchandise value (NMV) standing at Rs 10,995 crore, up 26% YoY. Over 9MFY26, it increased 37% YoY to Rs 30,189 crore. The company witnessed 690 million orders placed on its platform in the quarter under review, up 36% YoY. The contribution margin as a percentage of NMV stood at 2.3%, down 104 bps QoQ and 198 bps YoY due to accelerated Valmo scale-up following 3PL industry consolidation. "This is expected to normalise in the coming quarters," the company filing said. On a last twelve month basis, users transacted 9.78 times per year on average, growing 9% year-on-year, reflecting increasing purchase frequency. On a last twelve months basis, free cash flow stood at Rs 56 crore, supported by growth in NMV. As of 31 December 2025, Meesho's cash balance stood at Rs 7,277 crore, including Rs 4,088 crore raised through initial public offering in Dec FY26. Adjusted EBITDA marketplace margin for Q3FY26 was at -4.2% (Rs -460 crore) due to lower contribution margin and accelerated user growth and engineering investments. Adjusted EBITDA for New Initiatives was at Rs 19 crore, up 44% QoQ and 30% YoY with continuous improvement in user adoption for financial services platform. In a letter to the shareholders, Founder & CEO Vidit Aatrey said that the company has increased its investment into Advertising & Sales Promotion to 2.4% of NMV in Q3 FY26 from 1.3% of NMV in Q3 FY25. The company expects significant improvement in Adjusted EBITDA margin in the next two quarters returning to Q1 FY26 levels; driven by logistics cost recovery and operating leverage on user growth and technology investments made in FY26. The company said: "This marks our first quarter reporting as a public company and demonstrates our operating philosophy in action: continued growth in ATUs towards our mission of democratising internet commerce, and when forced to choose between near-term financial optimisation and long-term flywheel health, we chose the latter. We held order fulfillment charges stable, and increased user acquisition. Each decision positions us for stronger platform profitability in the long-term. These investments met our return thresholds; measured through payback periods, expected IRR against hurdle rates, and impact on long-term Free Cash Flow. 251 million ATUs, 9.78 purchase frequency, and 37% NMV growth for 9M FY26 validate such decisions made 12-18 months ago. Results lag strategy by several quarters in platform businesses. The growth we are capturing today compounds Meesho into a leadership position in value-led e-commerce over the next decade." Meesho is India’s largest e-commerce platform by annual transacting users and placed orders. Shares of Meesho rose 3.39% to settle at Rs 173.95 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MeeshoLtd_15936426_77963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MPS acquires US-based Unbound Medicine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mps-acquires-us-based-unbound-medicine/1669418</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669418</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The acquisition will be executed through MPS North America LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of MPS.

The acquisition will be executed through MPS North America LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of MPS. The transaction is expected to be completed on or before 10 February 2026, subject to the fulfilment of customary closing conditions, the company said in a regulatory filing. The acquisition will be carried out for a cash consideration of $16.50 million, subject to customary adjustments. Founded in 1999, Unbound Medicine provides digital medical reference tools, clinical decision-support solutions and healthcare learning platforms. Its services are delivered through proprietary mobile and web-based platforms and follow a subscription-led institutional business model. The company serves medical schools, hospital systems and healthcare associations across the United States and Canada. MPS said the acquisition aligns with its strategy of building platform-led, recurring-revenue businesses. The transaction is expected to support revenue diversification, enable cross-selling opportunities and strengthen the company’s presence in the North American market. MPS provides learning and platform solutions combining content, technology and artificial intelligence. The company is focused on scaling operations and strengthening its position in the global learning and knowledge services market. On a consolidated basis, net profit of MPS rose 57.32% to Rs 55.44 crore while net sales rose 9.42% to Rs 194.44 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. Shares of MPS rose 3.46% to settle at Rs 1884.80 on Friday, 30 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MPS_88654356883_18868.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>