<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:28:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta jumps as broker reiterates 'buy', raises target to Rs 806]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-jumps-as-broker-reiterates-buy-raises-target-to-rs-806/1664841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664841</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a note to investors, the broker highlighted that Vedanta is nearing the final stage of obtaining statutory clearances for its planned demerger into five separate listed entities.

In a note to investors, the broker highlighted that Vedanta is nearing the final stage of obtaining statutory clearances for its planned demerger into five separate listed entities. The move is expected to unlock significant shareholder value by distinctly valuing its diversified asset base. The brokerage also pointed to robust commodity prices, ongoing cost reduction efforts and volume growth as tailwinds for the company’s earnings. On the back of higher commodity price assumptions, it raised Vedanta’s EBITDA estimates for financial years 2027 and 2028, factoring in stronger profitability. The brokerage now forecasts Vedanta's EBITDA to grow at a compounded annual growth rate (CAGR) of about 20% between FY25 and FY28. The note further observed that Vedanta’s current market price does not fully reflect the value of its aluminium and zinc businesses, while other key businesses are trading at valuations implying limited value, offering potential upside as clarity around the demerger and earnings trajectory improves. Vedanta is a global producer of critical minerals, energy transition metals, power, and technology, with operations across India, South Africa, Namibia, Liberia, the UAE, Saudi Arabia, Korea, Taiwan, and Japan. It is the world’s largest integrated zinc producer, the fourth-largest silver producer, and among the top aluminum producers globally. Vedanta is also India’s only private oil and gas producer and one of the country’s largest private power generators. The company’s consolidated revenue rose 6% YoY to Rs 39,218 crore in Q2 FY26, up from Rs 37,171 crore in Q2 FY25. However, profit after tax (PAT) declined 38% YoY to Rs 3,479 crore, compared to Rs 5,603 crore in Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tokyo Plast International reports dismal Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tokyo-plast-international-reports-dismal-q3-performance/1664839</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664839</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s revenue from operations declined 10% to Rs 17.14 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 19.05 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year.

The company’s revenue from operations declined 10% to Rs 17.14 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 19.05 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Pre-tax loss for the quarter stood at Rs 0.03 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to a profit before tax of Rs 0.10 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses declined 9.39% YoY to Rs 17.18 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 18.96 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of materials consumed was Rs 11.08 crore, up 0.36% YoY. Employee benefit expenses were up 8.65% at Rs 4.27 crore versus Rs 3.93 crore a year earlier. Tokyo Plast International manufactures thermo food containers and coolers. Shares of Tokyo Plast International shed 0.94% to Rs 105 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TokyoPlastInternationalLtd_60698755021_4159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MoSPI undertaking base revision exercise of the Index of Industrial Production]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mospi-undertaking-base-revision-exercise-of-the-index-of-industrial-production/1664837</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664837</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Ministry of Statistics and Programme Implementation (MoSPI) is undertaking the base revision exercise of the Index of Industrial Production (IIP).

The Ministry of Statistics and Programme Implementation (MoSPI) is undertaking the base revision exercise of the Index of Industrial Production (IIP). In the process, MoSPI is revisiting methodologies, exploring new data sources and incorporating changes after comprehensive consultations with the experts, academicians, users and other stakeholders. Traditionally, the IIP has been compiled using a fixed-base Laspeyres framework, in which sectoral and industry weights remain unchanged until a base-year revision. However, with production shifts in response to demand, technology, and policy changes, some industries expand, while others decline or disappear, and entirely new industries or production lines within an industry emerge. Therefore, fixed weights become progressively less relevant and thus affects the efficacy of the indices. The chain-based method of compilation of IIP offers better accuracy by capturing these changes by allowing the increase and decrease in weights annually to correctly reflect a more recent production structure. To facilitate stakeholder engagement on this topic, MoSPI has prepared a Discussion Paper 2.0: Adoption of Chain-Based Index of Industrial Production (IIP) which outlines the proposed methodology for chain-linked indices. MoSPI has invited views and comments from experts, academicians, Central government Ministries/ departments, State governments, financial institutions and other stakeholders on the proposed methodology.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id4664857_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI invites public comments on Draft Amendment Directions on ‘Clarification on Owned Fund / Tier 1 Capital computation for NBFCs / ARCs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-invites-public-comments-on-draft-amendment-directions-on-clarification-on-owned-fund-tier-1-capital-computation-for-nbfcs-arcs/1664836</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664836</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RBI had invited public comments on Draft Amendment Directions on ‘Clarification on Owned Fund / Tier 1 Capital computation for NBFCs / ARCs and applicability to “Credit / Investment Concentration” Norms’.

RBI had invited public comments on Draft Amendment Directions on ‘Clarification on Owned Fund / Tier 1 Capital computation for NBFCs / ARCs and applicability to “Credit / Investment Concentration” Norms’. The comments on the said Draft Amendment Directions are invited from the stakeholders till January 28, 2026. Currently, NBFCs (other than NBFC-UL) and ARCs reckon Tier 1 Capital as on March 31 of the previous year for complying with Credit / Investment concentration norms. RBI has been receiving requests from NBFCs for a review of these provisions as well as for clarification on certain aspects of Owned Fund / Tier 1 Capital. Accordingly, RBI has reviewed the relevant provisions / Directions / guidelines and has proposed clarifications and revisions in the matter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-accountant-financial-papers-analysis-charts-pict_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trade above 25,750 mark; metal shares shine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trade-above-25750-mark-metal-shares-shine/1664838</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664838</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks erased early losses and traded with marginal gains in mid-morning trade amid heightened volatility.

Domestic equity benchmarks erased early losses and traded with marginal gains in mid-morning trade amid heightened volatility. Although it was a non-expiry session, volatility appeared to persist. The early market remained on the negative side due to persistent foreign fund outflows and elevated crude oil prices, which continued to weigh on sentiment despite steady corporate earnings growth. However, buying interest in metal and oil & gas stocks supported the rebound. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark, while metal shares extended gains for the third consecutive trading session. At 11:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 82.04 points or 0.10% to 83,709.73. The Nifty 50 index rose 39.10 points or 0.15% to 25,770.15. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.24% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.36%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,953 shares rose and 1,811 shares fell. A total of 215 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 23,08,833 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:25 IST on Wednesday (14 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.08 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 41 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index surged 3.02% to 11,697.60. The index rallied 5.43% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Vedanta (up 5.93%), Hindustan Zinc (up 5.41%), Hindustan Copper (up 3.74%), Tata Steel (up 3.65%), National Aluminium Company (up 3.39%), Steel Authority of India (up 2.98%), Jindal Steel (up 2.76%), Hindalco Industries (up 2.15%), NMDC (up 2.05%) and APL Apollo Tubes (up 1.54%) advanced. On the other hand, Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 0.30%) and Welspun Corp (down 0.01%), turned lower. Stocks in Spotlight: NLC India advanced 3.02% after the company signed Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Government of Gujarat for development of large-scale renewable energy (RE) projects. Garment Mantra Lifestyle rallied 4.35% after the company said it has achieved export sales of Rs 100 crore in the current financial year, marking the highest-ever export performance since its inception. Oswal Pumps rose 1.43% after the company received an LoA worth Rs 119.92 crore from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development for the supply and installation of 3,263 off-grid DC solar pumping systems across Karnataka. Global Markets: Asian markets traded mixed even as Japanese indexes hit record highs on Wednesday. The rally in Japanese stocks was fuelled by expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi could call for a snap election, likely in February. If called, it will be Takaichi’s first time facing Japan’s voters in an election. Overnight in the U.S., all three major indexes fell as investors grappled with volatility from a flurry of proposals from U.S. President Donald Trump floated in the past few days. The S&P 500 dipped 0.19% as investors sold JPMorgan despite better-than-expected numbers, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.8%. The Nasdaq Composite fell 0.1%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Polycab India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-polycab-india-ltd-counter/1664828</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664828</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bata India Ltd, Biocon Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Max Financial Services Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 14 January 2026.

Bata India Ltd, Biocon Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Max Financial Services Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 14 January 2026. Polycab India Ltd clocked volume of 8.35 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 63.27 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 13203 shares. The stock lost 2.28% to Rs.7,397.00. Volumes stood at 21247 shares in the last session. Bata India Ltd registered volume of 53946 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.18 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 5878 shares. The stock slipped 0.28% to Rs.905.40. Volumes stood at 5542 shares in the last session. Biocon Ltd registered volume of 5.65 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 6.36 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 88828 shares. The stock rose 1.03% to Rs.381.20. Volumes stood at 2.12 lakh shares in the last session. Go Digit General Insurance Ltd saw volume of 23620 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.03 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4699 shares. The stock dropped 4.29% to Rs.324.40. Volumes stood at 5848 shares in the last session. Max Financial Services Ltd notched up volume of 1.02 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.4 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 23060 shares. The stock slipped 0.26% to Rs.1,642.10. Volumes stood at 95781 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PolycabIndiaLtd_84608181_26603.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sundaram MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sundaram-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1664829</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664829</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced 16 January 2026 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes.

Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced 16 January 2026 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) will be: Sundaram Aggressive Hybrid Fund - Regular Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.250 Sundaram Aggressive Hybrid Fund - Direct Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.350 Sundaram Balanced Advantage Fund - Regular Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.115 Sundaram Balanced Advantage Fund - Direct Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.140

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NLC India gains after inking MoU with Gujarat govt to build RE projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nlc-india-gains-after-inking-mou-with-gujarat-govt-to-build-re-projects/1664826</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664826</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The non-binding MoU envisages the development of solar, wind, hybrid and battery energy storage (BESS) projects, with an aggregate investment potential of approximately Rs 25,000 crore and generation of substantial employment opportunities.

The non-binding MoU envisages the development of solar, wind, hybrid and battery energy storage (BESS) projects, with an aggregate investment potential of approximately Rs 25,000 crore and generation of substantial employment opportunities. The proposed projects shall be developed through the company’s wholly owned subsidiary, NLC India Renewables (NIRL). The strategic collaboration aligns with the NLC India’s corporate plan to achieve 10 GW of renewable energy capacity by 2030. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the listing of NLC India Renewables (NIRL), in line with the Government of India’s National Monetisation Pipeline targets. The listing will be carried through dilution of equity stake up to 25% in one or more tranches through public offer. NLC India is a public sector undertaking that is involved in lignite mining, coal mining, power generation and power trading. Government of India held 72.20% stake in the company as on 30 September 2025. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 27.1% to Rs 665.12 crore despite 14.2% jump in net sales to Rs 4,178.41 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NLCIndia_49674266520_2303.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jio BlackRock Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jio-blackrock-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1664827</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664827</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jio BlackRock Mutual Fund has been announced that Mr.

Jio BlackRock Mutual Fund has been announced that Mr. Virendra Kumar has been appointed as Fund Manager – Equity and is designated as Key Personnel of Jio BlackRock Asset Management Private Limited (“the AMC”) with effect from December 23, 2025. Details of Mr. Virendra Kumar Age: 39 years Designation: Fund Manager – Equity Qualification: • Master of Science (Integrated), Mathematics and Scientific Computing, IIT Kanpur, 2012 • Certificate in Quantitative Finance (CQF), 2025

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Garment Mantra Lifestyle jumps after clocking record Rs 100 crore export sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/garment-mantra-lifestyle-jumps-after-clocking-record-rs-100-crore-export-sales/1664824</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664824</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing on January 14, the Tamil Nadu-based apparel maker said the milestone reflects its successful transition into an export-focused textile and garment player, backed by rising acceptance of its products in international markets, particularly the Gulf region and the Middle East.

In a regulatory filing on January 14, the Tamil Nadu-based apparel maker said the milestone reflects its successful transition into an export-focused textile and garment player, backed by rising acceptance of its products in international markets, particularly the Gulf region and the Middle East. The company attributed the performance to consistent focus on quality manufacturing, product innovation, timely execution and strong customer relationships. It added that its modern manufacturing facilities, skilled workforce and efficient supply chain have enabled it to scale exports while maintaining stringent quality and compliance standards. Garment Mantra also said its export business has not been materially impacted by recent changes in US tariff policies, citing a diversified market presence and product mix. With adequate working capital in place, the company said it remains confident of sustaining growth in its export business while focusing on long-term value creation. Garment Mantra Lifestyle, formerly Junction fabrics & apparels, is engaged in the manufacture and wholesale of apparel and textiles, with operations spanning both domestic and export markets. On a consolidated basis, Garment Mantra Lifestyle's net profit surged 288.24% to Rs 2.64 crore while net sales rose 87.86% to Rs 65.02 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JunctionFabrics_76191600408_65916.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oswal Pumps rises after securing Rs 120-cr solar pump order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oswal-pumps-rises-after-securing-rs-120-cr-solar-pump-order/1664823</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664823</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the design, manufacture, supply, transportation, installation, testing, and commissioning of surface and submersible solar agriculture pump sets with capacities ranging from 3 HP to 10 HP at identified farmers’ sites under Component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme.

The project involves the design, manufacture, supply, transportation, installation, testing, and commissioning of surface and submersible solar agriculture pump sets with capacities ranging from 3 HP to 10 HP at identified farmers’ sites under Component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme. The scope also includes a complete system warranty, repair and maintenance, and a remote monitoring system (RMS) for five years. Installation, commissioning, RMS integration, and submission of invoices and related documents are scheduled to be completed in line with MNRE timelines, on or before 31 March 2026. The contract period extends up to five years from the installation and commissioning of the last pump under the agreement. Oswal Pumps manufactures solar-powered and grid-connected submersible and monoblock pumps, electric motors comprising induction and submersible motors, and solar modules, which it sells under the ‘Oswal’ brand. The company's consolidated net profit jumped 48.24% to Rs 97.50 crore on a 73.90% increase in revenue to Rs 539.64 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OswalPumpsLtd_50250161_39908.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1664821</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664821</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 14 January 2026.

Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 14 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) Bandhan Gold ETF Gold Portion: Mr. Abhishek Jain Debt portion: Mr. Brijesh Shah Mr. Abhishek Jain Bandhan Silver ETF Silver Portion: Mr. Abhishek Jain Debt portion: Mr. Brijesh Shah Mr. Abhishek Jain

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices pare early gains; Nifty slides below 25,700 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-pare-early-gains-nifty-slides-below-25700-level/1664820</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664820</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Headline equity indices pared early gains and traded marginally lower in morning trade, weighed down by persistent foreign fund outflows and elevated crude oil prices, which dampened investor sentiment despite steady corporate earnings growth.

Headline equity indices pared early gains and traded marginally lower in morning trade, weighed down by persistent foreign fund outflows and elevated crude oil prices, which dampened investor sentiment despite steady corporate earnings growth. The Nifty traded below the 25,700 level. Realty shares witnessed selling pressure for the seventh consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 198.72 points or 0.24% to 83,428.97. The Nifty 50 index fell 54.75 points or 0.21% to 25,676.80. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.19% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.08%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,657 shares rose and 1,898 shares fell. A total of 194 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Infosys (up 0.41), HDFC AMC (up 1.04), ICICI Prudential AMC (down 0.22), Union Bank of India (down 0.21), Billionbrains Garage Ventures (Groww) (down 0.37), Anand Rathi Share and Stock Brokers (down 0.27), Aditya Birla Money (down 0.43), Den Networks (up 0.13), HDB Financial Services (down 0.74), Indian Overseas Bank (up 0.99), Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals (up 1.03), Network 18 Media & Investments (up 0.29), Plastiblends India (up 2.56), Indosolar (up 2.49) and Waaree Renewable Technologies (down 1.35) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 1.53% to 844.80. The index dropped 7.91% in the seven consecutive trading sessions. Prestige Estates Projects (down 2.31%), SignatureGlobal India (down 1.94%), Phoenix Mills (down 1.82%), Lodha Developers (down 1.79%), Brigade Enterprises (down 1.53%), Godrej Properties (down 1.28%), DLF (down 1.18%), Oberoi Realty (down 0.79%), Sobha (down 0.69%) and Anant Raj (down 0.36%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Responsive Industries fell 1.73% after the company announced the resignation of Bhavneet Singh Chadha from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) and key managerial personnel of the company due to personal reasons. Mini Diamonds India added 1.10% after the company said it has received an order worth Rs 14 crore from Aura Diamond, a Mumbai-based domestic entity, for the supply of lab-grown polished diamonds.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Elxsi slides as Q3 PAT decline 45% YoY to Rs 109 cr  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-elxsi-slides-as-q3-pat-decline-45-yoy-to-rs-109-cr/1664793</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664793</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 1.52% to Rs 953.47 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 939.17 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

However, revenue from operations rose 1.52% to Rs 953.47 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 939.17 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 146.27 crore, down by 42.82% from Rs 255.84 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA dropped by 9.89% YoY to Rs 222.2 crore in the third quarter of FY26. EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 was 23.3% as against 26.3% in Q3 FY25. The company's total headcount in Q3 of FY26 stood at 11,594. Attrition rate stood at 15.6% in Q3 FY26 as compared to 12.4% in Q3 FY25. On the segmental front, revenue from software development and services stood at Rs 930.33 crore in Q3 FY26, reflecting a 1.26% jump year-on-year. Meanwhile, revenue from system integration and support services was Rs 23.13 crore, up 12.88% year-on-year during the same period. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, the company’s net profit fell 29.66%, while revenue from operations rose 3.85% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax was 146.27 crore in Q3 FY26, down 31.87% as against Rs 214.71 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA stood at Rs 222.2 crore in Q3 FY26, up 14.95% as against Rs 193.3 crore in Q2 FY26. The company’s EBITDA margin improved to 23.3% in Q3 FY26 from 21.1% in Q2 FY26. Tata Elxsi reported a one-time exceptional charge of Rs 95.69 crore in Q3 FY26 due to the implementation of the New Labour Codes effective November 21, 2025. The charge reflects higher employee benefit provisions under Ind AS 19, with the company noting that any further impact from pending rules will be accounted for once notified. Manoj Raghavan, CEO and managing director (MD) of Tata Elxsi, said, “The company reported operating revenue of Rs 953.5 crore in Q3 FY26, up 3.9% quarter-on-quarter, led primarily by growth in the transportation business. He said accelerated ramp-ups in software-defined vehicle (SDV) deals and normalisation of programmes with a strategic OEM supported performance during the quarter. The company also won a new programme from a US-based off-highway OEM for the development of a complex operator information and control system. Raghavan said Europe and the US led regional growth, with broad-based traction across key accounts and verticals. While the Media & Communications and Healthcare & Life Sciences verticals were impacted by seasonal furloughs and delayed deal closures, he expressed confidence in recovery from Q4 FY26. In healthcare, Tata Elxsi secured a multi-million, multi-year deal with a European MedTech major to transform regulatory workflows using GenAI-powered solutions, and also won a large deal for a next-generation drug delivery system. In telecom, the company was selected by a major European telco as a strategic partner for a three-year autonomous network transformation, leveraging its NEURON platform. Raghavan said EBITDA rose 220 basis points QoQ to Rs 222.2 crore, driven by operational excellence, delivery efficiencies and improved utilisation. He added that Tata Elxsi continues to invest in GenAI and AI-led innovation across verticals and enters the final quarter of the financial year with confidence, backed by a strong deal pipeline, large wins and a design-led, AI-enabled engineering proposition.” Tata Elxsi is amongst the world’s leading providers of design and technology services across industries including Automotive, Broadcast, Communications, Healthcare and Transportation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataElxsi_727602529_2322.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[World Bank raises India growth forecast to 7.2% for FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/world-bank-raises-india-growth-forecast-to-72-for-fy26/1664779</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664779</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The World Bank on Tuesday raised India's growth projection to 7.2 percent in fiscal year (FY) 2025/26 (April 2025 to March 2026), as domestic demand has remained robust, reflecting strong private consumption, supported by earlier tax reforms and improvements in real household earnings in rural areas.

The World Bank on Tuesday raised India's growth projection to 7.2 percent in fiscal year (FY) 2025/26 (April 2025 to March 2026), as domestic demand has remained robust, reflecting strong private consumption, supported by earlier tax reforms and improvements in real household earnings in rural areas. Alongside resilient services exports, merchandise exports rose in November, despite increases in U.S. import tariffs on many Indian goods. Growth in India is projected to slow to 6.5 percent in FY2026/27. Despite higher tariffs on certain exports to the United States—which accounts for about 12 percent of India’s merchandise exports— the growth forecast has remained unchanged relative to June projections, primarily because adverse impacts of higher tariffs will be offset by stronger momentum in domestic demand and more resilient exports than previously anticipated. Growth is set to inch up to 6.6 percent in FY2027/28, underpinned by robust services activity, as well as a recovery in exports and a pickup in investment, it said in the latest Global Economic Prospects.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Coking Coal ends with subscription of 146.87 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-coking-coal-ends-with-subscription-of-14687-times/1664780</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664780</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 50,95,55,58,000 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer.

The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 50,95,55,58,000 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 146.87 times. The Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 310.81 times, the Non-Institutional Investors category was subscribed 258.16 times, and the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 49.33 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 January 2026, and it closed on 13 January 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. The offer had been a pure offer-for-sale (OFS) of up to 46.57 crore equity shares of face value Rs 10 each by Coal India. At the upper price band of Rs 23 per equity share, Coal India had raised Rs 1,071 crore. The IPO had included a reservation of up to 2.32 crore equity shares for eligible employees and up to 4.66 crore shares for eligible shareholders of Coal India under the shareholder reservation portion. Ahead of the IPO of Bharat Coking Coal on 8 January 2026, the company raised Rs 273.13 crore from anchor investors by allotting 11.87 crore shares at Rs 23 each to 15 anchor investors. Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) produces coking coal, non-coking coal, and washed coal. BCCL is India's largest producer of coking coal and operates primarily in the Jharia coalfields of Jharkhand and the Raniganj coalfields of West Bengal. It is the wholly owned subsidiary of Coal India and was conferred with Mini Ratna status in 2014. The primary product is coking coal, catering to the steel and power industries. BCCL had an estimated coking coal reserve of approximately 7,910 million tonnes (mt) as of 01 April 2024. It accounted for 58.50% of the total domestic coking coal production in India in FY 2025. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 123.88 crore and sales of Rs 5,659 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[5paisa Capital slides as Q3 PAT tumbles 24% YoY to Rs 12 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/5paisa-capital-slides-as-q3-pat-tumbles-24-yoy-to-rs-12-cr/1664763</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664763</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operations fell 7.02% YoY to Rs 79.28 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total revenue from operations fell 7.02% YoY to Rs 79.28 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Total expenses declined 1.51% to Rs 62.80 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 63.76 crore in Q3 FY25. Finance costs rose 51.76% YoY to Rs 8.21 crore, while employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 22.34 crore, up 17.33% YoY during the period under review. Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 16.53 crore in Q3 FY26, down 23.29% from the Rs 21.55 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The company stated that it onboarded 0.78 lakh new clients during the quarter, taking the total number of registered customers to 50.8 lakh. Gaurav Seth, managing director & CEO of 5paisa Capital, said, “Q3 FY26 was an excellent quarter for investors, with the Nifty and Sensex touching all-time highs, supported by strong DII participation and improvement in Exchange ADTO and industry MTF book. We also delivered strong growth in our ADTO, up 24% QoQ, along with improvement in our MTF book. With continued focus on quality customer acquisition, enhancing customer experience through product and technology, and cost optimization, a PAT of Rs 12.3 crore resulted, reflecting a 30% QoQ growth along with margins of 15%. We will continue to remain in a growth phase, supported by healthy momentum across core metrics, and will continue investing in technology upgrades and AI integration to accelerate growth.” 5paisa Capital is engaged in providing financial products through its online technology platform and mobile applications. The company provides an online technology platform to clients through internet terminals and mobile applications for trading in securities in NSE and BSE. It is registered with SEBI as a stockbroker, depository participant, and research analyst, and with AMFI as a mutual fund distributor.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/5PaisaCapitalLtd_47826712_68848.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T's heavy civil infrastructure vertical bags 'large' order in Maharashtra]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lts-heavy-civil-infrastructure-vertical-bags-large-order-in-maharashtra/1664758</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664758</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Saidongar-1 pumped storage project (PSP) will comprise ten units of 300 MW each, taking its total capacity to 3000 MW.

The Saidongar-1 pumped storage project (PSP) will comprise ten units of 300 MW each, taking its total capacity to 3000 MW. The scope of the contract includes design, engineering and execution of all civil and hydro mechanical jobs associated with the project. With this order, L&T will play a pivotal role in bringing to life a project of immense significance – expected to enhance grid reliability and energy security for Maharashtra and beyond. L&T stated that pumped storage projects like Saidongar-1 are vital to ensuring grid stability and meeting peak power demand. “This order is a testament to L&T’s unmatched capability in delivering complex hydroelectric/pumped storage projects of national importance. With a track-record of engineering excellence, timely execution and world-class safety standards, the Saidongar-1 PSP reinforces L&T’s position as a trusted partner for large-scale, high-capacity pumped storage solutions,” the company stated. According to L&T’s classification, the value of this contract lies between Rs 2,500 crore and Rs 5,000 crore. L&T is a diversified EPC major operating across infrastructure, energy, hydrocarbons, defence, manufacturing and services in India and overseas. The company reported a 15.6% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Puravankara soars after Q3 sales value climbs 17% YoY to Rs 1,414-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/puravankara-soars-after-q3-sales-value-climbs-17-yoy-to-rs-1414-cr/1664723</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664723</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s collections climbed 22% YoY to Rs 1,140 crore in Q3 FY26.

The company’s collections climbed 22% YoY to Rs 1,140 crore in Q3 FY26. Sales area stood at 1.49 million square feet (msft) in Q3 FY26, up 4% compared with 1.43 msft in Q3 FY25. Average realization increased 12% YoY to Rs 9500 per sq.ft during the quarter. During the quarter, the company handed over 1.23 msft, delivering 1,116 homes. The company said that India’s macroeconomic momentum remained strong in Q2 FY26, with real GDP growth of around 8.2% YoY, leading the RBI to upgrade its FY26 growth outlook to 7.3%. While residential housing demand moderated in Q3 FY26, declining by approximately 16% YoY in volume terms. In contrast, the commercial real estate segment remained resilient, with leasing activity rising about 15% QoQ. Bengaluru led leasing absorption with a around 24% share, followed by Mumbai at approximately 22% and Delhi-NCR at around 18%, underscoring the continued strength of office demand in India’s key metros. Ashish Puravankara, managing director, Puravankara, said, “In 9MFY26, we made significant progress in expanding our portfolio, adding over 12.76 msft of potential developable area with an estimated GDV of approximately Rs 13,900 crore. These include marquee acquisitions across Bengaluru and Mumbai, such as a 53.5-acre land parcel in Anekal Taluk, Bengaluru; large-scale partnerships in North and East Bengaluru; and redevelopment projects at Malabar Hill and Chembur. Our focus remains on disciplined execution and value creation through strategic expansion in high-demand micro-markets In Q3FY26, we continued the growth momentum, driven substantially by sustenance sales, achieving pre-sales of Rs 1,414 crore and collections of Rs 1,140 crore, both improving year-on-year. This performance underscores the continued trust of our customers and the strength of our brand across markets.” Meanwhile, the company received letter of intent from Starworth Infrastructure & Construction for the construction of the proposed residential project, Sattva AANGANE, having approximate built-up area of 30,36,458 Sq. ft. at East Taluk, Bangalore. The contract value is approximately Rs 311.18 crore and it will be executed within 37 months. The Puravankara Group is one of India's most trusted realty majors, headquartered in Bengaluru with a pan-India presence. Over the past five decades, the company has established three distinct and successful residential brands – Puravankara, Provident Housing (PHL), and Purva Land - catering to the entire spectrum of housing and plotted development needs. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 41.79 crore in Q2 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 16.78 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales jumped 30% year on year to Rs 644.20 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Puravankara_83213463793_25459.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR continues to linger around Rs 90 per dollar ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-continues-to-linger-around-rs-90-per-dollar/1664724</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664724</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee continues to linger around Rs 90 per dollar mark in opening trades on Wednesday, tracking weakness in domestic equities on sustained foreign fund outflows.

The Indian rupee continues to linger around Rs 90 per dollar mark in opening trades on Wednesday, tracking weakness in domestic equities on sustained foreign fund outflows. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty ended with modest losses on Tuesday on the back of tariff concerns, some weak earnings announcements and sustained selling by foreign institutional investors. However, in its latest Global Economic Prospects report, the World Bank has revised its India's FY26 growth to 7.2 percent and projected 6.5 percent growth for FY27. INR opened at Rs 90.26 per dollar and briefly edged higher to 89.94 before slipping back to 90.13 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee ended lower at 90.23.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>