<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Anand Rathi Wealth incorporates subsidiary in GIFT City ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/anand-rathi-wealth-incorporates-subsidiary-in-gift-city/1678278</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678278</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The subsidiary will set up a fund management entity to undertake fund management activities through alternate investment fund (AIF).

The subsidiary will set up a fund management entity to undertake fund management activities through alternate investment fund (AIF). It will apply for fund management license under International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA) (Fund Management) Regulations, 2025. The company has subscribed to 100% of the share capital of Anand Rathi FME (IFSC), acquiring 10,000 equity shares of Rs 10 each for cash consideration of Rs 1,00,000. Anand Rathi Wealth is among India’s leading wealth management firms, catering to high and ultra-high-net-worth individuals with a unique and differentiated client strategy. The company reported 29.6% rise in net profit to Rs 100.1 crore on a 22.2% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 289.6 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The counter rose 0.09% to Rs 3001.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Anand-Rathi-Wealth_80898926_67729.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[The Anup Engineering Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/the-anup-engineering-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678276</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678276</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd, Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd and Engineers India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 17 February 2026.

Hindustan Copper Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd, Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd and Engineers India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 17 February 2026. The Anup Engineering Ltd crashed 4.67% to Rs 1793 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 14028 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14024 shares in the past one month. Hindustan Copper Ltd tumbled 4.66% to Rs 547.7. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 20.53 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 51.65 lakh shares in the past one month. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd lost 4.29% to Rs 259.7. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.65 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 93838 shares in the past one month. Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd shed 4.15% to Rs 540.4. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.06 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.04 lakh shares in the past one month. Engineers India Ltd slipped 3.97% to Rs 217.75. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 47.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7.43 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TheAnupEngg_12732804_73498.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Naksh Precious Metals Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/naksh-precious-metals-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678273</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678273</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shiva Mills Ltd, Semac Construction Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd and Indowind Energy Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 17 February 2026.

Shiva Mills Ltd, Semac Construction Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd and Indowind Energy Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 17 February 2026. Naksh Precious Metals Ltd lost 9.85% to Rs 5.49 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 11799 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7771 shares in the past one month. Shiva Mills Ltd crashed 9.32% to Rs 54.77. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 180 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 789 shares in the past one month. Semac Construction Ltd tumbled 8.42% to Rs 244.05. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 8 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 750 shares in the past one month. Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd corrected 7.97% to Rs 5.43. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6399 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11334 shares in the past one month. Indowind Energy Ltd plummeted 7.85% to Rs 11.03. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 68547 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 67238 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VaksonsAutomob_57424103445_66072.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KNR Constructions jumps after winning Rs 2,163-cr ECR elevated corridor project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/knr-constructions-jumps-after-winning-rs-2163-cr-ecr-elevated-corridor-project/1678274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678274</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project spans from Km 11+480 to Km 11+800 (West Avenue Road) and up to Km 24+780 (Thiruvanmiyur to Uthandi) on SH-49, strengthening the company’s presence in the road infrastructure segment.

The project spans from Km 11+480 to Km 11+800 (West Avenue Road) and up to Km 24+780 (Thiruvanmiyur to Uthandi) on SH-49, strengthening the company’s presence in the road infrastructure segment. The project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM) with a construction period of 1,095 days and an operation period of five years from the commercial operation date (COD). The signing of the concession agreement is subject to the outcome of W.A. No. 284 of 2026 pending before the Madras High Court. Once completed, the corridor is expected to improve traffic flow and connectivity along the ECR, reinforcing KNR Constructions’ position in large-scale infrastructure projects. KNR Constructions is engaged in the business of infrastructure sector, primarily in the construction of roads, bridges, flyovers and irrigation projects. The company’s consolidated net profit tanked 58.6% to Rs 102.80 crore on 12.4% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 743.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KNRConstruct_79641670773_28334.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Group stocks gain after $100 billion AI infrastructure push]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-group-stocks-gain-after-100-billion-ai-infrastructure-push/1678272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678272</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Adani Energy Solutions gained 2.59%, Adani Enterprises rose 2.44%, Adani Green Energy advanced 2.14%, and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone climbed 1.57%.

Adani Energy Solutions gained 2.59%, Adani Enterprises rose 2.44%, Adani Green Energy advanced 2.14%, and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone climbed 1.57%. Adani Total Gas added 0.80%, while Adani Power rose 0.67%. The Adani Group will invest $100 billion to develop green energy-backed, hyperscale AI-ready data centres, in what it described as one of the world’s largest integrated energy-compute commitments. The initiative is expected to catalyse an additional $150 billion across manufacturing, servers and sovereign cloud services over the next decade, creating a projected $250 billion AI infrastructure ecosystem. The group said the investment will expand its existing 2 GW national data centre platform under AdaniConnex toward a 5 GW capacity target. The infrastructure will integrate renewable power generation, transmission networks and high-density AI compute facilities within a unified architecture. The announcement also builds on partnerships with global technology players, including Google and Microsoft, and an expanded collaboration with Flipkart to develop additional AI-focused data centre capacity. A portion of GPU capacity will be reserved for Indian AI startups and research institutions to support domestic innovation. The proposed rollout is aligned with India’s push for technological self-reliance and data sovereignty, with the group positioning the initiative as a long-term energy and compute backbone for the country’s AI ecosystem.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniEnterp_85164503493_4244.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 124 pts; FMCG shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-124-pts-fmcg-shares-advance/1678269</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678269</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade. Nifty traded a tad above the 25,700 level after hitting the day's low of 25,570.30 in early trade. FMCG shares extended gains for the second consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 123.77 points or 0.15% to 83,400.92. The Nifty 50 index rose 3.50 points or 0.03% to 25,702.20. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.11% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.74%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,391 shares rose and 1,680 shares fell. A total of 194 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s total exports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $80.45 billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17% vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $90.83 billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76% vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $720.76 billion registering a positive growth of 6.15%. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $823.41 billion registering a growth of 6.54%. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were $36.56 billion as compared to $36.34 billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were $71.24 billion as compared to $59.77 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is $43.90 billion as compared to $34.75 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is $19.60 billion as compared to $16.71 billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy & poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports increased by 10.37% from $9.42 billion in January 2025 to $10.40 billion in January 2026, while petroleum products exports increased by 8.55% from $3.48 billion in January 2025 to $3.77 billion in January 2026. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index rose 0.72% to 51,690.90. The index rose 1.55% in the two consecutive trading sessions. United Spirits (up 1.36%), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (up 1.24%), Tata Consumer Products (up 0.93%), Emami (up 0.77%), Godrej Consumer Products (up 0.75%), Varun Beverages (up 0.68%), Patanjali Foods (up 0.64%), Dabur India (up 0.49%) and Radico Khaitan (up 0.42%) rose. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.40% to 6.641 compared with the previous session close of 6.668. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7150 compared with its close of 90.7400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 1.28% to Rs 152,780. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 97.13. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.81% to 4.019. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 32 cents or 0.47% to $68.07 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Delhivery jumped 3.05% after the company announced a strategic partnership with electric mobility startup RIDEV (ANV Web Ventures) to deploy 150 high-performance electric vehicles (EVs) across India over the next three months. Refex Industries rose 0.24%. The company said that it has secured an order worth Rs 49.22 crore from a Mini Ratna public sector undertaking (PSU).

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude stays in rangebound mode]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-stays-in-rangebound-mode/1678267</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678267</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures are holding around $63 per barrel in tight moves.

WTI crude oil futures are holding around $63 per barrel in tight moves. Markets continue to eye tensions escalate between the United States (US) and Iran ahead of renewed nuclear talks in Geneva. Chinese markets are shut due to New Year holiday and US stocks were closed yesterday as well due to a public holiday, making it an overall lacklustre session for oil. Focus will now shift to the US weekly supplies data. MCX Crude oil futures are trading at Rs 5719 per barrel, down 1.24% on the day, struggling after a weak open. WTI Crude oil soared around 13% in last month but shed around 3% this month so far.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-on-the-north-sea-picture-id48328_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Newgen Software Technologies Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-newgen-software-technologies-ltd-counter/1678263</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678263</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cochin Shipyard Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Ola Electric Mobility Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 17 February 2026.

Cochin Shipyard Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Ola Electric Mobility Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 17 February 2026. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd recorded volume of 394.09 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 36.82 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10.70 lakh shares. The stock gained 13.59% to Rs.526.00. Volumes stood at 13.16 lakh shares in the last session. Cochin Shipyard Ltd witnessed volume of 37.06 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.54 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4.92 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.60% to Rs.1,522.30. Volumes stood at 3.51 lakh shares in the last session. Go Digit General Insurance Ltd notched up volume of 20.79 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.89 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.53 lakh shares. The stock slipped 0.50% to Rs.330.55. Volumes stood at 6.38 lakh shares in the last session. Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd registered volume of 11.75 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 3.17 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.71 lakh shares. The stock rose 2.64% to Rs.489.80. Volumes stood at 25.55 lakh shares in the last session. Ola Electric Mobility Ltd registered volume of 1205.51 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 2.93 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 411.46 lakh shares. The stock slipped 3.05% to Rs.27.95. Volumes stood at 853.59 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewgenSoftwareTechnologiesLtd_46602882106_13722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godawari Power gains after Crisil Ratings revises rating outlook to 'Positive’ ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godawari-power-gains-after-crisil-ratings-revises-rating-outlook-to-positive/1678264</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678264</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The rating on the short-term bank facilities has been reaffirmed at 'Crisil A1+’.

The rating on the short-term bank facilities has been reaffirmed at 'Crisil A1+’. Crisil Ratings stated that the outlook revision reflects the expected improvement in the business risk profile of the company, driven by increase in revenue and higher backward integration. The expansion of the iron ore pellet facility to 4.7 million tonne per annum (MTPA) from 2.7 MTPA in December 2025 is expected to support increase in revenue. Furthermore, receipt of environmental clearance for expansion of the captive iron ore mining capacity at the Ari Dongri mines from 2.35 MTPA to 6.0 MTPA, with production expected to commence by the end of fiscal 2026, will enhance backward integration and reduce dependence on external suppliers. To expand its core business and new ventures, the company is expected to undertake capital expenditure (capex) of Rs 3,500 crore in this fiscal and the next, wherein it will expand its crushing and beneficiation capacity, set up a cold rolled mill complex, expand solar plant for captive use and enter the battery energy storage system (BESS) segment. These projects will be funded through internal accrual and debt of Rs 1,000-1,200 crore. The agency noted that the completion of the ongoing capex plans will strengthen the business risk profile and profitability, driven by increase in scale of operations and integrated operations. The company's strengths are partially offset by exposure to cyclicality in the steel industry and project risk, associated with capex planned over the medium term. Crisil Ratings will monitor any deviation from the expected growth plans and leverage position. Godawari Power and Ispat has two captive iron ore mines, a pellet plant and a vertically integrated steel plant in Raipur. The steel plant manufactures sponge iron, billets, MS rounds, HB wires, ferroalloys and pre-fab structures. For the first nine months of fiscal 2026, the company had reported revenue of Rs 3,770 crore and EBITDA of Rs 814 crore, as against Rs 3,908 crore and Rs 880 crore, respectively, during the corresponding period of the previous fiscal.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodawariPowerIspatLtd_38426015_26838.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1678249</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678249</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3479.9, down 0.85% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.21% on the day, quoting at 25736.1. The Sensex is at 83529.31, up 0.3%.Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd has eased around 4.85% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.79% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28028.2, up 0.36% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 13.37 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 28.56 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3489.1, down 0.58% on the day. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd jumped 24.73% in last one year as compared to a 12.16% rally in NIFTY and a 28.92% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 28.4 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Inox Wind Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inox-wind-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1678250</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678250</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Inox Wind Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Inox Wind Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 100.34, down 0.84% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.21% on the day, quoting at 25736.1. The Sensex is at 83529.31, up 0.3%.Inox Wind Ltd has eased around 10.2% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Inox Wind Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 6.52% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36386.75, down 0.13% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 111.53 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 98.3 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 100.26, down 1.16% on the day. Inox Wind Ltd tumbled 37.86% in last one year as compared to a 12.16% rally in NIFTY and a 17.8% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 26.9 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InoxWind_85471052866_43989.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindalco-industries-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1678251</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678251</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Hindalco Industries Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 891.2, down 1.79% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.21% on the day, quoting at 25736.1. The Sensex is at 83529.31, up 0.3%.Hindalco Industries Ltd has lost around 5.19% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Hindalco Industries Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.99% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11955, down 1.09% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 45.01 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 73.95 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 893.4, down 1.8% on the day. Hindalco Industries Ltd jumped 45.75% in last one year as compared to a 12.16% rally in NIFTY and a 43.23% spurt in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 23.42 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindalcoInds_40254437488_252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,700 level; PSU bank shares jump; VIX slumps 5.34%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25700-level-psu-bank-shares-jump-vix-slumps-534/1678252</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678252</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the afternoon trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,700 level. PSU bank, IT and consumer durables shares advanced, while metal, oil & gas and private bank shares advanced. At 13:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 247.35 points or 0.30% to 83,524.50. The Nifty 50 index added 61.55 points or 0.24% to 25,744. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.28% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.83%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,494 shares rose and 1,523 shares fell. A total of 198 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 5.34% to 12.62. Economy: India’s total exports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $80.45 billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17% vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $90.83 billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76% vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $720.76 billion registering a positive growth of 6.15%. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $823.41 billion registering a growth of 6.54%. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were $36.56 billion as compared to $36.34 billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were $71.24 billion as compared to $59.77 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is $43.90 billion as compared to $34.75 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is $19.60 billion as compared to $16.71 billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy & poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports increased by 10.37% from $9.42 billion in January 2025 to $10.40 billion in January 2026, while petroleum products exports increased by 8.55% from $3.48 billion in January 2025 to $3.77 billion in January 2026. Gainers & Losers: Infosys (up 3.77%), HCL Technologies (up 2.52%), Bharat Electronics (up 2.43%), Adani Enterprises (up 2.29%) and Wipro (up 2.25%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Kwality Wall's (down 4.79%), Eternal (down 2.58%), Trent (down 1.76%), Hindalco Industries (down 1.70%) and Shriram Finance (down 1.70%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Highway Infrastructure soared 6.82% after the company said it has secured a contract from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for toll operations on key stretches of the Vadodara–Mumbai Expressway in Gujarat. Infosys advanced 2.83% after the company announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic, an AI safety and research company, to develop and deliver advanced enterprise AI solutions to companies across industries. Cochin Shipyard advanced 4.27% after the state-run shipbuilder said it was declared the lowest bidder at a meeting held at the Ministry of Defence in New Delhi. TVS Supply Chain Solutions (TVS SCS) added 2.81% after the firm signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with ALA Group, to explore opportunities in India’s aerospace and defence supply chain. Lupin added 1.39% after the company announced that it has signed a licence and supply agreement with Spektus Pharma to commercialize the novel antidepressant DeslaFlex in Canada. Global Markets: European equities opened lower on Tuesday as investors keep an eye on earnings. Asian markets traded cautiously amid holiday-thinned volumes, while oil prices edged higher ahead of U.S.–Iran nuclear negotiations set to begin later today in Geneva. The Mainland Chinese, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan, and South Korean markets were closed on Tuesday for Lunar New Year holidays. U.S. markets were shut on Monday for Presidents’ Day. Japan’s weakening economy remained in focus on Tuesday, one day after much softer than expected GDP numbers. The country on Monday reported its economy grew an annualized 0.2% in the fourth quarter, far below the widely reported gain forecast of 1.6% as government spending dragged on activity. In today's session, the Japanese yen strengthened 0.15% against the greenback to 153.28 per dollar. The weak figures highlight the challenges ahead for Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and should support her push for more aggressive fiscal stimulus, media reports said. The Bank of Japan next meets on rates in March, with traders forecasting only a slim chance for a hike. Widely reported polls in the media suggest that investors expect the central bank to wait until July before tightening policy again. Meanwhile, oil saw some price gains as investors looked ahead to the U.S. and Iran nuclear negotiations that are scheduled to begin in Geneva later in the day. The higher volatility in crude was triggered by the latest drill that was reportedly held by Iran’s Revolutionary Guards in the Hormuz Strait on Monday. The passage accounts for about 20% of global oil shipments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Delhivery climbs after joining hands with RIDEV to deploy 150 EVs across India ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/delhivery-climbs-after-joining-hands-with-ridev-to-deploy-150-evs-across-india/1678247</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678247</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company will deploy EVs across North East India, Bengaluru, and Hyderabad, marking a significant step in the company’s roadmap to scale green logistics.

The company will deploy EVs across North East India, Bengaluru, and Hyderabad, marking a significant step in the company’s roadmap to scale green logistics. The collaboration introduces a specialized "EV-as-a-Service" leasing model designed to accelerate the transition for Delhivery’s delivery partners. By eliminating high upfront costs and technical barriers, the model ensures that the shift to an electrified last-mile ecosystem is both operationally seamless and financially lucrative for the gig workforce. This partnership signals a move toward a nationwide, systematic replacement of traditional internal combustion engine (ICE) vehicles. The initiative follows a successful pilot in Delhi-NCR and Bengaluru, where the transition to RIDEV’s electric two-wheelers resulted in the reduction of 4,260 Kg of CO2 and lowering daily operational costs for riders by more than 50%. Following the current rollout, a phased expansion is planned for major hubs, including Mumbai, Pune, Chennai, and Goa, aiming to eliminate tailpipe emissions and align with India’s PM E-DRIVE objectives for a cleaner transportation future. Prashant Gazipur, senior vice president of last mile operations at Delhivery, said, “Electrification is a fundamental shift in our approach to last-mile logistics, our partnership with RIDEV is a transformative step in our journey toward sustainable last-mile operations. By providing our delivery partners with a low-friction entry into electric mobility, we are not only advancing our carbon neutrality goals but also significantly enhancing the economic well-being of our riders through reduced operational overheads," Manish Kumar Jain, founder, RIDEV, said, “Integrating our tech-backed fleet into Delhivery’s network accelerates the transition to green logistics while simplifying daily work for the gig economy, our platform allows riders to focus on performance while we manage the complexities of energy and maintenance.” Delhivery is India's largest fully-integrated logistics services provider. With its nationwide network covering over 18,850 pin codes, the company provides a wide range of logistics services such as express parcel transportation, PTL freight, TL freight, cross-border, supply chain, and technology services. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 58.5% to Rs 39.61 crore on 17.9% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2,804.99 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/delhivery-ltd_88412953_68151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Groww Mutual Fund launches BSE Hospitals ETF, FOF to tap India’s healthcare growth story]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/groww-mutual-fund-launches-bse-hospitals-etf-fof-to-tap-indias-healthcare-growth-story/1678246</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678246</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Groww Mutual Fund has launched two passive investment schemes — the Groww BSE Hospitals ETF and the Groww BSE Hospitals ETF Fund of Fund (FOF) — providing investors with targeted exposure to India's organised hospital sector through the BSE Hospitals Index.

Groww Mutual Fund has launched two passive investment schemes — the Groww BSE Hospitals ETF and the Groww BSE Hospitals ETF Fund of Fund (FOF) — providing investors with targeted exposure to India's organised hospital sector through the BSE Hospitals Index. The new fund offer (NFO) for both schemes is currently open and will close on February 25, with allotment scheduled for 5 March 2026. The Groww BSE Hospitals ETF is an open-ended exchange traded fund that seeks to track the BSE Hospitals Index – Total Return Index (TRI) by investing in index constituents in the same proportion, subject to tracking error. The Groww BSE Hospitals ETF FOF, meanwhile, is an open-ended fund of fund scheme that will invest in units of the underlying ETF. The BSE Hospitals Index comprises listed hospital companies selected from the BSE 1000 universe and follows a rules-based, diversified methodology, with periodic rebalancing to reflect sectoral changes. The launch comes amid structural tailwinds for the healthcare sector. India’s healthcare expenditure is projected to rise from around 2.9% of GDP in 2018 to nearly 5% by 2030, supported by rising incomes, lifestyle-related diseases, expanding insurance coverage and policy support. Hospitals account for nearly 74% of the country’s healthcare ecosystem, placing them at the centre of demand growth across emergency care, surgeries and specialised treatments. India also faces a significant infrastructure gap, with only 1.62 hospital beds and 0.73 doctors per 1,000 people, well below global averages. This shortfall is driving capacity additions and private investment in the sector. Companies within the index have reported strong financial performance, with revenue roughly doubling and profits growing nearly fivefold between FY20 and FY25, reflecting improved occupancy, better case mix and operating leverage. The BSE Hospitals Index has outperformed the Nifty 50 TRI over medium- and long-term periods, aided by steady earnings growth and relatively defensive characteristics. Increased government spending on healthcare, rising public share in total health expenditure and expansion of medical education and insurance coverage are further expected to support long-term hospital utilisation. The schemes are positioned for investors seeking long-term capital appreciation through a passive, index-based approach to India’s expanding healthcare and hospital services segment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/hospital-bc-laboratory-form-with-syringe-1-1315580_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cigarette stocks gain on reports of ITC price hikes ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cigarette-stocks-gain-on-reports-of-itc-price-hikes/1678245</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678245</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The reported increases are seen as sufficient to offset the recent excise duty impact, while also adding to EBIT per stick, with stronger-than-expected hikes observed across nearly half of ITC’s portfolio.

The reported increases are seen as sufficient to offset the recent excise duty impact, while also adding to EBIT per stick, with stronger-than-expected hikes observed across nearly half of ITC’s portfolio. ITC gained 2.03% on the bourses, although the stock remains down 20.35% over the past three months. Godfrey Phillips India advanced 2.85%, even as it has declined 29.38% over the past three months. Cigarette prices rose sharply from February 1 following the imposition of additional excise duty. From February 2026, cigarettes and tobacco products are subject to additional excise duty and cess over and above the highest 40% GST slab, replacing the earlier structure of 28% GST plus compensation cess. The Central Excise Act has also been amended to levy a per-stick excise duty on cigarettes, with rates linked to cigarette length, altering the cost structure for manufacturers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITC_29088800077_301.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IndusInd Bank Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indusind-bank-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1678242</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678242</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IndusInd Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

IndusInd Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 943.8, up 1.28% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.23% on the day, quoting at 25741. The Sensex is at 83526.16, up 0.3%. IndusInd Bank Ltd has slipped around 0.63% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which IndusInd Bank Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 2.12% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60949.1, up 0.34% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 42.54 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 41.34 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 940.95, up 1.03% on the day. IndusInd Bank Ltd is down 7.84% in last one year as compared to a 12.18% jump in NIFTY and a 24.59% jump in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndusIndBankLtd_64968625_5531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Thermax Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/thermax-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1678243</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678243</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Thermax Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Thermax Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3012.8, up 3.03% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.23% on the day, quoting at 25741. The Sensex is at 83526.16, up 0.3%. Thermax Ltd has risen around 2.56% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Thermax Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 6.47% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36386.75, down 0.18% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 68768 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.2 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 59.24 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Thermax_89686957655_4767.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/persistent-systems-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1678244</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678244</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Persistent Systems Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5664, up 1.47% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.23% on the day, quoting at 25741. The Sensex is at 83526.16, up 0.3%. Persistent Systems Ltd has slipped around 12.02% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Persistent Systems Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 13.74% in last one month and is currently quoting at 32738.05, up 2.5% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.59 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.3 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5647.5, up 1.32% on the day. Persistent Systems Ltd is down 2.3% in last one year as compared to a 12.18% spurt in NIFTY and a 19.07% spurt in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 55.99 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PersistentSys_70071143_18286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[State Bank of India up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/state-bank-of-india-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1678240</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678240</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[State Bank of India rose for a fifth straight session today.

State Bank of India rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1221.8, up 1.13% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.22% on the day, quoting at 25738.7. The Sensex is at 83523, up 0.3%. State Bank of India has added around 17.66% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which State Bank of India is a constituent, has added around 2.12% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60949.1, up 0.35% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 116.22 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 150.5 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1216.6, up 0.96% on the day. State Bank of India is up 68.34% in last one year as compared to a 12.17% gain in NIFTY and a 24.6% gain in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 14.77 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StBkofIndia_57185891_1375.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>