<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:27:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Innova Captab surges after Q3 PAT climbs 23% YoY to Rs 421 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/innova-captab-surges-after-q3-pat-climbs-23-yoy-to-rs-421-cr/1667106</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667106</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 22.14% YoY to Rs 55.67 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 22.14% YoY to Rs 55.67 crore during the quarter. Total expenses increased 44% to Rs 396.27 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 275.19 crore posted corresponding quarter last year. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 280.83 crore (up 43.46% YoY), employee benefit expenses was at Rs 43.78 crore (up 55.25% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared dividend of Rs 2 per equity share with a face value of Rs 10 each for FY26. The record date has been fixed as on Friday, 30th January 2026. Innova Captab is an integrated pharmaceutical company in India with a presence across the pharmaceutical value chain, including research and development, manufacturing, drug distribution and marketing, and exports. The company has three businesses: CDMO (contract development and manufacturing organization) services and products, domestic branded generics, and international branded generics.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InnovaCaptabLtd_46397716_74713.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[H.G. Infra Engineering Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hg-infra-engineering-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1667090</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667090</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Pearl Polymers Ltd, California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Archidply Industries Ltd and N K Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 January 2026.

Pearl Polymers Ltd, California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Archidply Industries Ltd and N K Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 January 2026. H.G. Infra Engineering Ltd crashed 13.73% to Rs 572.15 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 4.5 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12367 shares in the past one month. Pearl Polymers Ltd lost 11.39% to Rs 19.69. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1075 shares in the past one month. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup tumbled 11.11% to Rs 4.08. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 500 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1629 shares in the past one month. Archidply Industries Ltd plummeted 10.61% to Rs 80. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 311 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 265 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd pared 10.00% to Rs 62.91. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 35 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 58 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HGInfraEngineeringLtd_52714149365_71631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SG Mart Q3 PAT tumbles 62% YoY to Rs 11 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sg-mart-q3-pat-tumbles-62-yoy-to-rs-11-crore/1667091</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667091</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 23.20% YoY to Rs 1,644.43 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 23.20% YoY to Rs 1,644.43 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 13.52 crore, registering a de-growth of 63.89% on a YoY basis. Total expenses rose 24.61% YoY to Rs 1,648.85 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Employee benefits expense stood at Rs 8.43 crore (up 92.07% YoY) and while finance costs increased 78.03% YoY to Rs 17.43 crore during the period under review. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit slipped 1.03% YoY to Rs 69.57 crore, while revenue increased 5.42% YoY to Rs 4492.44 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. SGMART is a premier B2B one-stop shop that provides a wide range of construction-related solutions from top brands under one roof. Its extensive network, with strategically positioned warehouses in Pune, Bangalore, Dujana, and Raipur, ensures seamless accessibility and efficient distribution of remarkable products to its valued customers. The counter soared 8.72% to Rs 361 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KintechRenewablesLtd_5350960382_6811.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex tumbles 706 pts; media shares decline; VIX jumps 6.29%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-tumbles-706-pts-media-shares-decline-vix-jumps-629/1667080</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667080</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade, as sentiment remained cautious with investors tracking global cues and awaiting further clarity on domestic triggers, keeping market moves range-bound.

The key equity barometers traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade, as sentiment remained cautious with investors tracking global cues and awaiting further clarity on domestic triggers, keeping market moves range-bound. The Nifty traded below the 25,100 level. Media shares declined after advancing in the past trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 706.09 points or 0.86% to 81,601.28. The Nifty 50 index fell 218.10 points or 0.86% to 25,073.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.33% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.89%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,254 shares rose and 2,871 shares fell. A total of 145 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.29% to 14.19. The rupee hit a fresh record low of 91.99 against the US dollar in intraday trade on Friday, pressured by weak global cues and persistent dollar demand. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 2.38% to 1,353.35. The index rose 2.39% in the past trading session. Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 4.58%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 4.51%), Prime Focus (down 4.29%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 4.09%), Tips Music (down 3.39%), Nazara Technologies (down 2.53%), PVR Inox (down 2.36%), D B Corp (down 0.08%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was up 0.39% to 6.662 as compared with the previous close of 6.636. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9400 compared with its close of 91.5800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.16% to Rs 1,56,092. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.07% to 98.35. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.26% to 4.240. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement added 62 cents or 0.97% to $64.68 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Gujarat State Petronet (GSPL) fell 1.27% after its standalone net profit fell 15.70% to Rs 114.26 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 4.5% to Rs 272.19 crore compared with the same quarter last year. Ideaforge Technology slipped 4.98% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 33.85 crore in Q3 FY26, widening from Rs 24.02 crore in Q3 FY25. Despite the wider loss, the company’s revenue from operations increased 79.15% year on year (YoY) to Rs 31.55 crore during the quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Home First Finance Company India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-counter/1667079</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667079</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Adani Green Energy Ltd, Bandhan Bank Ltd, Swan Corp Ltd, Syngene International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 23 January 2026.

Adani Green Energy Ltd, Bandhan Bank Ltd, Swan Corp Ltd, Syngene International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 23 January 2026. Home First Finance Company India Ltd recorded volume of 26.19 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 13.27 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.97 lakh shares. The stock gained 5.97% to Rs.1,111.20. Volumes stood at 2.89 lakh shares in the last session. Adani Green Energy Ltd recorded volume of 136.38 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.03 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 16.98 lakh shares. The stock lost 12.44% to Rs.791.80. Volumes stood at 18.52 lakh shares in the last session. Bandhan Bank Ltd witnessed volume of 571.47 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.14 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 80.03 lakh shares. The stock increased 5.05% to Rs.149.65. Volumes stood at 123.49 lakh shares in the last session. Swan Corp Ltd recorded volume of 58.68 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.89 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9.96 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.13% to Rs.417.55. Volumes stood at 5.89 lakh shares in the last session. Syngene International Ltd registered volume of 29.48 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.06 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 5.82 lakh shares. The stock slipped 6.11% to Rs.556.40. Volumes stood at 9.82 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HomeFirstFinanceCompanyIndiaLtd_56604898_71865.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DLF Q3 PAT rises 14% YoY to Rs 1,203 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dlf-q3-pat-rises-14-yoy-to-rs-1203-cr/1667068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667068</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations surged 32.15% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 2,020.22 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations surged 32.15% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 2,020.22 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. EBITDA for the quarter stood at Rs 849 crore, reflecting a YoY growth of 39%. However, EBITDA margin declined to 34% in Q3 FY26, down from 35% recorded in Q3 FY25. The company generated Rs 3,876 crore of surplus cash during the quarter, enabling it to achieve its target of zero gross debt, with a net cash position of Rs 11,660 crore. New sales bookings stood at Rs 419 crore, supported by healthy monetisation of launched inventory (excluding The Dahlias). The company remains confident of meeting its annual guidance and plans to continue rolling out new products aligned with its medium-term strategy. DLF with its subsidiaries, associates and JVs is engaged in real estate development, from the identification and acquisition of land to planning, execution, construction and marketing of projects. It is also engaged in business of leasing, generation of power, provision of maintenance services, hospitality and recreational services which are related to the overall development of real estate business. Shares of DLF fell 3.31% to Rs 593.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DLF_34979173164_6890.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Monarch Networth Q3 PAT rises 12% YoY to Rs 45 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/monarch-networth-q3-pat-rises-12-yoy-to-rs-45-cr/1667055</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667055</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 60.63 crore, registering a 21% YoY growth.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 60.63 crore, registering a 21% YoY growth. Total expenses increased 17.74% to Rs 31.32 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 26.60 crore in Q3 FY25. Finance cost stood at Rs 1.81 crore (down 45.81% YoY), fees and commission expenses were at Rs 7.28 crore (up 18.37% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 12.85 crore (down 1.53% YoY). Monarch Networth Capital is a provider of financial services in pure stock broking, primary market operations, mutual funds, insurance, and financial planning. It is a strategic amalgamation of two financial service providers, Monarch Group of Companies and Networth Stock Broking. Shares of Monarch Networth Capital shed 0.61% to Rs 286.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MonarchNetworth_91290286191_4092.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yes Bank Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yes-bank-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1667051</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667051</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Yes Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Yes Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 21.18, down 2.08% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.56% on the day, quoting at 25148.95. The Sensex is at 81826.26, down 0.58%.Yes Bank Ltd has eased around 2.35% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Yes Bank Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.51% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59200.1, down 0.54% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 583.92 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 1165.56 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 21.12, down 2.4% on the day. Yes Bank Ltd jumped 16.12% in last one year as compared to a 8.91% rally in NIFTY and a 21.74% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 21.64 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/YesBank_75840425465_25267.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-petroleum-corporation-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1667052</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667052</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 417.1, down 2.48% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.56% on the day, quoting at 25148.95. The Sensex is at 81826.26, down 0.58%.Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd has eased around 11.39% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 5.29% in last one month and is currently quoting at 33747, down 1.5% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 45.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 48.82 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 417.3, down 2.39% on the day. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd jumped 18.21% in last one year as compared to a 8.91% rally in NIFTY and a 0.07% fall in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 5.82 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HPCL_59291502793_2305.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Breweries Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-breweries-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1667053</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667053</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[United Breweries Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

United Breweries Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1440, down 0.25% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.56% on the day, quoting at 25148.95. The Sensex is at 81826.26, down 0.58%.United Breweries Ltd has lost around 11.13% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which United Breweries Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 5.65% in last one month and is currently quoting at 51978.4, up 0.04% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 39648 shares today, compared to the daily average of 71248 shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 100.55 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnitedBreweries_49738308528_23220.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with major cuts; realty shares slumps; VIX jumps 3.76%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-major-cuts-realty-shares-slumps-vix-jumps-376/1667054</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667054</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade as investors monitored global cues and awaited further clarity on domestic triggers, keeping market movements range-bound.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade as investors monitored global cues and awaited further clarity on domestic triggers, keeping market movements range-bound. The Nifty traded below the 25,200 level. Barring the IT index, all other indices traded in the red on the NSE. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 524.11 points or 0.64% to 81,784.31. The Nifty 50 index fell 163.30 points or 0.64% to 25,162.75. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.99% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 1.61%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,390 shares rose and 2,646 shares fell. A total of 165 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 3.76% to 13.85. Gainers & Losers: Dr Reddy's Laboratories (up 2.52%), Asian Paints (up 2.09%), Hindustan Unilever (up 1.52%), Tech Mahindra (up 1.08%) and Tata Consultancy Services (up 1.02%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Adani Enterprises (down 5.26%), Eternal (down 4.87%), Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (down 4.19%), Interglobe Aviation (down 4.05%) and Jio Financial Services (down 2.80%) were the major Nifty50 losers. InterGlobe Aviaition (Indigo) declined 4.05% after the company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 77.55% to Rs 549.8 crore despite 6.16% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 23,471.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Stocks in Spotlight: Gujarat State Petronet (GSPL) fell 1.08% after its standalone net profit fell 15.70% to Rs 114.26 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 4.5% to Rs 272.19 crore compared with the same quarter last year. Computer Age Management Services declined 2.97%. The company has reported 0.04% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 125.53 crore on a 5.52% increase in revenue from operations from operations to Rs 390.13 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Home First Finance Company India rallied 5.86% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 43.97% to Rs 140.20 crore on 18.8% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 482.24 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Adani Energy Solutions fell 6.81% after the company reported 1.68% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 552.31 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 561.78 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 15.73% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,729.65 crore in Q3 FY26. Global Markets: European markets opened lower on Friday as investors digest events at Davos, including Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy’s excoriating speech about the continent. Asian markets rose, tracking Wall Street gains as geopolitical concerns eased and investors looked ahead to the Bank of Japan’s decision. The central bank is expected to hold rates at 0.75%, according to media reports. Japan’s headline inflation rate in December slowed sharply to 2.1%, its lowest level since March 2022. Its core inflation rate came in at 2.4% on the year. Some tech stocks in Asia fell after shares of California-based Intel plummeted 13% in after-hours U.S. trading on its soft guidance for the current quarter, despite posting fourth-quarter earnings beats Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the main benchmarks extended their gains from the previous session after Greenland tensions eased. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 306.78 points, or 0.63%, and closed at 49,384.01. The 30-stock index recovered from the losses seen earlier this week following President Donald Trump’s new Europe tariffs announcement. The S&P 500 climbed 0.55% and ended at 6,913.35. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.91% and settled at 23,436.02, supported by gains in Nvidia, Microsoft, and Meta Platforms.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC climbs on decent Q3 performance, broker upgrades]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-climbs-on-decent-q3-performance-broker-upgrades/1667045</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667045</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 20% YoY to Rs 269.5 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 224.5 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 20% YoY to Rs 269.5 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 224.5 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit after tax increased 12% from Rs 241.3 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 478.1 crore in Q3 FY26, up 7% YoY from Rs 445.1 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, revenue increased 4% from Rs 461.3 crore in Q2 FY26. Other income surged sharply to Rs 84.3 crore in Q3 FY26, up 119% YoY and 87% sequentially, aiding profitability during the quarter. Operating profit came in at Rs 274 crore in Q3 FY26, up 5% YoY and 1% QoQ. Profit before tax stood at Rs 358.3 crore in Q3 FY26, up 19% YoY from Rs 299.9 crore and 14% higher sequentially compared with Rs 315.6 crore in Q2 FY26. Total expenses increased 11% YoY to Rs 204.1 crore in Q3 FY26 and were up 7% QoQ. Employee benefits expense rose 23% YoY to Rs 107.7 crore, while fees and commission expense increased 30% YoY to Rs 16.1 crore. Depreciation and amortisation stood at Rs 11.7 crore, up 5% YoY. Other expenses declined 5% YoY to Rs 68.6 crore. On the operational front, overall Quarterly Average Assets Under Management (QAAUM) including alternate assets grew 20% YoY to Rs 4,814 billion as of 31 December 2025. Mutual fund QAAUM increased 15% YoY to Rs 4,432 billion. Equity mutual fund QAAUM rose 11% YoY to Rs 1,994 billion, with equity-oriented schemes accounting for 45% of the mix. Individual monthly AAUM stood at Rs 2,119 billion, representing 48% of mutual fund AUM, while B-30 monthly AAUM grew 12% YoY to Rs 770 billion, accounting for 17.3% of AUM. PMS and AIF QAAUM including the ESIC mandate expanded eight-fold YoY to Rs 327 billion, with the ESIC mandate at Rs 282 billion. Passive QAAUM increased 28% YoY to Rs 387 billion. Monthly SIP contributions stood at Rs 10.8 billion in December 2025, supported by 4.04 million contributing SIP accounts. During the quarter, around 5.31 lakh new SIPs were registered. The company serviced 10.8 million folios as of 31 December 2025, through over 93,000 KYD-compliant distributors, 360+ national distributors and 90+ banks across more than 310 locations. A foreign broker double-upgraded Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC to 'Buy' with a target price of Rs 900, citing early signs of stabilisation in market share after years of muted performance. The brokerage said improving returns in key equity schemes and easing redemption pressures should help revive gross flows, support AAUM growth and potentially trigger a re-rating, despite lingering execution risks. Separately, a domestic brokerage upgraded the stock to 'Buy' from Hold and raised its target price to Rs 950, noting an earnings beat driven by higher other income. While it flagged weak operating metrics and continued market-share losses, it raised FY26-FY28 Net Operating Profit Less Adjusted Taxes (NOPLAT) estimates by up to 5.5% on better earnings visibility. Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC was incorporated in 1994 and is promoted by Aditya Birla Capital and Sun Life (India) AMC Investments Inc. The company is the investment manager to Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund and also operates across portfolio management services, alternative investment funds, offshore strategies and real estate investments. One of India’s leading asset managers, ABSLAMC services about 10.8 million investor folios through a pan-India network of over 310 locations, with total assets under management of Rs 4,814 billion as of the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdityaBirlaSunLifeAMCLtd_15162858_20665.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashok Leyland Ltd soars 2.61%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashok-leyland-ltd-soars-261-up-for-third-straight-session/1667037</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667037</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ashok Leyland Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Ashok Leyland Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 195.25, up 2.61% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25210.75. The Sensex is at 82029.72, down 0.34%. Ashok Leyland Ltd has added around 11.37% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Ashok Leyland Ltd is a constituent, has added around 3.26% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27110.2, down 0.49% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 243.99 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 169.12 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 196.15, up 2.73% on the day. Ashok Leyland Ltd is up 91.14% in last one year as compared to a 9.17% gain in NIFTY and a 21.67% gain in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 32.78 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokLeyland_6904859924_31.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Consultancy Services Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-consultancy-services-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1667038</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667038</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Consultancy Services Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Tata Consultancy Services Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3186.2, up 1.14% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25210.75. The Sensex is at 82029.72, down 0.34%. Tata Consultancy Services Ltd has slipped around 4% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Tata Consultancy Services Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 1.45% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38301.75, up 0.28% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 11.13 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 27.23 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3190.3, up 1.19% on the day. Tata Consultancy Services Ltd is down 23.27% in last one year as compared to a 9.17% spurt in NIFTY and a 11.75% spurt in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 23.35 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TCS_30661368_5400.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tech-mahindra-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1667039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667039</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Tech Mahindra Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1706.1, up 1.11% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25210.75. The Sensex is at 82029.72, down 0.34%. Tech Mahindra Ltd has gained around 4.57% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Tech Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.45% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38301.75, up 0.28% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 10.75 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 18.97 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1703.5, up 0.77% on the day. Tech Mahindra Ltd is down 0.98% in last one year as compared to a 9.17% jump in NIFTY and a 11.75% jump in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 39.34 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TechMahindra_28047796713_17215.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/national-aluminium-company-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1667040</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667040</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

National Aluminium Company Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 378.1, up 3.7% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25210.75. The Sensex is at 82029.72, down 0.34%. National Aluminium Company Ltd has gained around 28.04% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which National Aluminium Company Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 8.36% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11573.7, up 0.58% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 166.79 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 194.18 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 377.05, up 3.53% on the day. National Aluminium Company Ltd is up 86.07% in last one year as compared to a 9.17% jump in NIFTY and a 37.94% jump in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 10.87 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NatlAluminium_39819539035_2304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1667041</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667041</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Vedanta Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 695.7, up 2.51% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25210.75. The Sensex is at 82029.72, down 0.34%. Vedanta Ltd has gained around 16.31% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Vedanta Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 8.36% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11573.7, up 0.58% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 131.74 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 161.81 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 695.1, up 2.57% on the day. Vedanta Ltd is up 57.4% in last one year as compared to a 9.17% jump in NIFTY and a 37.94% jump in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 28.2 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindalco-industries-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1667042</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667042</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Hindalco Industries Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 954.05, up 1.02% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 25210.75. The Sensex is at 82029.72, down 0.34%. Hindalco Industries Ltd has risen around 10.36% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Hindalco Industries Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 8.36% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11573.7, up 0.58% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 37.9 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 60.85 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 952.5, up 1.21% on the day. Hindalco Industries Ltd is up 57.2% in last one year as compared to a 9.17% spurt in NIFTY and a 37.94% spurt in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 29.68 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindalcoInds_40254437488_252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty below 25,250 mark; oil & gas shares snap 2-day gains]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-below-25250-mark-oil-gas-shares-snap-2-day-gains/1667032</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667032</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty below 25,250 mark; oil & gas shares snap 2-day gains

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ideaforge Tech Q3 net loss widens to Rs 34-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ideaforge-tech-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-34-cr/1667029</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667029</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Despite the wider loss, the company’s revenue from operations increased 79.15% year on year (YoY) to Rs 31.55 crore during the quarter.

Despite the wider loss, the company’s revenue from operations increased 79.15% year on year (YoY) to Rs 31.55 crore during the quarter. The company posted a pre-tax loss of Rs 35.93 crore in Q3 FY26, as against a pre-tax loss of Rs 20.28 crore in Q3 FY25. Ideaforge reported a negative EBITDA of Rs 23.91 crore in Q3 FY26, declining from a negative EBITDA of Rs 12.58 crore in Q3 FY25. The EBITDA margin also reduced to - 75.8% in Q2 FY26 from -71.4% a year ago. As of 31st December 2025, the company’s order book stood at Rs 440 crore. Ankit Mehta, co-founder and CEO of ideaForge said, “FY26 has been a defining year for ideaForge so far. We’ve booked the highest quantum of ordersin our two-decade journey so far this year, with a sizable chunk coming in Q3 alone. Our priority now is crisp execution: we expect to deliver 40–45% of the open orders in Q4 FY26 and close FY26 with improved gross margins and turn profitable. Drones have become a critical element of counter-insurgency and counter-terrorism operations, and recent global conflicts have reinforced the need for nations to build strong indigenous capabilities. For India, this shift became especially evident post Operation Sindoor, with a clear acceleration in procurement through initiatives such as EP6 and decentralised command-level purchases. The recent reports of a fresh procurement outlay of approximately Rs 20,000 crore signal a strong, multi-year demand tailwind for the domestic drone industry. With indigenously developed platforms, subsystems, and full-stack technology, we are gearing up to meet evolving requirements by expanding beyond ISR and reinforcing leadership in India’s drone ecosystem. Further, the reports of PLI 2.0 and R&D incentives for drones also provide positive signs for the industry.” Ideaforge Technology (ideaForge) is the pioneer and the pre-eminent market leader in the Indian unmanned aircraft systems (UAS) market. It had the largest operational deployment of indigenous UAVs across India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IdeaforgeTechnologyLtd_35988136_78688.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>