<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KRN Heat Exchanger posts PAT of Rs 23 crore in Q3; EBITDA margin rises to 20.28%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/krn-heat-exchanger-posts-pat-of-rs-23-crore-in-q3-ebitda-margin-rises-to-2028/1673660</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673660</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 129.61 crore, up 33.32% YoY.

Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 129.61 crore, up 33.32% YoY. While EBITDA improved by 96.54% to Rs 31.08 crore, EBITDA margin expanded by 610 basis points to 20.28% in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 25.87 crore, up by 35.19% from Rs 19.13 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Santosh Kumar, chairman & managing director of KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration, said: "During the quarter and across the nine-month period, we have seen steady progress in our core business, driven by consistent execution and improving order visibility. Demand from both domestic and export customers has remained healthy, and our teams have responded well by maintaining delivery timelines and quality standards. Over the past nine months, our focus has been on building depth—stronger customer relationships, higher value products, and tighter control over operations. This has helped us grow in a balanced manner while improving the overall quality of earnings. With a stable order pipeline, expanding export engagements, and continued emphasis on operational efficiency, we believe the business is well positioned to grow steadily and strengthen its revenue base in the coming periods." KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration specializes in manufacturing aluminium and copper fin and tube heat exchangers, including water coils, condenser coils, and evaporator coils. Their products are widely used by OEMs in the HVAC&R industry for heating, ventilation, air conditioning, and refrigeration applications. The scrip shed 0.25% to end at Rs 672.25 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KRNHeatExchangerandRefrigerationLtd_36100110_92755.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[State Bank of India posts PAT of Rs 21,028 crore in Q3; clocks NIM of 3.12%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/state-bank-of-india-posts-pat-of-rs-21028-crore-in-q3-clocks-nim-of-312/1673595</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673595</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 45,190 crore, up 9.04% YoY.

Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 45,190 crore, up 9.04% YoY. Net interest margin was 3.12% for the December 2025 period as against 3.15% for the December 2024 period. Operating expenses rose by 6.05% to Rs 30,687 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 28,935 crore in the December 2024 quarter. Accordingly, the public sector bank registered an operating profit of Rs 32,862 crore in Q3 FY26, up 39.54% YoY. Total provisions expanded by 77.71% to Rs 11,834 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6,659 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 28,355 crore, up by 25.25% from Rs 22,640 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross NPAs declined to 1.57% as of 31 December 2025, from 2.07% as of 31 December 2024. Net NPAs fell to 0.39% as of 31 December 2025 from 0.53% as of 31 December 2024. The provision coverage ratio (PCR) (including AUCA) as on 31 December 2025 was at 92.37%. AUCA or advance under collection account (AUCA) is a dummy account maintained by SBI in which written off loan accounts are transferred. The bank had a deposit base of Rs 57,01,309 crore as on 31 December 2025, up 9.02% YoY. Gross advances of the bank as on 31 December 2025 were Rs 46,83,508 crore, up 15.14% YoY. Capital adequacy ratio (CAR) as at the end of Q3 FY26 stood at 14.04%. State Bank of India is engaged in providing a wide range of products and services to individuals, commercial enterprises, large corporates, public bodies, and institutional customers. The Government of India held 55.50% stake in the bank as on 31 December 2025. The scrip had lost 0.65% to end at Rs 1066.40 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StBkofIndia_57185891_1375.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank denies submission of bid for acquiring IDBI Bank ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-bank-denies-submission-of-bid-for-acquiring-idbi-bank/1673545</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673545</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On February 06, widely circulated media reports stated that Fairfax Financial and Kotak Mahindra Bank are set to submit financial bids separately for a majority stake in IDBI Bank along with supporting documents on Friday.

On February 06, widely circulated media reports stated that Fairfax Financial and Kotak Mahindra Bank are set to submit financial bids separately for a majority stake in IDBI Bank along with supporting documents on Friday. The two contenders are in a race to acquire the 60.72% stake belonging to the government and Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) that is on offer, the reports added. Providing a clarification on the same, Kotak Mahindra Bank said: “We would like to clarify that the Bank has not submitted a financial bid as part of disinvestment process relating to IDBI Bank Limited.” Kotak Mahindra Bank is the part of the Kotak Group and has diversified operations covering commercial vehicle financing, consumer loans, corporate finance, and asset reconstruction. Through its subsidiaries, the bank is engaged in investment banking, equity broking, securities-based lending, and car finance. As on 31 st December 2025, the bank has a national footprint of 2,218 branches and 2,749 ATMs (incl. cash recyclers) and branches in GIFT City and DIFC (Dubai). The bank reported a 4.28% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 3,446.14 crore on 4.3% increase in total income to Rs 16,741.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip had advanced 3.35% to end at Rs 422.35 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KotakMahBank_47062626511_2330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hi-Tech Pipes posts over 14% YoY drop in Q3 PAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hi-tech-pipes-posts-over-14-yoy-drop-in-q3-pat/1673544</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673544</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 1,046.63 crore, up 25.7% YoY.

Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 1,046.63 crore, up 25.7% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 23.20 crore, down by 14.3% from Rs 27.06 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Hi-Tech Pipes is one of the leading steel tubes and pipes manufacturers in India. It provides innovative products for nearly four decades with a strong presence in steel pipes, hollow sections, tubes, cold rolled coils & strips, road crash barriers, solar mounting structures, GP/GC Sheets, color coated coils and a variety of other galvanised products. The scrip had shed 0.12% to end at Rs 80.79 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HiTechPipes_75760192686_23653.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ram Ratna Wires Q3 PAT climbs 73% YoY to Rs 31 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ram-ratna-wires-q3-pat-climbs-73-yoy-to-rs-31-cr/1673420</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673420</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 97.87% YoY to Rs 47.45 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 97.87% YoY to Rs 47.45 crore during the quarter. The company reported exceptional loss of Rs 3.56 crore in Q3 FY26, related to labour code compliance. EBITDA stood at Rs 72 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 84.9% compared with Rs 39 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 5.6% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.4% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter 92% of revenue contributed from domestic region while 8% revenue came from exports. Mahendrakumar Kabra, MD said, “We are delighted to report yet another quarter of exceptional performance, led by rising demandfor copper tubes driven by the growth in the HVAC industry. This segment has seen its contributionto revenues increase from 17% last year to 27% this quarter, driving profitability and underscoringour focus on expanding domestic capacity and reducing import reliance. To further strengthen thissegment, Inner Grooved Tube (IGT) manufacturing is currently in progress and at the evaluation stage. At the same time, copper winding wires continue to benefit from India’s electrification push andthe rapid expansion of power transmission and distribution infrastructure, resulting in robustgrowth across our portfolio. Our consolidated revenue for this quarter grew by 43.8% year-on-year,with Operating EBITDA rising 84.9% and Profit After Tax improving 72.5%, reflecting operationalexcellence and disciplined execution. Looking ahead, strong demand momentum supported by industry tailwinds and capacity additionswill continue to drive growth. In addition, developments in our joint venture and subsidiary areadvancing well and will further enhance our growth trajectory. We remain committed to deliveringsustainable value for all our stakeholders.” Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the change in designation of Rajeev Maheshwari from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) of the company to senior vice president (Accounts & Taxation) with effect from April 01, 2026, consequent to this change Maheshwari will cease to be the CFO of the Company from the closure of business hours on March 31, 2026. Additionally, the board approved the appointment of Iqbal Singh Saggu, as senior vice president (Finance) and CFO with effect from April 01, 2026. Iqbal Singh Saggu is a qualified chartered accountant with over 23 years of experience in handling treasury department, plant & finance operations, strategic planning, capital structuring, and regulatory compliance with expertise in driving profitability and optimizing capital. Ram Ratna Wires (RRWL) is a prominent part of RR Global, a leading conglomerate in the electrical and copper industry. The company manufactures super enameled copper winding wires in India that offers a wide range of sizes under its brand, RR Shramik. The scrip rose 0.36% to settle at Rs 296.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RamRatnaWires_52194664867_4453.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PM Modi: India to Boost Defence, Security, and Innovation Partnership with Malaysia]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pm-modi-india-to-boost-defence-security-and-innovation-partnership-with-malaysia/1673419</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673419</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Saturday said India is looking at boosting defence and security ties and enhancing economic and innovation partnership with Malaysia.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Saturday said India is looking at boosting defence and security ties and enhancing economic and innovation partnership with Malaysia. "The historic ties between India and Malaysia have seen steadfast progress in recent years," he said in a departure statement.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/world-economy-3513561__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[U.S. and India Reach Framework for Interim Trade Agreement to Boost Reciprocal Market Access and Supply Chain Resilience]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-and-india-reach-framework-for-interim-trade-agreement-to-boost-reciprocal-market-access-and-supply-chain-resilience/1673396</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673396</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The United States of America (United States) and India announced that they have reached a framework for an Interim Agreement regarding reciprocal and mutually beneficial trade (Interim Agreement).

The United States of America (United States) and India announced that they have reached a framework for an Interim Agreement regarding reciprocal and mutually beneficial trade (Interim Agreement). The framework reaffirms the countries commitment to the broader U.S.-India Bilateral Trade Agreement (BTA) negotiations, launched by President Donald J. Trump and Prime Minister Narendra Modi on February 13, 2025 which will include additional market access commitments and support more resilient supply chains. The Interim Agreement between the United States and India will represent a historic milestone in our countries’ partnership, demonstrating a common commitment to reciprocal and balanced trade based on mutual interests and concrete outcomes. India will eliminate or reduce tariffs on all U.S. industrial goods and a wide range of U.S. food and agricultural products, including dried distillers’ grains (DDGs), red sorghum for animal feed, tree nuts, fresh and processed fruit, soybean oil, wine and spirits, and additional products. The United States will apply a reciprocal tariff rate of 18 percent under Executive Order 14257 of April 2, 2025 (Regulating Imports With a Reciprocal Tariff to Rectify Trade Practices That Contribute to Large and Persistent Annual United States Goods Trade Deficits), as amended, on originating goods of India, including textile and apparel, leather and footwear, plastic and rubber, organic chemicals, home décor, artisanal products, and certain machinery, and, subject to the successful conclusion of the Interim Agreement, will remove the reciprocal tariff on a wide range of goods identified in the Potential Tariff Adjustments for Aligned Partners Annex to Executive Order 14346 of September 5, 2025 (Modifying the Scope of Reciprocal Tariffs and Establishing Procedures for Implementing Trade and Security Agreements), as amended, including generic pharmaceuticals, gems and diamonds, and aircraft parts. The United States will also remove tariffs on certain aircraft and aircraft parts of India imposed to eliminate threats to national security found in Proclamation 9704 of March 8, 2018, as amended and Proclamation 10962 of July 30, 2025(Adjusting Imports of Copper Into the United States). Similarly, consistent with U.S. national security requirements, India will receive a preferential tariff rate quota for automotive parts subject to the tariff imposed to eliminate threats to national security found in Proclamation 9888 of May 17, 2019 (Adjusting Imports of Automobiles and Automobile Parts Into the United States) as amended. The United States and India commit to provide each other preferential market access in sectors of respective interest on a sustained basis. The United States and India will establish rules of origin that ensure that the benefits of the Agreement accrue predominately to the United States and India. The United States and India will address non-tariff barriers that affect bilateral trade. India agrees to address long-standing barriers to the trade in U.S. medical devices; eliminate restrictive import licensing procedures that delay market access for, or impose quantitative restrictions on, U.S. Information and Communication Technology (ICT) goods and also determine with a view towards a positive outcome, within six months of entry into force of the Agreement whether U.S. developed or international standards including testing requirements that are acceptable for the purposes of U.S. exports entering the Indian market in identified sectors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/world-trade-center-582928__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baazar Style Retail Q3 PAT slips 37% YoY to Rs 19 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baazar-style-retail-q3-pat-slips-37-yoy-to-rs-19-cr/1673379</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673379</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax declined 34.02% to Rs 26.90 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 40.77 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before exceptional item and tax declined 34.02% to Rs 26.90 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 40.77 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported exceptional loss of Rs 1.33 crore in Q3 FY26, related to labour code compliance. EBITDA increased 7% to Rs 89.4 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 83.3 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin reduced to 19.2% in Q3 FY26 as against 20.2% in Q3 FY25. Average transaction value stood at Rs 992, down 3.78% compared with 1,031 in Q3 FY25. Sales per square feet declined 15.25% YoY to Rs 700 per month in Q3 FY26. As on 31 December 2025, total store count stood at 252 stores (up 27% YoY) and total rental area of stores aggregated to 2.35 million square feet (up 31% YoY). Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the appointment of Rohit Kedia as the chairman of the company following resignation of Pradeep Kumar Agarwal as chairman, Agarwal will cease to hold the office of chairman with effect from close of business on February 06, 2026 and will continue to be associated with the company as a whole-time director. Baazar Style Retail is a value fashion retailer with a leadership position in the states of West Bengal and Odisha in the organized value retail market. The company offers quality and affordable products under the apparel and general merchandise segments, through a chain of 'value retail' stores. Within the apparel vertical, it offers garments for men, women, boys, girls, and infants, whereas the general merchandise offerings include both non-apparels and home furnishing products. The counter rallied 2.80% to settle at Rs 320.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BaazarStyleRetailLtd_39054535_76733.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1673368</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673368</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 10 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 10 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: ICICI Prudential MNC Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.75 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.75 ICICI Prudential Commodities Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 2.50 Direct Plan – IDCW: 2.50

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Steel Q3 PAT surges over seven-fold to Rs 2,688 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-steel-q3-pat-surges-over-seven-fold-to-rs-2688-cr/1673334</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673334</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax surged 122.92% YoY to Rs 4,008.65 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional items and tax surged 122.92% YoY to Rs 4,008.65 crore during the quarter. However, the company reported a net exceptional loss Rs 139.88 crore in Q3 FY26. The exceptional losses were primarily driven by restructuring and other provisions amounting to Rs 737.19 crore, which represented the largest impact. This was accompanied by impairment of non-current assets of Rs 94.18 crore, provisions for demands and claims of Rs 102.24 crore, employee separation compensation costs of Rs 43.05 crore, and a statutory charge of Rs 81.79 crore arising from the implementation of new labour codes. These exceptional expenses were partially offset by a fair value gain of Rs 918.57 crore on non-current investments. EBITDA jumped 39% YoY to Rs 8,309 crore with a margin of around 15%. India revenues were Rs 35,725 crore and EBITDA was Rs 8,291 crores, which translates to a margin of 23%. During the quarter, Crude steel production was up 12% YoY to 6.34 million tons. Improved production supported deliveries volumes of 6.04 million tons in Q3 FY26, up 14% YoY. UK revenues were euro 468 million and EBITDA loss stood at euro 63 million. Deliveries stood at 0.52 million tons and were impacted by subdued demand and steady imports. The company has spent Rs 3,291 crore on capital expenditure during the quarter. T V Narendran, chief executive officer & managing director, said, “Our global operating environment continues to be shaped by tariffs, geopolitical shifts and policy divergence. Steel markets were impacted by elevated finished steel exports from China, which at 119 million tons surpassed the 2015 peak. Against this backdrop, Tata Steel delivered a strong performance in this quarter, with India crude steel production rising 12% while deliveries grew faster at 14% YoY, surpassing the 6 million tons mark in a quarter for the first time. Automotive volumes grew 20% YoY, while our retail vertical gained further momentum. Tata Tiscon continued its growth, and our e-commerce platforms, Aashiyana and DigECA, achieved Gross Merchandise Value of Rs 2,380 crores for the quarter, up 68% YoY. Within the downstream portfolio, our tubes and wires businesses delivered their best-ever quarterly performance, supported by capacity additions, a richer product mix and dominant share in high-value infrastructure projects. Looking ahead, the proposed 4.8 MTPA expansion at NINL and the 0.75 MTPA EAF at Ludhiana will significantly enhance our long products portfolio. At the same time, our strategic partnership in Maharashtra will fortify raw material needs beyond 2030 and help cater to the growing demand in western and southern India. In our overseas operations, deliveries stood at 0.52 million tons in the UK and 1.40 million tons in the Netherlands. Supportive policy frameworks are vital to transition to a more sustainable operating model. While the recent progress in Europe has supported sentiment, the UK market continues to be depressed, and the quota framework needs to be revised to reflect underlying market conditions.” Koushik Chatterjee, executive director and chief financial officer, said, “For the nine months ended 31st December 2025, EBITDA margin improved by around 300 bps YoY, reflecting strong operational execution and sustained cost discipline. Our cost transformation program, focused on multiple levers including operating KPIs, supply chain efficiencies and procurement, has delivered savings of around Rs 3,000 crore for the quarter and around Rs 8,600 crore for the first nine months of the financial year. During the quarter, consolidated EBITDA was Rs 8,309 crore, translating to a margin of around 15%. In India, domestic steel prices were at multiyear lows weighing on the steel spot spreads. Despite this, our India operations delivered an EBITDA margin of 23% aided by value led growth and cost optimisation. Both in UK and Netherlands, volumes moderated on QoQ basis. UK performance was adversely impacted by subdued demand dynamics while the Netherlands delivered an EBITDA of euro 55 million. Overall, operating cash flows before capex were Rs 10,345 crore for the quarter. Our consolidated Net debt declined to Rs 81,834 crore. Our group liquidity remains strong at Rs 44,062 crore, which includes cash & cash equivalents of Rs 10,765 crore. In India, we remain focused on volume growth, investments in downstream and strengthening our raw material linkages. UK market conditions continue to be pressured by subdued demand, while policy interventions are taking longer than anticipated to materialise. We are closely monitoring the situation and the evolving tariff framework and CBAM in EU, which are pivotal for rebalancing EU market dynamics. We remain focused on prioritising, optimising and sequencing our capital allocation to balance investment needs with returns, while maintaining financial discipline and long term value creation for stakeholders.” Tata Steel group is among the top global steel companies with an annual crude steel capacity of 35 million tonnes per annum. It is one of the world's most geographically diversified steel producers, with operations and commercial presence across the world. The scrip fell 0.30% to end at Rs 197.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataSteel_98454158604_566.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Canara Robeco Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/canara-robeco-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1673333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673333</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Canara Robeco Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Canara Robeco Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Keshav Agarwal has been appointed as the Research Analyst - Equity with effect from February 02, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Mr. Keshav Agarwal Age: 43 years Designation: Research Analyst - Equity Qualification: B.Com, CA (ICAI)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sonata Software Q3 PAT drops 13% QoQ to Rs 104 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sonata-software-q3-pat-drops-13-qoq-to-rs-104-cr/1673297</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673297</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s profit after tax fell 0.62%, while revenue from operations jumped 8.36% in Q3 FY26.

On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s profit after tax fell 0.62%, while revenue from operations jumped 8.36% in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax (PBT) increased 5.18% QoQ to Rs 172.07 crore during the quarter. Exceptional item of Rs 31.3 crore was recorded during the quarter, comprising gratuity of Rs 23.3 crore and leave encashment of Rs 8.0 crore. EBITDA stood at Rs 200.2 crore, registering the growth of 15.9% QoQ. Revenue from domestic product & services stood at Rs 2,345.9 crore, up 68.6% QoQ. In International IT Services segment, revenues for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 738.6 crore, up 1.1% QoQ. In USD terms, revenue stood at $82.3 million, marking a modest 0.4% increase quarter-on-quarter (QoQ). However, when adjusted for constant currency (CC), revenue witnessed a 0.3% QoQ growth. Samir Dhir, MD & CEO of Sonata Software, said: “International IT Services delivered steady progress during the quarter, with consolidated PAT improving significantly in the last two quarters. Following a 10% PAT growth in the previous quarter, we achieved a further 6.1% quarter-on-quarter growth in the current quarter. The business secured a large deal in the BFSI vertical with a Fortune 500 fintech client, reinforcing our strategy of driving growth through large deals backed by disciplined execution. Our continued strategic investments in Artificial Intelligence contributed approximately 14% of the overall order book for the quarter. Sujit Mohanty, MD & CEO of Sonata Information Technology Limited, added: “We delivered a seasonally strong quarter in our domestic business. Our three-pillar strategy to diversify the business is in motion, focused on building a scaled and resilient operating model. We remain confident that this strategic direction will drive a more diversified, scalable, and future-ready business.” Meanwhile, the company’s board declared a third interim dividend of Rs 1.25 per equity share with a face value of Re 1 for FY26. The record dated has been fixed as 13th February 2026, the dividend will be paid to shareholders on or after 26h February 2026. Sonata Software is primarily engaged in the business of providing Information Technology (IT) Services and Solutions to its various customers in the United States of America, Europe, Middle East, Australia and India. The counter declined 1.05% to settle at Rs 306.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SonataSoftware_68199282617_12490.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>