<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:29:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Rasayan Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-rasayan-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1665980</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665980</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Best Agrolife Ltd, Shree Rama Newsprint Ltd, Brigade Hotel Ventures Ltd and Universus Photo Imagings Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 January 2026.

Best Agrolife Ltd, Shree Rama Newsprint Ltd, Brigade Hotel Ventures Ltd and Universus Photo Imagings Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 January 2026. Bharat Rasayan Ltd lost 13.71% to Rs 1760.2 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 29948 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1311 shares in the past one month. Best Agrolife Ltd crashed 10.91% to Rs 24.1. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.79 lakh shares in the past one month. Shree Rama Newsprint Ltd tumbled 10.54% to Rs 30.65. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 16238 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4730 shares in the past one month. Brigade Hotel Ventures Ltd corrected 10.41% to Rs 59.37. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 25476 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13627 shares in the past one month. Universus Photo Imagings Ltd shed 10.23% to Rs 186.85. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 303 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 752 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatRasayan_25350356075_2777.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Senores Pharma slumps as Q3 PAT slides 2% QoQ to Rs 32 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/senores-pharma-slumps-as-q3-pat-slides-2-qoq-to-rs-32-cr/1665979</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665979</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, Senores Pharma’s net profit fell 2.22% to Rs 31.66 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 32.38 crore in Q2 FY26.

On a consolidated basis, Senores Pharma’s net profit fell 2.22% to Rs 31.66 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 32.38 crore in Q2 FY26. However, total revenue from operations rallied 7.91% to Rs 174.56 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. PBT jumped 9.74% to Rs 44.60 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company's consolidated net profit zoomed 104.50% while total revenue from operations advanced 69.44% in Q3 FY26. PBT rallied 117.77% YoY. Senores Pharmaceuticals reported robust operational and financial performance for Q3 and 9M FY26. Cash flow from operations for Q3 FY26 stood at around Rs 19 crore, while for 9M FY26 it was approximately Rs 51 crore, marking significant growth over the previous year. The company said its EBITDA-to-operating cash flow conversion has improved. The pharma firm has 46 approved ANDAs covering 137 strengths, with over 100 strengths yet to be launched. Additionally, 22 ANDAs with more than 50 strengths are under development, providing strong growth visibility for its regulated business in the coming years. The Emerging Markets business recorded its highest-ever revenue and EBITDA in Q3 FY26, with revenue up nearly 48% YoY. EBITDA margin for the segment surged to around 13% from 1% in Q3FY25, a jump of 1,200 basis points. On the acquisition front, Senores Pharmaceuticals completed the first phase of acquiring a 75% stake in Apnar Pharmaceuticals, with the remaining 25% expected to be completed by Q2 FY27. Of the five approved ANDAs under Apnar, three are slated for launch in Q4 FY26, expected to generate positive cash flow. The company noted that business integration and scale-up are progressing faster than anticipated. Commenting on the results, Swapnil Shah, MD, Senores Pharmaceuticals, said, “The company delivered a robust performance in Q3FY26, with revenue rising 64% and profit after tax increasing 86% year-on-year. In the Regulated Markets, two new ANDAs with 56 strengths were launched during the quarter, with 28 approved ANDAs still awaiting launch and 22 additional molecules involving 50+ strengths under development, providing a healthy pipeline for the coming quarters. Shah highlighted the company’s expansion through the acquisition of Apnar Pharmaceuticals, with 75% of the stake already completed and the remaining 25% expected by Q2 FY27. He noted that integration and scale-up of Apnar’s operations are progressing faster than expected, enhancing scalability, deepening access to Regulated Markets, accelerating product launches, improving margins, and expanding CDMO-CMO opportunities. On the Emerging Markets business, Shah said the product portfolio continues to expand, with EBITDA margins now in the mid-teens. The segment achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue and EBITDA in Q3FY26 and is now cash flow positive. The Branded Generics business also showed strong growth, with revenue more than six-fold YoY in Q3FY26, supported by strong product acceptance and supply to multiple large hospital chains across India. Shah concluded that the company remains on track to deliver its full-year guidance, focusing on four key pillars: expanding the ANDA portfolio in Regulated Markets, scaling up CDMO/CMO operations, improving profitability in Emerging Markets, and expanding the Branded Generics business in India.” Senores Pharmaceuticals manufactures and develops affordable and high-quality complex generics certified by global food and drugs authorities.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SENORESPHARMACEUTICALSLIMITED_30889871_93477.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Saw surges over 20% in two days on robust sequential Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-saw-surges-over-20-in-two-days-on-robust-sequential-q3-performance/1665978</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665978</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of Jindal Saw surged 20.28% in two trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 154.85 recorded on 16 January 2026.

Shares of Jindal Saw surged 20.28% in two trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 154.85 recorded on 16 January 2026. Meanwhile, the company reported a 69.85% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 257.99 crore on 16.77% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 4,943.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a Year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations declined 49.06% and 6.22% respectively in Q3 FY26. EBITDA stood at Rs 632.2 crore in Q3 FY26, up 31.27% QoQ while down 34.24% YoY. The EBITDA margin improved to 12.7% in Q3 FY26 from 11.3% in Q2 FY26, but moderated from 16.8% in Q3 FY25. Jindal Saw is engaged into manufacturing of iron and steel pipes and pellets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalSaw_11729026871_965.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops over 567 pts; media shares slide]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-over-567-pts-media-shares-slide/1665977</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665977</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with major cuts in mid-afternoon trade amid the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with major cuts in mid-afternoon trade amid the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. The Nifty slipped below the 25,400 level after hitting an intraday high of 25,585 in early trade. Investors are closely tracking the ongoing Q3 earnings season and developments from the World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos. Media shares extended losses for the third consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 567.07 points or 0.68% to 82,679.11. The Nifty 50 index lost 206.55 points or 0.81% to 25,380.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 2.06% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 2.29%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,179 shares rose and 3,043 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty media index declined 1.15% to 1,368.70. The index jumped 3.3% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Prime Focus (down 4.9%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 4.28%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 3.94%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 3.88%), Saregama India (down 3.57%), PVR Inox (down 2.84%), D B Corp (down 0.84%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.06% to 6.680 as compared with the previous close of 6.684. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9400 compared with its close of 90.9000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 1.76% to Rs 1,50,008. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.51% to 98.53. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 1.13% to 4.281. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 59 cents or 0.92% to $63.54 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Punjab National Bank fell 2%. The company reported a 13.1% rise in net profit to Rs 5,100 crore on a 7.2% increase in total income to Rs 37,253 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Teleservices (Maharashtra) declined 4.86% after the company reported a net loss of Rs 150.43 crore in Q3 FY26 as against a net loss of Rs 315.11 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 11.6% YoY to Rs 294.31 crore during the quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Aditya Birla Fashion & Retail Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-aditya-birla-fashion-retail-ltd-counter/1665974</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665974</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Deepak Nitrite Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd, Oberoi Realty Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 20 January 2026.

Deepak Nitrite Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd, Oberoi Realty Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 20 January 2026. Aditya Birla Fashion & Retail Ltd recorded volume of 875.18 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 26.82 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 32.63 lakh shares. The stock lost 5.49% to Rs.67.94. Volumes stood at 78.31 lakh shares in the last session. Deepak Nitrite Ltd recorded volume of 13.41 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 18.07 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 74208 shares. The stock gained 3.28% to Rs.1,586.00. Volumes stood at 59157 shares in the last session. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd witnessed volume of 28.58 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.76 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.66 lakh shares. The stock dropped 12.62% to Rs.642.40. Volumes stood at 3.73 lakh shares in the last session. Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd clocked volume of 74.16 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.6 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9.75 lakh shares. The stock lost 1.89% to Rs.113.74. Volumes stood at 13.95 lakh shares in the last session. Oberoi Realty Ltd saw volume of 30.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.73 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4.47 lakh shares. The stock dropped 8.57% to Rs.1,513.00. Volumes stood at 4.43 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdityaBirFas_74925452111_40912.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British pound jumps sharply to one-week high against a weak dollar; UK unemployment rate steadies at 5.1%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-jumps-sharply-to-one-week-high-against-a-weak-dollar-uk-unemployment-rate-steadies-at-51/1665972</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665972</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The British pound is seen adding close to 1% against the dollar on Tuesday amid sharp decline in the greenback overseas.

The British pound is seen adding close to 1% against the dollar on Tuesday amid sharp decline in the greenback overseas. The dollar index lingers at a one-week low, well below 99 mark on escalating tensions after US President Donald Trump announcement to impose new tariffs on goods from eight European countries fueled concerns about a broader trade war. US President Donald Trump said over the weekend that a 10% tariff would be imposed from February 1 on goods from Denmark, Sweden, France, Germany, the Netherlands, Finland, Britain, and Norway until the US is allowed to purchase Greenland. Besides, UK labor market report showed that the unemployment rate remained steady at 5.1%, while it was expected to drop to 5%. The report also showed that the economy added 82K fresh workers after a reduction in the labor force by 17K in the three months ending in October. Pound Sterling jumps to near 1.3481 against the dollar, up 0.78% on the day. On the NSE, GBP/INR futures climb 0.54% at 122.66.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures reassess demand outlook]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-oil-futures-reassess-demand-outlook/1665968</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665968</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Crude oil prices stayed on the back foot on Tuesday, with WTI futures drifting below the $59 per barrel mark as investors reassessed the demand outlook amid rising global trade frictions.

Crude oil prices stayed on the back foot on Tuesday, with WTI futures drifting below the $59 per barrel mark as investors reassessed the demand outlook amid rising global trade frictions. Concerns grew after President Trump warned of additional tariffs on European partners over the Greenland issue, a move that could weigh on economic momentum and energy consumption. While demand worries dominated sentiment, immediate supply risks eased after signals from Washington suggested a delay in any military action involving Iran, calming fears of near-term disruptions to Middle Eastern oil flows. With the market already struggling with a notable supply glut, pressure persisted on prices, and MCX April crude futures slipped around 0.5% to Rs 5,396 per barrel. Traders are now focused on the IEA’s monthly report due Wednesday for fresh guidance on global supply-demand dynamics.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/steel-long-pipes-in-crude-oil-factory-during-sunset-picture_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank posts 13% YoY jump in Q3 PAT; deposits rise to Rs 16.60 lakh crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/punjab-national-bank-posts-13-yoy-jump-in-q3-pat-deposits-rise-to-rs-1660-lakh-crore/1665962</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665962</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income fell by 4.5% to Rs 10,533 crore in the December’25 quarter from Rs 11,032 crore recorded in the December’24 quarter.

Net interest income fell by 4.5% to Rs 10,533 crore in the December’25 quarter from Rs 11,032 crore recorded in the December’24 quarter. Net interest margin (NIM) for Q3 FY26 was 2.52% as against 2.93% for Q3 FY25. Operating expenses for the period under review added up to Rs 8,074 crore, up 3.2% YoY. Accordingly, operating profit for Q3 FY26 was Rs 7481 crore, higher by 13% as compared with Rs 6621 crore posted in Q3 FY25. The bank has made a provision of Rs 1,150 crore in Q3 FY26. It had written back provision amounting to Rs 285 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 6,331 crore, down by 8.3% from Rs 6,906 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The gross NPA ratio improved by 90 basis points YoY to 3.19% as on 31 December 2025 from 4.09% as on 31 December 2024. The net NPA ratio improved by 9 basis points YoY to 0.32% as on 31 December 2025 from 0.41% as on 31 December 2024. The provision coverage ratio improved by 22 basis points YoY 96.99% as on 31 December 2025. The global business of the bank grew by 9.5% to Rs 28,91,528 crore as on 31 December 2025 from Rs 26,39,991 crore as on 31 December 2024. Global deposits registered a growth of 8.5% YoY basis to Rs 16.60 lakh crore while global advances increased by 10.9% on YoY basis to Rs 12.31 lakh croreas on 31 December 2025. CRAR improved to 16.77% as on 31 December 2025 from 15.41% as on 31 December 2024, reflecting an increase of 136 basis points. Punjab National Bank is engaged in treasury operations, corporate/wholesale banking, retail banking, digital banking, and others. As on 31 December 2025, the bank has 10,261 domestic branches and 2 international branches. Out of total branches, the bank has 63.3% branches in rural & semi-urban areas. The scrip fell 1.99% to currently trade at Rs 125.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/exide-industries-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1665934</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665934</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Exide Industries Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 335.5, down 1.99% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.Exide Industries Ltd has lost around 8.4% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Exide Industries Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.32% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27632.45, down 1.42% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.22 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.43 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 335, down 2.22% on the day. Exide Industries Ltd tumbled 11.04% in last one year as compared to a 10.4% rally in NIFTY and a 22.13% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 27.97 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ExideInds_97756038201_111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Power Company Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-power-company-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1665935</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665935</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Power Company Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Tata Power Company Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 358, down 1.43% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.Tata Power Company Ltd has eased around 5.99% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Tata Power Company Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34116.8, down 1.51% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 18.54 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 38.76 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 358.7, down 1.32% on the day. Tata Power Company Ltd tumbled 2.16% in last one year as compared to a 10.4% rally in NIFTY and a 2.06% fall in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 49.66 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataPowerCo_38377109932_554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Total Gas Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-total-gas-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1665936</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665936</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Adani Total Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Adani Total Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 536.8, down 1.45% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.Adani Total Gas Ltd has lost around 5.61% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Adani Total Gas Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34116.8, down 1.51% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.81 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.1 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 97.17 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniGas_11917231_39108.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NHPC Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nhpc-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1665937</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665937</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NHPC Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

NHPC Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 77.77, down 2.08% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.NHPC Ltd has gained around 0.13% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which NHPC Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34116.8, down 1.51% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 69.09 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 152.79 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 78.05, down 1.77% on the day. NHPC Ltd tumbled 1.58% in last one year as compared to a 10.4% rally in NIFTY and a 2.06% fall in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 25.2 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NHPCLtd_36439171799_12584.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SJVN Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sjvn-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1665938</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665938</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SJVN Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

SJVN Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 72.31, down 2.97% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.SJVN Ltd has eased around 0.88% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which SJVN Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34116.8, down 1.51% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 43.9 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 149.83 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 36.52 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SJVN_64650197956_12076.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/patanjali-foods-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1665939</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665939</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Patanjali Foods Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 503.7, down 3.37% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.Patanjali Foods Ltd has eased around 8.44% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Patanjali Foods Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 5.09% in last one month and is currently quoting at 52489.95, down 0.44% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 11.62 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 15.21 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 502.7, down 3.79% on the day. Patanjali Foods Ltd tumbled 17.59% in last one year as compared to a 10.4% rally in NIFTY and a 6.05% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 39.95 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RuchiSoyaInds_47333195530_704.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prime Focus Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prime-focus-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1665940</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665940</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Focus Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Prime Focus Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 207.6, down 4.49% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.Prime Focus Ltd has eased around 5.94% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Prime Focus Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.98% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1384.6, down 0.71% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 15.82 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 52.1 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PrimeFocus_61388003233_27264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Abbott India Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/abbott-india-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1665941</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665941</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Abbott India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Abbott India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 27530, down 0.79% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.65% on the day, quoting at 25418.8. The Sensex is at 82812.65, down 0.52%.Abbott India Ltd has lost around 1.71% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Abbott India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.58% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22136.25, down 1.16% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1904 shares today, compared to the daily average of 8029 shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 39.11 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AbbottIndia_90273760573_90.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with major losses; realty shares tumble; VIX jumps 4.67%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-major-losses-realty-shares-tumble-vix-jumps-467/1665933</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665933</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in the afternoon trade as investors weighed persistent global trade uncertainties and continued foreign fund outflows, even as attention remained fixed on the unfolding quarterly earnings season.

The key equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in the afternoon trade as investors weighed persistent global trade uncertainties and continued foreign fund outflows, even as attention remained fixed on the unfolding quarterly earnings season. The Nifty traded below the 25,450 mark. All the sectoral indices in the NSE traded in the red with realty, IT and auto shares losing the most. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 481.02 points or 0.58% to 82,766.84. The Nifty 50 index fell 170.05 points or 0.67% to 25,415.95. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.85% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.96%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 853 shares rose and 3,257 shares fell. A total of 165 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 4.67% to 12.38. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 2,04,17,040shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 13:20 IST on Tuesday (20 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.23 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Gainers & Losers: Tata Consumer Products (up 1.79%), Dr Reddy's Laboratories (up 1.70%), HDFC Bank (up 0.58%), Hindustan Unilever (up 0.31%) and ICICI Bank (up 0.30%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Eternal (down 3.61%), Coal India (down 2.73%), Interglobe Aviation (down 2.59%), Bajaj Finance (down 2.48%) and Trent (down 2.42%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: LTIMindtree dropped 6.37% after the company reported a 30.73% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 970.6 crore despite a 3.72% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q2 September 2025. Ceat declined 3.37%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 60.40% to Rs 155.77 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 97.11 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 25.97% to Rs 4,157.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atishay hit a lower circuit of 10% after its standalone net profit slipped 10.90% to Rs 1.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2.11 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 1.51% to Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Oberoi Realty dropped 7.90% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 18.10% to Rs 622.64 crore, despite a 5.77% rise in net sales to Rs 1,492.64 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Global Markets: European markets opened lower on Tuesday as the specter of fresh trade tariffs lingers, hurting market sentiment. Asian stocks traded lower as a resurgence of trade-war concerns hit risk sentiment and sparked selling in U.S. assets. U.S. President Donald Trump's push to take control of Greenland by threatening additional tariffs—a move that risks fueling trade tensions with Europe—has led to uncertainty in the markets, with investors scurrying for safe-haven assets, including the Swiss franc and gold. The tensions have revived talk of the 'Sell America' trade that emerged in the aftermath of his sweeping "Liberation Day" levies last April, where investors sell U.S. stocks, dollars, and Treasuries. That trade appeared to be gathering momentum in Asian hours on Tuesday. Trump's threats triggered a sharp pushback in Europe, and his remarks have raised questions on the outlook of trade deals struck since then with Europe. All eyes will now be on Davos, where Trump is expected to meet global business leaders on Wednesday, as the U.S. president's presence looms large over the annual gathering of the global elite in Switzerland. Meanwhile, Japan's Nikkei saw some selling as investors looked ahead to next month's election. Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi is seeking voter backing for increased spending, tax cuts, and a new security strategy that is expected to accelerate a defence buildup. U.S. cash equity markets were closed on Monday for Martin Luther King Jr. Day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Teleservices' net loss narrows to Rs 150 crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-teleservices-net-loss-narrows-to-rs-150-crore-in-q3/1665929</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665929</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 11.6% YoY to Rs 294.31 crore during the quarter.

Revenue from operations fell 11.6% YoY to Rs 294.31 crore during the quarter. EBITDA improved by 17.2% to Rs 175.62 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 149.79 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Depreciation charge added up to Rs 35.67 crore while finance costs aggregated to Rs 287.82 crore in Q3 FY26. The company had a negative networth Rs 20,564.48 crore as on 31 December 2025. Tata Teleservices (Maharashtra) provides connectivity and communication solutions market for SME segment in India. The company offers a comprehensive portfolio of Information and Communication Technology (ICT) services, including connectivity, collaboration, cloud & SaaS, security, and marketing solutions - under its brand Tata Tele Business Services (TTBS). The scrip fell 1.47% to currently trade at Rs 44.39 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataTeleMah_38725974253_21214.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sai Silks (Kalamandir) slips after Q3 PAT slides 17% YoY to Rs 38 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sai-silks-kalamandir-slips-after-q3-pat-slides-17-yoy-to-rs-38-crore/1665928</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665928</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) dropped 16.97% YoY to Rs 51.09 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) dropped 16.97% YoY to Rs 51.09 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA declined 10.99% to Rs 70.24 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 78.91 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin reduced to 17.08% in Q3 FY26 from 17.59% in Q3 FY25. Total expense tanked 7.26% year on year to Rs 364.15 crore during the quarter. Employee benefits expense was at Rs 58.01 crore (up 7.97% YoY), while other expenses stood at Rs 45.45 crore (up 17.56% YoY) during the period under review. Sai Silks (Kalamandir) is predominantly engaged in the business of buying and selling textiles and textile articles as a retailer. It retails sarees, women's wear, men's wear, and kids' wear.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SaiSilksKalamandirLtd_62265977_34768.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen softens to 158.4 as political and policy uncertainty loom]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-softens-to-1584-as-political-and-policy-uncertainty-loom/1665927</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665927</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen edged lower to near 158.4 per dollar on Tuesday, following a bout of sharp volatility, as domestic political developments unsettled investor sentiment.

The Japanese yen edged lower to near 158.4 per dollar on Tuesday, following a bout of sharp volatility, as domestic political developments unsettled investor sentiment. Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s announcement to dissolve parliament and call a snap election on February 8 injected fresh uncertainty, with the scale of the ruling party’s majority seen as pivotal for the future direction of fiscal policy. Market participants also remained cautious ahead of the Bank of Japan’s two-day policy meeting concluding Friday, preferring to wait for clearer guidance on the timing of the next rate increase. Even so, expectations of an eventual policy shift by the BoJ, the likelihood of official intervention to curb excessive currency weakness, and a prevailing risk-averse global backdrop may continue to provide some underlying support to the yen.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>