<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:42:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patel Retail climbs after Q3 PAT surges 96% YoY to Rs 12 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/patel-retail-climbs-after-q3-pat-surges-96-yoy-to-rs-12-cr/1670260</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670260</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) surged 101.64% YoY to Rs 15.99 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) surged 101.64% YoY to Rs 15.99 crore during the quarter. Total expenses climbed 33.14% to Rs 295.12 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 221.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 136.97 crore (up 66.83% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 8.96 crore (up 10.34% YoY) while finance cost stood at Rs 3.04 crore (down 26.39% YoY) during the period under review. Patel Retail is a diversified retail and food processing company with a strong presence in value retail supermarkets, food exports, and agri-processing. Its business spans retail (including private labels Patel Fresh, Indian Chaska, Blue Nation, and Patel Essentials) and non-retail activities like trading and exports.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PatelRetailLtd_42397023_86600.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Forge gains as subsidiary raises Rs 300 crore from Premji Invest]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-forge-gains-as-subsidiary-raises-rs-300-crore-from-premji-invest/1670259</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670259</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Following the transaction, Premji Invest will hold a 23% stake in JSA on a fully diluted basis.

Following the transaction, Premji Invest will hold a 23% stake in JSA on a fully diluted basis. The funds will be used to accelerate JSA’s growth by expanding casting capacity, investing in medium-casting capabilities and pursuing industry consolidation through acquisitions. JSA is a key supplier of critical ferrous castings for industrial and automotive applications. Commenting on this partnership, Amit Kalyani, vice chairman & joint managing director, Bharat Forge said, “Since 2022 when we acquired JSA, the company has delivered excellent financial performance with topline, exports and profitability growing at a CAGR of 17%, 24% and 25% respectively, while enhancing its product mix and customer base. We are delighted to partner with Premji Invest (PI), a renowned and highly respected investor, in the next phase of JSA’s growth journey.” Manoj Jaiswal, Partner, Premji Invest, who leads the firm’s Industrials and Buyout investmentssaid, “We are excited to partner with Bharat Forge, a premier engineering and manufacturing conglomerate in the country. Collaborating with leading conglomerates on their growth and consolidation journey is one of our strategic pillars. Through our investment in JSA, we look forward to jointly building a leading ferrous casting platform in the country.” Bharat Forge manufactures an extensive array of critical and safety components for several sectors, including automobiles (across commercial & passenger vehicles), oil & gas, aerospace, locomotives, marine, energy (across renewable and non-renewable sources), construction, mining, and general engineering. The company’s consolidated net profit rallied 23% to Rs 299.27 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 243.29 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations soared 9.31% YoY to Rs 4,031.92 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatForge_36016338711_69.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gokaldas Exports Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gokaldas-exports-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1670254</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670254</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Northern ARC Capital Ltd, Intellect Design Arena Ltd, MOIL Ltd and OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 February 2026.

Northern ARC Capital Ltd, Intellect Design Arena Ltd, MOIL Ltd and OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 February 2026. Gokaldas Exports Ltd tumbled 6.77% to Rs 568.8 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 67555 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 83053 shares in the past one month. Northern ARC Capital Ltd crashed 6.45% to Rs 239.9. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 76404 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 23870 shares in the past one month. Intellect Design Arena Ltd lost 6.43% to Rs 826.3. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 43200 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14686 shares in the past one month. MOIL Ltd shed 6.20% to Rs 326.65. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 71750 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 79571 shares in the past one month. OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd corrected 6.17% to Rs 1135.85. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 51789 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18688 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GokaldasExports_17758090823_12966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Asian Paints rises as broker flags crude tailwind, easing competition]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/asian-paints-rises-as-broker-flags-crude-tailwind-easing-competition/1670256</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670256</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Brent crude, a key raw material for paint makers, was down around 5% on the day, providing relief on input costs.

Brent crude, a key raw material for paint makers, was down around 5% on the day, providing relief on input costs. The brokerage expects Asian Paints to deliver volume growth of about 11% in Q4, aided by improving cost dynamics and a shift toward more rational competitive behaviour in the industry. It noted that a new paint entrant is likely to adopt a more measured strategy following price hikes implemented in January. The research firm also expects a reversal of the earlier 10% promotional intensity on 4-litre packs. From a valuation perspective, the brokerage said Asian Paints is now trading in a more comfortable zone. Asian Paints, established in 1942, is the largest listed company in India's decorative paints segment. It ranked among the top eight decorative coatings companies in the world. It is engaged in the business of manufacturing, selling, and distributing paints, coatings, and products related to home décor and bath fittings and providing related services. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 4.55% to Rs 1,059.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,110.48 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AsianPaints_3886867460_34.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/california-software-company-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-losers-in-b-group/1670248</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670248</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Wealth First Portfolio Managers Ltd, Arisinfra Solutions Ltd, Rajdarshan Industries Ltd and Integra Essentia Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 February 2026.

Wealth First Portfolio Managers Ltd, Arisinfra Solutions Ltd, Rajdarshan Industries Ltd and Integra Essentia Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 February 2026. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup tumbled 18.85% to Rs 3.1 at 14:17 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 32591 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4231 shares in the past one month. Wealth First Portfolio Managers Ltd lost 14.18% to Rs 750. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 13 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 69 shares in the past one month. Arisinfra Solutions Ltd crashed 12.87% to Rs 95.1. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 58663 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 50097 shares in the past one month. Rajdarshan Industries Ltd pared 11.81% to Rs 38. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 19 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 229 shares in the past one month. Integra Essentia Ltd fell 10.98% to Rs 1.46. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.85 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.58 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Electronics gains after foreign broker hikes target price]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-electronics-gains-after-foreign-broker-hikes-target-price/1670245</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670245</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The broker cited strong multi-year revenue visibility and a solid order book.

The broker cited strong multi-year revenue visibility and a solid order book. It flagged BEL's order backlog and indigenisation levels of about 70%-73%. Key programmes in the pipeline include QRSAM and Kusha, which are largely indigenous. The brokerage also highlighted the Union Budget’s 18% rise in defence capital expenditure for FY27 to Rs 2.2 lakh crore, with 75% of procurement earmarked for the domestic market, as a positive driver for the stock. Bharat Electronics (BEL) is a Navratna PSU under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. It manufactures electronic products and systems for the army, navy, and air force. Its standalone net profit jumped 20.81% to Rs 1,590.06 crore on 23.72% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,121.98 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company’s order book position stood at Rs 73,015 crore as of 1 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatElectron_81586952923_2298.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 24,950 mark; media shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-24950-mark-media-shares-decline/1670244</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670244</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major gains in the mid- afternoon trade, rebounding from losses in a special weekend session, even as investors assessed the implications of the federal budget, which fell short of expectations on measures to attract foreign capital.

The domestic equity indices traded with major gains in the mid- afternoon trade, rebounding from losses in a special weekend session, even as investors assessed the implications of the federal budget, which fell short of expectations on measures to attract foreign capital. The Nifty traded above the 24,950 mark. Media shares extended losses for second consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 539.29 points or 0.67% to 81,262.23. The Nifty 50 index rose 137.05 points or 0.55% to 24,962.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 Mid-Cap index fell 0.22% and the S&P BSE 250 Small-Cap index shed 0.68%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,490 shares rose and 2,647 shares fell. A total of 159 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index declined 0.92% to 1,347.70. The index fell 2.70% in for the two consecutive trading session. Saregama India (down 3.79%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 2.82%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 2.12%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 2.08%), Nazara Technologies (down 1.91%), D B Corp (down 1.15%), Sun TV Network (down 0.62%) declined. On the other hand, Prime Focus (up 2.62%), Tips Music (up 1.78%) and PVR Inox (up 0.66%) added. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 1.19% to 6.775 compared with previous session close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.4700 compared with its close of 90.9350 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 2.59% to Rs 143,927. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.11% to 97.12. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.47% to 4.224. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell $3.11 or 4.49% to $64.21 a barrel. Brent crude prices slid after U.S. President Donald Trump said over the weekend that Iran was “seriously talking” with Washington, signaling a possible easing of tensions with the OPEC member. The comments helped temper fears of a potential military strike that had earlier pushed oil prices to multi-month highs. Stocks in Spotlight: Atul Auto soared 5.26% after the company reported a 30.09% rise in total sales to 3,606 units in January 2026 as against 2,772 units sold in January 2025. Bartronics India added 1.11% after the company reported standalone net profit of Rs 2.44 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with net loss of Rs 0.32 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 48.34 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 455.63%, compared with Rs 8.70 crore in Q3 FY25. Brahmaputra Infrastructure rose 2.04% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 68.91 crore from the Water Resources Department, Assam, for riverbank protection works in the state.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Latent View Analytics Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-latent-view-analytics-ltd-counter/1670242</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670242</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Clean Science & Technology Ltd, Godrej Agrovet Ltd, ZF Commercial Vehicle Control System India Ltd, Can Fin Homes Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 02 February 2026.

Clean Science & Technology Ltd, Godrej Agrovet Ltd, ZF Commercial Vehicle Control System India Ltd, Can Fin Homes Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 02 February 2026. Latent View Analytics Ltd saw volume of 118.57 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 49.15 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.41 lakh shares. The stock increased 9.01% to Rs.455.75. Volumes stood at 3.43 lakh shares in the last session. Clean Science & Technology Ltd recorded volume of 17.22 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.5 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.30 lakh shares. The stock lost 1.16% to Rs.798.70. Volumes stood at 7.15 lakh shares in the last session. Godrej Agrovet Ltd clocked volume of 8.45 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.98 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.21 lakh shares. The stock gained 5.62% to Rs.548.45. Volumes stood at 86531 shares in the last session. ZF Commercial Vehicle Control System India Ltd clocked volume of 58194 shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.74 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10134 shares. The stock lost 0.71% to Rs.15,102.00. Volumes stood at 7991 shares in the last session. Can Fin Homes Ltd witnessed volume of 8.55 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.87 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.75 lakh shares. The stock dropped 0.83% to Rs.890.80. Volumes stood at 88385 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/latentviewanalytics_44641535_39858.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brahmaputra Infra rises after securing order worth Rs 69 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brahmaputra-infra-rises-after-securing-order-worth-rs-69-crore/1670237</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670237</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves underwater and above-water riverbank protection works under the Jorhat sub-project, spanning the Sivasagar, Jorhat and Golaghat districts, and forms part of Package No.

The order involves underwater and above-water riverbank protection works under the Jorhat sub-project, spanning the Sivasagar, Jorhat and Golaghat districts, and forms part of Package No. W-AF-03-RP-JH (Lot 2) under the ADB-funded Climate Resilient Brahmaputra Integrated Flood and Riverbank Erosion Risk Management Project. The contract has been awarded on an engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) basis and is to be executed within a period of 30 months. Brahmaputra Infrastructure is a versatile construction company with a significant presence in sectors like highways & roads, buildings, bridges/flyovers, airports, tunnels, and other civil construction works. On a consolidated basis, Brahmaputra Infrastructure reported a net profit of Rs 14.64 crore in Q2 September 2025, a surge of 3,653.85% from Rs 0.39 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales rose 188.89% year-on-year to Rs 90.19 crore during the same period.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrahmaputraInf_89782917235_28067.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Saksoft drops after Q3 PAT slides 19% QoQ to Rs 29 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/saksoft-drops-after-q3-pat-slides-19-qoq-to-rs-29-cr/1670238</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670238</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax fell 16.36% QoQ to Rs 42.88 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional items and tax fell 16.36% QoQ to Rs 42.88 crore during the quarter. Exceptional items of Rs 4.86 crore were related to labour codes. Total expenses dropped 1.28% to Rs 210.73 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 213.47 crore in Q2 FY26.employeee benefit expenses stood at Rs 130.76 crore (up 1.51% QoQ), support/third party charges was at Rs 65.45 crore (down 4.62% QoQ) during the period under review. Saksoft is leading digital transformation solution partner for fintech, transportation & logistics, telecom & utilities, retail e-commerce and healthcare customers worldwide.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Saksoft_75874315701_26503.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Force Motors’ January 2026 sales rise 5% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/force-motors-january-2026-sales-rise-5-yoy/1670236</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670236</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s domestic sales grew 4.92% to 3,665 units in January 2026, compared with 3,493 units sold in January 2025.

The company’s domestic sales grew 4.92% to 3,665 units in January 2026, compared with 3,493 units sold in January 2025. Exports declined 4.81% to 99 units in January 2026, compared with 104 units in the same period last year. Force Motors is engaged in manufacturing light commercial vehicles, utility vehicles, and engines. It is an automobile company with a focus on the design, development, and manufacture of a range of automotive components, aggregates, and vehicles. The company reported a 159.68% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 350.7 crore in Q2 FY25, compared with Rs 135.05 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Revenue from operations rose 7.21% to Rs 2,081.4 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 1,941.33 crore in Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.90% to Rs 18,631.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ForceMotors_49967151331_53.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 24,850; European mrkt decline ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-24850-european-mrkt-decline/1670212</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670212</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 24,850 mark. Oil & gas, realty and FMCG shares advanced, while media, healthcare, and IT shares declined. At 1:35 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 296.76 points or 0.37% to 81,019.70. The Nifty 50 index rose 65.70 points or 0.26% to 24,891.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 Mid-Cap index fell 0.62% and the S&P BSE 250 Small-Cap index shed 1.15%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,279 shares rose and 2,825 shares fell. A total of 159 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. Politics: Sunetra Pawar was sworn in Maharashtra's first woman Deputy Chief Minister on 31 January 2026, days after her husband Ajit Pawar's fatal plane crash on January 28 near Baramati Airport. A former Rajya Sabha MP and social activist from Baramati, Sunetra Pawar took oath at Lok Bhavan in Mumbai and said she would carry forward Ajit Pawar’s legacy of public service, focusing on social equality, women and youth empowerment, rural upliftment, and administrative reform. She will work alongside Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis and Deputy Chief Minister Eknath Shinde, strengthening the Mahayuti alliance. Sunetra Pawar is expected to handle portfolios such as Excise, Sports, and Youth Welfare and Minorities Development, with the Finance portfolio temporarily retained by the chief minister. Gainers & Losers: Power Grid Corporation of India (up 4.34%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 4%), Tata Consumer ProductS (up 3.33%), Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (up 3.09%) and Reliance Industries (up 2.15%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Shriram Finance (down 5.66%), Max Healthcare Institute (down 2.86%), Cipla (down 2.53%), Axis Bank (down 2.17%) and Infosys (down 1.98%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Atul Auto soared 6.87% after the company reported a 30.09% rise in total sales to 3,606 units in January 2026 as against 2,772 units sold in January 2025. Gokaldas Exports dropped 6.86% after the company reported 70.97% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 14.61 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 50.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations shed 0.92% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 978.65 crore during the quarter. Maruti Suzuki India shed 0.01%. The company reported total sales of 236,963 units in January 2026, registering an 11.6% YoY growth compared with 212,251 units sold in January 2025. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 394 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European equities traded lower on Monday as a sell-off in precious metals dented investor sentiment at the start of a data-heavy week marked by key corporate earnings, central bank meetings, and macroeconomic releases. Data released earlier showed that German retail sales edged up 0.1% month-on-month in December, improving from a 0.5% decline recorded in the previous month. Asian equities slipped as investors digested fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold continued to slide after last week’s drop. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Marico Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/marico-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1670210</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670210</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Marico Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Marico Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 718.35, down 0.32% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.25% on the day, quoting at 24887.8. The Sensex is at 81014.79, up 0.36%.Marico Ltd has eased around 7.08% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Marico Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 5.94% in last one month and is currently quoting at 50042.8, up 0.45% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 21 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 20.29 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 722.4, up 0.06% on the day. Marico Ltd jumped 6.68% in last one year as compared to a 6.54% rally in NIFTY and a 12.46% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 48.22 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Marico_77423580094_12585.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alkem Laboratories Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alkem-laboratories-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1670211</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670211</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Alkem Laboratories Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Alkem Laboratories Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5432, down 2.39% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.25% on the day, quoting at 24887.8. The Sensex is at 81014.79, up 0.36%.Alkem Laboratories Ltd has eased around 2.17% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Alkem Laboratories Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 6.26% in last one month and is currently quoting at 21535.3, down 1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 36448 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.21 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5435.5, down 1.99% on the day. Alkem Laboratories Ltd jumped 7.6% in last one year as compared to a 6.54% rally in NIFTY and a 0.2% fall in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 29.73 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlkemLab_4180671424_19299.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Atul Auto spurts on reporting 30% YoY increase in January’25 sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/atul-auto-spurts-on-reporting-30-yoy-increase-in-january25-sales/1670208</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670208</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s domestic sales increased 23.72% to 2,942 units in January 2026, compared to 2,378 units posted in January 2025.

The company’s domestic sales increased 23.72% to 2,942 units in January 2026, compared to 2,378 units posted in January 2025. Atul Auto is a leading three-wheeler manufacturing company in Rajkot, Gujarat, India. It has a complete range of 3-wheeler products across the fuel range: diesel, petrol, CNG, LPG, and electric. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 69.5% to Rs 9.17 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 5.41 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Total revenue from operations grew by 10.2% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 200.17 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AtulAuto_3226523977_14817.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bartronics India gains on reporting turnaround Q3 numbers ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bartronics-india-gains-on-reporting-turnaround-q3-numbers/1670206</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670206</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations stood at Rs 48.34 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 455.63%, compared with Rs 8.70 crore in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations stood at Rs 48.34 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 455.63%, compared with Rs 8.70 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported pre-tax profit of Rs 2.68 crore during the quarter, compared with pre-tax loss of Rs 0.32 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Total expenses surged 403.85% to Rs 45.80 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 9.09 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating expenses stood at Rs 43.37 crore (up 539.68% YoY) and employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 1.67 crore (up 16.78% YoY) during the period under review. Bartronics India (BIL), is a financial inclusion and rural fintech infrastructure company focused on strengthening access to digital and assisted banking across rural and semi-urban India. Through its Corporate Business Correspondent network and technology-enabled operating model, Bartronics supports public sector banks and Regional Rural Banks in delivering secure, scalable, and socially impactful financial services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BartronicsIndia_49614244830_26860.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen stabilises after sharp drop as fed shift and election risks loom]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-stabilises-after-sharp-drop-as-fed-shift-and-election-risks-loom/1670204</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670204</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen pared earlier losses on Monday, trading around 154.62 per dollar after last week’s sharp selloff.

The Japanese yen pared earlier losses on Monday, trading around 154.62 per dollar after last week’s sharp selloff. The currency had fallen nearly 1% on Friday following President Trump’s nomination of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair, a move seen as reinforcing a stronger dollar. Pressure on the yen was compounded by Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s comments endorsing the benefits of a weaker currency for exporters, while investors brace for volatility ahead of the February 8 snap election. Expectations of fiscal stimulus continue to weigh on the yen and government bonds, even as the Bank of Japan held its policy rate at 0.75%, keeping borrowing costs at their highest level since 1995.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers pare losses; Nifty trades above 24,850 marks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-pare-losses-nifty-trades-above-24850-marks/1670202</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670202</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks pared all early losses and traded with modest gains in the afternoon trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks pared all early losses and traded with modest gains in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 24,850 mark. Auto shares advanced after declining in the previous trading session. At 12:28 ST, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 383.84 points or 0.48% to 81,105.96. The Nifty 50 index added 70.15 points or 0.30% to 24,895.60. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 1.10% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index declined 1.42%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,189 shares rose and 2,779 shares fell. A total of 197 shares were unchanged. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, slipped 2.31% to 14.75. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures were trading at 24,955.10, at a premium of 59.50 points as compared with the spot at 24,895.60. The Nifty option chain for the 24 February 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 55.3 lakh contracts at the 25,500 strike price. Maximum put OI of 49.1 lakh contracts was seen at 25,000 strike price. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. Politics: Sunetra Pawar was sworn in Maharashtra's first woman Deputy Chief Minister on 31 January 2026, days after her husband Ajit Pawar's fatal plane crash on January 28 near Baramati Airport. A former Rajya Sabha MP and social activist from Baramati, Sunetra Pawar took oath at Lok Bhavan in Mumbai and said she would carry forward Ajit Pawar’s legacy of public service, focusing on social equality, women and youth empowerment, rural upliftment, and administrative reform. She will work alongside Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis and Deputy Chief Minister Eknath Shinde, strengthening the Mahayuti alliance. Sunetra Pawar is expected to handle portfolios such as Excise, Sports, and Youth Welfare and Minorities Development, with the Finance portfolio temporarily retained by the chief minister. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index rose 0.37% to 26,286.70. The index fell 2.09% in the past trading session. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 3.03%), Bharat Forge (up 2.31%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 0.75%), Uno Minda (up 0.74%), TVS Motor Company (up 0.56%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 0.36%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (up 0.2%), Ashok Leyland (up 0.12%), Bosch (up 0.1%) and Eicher Motors (up 0.09%) advanced. On the other hand, Tube Investments of India (down 1.91%), Exide Industries (down 1.41%) and Bajaj Auto (down 0.77%) edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: Agarwal Industrial Corporation rose 0.38%. The company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 218.59 crore from Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL). Gokaldas Exports dropped 7.06% after the company reported 70.97% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 14.61 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 50.34 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/biofil-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1670193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670193</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd, United Foodbrands Ltd, Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd and Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 February 2026.

Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd, United Foodbrands Ltd, Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd and Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 February 2026. Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd surged 17.88% to Rs 40.81 at 12:01 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 51521 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16624 shares in the past one month. Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd spiked 13.24% to Rs 135.95. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 6910 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5797 shares in the past one month. United Foodbrands Ltd soared 13.00% to Rs 245.1. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.89 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5029 shares in the past one month. Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd advanced 12.15% to Rs 107.88. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1192 shares in the past one month. Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd jumped 11.01% to Rs 25.2. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 203 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 769 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BiofilChemicals_25533397190_3284.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Agarwal Industrial Corp gains on bagging Rs 219-cr order from BPCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/agarwal-industrial-corp-gains-on-bagging-rs-219-cr-order-from-bpcl/1670192</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670192</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves the supply of bulk bitumen (VG-30 and VG-40 grades) to BPCL’s Kakinada and Mangalore locations.

The contract involves the supply of bulk bitumen (VG-30 and VG-40 grades) to BPCL’s Kakinada and Mangalore locations. The firm order comprises 32,000 metric tonnes for Kakinada and 10,800 metric tonnes for Mangalore, aggregating to a total quantity of around 42,800 metric tonnes. The estimated contract value includes firm orders of approximately Rs 166.68 crore for Kakinada and Rs 51.91 crore for Mangalore. The project is scheduled to be executed over a one-year period from January 23, 2026, to January 22, 2027. Agarwal Industrial Corporation is primarily engaged in the manufacturing of bitumen and bitumen products. It also transports liquefied petroleum gas (LPG) and bituminous product. The company also forayed into the ship operating and chartering business through its subsidiary in the UAE. The company reported a 35% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 11.99 crore on a 24.8% fall in revenue to Rs 244.80 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AgarwalIndustrialCorporationLtd_81781984596_7400.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>