<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:37:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank credit growth stays firm above 14% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-credit-growth-stays-firm-above-14-on-year/1664963</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664963</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank credit growth in India continues to remain strong.

The bank credit growth in India continues to remain strong. As per the latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India, total bank credit stood at Rs 208.10 lakh crore as of 31 December 2025, marking a year-on-year surge of 14.40%. Credit growth has consistently remained above 10% in recent months.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-markets-currency-trading-concept-picture-id609801990_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee settles lower]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-settles-lower/1664959</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664959</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.4100 per Dollar on Wednesday (14 January 2025), versus its previous close of 90.2550 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Amagi Media Labs subscribed 13%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/amagi-media-labs-subscribed-13/1664950</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664950</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 35,08,780 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Wednesday (14 January 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 35,08,780 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Wednesday (14 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.13 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 41 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The IPO consists of a fresh issue of Rs 816.0 crore and offer for sale of 2,69,42,343 equity shares. At the upper end price, the issue size stands at Rs 1788.62 crore. The offer for sale (OFS) by PI Opportunities Fund-I includes up to 98,89,646 shares at the upper price band of Rs 361 per share, aggregating Rs 357.02 crore. Accel India VI (Mauritius) and Trudy Holdings are each offering up to 50,72,582 shares at the same price, amounting to Rs 183.12 crore apiece. In addition, PI Opportunities Fund-II is proposing to sell up to 3,411,792 shares at Rs 361 per share, valued at Rs 123.17 crore. Norwest Venture Partners plans to offload up to 3,381,721 shares worth Rs 122.08 crore, while multiple individual investors will collectively offer up to 228,024 shares, aggregating Rs 8.03 crore. Amagi Media Labs proposes to utilise Rs 550.06 crore from the net fresh issue proceeds towards technology and cloud infrastructure and the balance will be utilised towards funding inorganic growth through unidentified acquisitions and for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Amagi Media Labs on Monday, 12 January 2026, the company raised Rs 804.87 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 2.22 crore shares at Rs 361 each to 42 anchor investors. Amagi Media Labs (Amagi) is a software-as-a-service (SaaS) company that connects media companies to their audiences through cloud-native technology. Its platform helps content providers and distributors upload and deliver video over the internet (commonly known as streaming) through smart televisions, smartphones and applications, instead of traditional cable or set-top box services. It also helps monetize such content through targeted advertising services for advertisers. The company enables broadcasters, content owners, and streaming platforms to launch, manage, and monetise live linear channels on Free Ad-supported Streaming TV (FAST) platforms such as Pluto TV, Samsung TV Plus, Roku Channel, and others. The company’s customers include global media companies such as Vevo, Lionsgate Studios, DAZN, E.W. Scripps, Sinclair, Inc., VIZIO, Roku, The Trade Desk, JioAds and the Tennis Channel. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 6.47 crore and income from operations of Rs 704.82 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty slip for second day amid FII selling and trade deal caution]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-slip-for-second-day-amid-fii-selling-and-trade-deal-caution/1664947</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664947</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Benchmark equity indices closed lower for a second straight session on Wednesday as profit booking, foreign institutional selling, and F&O contract expiry on the BSE weighed on sentiment.

Benchmark equity indices closed lower for a second straight session on Wednesday as profit booking, foreign institutional selling, and F&O contract expiry on the BSE weighed on sentiment. Investors tracked progress on the India-US trade agreement, ongoing Q3 earnings results, and global geopolitical developments, while remaining cautious ahead of a US Supreme Court ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump’s tariff measures. The Nifty slipped below the 25,700 level. IT and automobile stocks led the declines, while metal stocks and PSU banks attracted buying interest. The S&P BSE Sensex slipped 244.98 points or 0.29% to 83,382.71. The Nifty 50 index lost 66.70 points or 0.26% to 25,665.60. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.60% while the Nifty fell 0.48%. Kotak Mahindra Bank (down 1.48%), ICICI Bank (down 1.42%) and HDFC Bank (down 1.32%) were major Nifty drags today. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.25%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 2,017 shares rose and 2,150 shares fell. A total of 178 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.09% to 11.32. Indian stock exchanges will remain shut on Thursday, 15 January 2026, on account of the Maharashtra municipal corporation elections. Economy: India's inflation based on the all-India Wholesale Price Index (WPI) increased 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, compared with a decline of 0.32% in November 2025. This marked the first increase in three months and the fastest pace since April, mainly supported by faster rises in manufacturing prices. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.32% to 6.648 compared with previous session close of 6.627. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2975 compared with its close of 90.2300 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.74% to Rs 143,299. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.12% to 99.07. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.29% to 4.159. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 18 cents or 0.27% to $65.65 a barrel. Global Markets: Dow Jones futures are down by 173 points, signaling a negative start for US stocks today. Most European indices traded higher on Wednesday as investors focused on a meeting between U.S., Greenlandic and Danish officials to discuss the future of the Arctic island. Asian indices ended higher as Japanese indexes hit record highs on Wednesday. The rally in Japanese stocks was fuelled by expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi could call for a snap election, likely in February. If called, it will be Takaichi's first time facing Japan’s voters in an election. Overnight in the U.S., all three major indexes fell as investors grappled with volatility from a flurry of proposals from U.S. President Donald Trump floated in the past few days. The S&P 500 dipped 13.53 points or 0.2% to 6,963.74, as investors sold JPMorgan despite better-than-expected numbers. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 398.21 points or 0.8% to 49,191.99. The Nasdaq Composite fell 24.03 points or 0.1% to 23,709.87. Stocks in Spotlight: Infosys rose 0.07%. The IT major reported Q3 revenue of Rs 45,479 crore, up 8.9% YoY and 2.2% QoQ. In constant currency terms, revenue grew 1.7% YoY and 0.6% QoQ. Reported IFRS operating margin stood at 18.4%, lower than 21.3% in Q3 FY25. Net profit after non-controlling interests came in at Rs 6,654 crore, down 2.2% YoY and 9.6% QoQ, impacted by a one-time Rs 1,289 crore charge related to the implementation of the labour codes. The company reported large deal total contract value of $4.8 billion, with net new deals accounting for 57%. For FY26, Infosys raised its constant currency revenue growth guidance to 3.0%-3.5% from 2%-3% earlier, while maintaining its operating margin outlook at 20%-22%. Larsen & Toubro shed 0.58%. The company said that its Heavy Civil Infrastructure business has secured a ‘large’ order from Torrent Energy Storage Solutions for the construction of India’s biggest pumped storage project in Raigad, Maharashtra. Just Dial slipped 2.05% after the company reported 10.2% decline in net profit to Rs 118 crore despite a 6.4% rise in operating revenue to Rs 305.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Elxsi fell 5.08% after the company reported 45.28% decline in net profit to Rs 108.89 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 199 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 1.52% to Rs 953.47 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 939.17 crore posted in Q3 FY25. 5paisa Capital jumped 7.60%. The company reported a 23.98% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 12.30 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 16.18 crore in the same quarter last year. Total revenue from operations fell 7.02% YoY to Rs 79.28 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Puravankara surged 9.82% after the real estate developer reported a 17% increase in sales value to Rs 1,414 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,209 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s collections climbed 22% YoY to Rs 1,140 crore in Q3 FY26. Billionbrains Garage Ventures (Groww) added 0.95%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 16.04% to Rs 546.33 crore on 19.37% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,216.07 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Union Bank of India surged 8.03% after the bank reported 8.97% rise in net profit to Rs 5,017 crore on a 1.55% increase in operating income to Rs 13,869 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Indian Overseas Bank added 1.83% after the bank's standalone net profit jumped 56.25% to Rs 1,365.12 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 873.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income rallied 15.01% year on year (YoY) to Rs 9,671.58 crore in Q3 FY26. Mini Diamonds India added 2.78% after the company said it has received an order worth Rs 14 crore from Aura Diamond, a Mumbai-based domestic entity, for the supply of lab-grown polished diamonds. Kolte-Patil Developers rose 1.02%. The company said that it has signed a joint development deal for a 1.1 million square feet residential project in Bhugaon, Pune, that has an expected gross developable value (GDV) of Rs 850 crore. Responsive Industries fell 1.78%. The company announced the resignation of Bhavneet Singh Chadha from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) and key managerial personnel of the company due to personal reasons. Quadrant Future Tek soared 9.71% after the company has received an order from Chittaranjan Locomotive Works (CLW) for the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of 353 onboard KAVACH locomotive equipment. NLC India advanced 2.04% after signing a non-binding MoU with the Government of Gujarat to develop large-scale renewable energy projects, including solar, wind, hybrid and battery storage. The projects, to be executed via its arm NLC India Renewables, carry an investment potential of about Rs 25,000 crore and align with its plan to reach 10 GW of RE capacity by 2030. Garment Mantra Lifestyle rallied 3.48% after the company said it has achieved export sales of Rs 100 crore in the current financial year, marking the highest-ever export performance since its inception. Oswal Pumps rose 1.16%. The company received an LoA worth Rs 119.92 crore from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development for the supply and installation of 3,263 off-grid DC solar pumping systems across Karnataka. Ajmera Realty & Infra India added 1.95% after the company reported quarterly sales of Rs 630 crore for Q3 FY26, marking a sharp increase of 123% compared with sales of Rs 270 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 35,08,780 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Wednesday (14 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.13 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MRPL rallies as Q3 PAT soars nearly five-fold to Rs 1,445 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mrpl-rallies-as-q3-pat-soars-nearly-five-fold-to-rs-1445-cr/1664941</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664941</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) jumped 12.99% YoY to Rs 24,711.65 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) jumped 12.99% YoY to Rs 24,711.65 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) soared 371.78% YoY to Rs 2,214.28 crore during the quarter. EBITDA stood at Rs 2,824 crore, recording the growth of 165.41% compared with Rs 1,064 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Throughput (crude and others) stood at 4.70 MMT in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 2.17% compared with Rs 4.60 crore in Q3 FY25. Debt Equity Ratio improved from 0.79 as at 30 September 2025 to 0.63 as at 31 December 2025. Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals, a subsidiary of ONGC, is Category 1 Miniratna Central Public Sector Enterprise (CPSE) under the Ministry of Petroleum & Natural Gas. The refinery has flexibility to process crudes of various API, delivering a variety of quality products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MRPL_78642234969_2496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Infosys Q3 profit slips 10% QoQ; FY26 revenue guidance raised]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/infosys-q3-profit-slips-10-qoq-fy26-revenue-guidance-raised/1664940</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664940</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On November 21, 2025, the Government of India notified provisions of the Labour Codes, which consolidate 29 existing labour laws into a unified framework governing employee benefits during and after employment.

On November 21, 2025, the Government of India notified provisions of the Labour Codes, which consolidate 29 existing labour laws into a unified framework governing employee benefits during and after employment. The changes introduce, among other measures, a uniform definition of wages and enhanced leave-related benefits. The Labour Codes have resulted in an increase in gratuity liability due to past service costs and higher leave liability, together amounting to $143 million (Rs 1,289 crore). This impact has been recognized in the Consolidated Statement of Comprehensive Income. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company's net profit declined 2.2%, while revenue increased 8.9% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 9,229 crore in Q3 FY26, down 9.78% quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) and 4.56% year-on-year (YoY). Operating profit for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 8,355 crore, declining 10.7% QoQ and 6.3% YoY. Operating margin slipped to 18.4% during the quarter, compared with 21.3% in Q3 FY25 and 21% in Q2 FY25. During Q3 FY26, constant currency (CC) revenue grew by 1.7% YoY and 0.6% QoQ. In dollar terms, the IT firm reported revenues of $5,099 million, registering a 3.2% year-on-year growth for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Free cash flow (FCF) as of 31 December 2025 was Rs 8,176 crore, down 23.20% YoY. FCF conversion was at 113.1% of net profit. The total contract value (TCV) of large deal wins was $4.8 billion in Q3 FY26, with a net new of 57%. For FY26, the company raised its revenue growth forecast to 3.0%-3.5% in constant currency terms in Q3 from 2%-3% in Q2, while maintaining its operating margin guidance at 20%-22%. The company had 1,949 active clients as of 31 December 2025, compared with 1,876 active clients as of 31 December 2024. Total headcount as of 31 December 2025 was 337,034, up 4.22% YoY. In the last twelve months, the IT services attrition rate stood at 12.3% as of 31 December 2025, as against 13.7% as of 31 December 2024. Salil Parekh, CEO and MD, said, “Infosys delivered a strong Q3 performance, demonstrating how our differentiated enterprise AI offerings, through Infosys Topaz, are consistently driving higher market share. Clients increasingly view Infosys as their preferred AI partner, given our expertise, innovation capabilities, and strong delivery track record. This has helped them unlock business potential and enhance value realization. Central to this journey is our commitment to reskill, transform, and empower our workforce to succeed in an AI-augmented world.” Infosys is a global leader in next-generation digital services and consulting. Shares of Infosys rose 0.07% to end at Rs 1,599.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Infosys_56909713360_2806.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Diversified Equity Flexicap Passive Fof  Announces Extension of NFO period]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/motilal-oswal-diversified-equity-flexicap-passive-fof-announces-extension-of-nfo-period/1664938</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664938</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced that New Fund Offer (NFO) Period of the Scheme has been modified as follows: Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Name of the Scheme Existing closing date of NFO Revised closing date of NFO Motilal Oswal Diversified Equity Flexicap Passive Fof 15 January 2026 16 January 2026

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1664935</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664935</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2025 futures closed at 25,728, a premium of 62.40 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,665.60 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2025 futures closed at 25,728, a premium of 62.40 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,665.60 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index lost 66.70 points or 0.26% to 25,665.60. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.09% to 11.32. HDFC Bank, Infosys and Vedanta were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 245 pts lower; metal index outperforms; VIX jumps 1.09% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-245-pts-lower-metal-index-outperforms-vix-jumps-109/1664934</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664934</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with moderate losses today, slipping for the second consecutive session, pressured by profit booking, continued foreign fund outflows, and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE.

The key equity barometers ended with moderate losses today, slipping for the second consecutive session, pressured by profit booking, continued foreign fund outflows, and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE. Investors remained cautious as they monitored developments on the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements, and global geopolitical events. The Nifty closed below the 25,700 mark. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex slipped 244.98 points or 0.29% to 83,382.71. The Nifty 50 index lost 66.70 points or 0.26% to 25,665.60. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.60% while the Nifty fell 0.48%. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.25%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.09% to 11.32. Trading on Indian stock exchanges will remain suspended on Thursday, 15 January 2026, as the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and the National Stock Exchange (NSE) will remain closed on account of the Maharashtra municipal corporation elections. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Metal index (up 2.70%), the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 2.13%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 0.54%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 1.08%), the Nifty Realty index (down 0.92%) and the Nifty Auto index (down 0.69%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: The annual rate of inflation based on the all-India Wholesale Price Index (WPI) increased 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, compared with a decline of 0.32% in November 2025. Inflation turned positive after three months and marked the fastest pace since April, mainly driven by higher prices of manufactured products. Inflation in manufactured products accelerated to 1.82% in December 2025 from 1.33% in November 2025, led by an increase in prices of food products, pharmaceuticals, medicinal chemical and botanical products, and cement, lime & plaster. Inflation in food products rose to 0.90% from 0.62%, while prices of pharmaceuticals increased to 1.60% from 1.39% a month earlier. Inflation in cement, lime & plaster stood at 0.30% compared with 0.08% in November. Food prices remained unchanged in December after declining 2.27% in November, supported by higher prices of milk, fruits, eggs, meat & fish. Meanwhile, inflation in fuel and power remained negative at 2.31% in December 2025 compared with a contraction of 2.27% in November, weighed down by lower prices of LPG, petrol, and high-speed diesel. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.32% to 6.648 compared with previous session close of 6.627. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2975 compared with its close of 90.2300 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.74% to Rs 143,299. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.12% to 99.07. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.29% to 4.159. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 18 cents or 0.27% to $65.65 a barrel. Global Markets: Dow Jones futures are down by 128 points, signaling a negative start for US stocks today. European markets traded higher on Wednesday as investors focused on a meeting between U.S., Greenlandic and Danish officials to discuss the future of the Arctic island. Asian markets ended higher as Japanese indexes hit record highs on Wednesday. The rally in Japanese stocks was fuelled by expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi could call for a snap election, likely in February. If called, it will be Takaichi’s first time facing Japan’s voters in an election. Overnight in the U.S., all three major indexes fell as investors grappled with volatility from a flurry of proposals from U.S. President Donald Trump floated in the past few days. The S&P 500 dipped 13.53 points or 0.2% to 6,963.74, as investors sold JPMorgan despite better-than-expected numbers. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 398.21 points or 0.8% to 49,191.99. The Nasdaq Composite fell 24.03 points or 0.1% to 23,709.87.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC AMC climbs after Q3 PAT rises 20% YoY to Rs 770 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-amc-climbs-after-q3-pat-rises-20-yoy-to-rs-770-cr/1664932</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664932</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax in the December 2025 quarter stood at Rs 1,014.60 crore, up 20.79% YoY.

Profit before tax in the December 2025 quarter stood at Rs 1,014.60 crore, up 20.79% YoY. Operating profit for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 was Rs 855.7 crore, up 15% from Rs 747.2 crore posted in the same period a year ago. The AMC had a QAAUM of Rs 9,24,900 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 compared to Rs 7,87,400 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2024, 11.4% market share in QAAUM of the mutual fund industry. QAAUM in actively managed equity-oriented funds i.e. equity oriented QAAUM excluding index funds stood at Rs 5,66,100 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 with a market share of 13.0%. The AMC is amongst the largest actively managed equity-oriented mutual fund managers in the country. The ratio of equity and non-equity oriented QAAUM is 65:35, compared to the industry ratio of 56:44 for the quarter ended December 31,2025. As of 31 December 2025, 69% of the company’s total monthly average AUM is contributed by individual investors compared to 60% for the industry. According to the company, 14.5 million Systematic transactions with a value of Rs 4,730 crore processed during the month of December 2025. As of 31 December 2025, total Live Accounts stood at 27.7 million as on December 31, 2025. Unique customers as identified by PAN or PEKRN now stands at 15.4 million as on December 31,2025 compared to 59.0 million for the industry, a penetration of 26%. HDFC Asset Management Company (HDFC AMC) is the investment manager of HDFC Mutual Fund, one of the largest mutual funds in the country. The AMC has a diversified asset class mix across equity and fixed income/others. It also has a countrywide network of branches along with a diversified distribution network comprising banks, independent financial advisors, and national distributors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCAssetManagementCompanyLtd_12019358568_21272.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index records a surge of 2.70%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-records-a-surge-of-270/1664929</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664929</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index ended up 2.70% at 11661.4 today.

Nifty Metal index ended up 2.70% at 11661.4 today. The index has added 11.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Hindustan Copper Ltd rose 6.18%, Vedanta Ltd added 6.05% and National Aluminium Company Ltd gained 4.52%. The Nifty Metal index has increased 41.00% over last one year compared to the 10.74% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index increased 2.13% and Nifty Commodities index gained 1.48% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 0.26% to close at 25665.6 while the SENSEX has slid 0.29% to close at 83382.71 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-woman-are-checking-stock-market-picture-id51119792_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends with modest cuts; Nifty settles below 25,700 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-with-modest-cuts-nifty-settles-below-25700-mark/1664930</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664930</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Headline equity indices ended a choppy session with modest losses on Wednesday, weighed down by profit booking, persistent foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE.

Headline equity indices ended a choppy session with modest losses on Wednesday, weighed down by profit booking, persistent foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE. Investors remained cautious as they tracked developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical developments. The Nifty closed below the 25,700 mark after touching an intraday high of 25,791.75 in afternoon trade. IT, realty and auto shares declined, while metal, PSU bank and oil & gas shares advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex slipped 244.98 points or 0.29% to 83,382.71. The Nifty 50 index lost 66.70 points or 0.26% to 25,665.60. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.60% while the Nifty fell 0.48%. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.25%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 2,016 shares rose and 2,147 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.09% to 11.32. Trading on Indian stock exchanges will remain suspended on Thursday, 15 January 2026, as the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and the National Stock Exchange (NSE) will remain closed on account of the Maharashtra municipal corporation elections. Economy: The annual rate of inflation based on the all-India Wholesale Price Index (WPI) increased 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, compared with a decline of 0.32% in November 2025. Inflation turned positive after three months and marked the fastest pace since April, mainly driven by higher prices of manufactured products. Inflation in manufactured products accelerated to 1.82% in December 2025 from 1.33% in November 2025, led by an increase in prices of food products, pharmaceuticals, medicinal chemical and botanical products, and cement, lime & plaster. Inflation in food products rose to 0.90% from 0.62%, while prices of pharmaceuticals increased to 1.60% from 1.39% a month earlier. Inflation in cement, lime & plaster stood at 0.30% compared with 0.08% in November. Food prices remained unchanged in December after declining 2.27% in November, supported by higher prices of milk, fruits, eggs, meat & fish. Meanwhile, inflation in fuel and power remained negative at 2.31% in December 2025 compared with a contraction of 2.27% in November, weighed down by lower prices of LPG, petrol, and high-speed diesel. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 28,88,245 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:25 IST on Wednesday (14 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.11 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 41 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index dropped 1.08% to 37,822.70. The index rose 0.65% in the past trading session. Mphasis (down 2.87%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 2.27%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 2.22%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.74%), Coforge (down 1.68%), Wipro (down 1.59%), Persistent Systems (down 1.38%), LTIMindtree (down 1.16%) and Infosys (down 0.13%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro shed 0.49%. The company said that its Heavy Civil Infrastructure business has secured a ‘large’ order from Torrent Energy Storage Solutions for the construction of India’s biggest pumped storage project in Raigad, Maharashtra. Just Dial slipped 2.32% after the company reported 10.2% decline in net profit to Rs 118 crore despite a 6.4% rise in operating revenue to Rs 305.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Elxsi fell 5.41% after the company reported 45.28% decline in net profit to Rs 108.89 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 199 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 1.52% to Rs 953.47 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 939.17 crore posted in Q3 FY25. 5paisa Capital jumped 5.40%. The company reported a 23.98% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 12.30 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 16.18 crore in the same quarter last year. Total revenue from operations fell 7.02% YoY to Rs 79.28 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Puravankara surged 6.80% after the real estate developer reported a 17% increase in sales value to Rs 1,414 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,209 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s collections climbed 22% YoY to Rs 1,140 crore in Q3 FY26. Billionbrains Garage Ventures (Groww) added 0.55%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 16.04% to Rs 546.33 crore on 19.37% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,216.07 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Union Bank of India surged 7.73% after the bank reported 8.97% rise in net profit to Rs 5,017 crore on a 1.55% increase in operating income to Rs 13,869 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Indian Overseas Bank added 1.72% after the bank’s standalone net profit jumped 56.25% to Rs 1,365.12 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 873.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income rallied 15.01% year on year (YoY) to Rs 9,671.58 crore in Q3 FY26. Mini Diamonds India added 0.94% after the company said it has received an order worth Rs 14 crore from Aura Diamond, a Mumbai-based domestic entity, for the supply of lab-grown polished diamonds. Kolte-Patil Developers rose 1.09%. The company said that it has signed a joint development deal for a 1.1 million square feet residential project in Bhugaon, Pune, that has an expected gross developable value (GDV) of Rs 850 crore. Responsive Industries fell 2.26%. The company announced the resignation of Bhavneet Singh Chadha from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) and key managerial personnel of the company due to personal reasons. Quadrant Future Tek soared 7.88% after the company has received an order from Chittaranjan Locomotive Works (CLW) for the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of 353 onboard KAVACH locomotive equipment. NLC India advanced 1.49% after the company signed Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Government of Gujarat for development of large-scale renewable energy (RE) projects. Garment Mantra Lifestyle rallied 3.48% after the company said it has achieved export sales of Rs 100 crore in the current financial year, marking the highest-ever export performance since its inception. Oswal Pumps rose 0.82%. The company received an LoA worth Rs 119.92 crore from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development for the supply and installation of 3,263 off-grid DC solar pumping systems across Karnataka. Pace Digitek slipped 1.30%. The company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 375.7 crore from Bondada Engineering for the development of a 300 MW solar power project. Ajmera Realty & Infra India added 1.45% after the company reported quarterly sales of Rs 630 crore for Q3 FY26, marking a sharp increase of 123% compared with sales of Rs 270 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Wednesday as investors focused on a meeting between U.S., Greenlandic and Danish officials to discuss the future of the Arctic island. Asian markets ended higher as Japanese indexes hit record highs on Wednesday. The rally in Japanese stocks was fuelled by expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi could call for a snap election, likely in February. If called, it will be Takaichi’s first time facing Japan’s voters in an election. Overnight in the U.S., all three major indexes fell as investors grappled with volatility from a flurry of proposals from U.S. President Donald Trump floated in the past few days. The S&P 500 dipped 13.53 points or 0.2% to 6,963.74, as investors sold JPMorgan despite better-than-expected numbers. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 398.21 points or 0.8% to 49,191.99. The Nasdaq Composite fell 24.03 points or 0.1% to 23,709.87.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude eases marginally after recent rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-eases-marginally-after-recent-rally/1664925</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664925</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures dipped below $61 per barrel in Asia on Wednesday, snapping a four-day rally as Venezuela resumed oil exports, raising near-term supply concerns.

WTI crude oil futures dipped below $61 per barrel in Asia on Wednesday, snapping a four-day rally as Venezuela resumed oil exports, raising near-term supply concerns. Expectations that up to 50 million barrels of previously sanctioned crude could return to the market added downward pressure on prices. At the same time, geopolitical risks continued to cap losses, with escalating unrest in Iran fueling concerns over potential disruptions through the Strait of Hormuz. Further uncertainty stemmed from possible supply risks in Russia amid continued attacks on energy infrastructure. On the data front, US crude inventories were estimated to have risen by 5.27 million barrels last week, weighing on sentiment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/the-triumph-of-nature-1222518_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Groww gains after Q3 PAT climbs 16% QoQ to Rs 546-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/groww-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-16-qoq-to-rs-546-cr/1664923</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664923</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit declined 27.76% while revenue from operations jumped 24.79% in Q3 FY26.

On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit declined 27.76% while revenue from operations jumped 24.79% in Q3 FY26. The YoY decline in profit was largely attributable to a one-time gain of Rs 314.8 crore related to long-term incentive paid to management. Excluding this impact, operational performance remained robust, with profit after tax (PAT) recording 24% YoY growth to Rs 442.3 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax (PBT) fell 27.09% YoY to Rs 744.85 crore during the quarter. Adjusted EBITDA stood at Rs 741.8 crore, up 24.03% YoY and 18.86% QoQ. The company’s total transacting users reached 20.4 million, marking a growth of 7% QoQ and 25% YoY. Active Users grew 7.5% QoQ. Meanwhile, the company, along with Groww AMC—its wholly owned, non-material subsidiary—has executed a Share Subscription and Purchase Agreement (SSPA) and a Shareholders’ Agreement (SHA) with State Street Global Advisors. Under the SSPA, State Street Global Advisors has agreed to invest up to Rs 580.02 crore through a combination of secondary share purchases and primary subscriptions, resulting in a dilution of up to 23% of Groww AMC’s fully diluted share capital. Upon completion of the proposed transaction, State Street Global Advisors will hold no more than 4.99% of the aggregate voting power in Groww AMC. Billionbrains Garage Ventures (Groww) has built a sizeable footprint since its launch in 2018, emerging as a full-stack digital investment platform with offerings across stocks, mutual funds, derivatives and loans. It serves customers across 98% of Indian pin codes, operates 37 million demat accounts and oversees Rs 2.6 lakh crore in AUM through subsidiaries spanning broking, lending and asset management.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BillionbrainsGarageVenturesLtd_87132138_77966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Bank of India jumps after PAT climbs to Rs 5,017 crore; provisions drop nearly 80% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-bank-of-india-jumps-after-pat-climbs-to-rs-5017-crore-provisions-drop-nearly-80-yoy/1664922</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664922</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 9,328 crore, up 0.95% YoY.

Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 9,328 crore, up 0.95% YoY. Net interest margin was 2.76% for the December 2025 period as against 2.91% for the December 2024 period. Operating expenses jumped 12.36% to Rs 6,927 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 6,165 crore in the December 2024 quarter. Accoridingly, the public sector bank registered an operating profit of Rs 6,942 crore in Q3 FY26, down 7.34% YoY. Provisions and contingencies dropped by 79.85% to Rs 322.23 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,599.05 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 6,619.37 crore, up by 12.33% from Rs 5,892.77 in Q3 FY25. Gross NPAs declined to 3.06% as of 31 December 2025, from 3.85% as of 31 December 2024. Net NPAs fell to 0.51% as of 31 December 2025 from 0.82% as of 31 December 2024. Total business of the bank increased by 5.04% YoY to Rs 22,39,740 crore as on 31 December 2025. The bank had total deposits base of Rs 12,22,856 crore as on 31 December 2025, up 3.36% YoY. The RAM advances of the bank increased by 11.50% YoY to Rs 5,77,038 crore. The retail segment had recorded a growth of 21.67% and the MSME advances rose by 19.75% during the period under review. Agriculture advances fell by 5.39% YoY in the December 2025 period. RAM advances as a percent of domestic advances stood at 58.84%. Gross advances of the bank as on 31 December 2025 were Rs 10,16,884 crore, up 7.13% YoY. Union Bank of India is engaged in the business of treasury operations, corporate and wholesale banking, retail banking operations, and other banking operations. The Government of India held a 74.76% stake in the bank.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnionBankI_88937846814_5493.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NITI Aayog releases export preparedness index for states, Maharashtra tops list]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/niti-aayog-releases-export-preparedness-index-for-states-maharashtra-tops-list/1664918</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664918</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NITI Aayog has released the Export Preparedness Index (EPI) 2024, a comprehensive assessment of export readiness across India’s States and Union Territories (UTs).

NITI Aayog has released the Export Preparedness Index (EPI) 2024, a comprehensive assessment of export readiness across India’s States and Union Territories (UTs). The Index recognises the diversity of subnational economic structures and their critical role in advancing India’s global trade ambitions. The first edition of the EPI was published in August 2020 and this is the 4th edition. The Export Preparedness Index provides an evidence-based framework to evaluate the strength, resilience, and inclusiveness of subnational export ecosystems. The Index identifies key structural challenges, growth levers, and policy opportunities for enhancing export competitiveness at the State and district levels. Based on the overall assessment under EPI 2024, leading performers in export preparedness include -Maharashtra, Tamil Nadu, Gujarat, Uttar Pradesh and Andhra Pradesh.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concept-with-oil-rig-in-the-gulf-picture-id597_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IOB gains as Q3 PAT jumps 56% YoY to Rs 1,365 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/iob-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-56-yoy-to-rs-1365-cr/1664914</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664914</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income rallied 15.01% year on year (YoY) to Rs 9,671.58 crore in Q3 FY26.

Total income rallied 15.01% year on year (YoY) to Rs 9,671.58 crore in Q3 FY26. Operating profit stood at Rs 2,603.1 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 14.87% increase over Rs 2,266.01 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Profit before tax surged 10.51% year-on-year to Rs 1,367.45 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 1,237.37 crore in Q3 FY25. Net Interest Income (NII) jumped 18.29% to Rs 3,299 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,789 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Net interest margin (NIM) stood to 3.32% in Q3 FY26, compared to 3.33% registered in the same period a year ago. IOB’s total business increased 18.71% to Rs 6,44,276 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 5,42,753 crore in Q3 FY25. Total Deposits increased 14.48% to Rs 3,49,302 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3,05,121 crore in Q3 FY25. Current Account and Savings Account (CASA) deposits grew 7.81% to Rs 1,42,676 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,32,338 crore in Q3 FY25. The CASA ratio declined to 40.85% in Q3 FY26 from 43.37% a year ago. Gross advances during the quarter stood at Rs 2,94,974 crore, showing a strong growth of 24.13% from Rs 2,37,632 crore reported in the corresponding quarter last year. During the quarter, gross non-performing assets (NPAs) stood at Rs 4,530 crore, down 25.38% year-on-year from Rs 6,071 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Net NPAs declined 27.46% YoY to Rs 708 crore, compared with Rs 976 crore a year earlier. Gross NPA ratio stood at 1.54% as on 31 December 2025 as against 2.55% as on 31 December 2024. Net NPA ratio stood at 0.24% as on 31 December 2025, compared with 0.42% as on 31 December 2024. The Provision Coverage Ratio (PCR) stood at 97.49% as of 31 December 2025, compared to 97.07% in the year-ago quarter. On a year-on-year basis, the bank’s performance remained strong in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. The Provision Coverage Ratio (PCR) increased by 42 basis points to 97.49%, highlighting improved credit protection. The bank’s profitability strengthened, with Return on Assets (ROA) rising 35 basis points to 1.28% and Return on Equity (ROE) climbing sharply by 312 basis points to 20.98%, reflecting higher earnings efficiency. However, the Capital to Risk-weighted Assets Ratio (CRAR) moderated slightly, declining 67 basis points to 16.30%, indicating slightly higher capital deployment over the year. Indian Overseas Bank is engaged in the business of banking & financial services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IOB_23876379718_5955.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Allcargo Logistics Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/allcargo-logistics-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1664913</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664913</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Elxsi Ltd, Globus Spirits Ltd, Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd and The Anup Engineering Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 14 January 2026.

Tata Elxsi Ltd, Globus Spirits Ltd, Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd and The Anup Engineering Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 14 January 2026. Allcargo Logistics Ltd lost 5.78% to Rs 10.44 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 5.21 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.36 lakh shares in the past one month. Tata Elxsi Ltd crashed 4.46% to Rs 5537.45. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 57646 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 23904 shares in the past one month. Globus Spirits Ltd tumbled 3.77% to Rs 971.7. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8152 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21011 shares in the past one month. Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd dropped 3.74% to Rs 747.6. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3838 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4022 shares in the past one month. The Anup Engineering Ltd shed 3.50% to Rs 2002.4. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 715 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1131 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AllcargoLogist_28856893835_27333.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold rally intensifies amid geopolitical and policy risks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-rally-intensifies-amid-geopolitical-and-policy-risks/1664910</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664910</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures surged to fresh record highs near $4,650 per ounce in Asian trade on Wednesday, underpinned by firm expectations of US rate cuts and an intensification of safe-haven flows.

Gold futures surged to fresh record highs near $4,650 per ounce in Asian trade on Wednesday, underpinned by firm expectations of US rate cuts and an intensification of safe-haven flows. Market focus now shifts to the US PPI and retail sales data for further insight into the economic outlook and the Federal Reserve’s policy trajectory. Haven demand was further reinforced by renewed concerns over the Fed’s independence following a criminal probe linked to Chair Powell’s June testimony, alongside elevated geopolitical risks tied to Iran’s internal unrest and potential US involvement. In the domestic market, MCX February gold futures advanced over ₹1,000 to ₹143,330 per 10 grams, marking a fresh all-time high and mirroring strength across global precious metals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Realty stocks extends losses as IT layoffs pressure housing demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/realty-stocks-extends-losses-as-it-layoffs-pressure-housing-demand/1664911</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664911</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Weak sentiment was driven by concerns over sustained layoffs in the information technology sector.

Weak sentiment was driven by concerns over sustained layoffs in the information technology sector. In the stock-specific moves, Signatureglobal (India) fell 2.15%, Macrotech Developers (Lodha Group) slipped 1.82%, Brigade Enterprises declined 1.54%, Anant Raj dropped 1.44%, and Prestige Estates Projects lost 1.36%. Phoenix Mills eased 1.31%, while Godrej Properties fell 0.84%, Oberoi Realty slipped 0.78%, and DLF was marginally lower by 0.05%. Media reports indicated that prolonged IT job cuts are starting to impact housing demand. The effect is more visible in technology-driven cities such as Bengaluru and Hyderabad. Employment uncertainty has discouraged high-income buyers from upgrading homes. Mid-to-premium and luxury housing segments continue to face the most pressure. Reports also flagged hiring softness and AI-led automation as ongoing concerns. Market participants expect real estate stocks to remain volatile without policy support or a recovery in tech-sector employment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>