<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:57:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SMS Pharma edges higher after Q3 PAT rises nearly 29% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sms-pharma-edges-higher-after-q3-pat-rises-nearly-29-yoy/1673888</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673888</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 166.80 crore, up 19.0% YoY.

Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 166.80 crore, up 19.0% YoY. PBIDT improved by 34.1% to Rs 47.40 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 35.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 31.16 crore, up by 38.9% from Rs 22.44 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. SMS Pharmaceuticals is a diversified and integrated pharmaceutical company specializing in APIs and intermediates for global customers. The company operates two state-of-the-art manufacturing facilities in Hyderabad and Vizag.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SMSPharma_56135329409_25807.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ram Ratna Wires climbs after Q3 PAT surges 73% YoY to Rs 31 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ram-ratna-wires-climbs-after-q3-pat-surges-73-yoy-to-rs-31-cr/1673873</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673873</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 97.87% YoY to Rs 47.45 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 97.87% YoY to Rs 47.45 crore during the quarter. The company reported exceptional loss of Rs 3.56 crore in Q3 FY26, related to labour code compliance. EBITDA stood at Rs 72 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 84.9% compared with Rs 39 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 5.6% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.4% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter 92% of revenue contributed from domestic region while 8% revenue came from exports. Mahendrakumar Kabra, MD said, “We are delighted to report yet another quarter of exceptional performance, led by rising demandfor copper tubes driven by the growth in the HVAC industry. This segment has seen its contributionto revenues increase from 17% last year to 27% this quarter, driving profitability and underscoringour focus on expanding domestic capacity and reducing import reliance. To further strengthen thissegment, Inner Grooved Tube (IGT) manufacturing is currently in progress and at the evaluation stage. At the same time, copper winding wires continue to benefit from India’s electrification push andthe rapid expansion of power transmission and distribution infrastructure, resulting in robustgrowth across our portfolio. Our consolidated revenue for this quarter grew by 43.8% year-on-year,with Operating EBITDA rising 84.9% and Profit After Tax improving 72.5%, reflecting operationalexcellence and disciplined execution. Looking ahead, strong demand momentum supported by industry tailwinds and capacity additionswill continue to drive growth. In addition, developments in our joint venture and subsidiary areadvancing well and will further enhance our growth trajectory. We remain committed to deliveringsustainable value for all our stakeholders.” Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the change in designation of Rajeev Maheshwari from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) of the company to senior vice president (Accounts & Taxation) with effect from April 01, 2026, consequent to this change Maheshwari will cease to be the CFO of the Company from the closure of business hours on March 31, 2026. Additionally, the board approved the appointment of Iqbal Singh Saggu, as senior vice president (Finance) and CFO with effect from April 01, 2026. Iqbal Singh Saggu is a qualified chartered accountant with over 23 years of experience in handling treasury department, plant & finance operations, strategic planning, capital structuring, and regulatory compliance with expertise in driving profitability and optimizing capital. Ram Ratna Wires (RRWL) is a prominent part of RR Global, a leading conglomerate in the electrical and copper industry. The company manufactures super enameled copper winding wires in India that offers a wide range of sizes under its brand, RR Shramik.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RamRatnaWires_52194664867_4453.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pace Digitek Q3 PAT jumps 8% YoY to Rs 76 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pace-digitek-q3-pat-jumps-8-yoy-to-rs-76-cr/1673872</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673872</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 16.8% YoY to Rs 114.25 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 16.8% YoY to Rs 114.25 crore in Q3 FY26. Total expenses rose 15.01% to Rs 539.90 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 469.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 91.98 crore (down 20.8% YoY), engineering, procurement, and construction project expenses stood at Rs 201.23 (down 22.25% YoY), finance cost was at Rs 9.27 crore (down 58.34% YoY), while employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 24.91 crore (up 44.49% YoY) during the period under review. Pace Digitek (PDL) is a telecom infrastructure solutions provider offering manufacturing, installation, commissioning, and operation & maintenance (O&M) services for telecom towers and optical fiber networks. Shares of Pace Digitek shed 0.70% to Rs 190.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PACEDIGITEKLIMITED_26475505_94643.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Atul Auto gains as Q3 PAT spurts 90% YoY to Rs 15 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/atul-auto-gains-as-q3-pat-spurts-90-yoy-to-rs-15-cr/1673838</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673838</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operations grew by 18.39% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 230.86 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total revenue from operations grew by 18.39% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 230.86 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of Rs 20.02 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, marking a 100.60% increase compared to Rs 9.98 crore recorded in the same period of the previous year. Total expenses jumped 13.07% to Rs 210 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 185.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses were at Rs 20.31 crore (up 8.55% YoY), while the cost of material consumed stood at Rs 152.06 crore (up 11.75% YoY) during the period under review. On the segmental front, revenue from the automobiles business was Rs 220.56 crore (up 20.62% YoY), while revenue from the non-banking financial business was Rs 12.14 crore (down 12.34% YoY) during the quarter. Atul Auto is a leading three-wheeler manufacturing company in Rajkot, Gujarat, India. It has a complete range of 3-wheeler products across the fuel range: diesel, petrol, CNG, LPG, and electric.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AtulAuto_3226523977_14817.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahanagar Gas posts PAT of Rs 201 crore in Q3; clocks total volumes of 425.07 SCM million]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahanagar-gas-posts-pat-of-rs-201-crore-in-q3-clocks-total-volumes-of-42507-scm-million/1673836</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673836</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[EBIDTA rose by 12% YoY to Rs 352.07 crore during the period under review.

EBIDTA rose by 12% YoY to Rs 352.07 crore during the period under review. EBIDTA margin for Q3 FY26 was 17.10% as against 17.89%% in Q3 FY25. Total sales volume for the December’25 quarter was 425.07 SCM million, 12.3% YoY. For the period under review, CNG sales volume added up to 301.88 SCM million (up 12.4% YoY) and PNG sales aggregated to 123.19 SCM million (up 11.9% YoY). Mahanagar Gas is in the business of city gas distribution (CGD), presently distribution of natural gas for domestic industrial, commercial customers and CNG vehicles. The scrip rose 2.19% to currently trade at Rs 1178.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahanagarGasLtd_64664984058_13369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends gains amid weak dollar overseas; Positive cues from equities support]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-gains-amid-weak-dollar-overseas-positive-cues-from-equities-support/1673834</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673834</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee is extending gains against the dollar in opening trades on Monday, tracking weakness in dollar overseas and positive cues from local equities.

The Indian rupee is extending gains against the dollar in opening trades on Monday, tracking weakness in dollar overseas and positive cues from local equities. INR opened at Rs 90.66 per dollar and hit a high of 90.44 so far during the day. On Friday, rupee declined 31 paise to settle at 90.65 against the US dollar, weighed down by geopolitical uncertainties over the US-Iran talks, and a sharp rise in global crude oil prices. The Reserve Bank of India decided to hold its benchmark rates on Friday, as economic growth momentum is expected to be sustained, with the signing of a trade deal with the EU and the progress made on US trade agreement. At the meeting, the Monetary Policy Committee, governed by Sanjay Malhotra, unanimously decided to keep the policy repo rate unchanged at 5.25 percent. Meanwhile, Indian shares turned in a mixed performance on Friday with investors digesting the Reserve Bank of India's rate decision and views on the economy, in addition to reacting to the earnings updates. The benchmark BSE Sensex ended the session with a gain of 266.47 points or 0.32% at 83,580.40 while the National Stock Exchange's Nifty50 settled with a gain of 50.90 points or 0.2% at 25,693.70.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade firm in early trade; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-firm-in-early-trade-breadth-strong/1673832</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673832</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with modest gains in early trade as investors sentiment remained optimistic following the recently signed India- US trade deal agreement and positive global cues.

The key equity indices traded with modest gains in early trade as investors sentiment remained optimistic following the recently signed India- US trade deal agreement and positive global cues. Investors will track earnings reports, global cues, gold and crude oil prices. The Nifty traded above the 25,800 level. Barring FMCG index the lone laggard, all the sectoral indices on the NSE were traded in green. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 404.88 points or 0.48% to 83,965.73. The Nifty 50 index added 117.55 points or 0.45% to 25,808.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.82% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 1.09%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,390 shares rose and 833 shares fell. A total of 174 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 1,950.77 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,265.06 crore in the Indian equity market on 06 February 2026, provisional data showed. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 1.23% to 6.733 compared with previous session close of 6.651. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.5200 compared with its close of 90.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement advanced 1.29% to Rs 157,454. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 97.60. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.43% to 4.221. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement declined 68 cents or 1.80% to $67.37 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration rallied 3% after the company reported 65.09% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 22.66 crore on a 33.29% increase in total income to Rs 155.09 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. State Bank of India jumped 6.39% after the bank reported 24.49% jump in net profit to Rs 21,028 crore on a 9.69% increase in total income to Rs 1,40,915 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Sula Vineyards declined 3.61% after the company reported a sharp 67.6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 9.1 crore on a 9.9% fall in revenue to Rs 180 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asian markets advanced on Monday, led by a surge in Japanese stocks following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s historic landslide election victory. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party captured a two-thirds supermajority in the 465-seat lower house, public broadcaster NHK reported. A decisive win for Takaichi could be the “best outcome” for markets over the medium term, as strategic investments and tax reform bolster equities, said Sree Kochugovindan, media report said. Japanese stocks have hit several highs over the past few months, driven by the so-called 'Takaichi trade' as markets expect the prime minister’s economic policies — seen as growth‑focused continuation of Abenomics — to boost equities, while weakening the yen as she pushes for a looser monetary policy and higher government spending. U.S. President Donald Trump congratulated Takaichi on her victory in a TruthSocial post. Last Friday in the U.S., stocks surged as tech names recovered following several days of heavy selling in the sector and bitcoin rebounded following a rout that took the popular cryptocurrency down more than 50% from its high in October last year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 1,206.95 points, or 2.47%, closing at 50,115.67. Friday marked the first time the Dow exceeded the 50,000 level. The S&P 500 jumped 1.97% and ended at 6,932.30, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 2.18% to 23,031.21. With those moves, the S&P 500 climbed back into the green for 2026. Even with Friday’s rise, the S&P 500 posted a 0.1% decline for the week, while the Nasdaq fell 1.8% on the week. The 30-stock Dow rose 2.5% week to date, benefiting from some rotation into some economically cyclical stocks even as the overall market was weighed down by tech selling.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd Spikes 1.76%, BSE Metal index Rises 1.48%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/national-aluminium-company-ltd-spikes-176-bse-metal-index-rises-148/1673826</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673826</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd rose 1.76% today to trade at Rs 360.7.

National Aluminium Company Ltd rose 1.76% today to trade at Rs 360.7. The BSE Metal index is up 1.48% to quote at 39938.18. The index is up 9.09 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Tata Steel Ltd increased 1.52% and Adani Enterprises Ltd added 1.4% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 38.13 % over last one year compared to the 8.11% surge in benchmark SENSEX. National Aluminium Company Ltd has added 3.65% over last one month compared to 9.09% gain in BSE Metal index and 0.72% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 26446 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 15.75 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 431.6 on 29 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 140 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NatlAluminium_39819539035_2304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at green start for equities; Takaichi secures historic mandate in Japan]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-green-start-for-equities-takaichi-secures-historic-mandate-in-japan/1673817</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673817</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 32.50 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 32.50 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 1,950.77 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,265.06 crore in the Indian equity market on 06 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 2,645.53 so far in February (till 06 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian markets trended higher on Monday, led by a surge in Japanese stocks following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s historic landslide election victory. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party captured a two-thirds supermajority in the 465-seat lower house, public broadcaster NHK reported. A decisive win for Takaichi could be the “best outcome” for markets over the medium term, as strategic investments and tax reform bolster equities, said Sree Kochugovindan, media report said. Japanese stocks have hit several highs over the past few months, driven by the so-called 'Takaichi trade' as markets expect the prime minister’s economic policies — seen as growth‑focused continuation of Abenomics — to boost equities, while weakening the yen as she pushes for a looser monetary policy and higher government spending. U.S. President Donald Trump congratulated Takaichi on her victory in a TruthSocial post. Last Friday in the U.S., stocks surged as tech names recovered following several days of heavy selling in the sector and bitcoin rebounded following a rout that took the popular cryptocurrency down more than 50% from its high in October last year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 1,206.95 points, or 2.47%, closing at 50,115.67. Friday marked the first time the Dow exceeded the 50,000 level. The S&P 500 jumped 1.97% and ended at 6,932.30, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 2.18% to 23,031.21. With those moves, the S&P 500 climbed back into the green for 2026. Even with Friday’s rise, the S&P 500 posted a 0.1% decline for the week, while the Nasdaq fell 1.8% on the week. The 30-stock Dow rose 2.5% week to date, benefiting from some rotation into some economically cyclical stocks even as the overall market was weighed down by tech selling. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks closed deep in the red on Thursday, breaking a three-day winning streak as investors locked in profits at stretched valuations. The rally, fuelled by optimism around the India-US trade deal, ran into selling as caution crept in ahead of the Reserve Bank of India’s monetary policy decision due on Friday. Weakness was not limited to frontline stocks, with the broader market also sliding under pressure. The Nifty 50 slipped below the 25,650 mark, dragged down by sharp losses in metal, consumer durables and auto stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex slumped 503.76 points or 0.60% to 83,313.93. The Nifty 50 index fell 133.20 points or 0.52% to 25,642.80. Over the past three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex advanced 3.20%, while the Nifty gained 3.29%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves rise to record $723.77 billion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-rise-to-record-72377-billion/1673815</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673815</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s foreign exchange reserves jumped by USD 14.36 billion to a fresh all-time high of USD 723.77 billion in the week ended January 30, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) said on Friday.

India’s foreign exchange reserves jumped by USD 14.36 billion to a fresh all-time high of USD 723.77 billion in the week ended January 30, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) said on Friday. According to the central bank’s data, foreign currency assets (FCAs) — the largest component of the reserves — declined by USD 493 million to USD 562.39 billion during the week. In contrast, the value of gold reserves surged by USD 14.59 billion to USD 137.68 billion, emerging as the primary driver behind the sharp overall increase in reserves. The RBI data also showed that Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) rose by USD 216 million to USD 18.95 billion, while India’s reserve position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) increased by USD 44 million to USD 4.75 billion during the reporting week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-2891849__340_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GRSE secures Rs 33-cr MEA order for seychelles coast guard ship refit]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/grse-secures-rs-33-cr-mea-order-for-seychelles-coast-guard-ship-refit/1673785</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673785</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is scheduled to be executed within three months.

The project is scheduled to be executed within three months. Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers (GRSE) is a public sector defence undertaking under the administrative control of the Ministry of Defence and a Schedule ‘A’ Mini Ratna Category-I company. The company reported a 74% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 171 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 98 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased to Rs 1,896 crore during the period under review, up 49% YoY. The scrip fell 1.56% to settle at Rs 2,401.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GardenReachShipbuildersEngineersLtd_23484985591_13229.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: State Bank of India, Hi-Tech Pipes, Ram Ratna Wires, Tata Steel, Godawari Power ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-state-bank-of-india-hi-tech-pipes-ram-ratna-wires-tata-steel-godawari-power/1673784</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673784</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 9 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 9 February 2026. Result Today: Zydus Lifesciences, Aurobindo Pharma, All Time Plastics, Amber Enterprises India, Bajaj Electricals, Bata India, Enviro Infra Engineers, PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery, GlaxoSmithKline Pharmaceuticals, Happiest Minds Technologies, Navin Fluorine International, P N Gadgil Jewellers, Ramco Cements, Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company, Trident, and Vadilal Industries will release quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration has reported 65.09% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 22.66 crore on a 33.29% increase in total income to Rs 155.09 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. State Bank of India has reported 24.49% jump in net profit to Rs 21,028 crore on a 9.69% increase in total income to Rs 1,40,915 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Hi-Tech Pipes has reported 14.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.38 crore despite a 24.6% increase in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,069.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Ram Ratna Wires reported a 73.1% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 31.28 crore on 43.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,277.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Baazar Style Retail’s consolidated net profit declined 37.65% to Rs 18.96 crore on 13.33% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 466.47 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Steel reported a sharp 723.14% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 2688.70 crore on 6.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 56,646.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sonata Software reported a 13.17% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 104.36 crore despite a 45.36% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3,080.58 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Godawari Power & Ispat reported a 1.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 143 crore despite a 12.2% fall in revenue to Rs 1,139 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Sula Vineyards reported a sharp 67.6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 9.1 crore on a 9.9% fall in revenue to Rs 180 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id51_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>