<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:17:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Overall tally of Dmat accounts in India stands at 21.6 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/overall-tally-of-dmat-accounts-in-india-stands-at-216-crore/1667219</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667219</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Board of India has stated in its latest monthly update that in December 2025, 4.4 lakh net demat accounts were added with NSDL, registering M-o-M growth of 1% in total demat accounts.

Securities and Exchange Board of India has stated in its latest monthly update that in December 2025, 4.4 lakh net demat accounts were added with NSDL, registering M-o-M growth of 1% in total demat accounts. A total of 27.3 lakh net accounts were added with CDSL during the month,registering an increase of 1.6% in total demat accounts over November 2025. At the end of December 2025, overall tally of demat accounts stood at 21.6 crore with 4.3 crore demat accounts at NSDL and 17.3 crore accounts at CDSL.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shriram Finance Q3 PAT slides 29% YoY to Rs 2,522 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shriram-finance-q3-pat-slides-29-yoy-to-rs-2522-cr/1667217</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667217</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 3,360.20 crore in Q3 FY26, down 23.91% as against Rs 4,415.92 crore reported in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 3,360.20 crore in Q3 FY26, down 23.91% as against Rs 4,415.92 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Net interest income grew 16.17% to Rs 6,764.09 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 5,822.69 crore recorded in the same period a year ago. As of 31 December 2025, total assets under management climbed 14.63% to Rs 291,709.03 crore compared to Rs 254,469.69 crore as of 31 December 2024. The liquidity coverage ratio was at 334.93% as of 31 December 2025, as against 265.24% as of 31 December 2024. The cost-to-income ratio increased to 29.66% in Q3 FY26 from 28.59% in Q3 FY25. The firm's return on assets (ROA) (including exceptional items) and return on equity (ROE) (including exceptional items) stood at 3.09% and 4.94%, respectively, in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Operating profit improved by 14.33% to Rs 4,670.52 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,084.98 crore in Q3 FY25. The board of directors had earlier, on 19 December 2025, approved a proposal to raise Rs 39,618 crore through a preferential issue of 47.11 crore fully paid-up equity shares of face value Rs 2 each at an issue price of Rs 840.93 per share to Japan-based MUFG Bank. The proposed allotment represents 20% of the post-preferential equity share capital on a fully diluted basis. The company said the requisite resolutions were approved by shareholders at the extraordinary general meeting held on 14 January 2026. The preferential issue is currently awaiting statutory and regulatory approvals. Upon completion, MUFG Bank will become a minority public shareholder in the company. Shriram Finance said its overseas subsidiary, Shriram Overseas Investments (SOIL), formerly known as Shriram Overseas Investments, became a wholly-owned subsidiary on May 9, 2025. SOIL holds an 81.63% stake in Bharat Investments Pte., Singapore, which has an associate entity in Bahrain. Shriram Finance is India's largest retail asset financing non-banking finance company (NBFC). It is the flagship company of the Shriram Group, which has a significant presence in consumer finance, life insurance, general insurance, housing finance, stock broking, and distribution businesses. Shares of Shriram Finance fell 0.29% to close at Rs 1,003.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShriramFinanceLtd_71599469_1745.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian states consolidated gross fiscal deficit increased to 3.3% of GDP in 2024-25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-states-consolidated-gross-fiscal-deficit-increased-to-33-of-gdp-in-2024-25/1667218</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667218</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released the Report ‘State Finances: A Study of Budgets of 2025-26’.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released the Report ‘State Finances: A Study of Budgets of 2025-26’. The theme of this year’s Report is ‘Demographic Transition in India - Implications for State Finances’. It provides a comprehensive assessment of the finances of State governments for 2025-26 against the backdrop of actual and revised/provisional accounts for 2023-24 and 2024-25, respectively. The paper noted that states consolidated gross fiscal deficit increased to 3.3 per cent of gross domestic product (GDP) in 2024-25, after remaining below 3.0 per cent during the previous three years. The deficit exceeding 3 per cent mainly reflects 50-year interest free loans from the Centre under Special Assistance to States for Capital Investment, which is over and above the normal net borrowing ceiling of the States. In 2025-26, States have budgeted a gross fiscal deficit of 3.3 per cent of GDP. The thrust on capital expenditure was sustained as capital expenditure remained steady at 2.7 per cent of GDP in 2023-24 and 2024-25 and is budgeted at 3.2 per cent of GDP in 2025-26. The consolidated outstanding liabilities of States remained elevated in the post-pandemic period with a budget estimate of 29.2 per cent of GDP at end-March 2026. Indian States are at different stages of demographic transition, which increasingly shape their finances. Youthful States have a wider window of opportunity due to an expanding working-age population and stronger revenue mobilisation, which can be harnessed through higher investment in human capital. In contrast, ageing States face a narrowing window, with fiscal pressures arising from shrinking tax bases and rising committed expenditure, calling for higher revenue capacity and reforms in healthcare, pensions and workforce policies. Intermediate States need to balance growth priorities with early preparation for ageing.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee closes flat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-closes-flat/1667197</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667197</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed weaker at 91.8650 per Dollar on Friday (23 January 2026), versus its previous close of 91.6375 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India will continue to grow 6 to 8% in real terms and 10 to 13% nominal in next 5 years: Ashwini Vaishnaw]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-will-continue-to-grow-6-to-8-in-real-terms-and-10-to-13-nominal-in-next-5-years-ashwini-vaishnaw/1667168</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667168</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[“India will continue to grow 6 to 8% in real terms and 10 to 13% in nominal terms, supported by moderate inflation and strong growth”, said Mr Ashwini Vaishnaw, Hon’ble Minister of Railways, Information and Broadcasting, Electronics and Information Technology, Government of India.

“India will continue to grow 6 to 8% in real terms and 10 to 13% in nominal terms, supported by moderate inflation and strong growth”, said Mr Ashwini Vaishnaw, Hon’ble Minister of Railways, Information and Broadcasting, Electronics and Information Technology, Government of India. He was speaking at the session on 'Bet on India – Bank on the Future' organised by Confederation of Indian Industry (CII) in association with EY coinciding with the World Economic Forum (WEF) Annual Meeting 2026 at Davos. Mr Vaishnaw highlighted the importance of simplification of permissions and affirmed that the average time for installation of telecom tower permission has decreased from 270 days to 7 days, with 89% permissions coming in zero time. He further highlighted that there is a need to bridge the gap between the intent and the functioning. As political leaders, there is a need to make sure that the bureaucracy aligns with political power. He further discussed the importance of communicating challenges amongst the industry members, mentioning standardisation of data localisation norms across the US and Europe.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indusind Bank Q3 PAT plunges 88% YoY to Rs 161 cr; NII slides 13% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indusind-bank-q3-pat-plunges-88-yoy-to-rs-161-cr-nii-slides-13-yoy/1667167</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667167</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The profit before tax (PBT) fell 88.24% YoY to Rs 218.16 crore during the quarter.

The profit before tax (PBT) fell 88.24% YoY to Rs 218.16 crore during the quarter. The bank's financial results include the financial results of its wholly owned subsidiary, Bharat Financial Inclusion (BFIL), a business correspondent (BC) of the Bank involved in originating small ticket loans for the Bank and IndusInd Marketing and Financial Services Private (IMFS), an associate of the bank. The bank reported a 90.87% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 127.98 crore on 13.7% decline in total income to Rs 13,080.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Pre-provision operating profit (PPOP) stood at Rs 2,270 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 3,601 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net Interest Income (NII) declined 12.74% YoY to Rs 45.62 crore in Q3 FY26.Net interest margin (NIM) reduced to 3.52% in Q3 FY26 as against 3.93% in Q3 FY25. The bank’s deposits declined 3.82% to Rs 3,93,815 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 4,09,438 crore in Q3 FY25. CASA deposits stood at Rs 1,19,104 crore with current account deposits at Rs 31,416 crore and savings account deposits at Rs 87,688 crore. CASA deposits comprised 30% of total deposits as on 31st December 2025. Advances as of December 31, 2025, were Rs 3,17,536 crore, recording de-growth of 13.45% as against Rs 3,66,889 crores previous year Gross NPA were at 3.56% of gross advances as on December 31, 2025, as against 2.25% as Q3 FY25. Net NPA were 1.04% of net advances as on December 31, 2025, as compared to 0.68% as on Q3 FY25. The provision coverage ratio (PCR) was improved at 71.50% as on December 31, 2025. Provisions and contingencies for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, were Rs 2,096 crore as compared to Rs 1,744 crore for the corresponding quarter of previous year. The Bank's total capital adequacy ratio as per Basel III guidelines stands at 16.94% as on December 31, 2025, as compared to 16.46% as on December 31, 2024. Tier 1 CRAR was at 15.74% as on December 31, 2025, compared to 15.18% as on December 31, 2024. Risk-Weighted Assets were at Rs 4,01,497 crore as against Rs 4,20,519 crore a year ago. As of December 31, 2025, the Bank's distribution network included 3,120 branches/ Banking outlets and 3,063 onsite and offsite ATMs, as against 3,063 branches/banking outlets and 2,993 onsite and offsite ATMs, As of December 31, 2024. The client base stood at approx. 42 million as on December 31, 2025. Rajiv Anand, the MD and CEO, IndusInd Bank said: "During Q3FY26, the bank continued focus on optimisation of its balance sheet by letting go unprofitable loans and deposits along with being cautious on microfinance disbursements. The operating performance was steady with Pre-Provision Operating Profit at Rs 2,270 crore growing 11% QoQ. Our asset quality trends have been stable in all core businesses except in microfinance wherein industry is now showing early signs of recovery. Overall, the Bank has returned to profitability with a Profit After Tax of Rs. 128 crore. The Balance sheet remains robust with a healthy capital adequacy, excess liquidity and reducing stressed asset pool. We are optimistic about resilient domestic economy and aim to participate in the growth recovery in a calibrated manner." Indusind Bank offers a wide range of products and services for individuals and corporates, including microfinance, personal loans, personal and commercial vehicle loans, credit cards and SME loans. The counter delcined 1.04% to settle at Rs 893.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndusIndBankLtd_64968625_5531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Copper rallies more than 1%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-copper-rallies-more-than-1/1667166</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667166</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures edged up steadily today, building on gains after testing a three-week low in last session.

COMEX Copper futures edged up steadily today, building on gains after testing a three-week low in last session. The counter currently trades at $5.85 per pound, up 1.36% on the day as equities provided decent inputs for the entire metals complex. Weak US dollar also boosted the metal as it clocked a 3% gain for this month. Meanwhile, in Asia, Shanghai Composite index added 0.33% while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index gained 0.45%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index moved up 0.29%. European stocks edged up as geopolitical worries eased. The US stocks edged up across the board. Dow climbed 0.6% while the Nasdaq added 0.9% and the S&P 500 gained 0.6%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures surge above 124 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-surge-above-124-mark/1667165</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667165</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures add 0.23% to end at 91.86.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures add 0.23% to end at 91.86. GBP/INR futures surge above 124 mark, up almost1% on the day while EUR/INR add over half a percent at 107.84. JPY/INR closed flat for the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JSW Steel Q3 PAT zooms 198% YoY to Rs 2,139 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jsw-steel-q3-pat-zooms-198-yoy-to-rs-2139-cr/1667163</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667163</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total, revenue from operations rose 11.14% year-on-year to Rs 45,991 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total, revenue from operations rose 11.14% year-on-year to Rs 45,991 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 1,457 crore in Q3 FY26, rising 23.68% from Rs 1,178 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The company’s reported EBITDA stood at Rs 6,496 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 16% increase compared to Rs 5,579 crore in Q3 FY25. The EBITDA margin improved significantly to 14.4% in Q3 FY26, up from 13.1% in the same quarter last year. Consolidated crude steel production stood at 7.48 million tonnes in Q3 FY26, up 6% year-on-year, driven by the ramp-up of the JVML–Vijayanagar project. However, production declined 5% quarter-on-quarter due to the shutdown of Blast Furnace-3 (BF-3) at Vijayanagar from End-September 2025 for capacity upgradation. Consolidated sales hit an all-time high of 7.64 million tonnes, marking a 14% YoY increase, supported by strong domestic demand. Domestic sales rose 10% YoY to 6.59 million tonnes, while exports jumped 53% YoY to 0.84 million tonnes, accounting for 11% of Indian operations’ sales in Q3 FY26. Retail sales volumes increased 12% YoY. Crude steel production at Indian operations stood at 7.28 million tonnes in the quarter, up 7% year-on-year. Capacity utilisation was around 93%, excluding Blast Furnace-3 (BF-3) at Vijayanagar, which is under shutdown, and 85% including BF-3 capacity. Steel sales during the quarter touched a record high of 7.42 million tonnes, marking a 14% YoY increase. The company also reduced steel product inventories by around 0.3 million tonnes during the period. During the quarter, Bhushan Power & Steel (BPSL) recorded crude steel production of 1.0 million tonnes and sales volume of 0.98 million tonnes. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 5,770 crore, while adjusted EBITDA was Rs 1,011 crore. Adjusted EBITDA declined 16% quarter-on-quarter, primarily due to lower realisations and higher coking coal costs. The company reported a profit after tax of around Rs 1,578 crore for the quarter. During the quarter, JSW Vijayanagar Metallics (JVML) reported crude steel production of 1.18 million tonnes, achieving rated capacity following the commissioning of all balance facilities in Q2 FY26. Sales volume stood at 1.23 million tonnes. Revenue from operations was Rs 6,099 crore, while adjusted EBITDA came in at Rs 921 crore. Adjusted EBITDA rose 47% quarter-on-quarter, driven primarily by higher volumes. The company reported a profit after tax of Rs 382 crore for the quarter. On its outlook, the global economy remains resilient, with the IMF marginally raising its 2026 growth forecast to 3.3%, in line with 2025. Growth continues to be supported by investments in AI and technology, particularly in North America and Asia, despite trade policy uncertainty and geopolitical risks. Supportive policies, easy financial conditions and rapid private-sector adaptation are aiding momentum. In the US, growth remains firm heading into CY26, driven by strong tech investments and resilient consumer spending, even as the labour market shows signs of cooling. Following 75 bps of rate cuts in 2025, further policy easing is expected, while the impact of tariffs on growth and inflation remains limited so far. The Eurozone is witnessing modest expansion led by services, while manufacturing remains weak. Policy rates are on hold, inflation is near target and growth expectations have been revised upward, with expansionary fiscal policies expected to support medium-term growth. China’s growth momentum softened in H2CY25 due to weak fixed asset investment and continued stress in real estate, though manufacturing and exports provided some support. Fiscal and monetary policy are expected to remain growth-supportive in 2026. India’s outlook remains strong, supported by GST rationalisation, accommodative monetary policy, benign inflation and sustained government capex. The NSO has projected FY26 GDP growth at 7.4%, with upward revisions by the RBI and IMF. Domestic demand remains healthy, aided by strong auto sales, firm rural indicators and improving private capex conditions. Recent progress on economic reforms and trade agreements is expected to strengthen India’s medium-term growth prospects and enhance resilience amid global uncertainties. JSW Steel said its board has approved the formation of a joint venture company for a land development project in Mumbai. The JV will be set up through Peddar Realty Ltd (PRL), a wholly owned subsidiary of JSW Steel, which will hold a 51% stake, along with JSW Realty Pvt Ltd (JSWRPL) and other partners. The proposed transaction qualifies as a related-party transaction and will be undertaken on an arm’s-length basis. JSWRPL, a promoter group entity, will have an interest in the JV to the extent of its shareholding. The JV will participate in a formal tender process to acquire an identified land parcel in Mumbai for the development of office and commercial spaces. The company said the project aligns with its expansion plans and will help meet future captive office and commercial space requirements. PRL will invest up to Rs 51 crore in the JV through cash consideration, acquiring a 51% controlling stake. The acquisition is expected to be completed on or before March 31, 2026, subject to mutual extension by JV partners. No governmental or regulatory approvals are required. The JV company will be incorporated in due course and will operate in the real estate sector. JSW Steel is the flagship business of the diversified, US$ 23 billion JSW Group. As one of India’s leading business houses, JSW Group also has interests in energy, infrastructure, cement, paints, realty, e-platforms, mobility, defence, sports, and venture capital. Shares of JSW Steel fell 1.31% to end at Rs 1,169.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JSWSteel_59462548667_4764.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex tanks 769 pts, Nifty slips below 25,050 amid FII outflows]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-tanks-769-pts-nifty-slips-below-25050-amid-fii-outflows/1667162</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667162</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, erasing early gains as persistent foreign institutional investor selling weighed heavily on sentiment and sparked a broad-based selloff in the latter half of the session.

Domestic equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, erasing early gains as persistent foreign institutional investor selling weighed heavily on sentiment and sparked a broad-based selloff in the latter half of the session. The Sensex and Nifty opened marginally higher, supported by positive cues from Asian markets and easing geopolitical concerns linked to Greenland. However, sentiment turned decisively weaker post noon, with aggressive profit-booking and sustained selling pressure dragging the indices into the red. The Nifty closed below the 25,050 level, with all NSE sectoral indices ending in the red. Realty and PSU bank stocks led the losses amid heavy selling pressure. Foreign fund outflows remained the key overhang, with FIIs extending their net selling streak to 13 consecutive sessions in January, a trend that has steadily dented market capitalisation and investor confidence. Pressure on domestic shares intensified as the Indian rupee slid to a fresh all-time low against the US dollar, amplifying risk aversion. A subdued earnings season added to the gloom, as weak December-quarter results from several heavyweight companies triggered sharp, stock-specific declines. Rising crude oil prices further stoked concerns over inflation and external balances, capping any recovery attempts. The focus is now shifting to the Union Budget, which will take place on February 1. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 769.67 points or 0.94% to 81,537.70. The Nifty 50 index lost 241.25 points or 0.95% to 25,048.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index dropped 1.56%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 2.19%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,321 shares rose and 2,887 shares fell. A total of 157 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.31% to 14.19. The rupee hit a fresh record low of 91.99 against the US dollar in intraday trade on Friday, pressured by weak global cues and persistent dollar demand. Indian stock market will remain shut on Monday, 26 January 2026, for Republic Day. World Economic Forum: In a surprise appearance at the World Economic Forum in Davos, billionaire Elon Musk said artificial intelligence could become smarter than all of humanity combined within the next five years. India has emerged as a premier hub for artificial intelligence applications, leveraging its tech-positive population and strong software legacy to transition into a “full-on AI economy”, according to the World Economic Forum’s Cathy Li. “India is a fascinating market, particularly in terms of AI applications and services. It is a no-brainer to leverage these strengths, and the country is already using its strong building blocks to move toward a full-on AI economy,” she said. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was up 0.27% to 6.654 as compared with the previous close of 6.636. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.8950 compared with its close of 91.5800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement gained 0.25% to Rs 1,56,769. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.01% to 98.17. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.28% to 4.239. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement gained 80 cents or 1.25% to $64.86 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares declined on Friday as investors digest events at Davos, including Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy's excoriating speech about the continent. Asian indices ended higher, tracking Wall Street gains as geopolitical concerns eased. The Bank of Japan kept its key policy rate unchanged at 0.75% but raised Japan’s growth outlook ahead of the upcoming election. The central bank lifted its GDP growth forecast for FY26 to 0.9% from 0.7% and for FY27 to 1% from 0.7%, citing a moderate global recovery, rising wages and prices, supportive government measures, and accommodative financial conditions. Japan’s headline inflation rate in December slowed sharply to 2.1%, its lowest level since March 2022. Its core inflation rate came in at 2.4% on the year. Some tech stocks in Asia fell after shares of California-based Intel plummeted 13% in after-hours U.S. trading on its soft guidance for the current quarter, despite posting fourth-quarter earnings beats Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the main benchmarks extended their gains from the previous session after Greenland tensions eased. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 306.78 points, or 0.63%, and closed at 49,384.01. The 30-stock index recovered from the losses seen earlier this week following President Donald Trump’s new Europe tariffs announcement. The S&P 500 climbed 0.55% and ended at 6,913.35. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.91% and settled at 23,436.02, supported by gains in Nvidia, Microsoft, and Meta Platforms. Stocks in Spotlight: Adani Group stocks came under heavy selling pressure on Friday after media reports said the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has sought court approval to directly email summons to Gautam Adani and Sagar Adani, citing court filings. The development triggered sharp declines across the conglomerate’s listed entities as investors reacted to the regulatory overhang. Shares of Adani Green Energy plunged 14.63%, while Adani Energy Solutions fell 11.97%. Adani Enterprises dropped 10.76% and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone slid 7.52%. Adani Total Gas declined 5.71%, while Adani Power lost 5.50%. Meanwhile, Adani Energy Solutions reported 1.68% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 552.31 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 561.78 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 15.73% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,729.65 crore in Q3 FY26. Home First Finance Company India jumped 5.97% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 43.97% to Rs 140.20 crore on 18.8% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 482.24 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atul rose 1.04% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 47.82% to Rs 160.74 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 108.74 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 11.06% YoY to Rs 1,573.62 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Innova Captab soared 3.28% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 23.11% to Rs 42.14 crore on 42.29% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 450.29 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Cipla tanked 4.13% after the company reported 56.96% decrease in consolidated net profit to Rs 675.80 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,570.51 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations marginally rose 0.02% to Rs 7,074.48 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7,072.97 crore in Q3 FY25. InterGlobe Aviaition (Indigo) declined 4.27% after the company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 77.55% to Rs 549.8 crore despite 6.16% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 23,471.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Coforge declined 2.81% after the company reported 33.4% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 250.2 crore despite a 5.1% increase in gross revenues to Rs 4,188.1 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY26. Gujarat State Petronet (GSPL) fell 1.39% after its standalone net profit fell 15.70% to Rs 114.26 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 4.5% to Rs 272.19 crore compared with the same quarter last year. Computer Age Management Services declined 3.96%. The company reported 0.04% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 125.53 crore on a 5.52% increase in revenue from operations from operations to Rs 390.13 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. DLF fell 4.08%. The company reported an 13.66% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,203.36 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,058.73 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations surged 32.15% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 2,020.22 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Ideaforge Technology slipped 7.01% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 33.85 crore in Q3 FY26, widening from Rs 24.02 crore in Q3 FY25. Despite the wider loss, the company’s revenue from operations increased 79.15% year on year (YoY) to Rs 31.55 crore during the quarter. Premier Energies fell 7.36%. The company reported a 53.44% year-on-year (YoY) surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 391.62 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 255.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.02% YoY to Rs 1,936.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR hits all-time low of 92 during intraday moves; Local shares end deep in red]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-hits-all-time-low-of-92-during-intraday-moves-local-shares-end-deep-in-red/1667161</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667161</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee hit an all-time low of 92 on Friday and recovered marginally to settle at 91.88 (provisional) against the American currency, amid selling pressure from foreign funds and risk-off sentiment in global markets.

The Indian rupee hit an all-time low of 92 on Friday and recovered marginally to settle at 91.88 (provisional) against the American currency, amid selling pressure from foreign funds and risk-off sentiment in global markets. The domestic currency gave up early gains and hit a record low of 92.005 per US dollar in intraday trade due to weak domestic markets and persistent foreign fund outflows. Moreover, gains in crude oil prices and a surge in US treasury yields weighed on the rupee. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 91.45 and then gained ground to touch an intraday high of 91.41 against the greenback. It touched an all-time intraday low of 92.00 before settling for the day at a record closing low of 91.88 (provisional), down 30 paise from its previous closing level. The benchmark BSE Sensex ended down 769.67 points, or 0.94 percent, at 81,537.70 while the broader NSE Nifty index slumped 241.25 points, or 0.95 percent, to 25,048.65.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US Fed Meet, geopolitical developments, pre-Budget announcements to remain in focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-fed-meet-geopolitical-developments-pre-budget-announcements-to-remain-in-focus/1667160</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667160</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equities enter the late-January week under pronounced volatility and mixed global cues.

Indian equities enter the late-January week under pronounced volatility and mixed global cues. Domestic benchmarks endured deep corrections mid-week, with persistent foreign institutional investor (FII) outflows and a weakening rupee denting sentiment, even as occasional value buying surfaced. While the broader market struggled, key defensive and sectoral themes provided intermittent support. Globally, the easing of geopolitical tensions, particularly softened tariff rhetoric from the U.S., helped rebound risk assets in Asia and supported a recovery in select Indian stocks later in the week. However, uncertainty around trade policies and mixed earnings reports kept investors cautious. With the Union Budget looming and rate expectations in focus, would continue to closely monitor macro indicators and global risk sentiment. In India, the Industrial Production for the month of December 2025 would be announced on Wednesday (28 January 2026). The industrial production in India grew 6.7% from the previous year in November of 2025, accelerating from the upwardly revised 0.5% increase in the previous month, to mark the sharpest pace of expansion since October of 2023. On Friday (30 January 2026), the government budget value for the period ended in December would be made public. India’s fiscal deficit widened to Rs 9.77 trillion in April–November 2025–26, up from Rs 8.47 trillion a year earlier, reaching 62.3% of the government’s full-year target compared with 52.5% in the same period last year. Total receipts rose 2.9% year-on-year to INR 19.49 trillion (55.7% of the annual target) while total expenditure increased 6.7% to Rs 29.26 trillion (57.8% of the full-year target). Lastly, the foreign exchange reserves position for the week ended on January 23 would be unveiled on the same day. The foreign exchange reserves in India increased to $687,190 million in January 9 from $686,800 million in the previous week. In China, Industrial Profits (YTD) data for the period ended in December 2025 would be released in Tuesday (27 January 2026). The profits at China’s industrial firms edged up 0.1% yoy to CNY 6.63 trillion in January–November 2025, notably easing from a 1.9% increase in the first ten months but still marking a fourth consecutive gain since August. In the United States, the Dallas Fed Manufacturing Index data for the month of January would be announced on Monday (26 January 2026). The Dallas Fed’s general business activity index for Texas manufacturing fell 0.5 points to (-10.9) in December 2025, its lowest level since June, while the outlook index sank deeper into negative territory at (-11.9), indicating a deterioration in perceptions of broader business conditions. On Tuesday (27 January 2026), the ADP Employment Change Weekly figures would be made public. The US private employers added an average of 8,000 jobs per week in the four weeks ending December 27, 2025, down from an average gain of 11,250 in the previous period, according to ADP Research. On Wednesday, the API Crude Oil Stock Change for the week ended on January 23 would be unveiled. US crude oil inventories rose by 3.04 million barrels in the week ended 16 January 2025, building on a 5.3 million-barrel increase in the prior week. On Thursday (29 January 2026), the US Federal Reserve will announce its latest monetary policy decision. The minutes from the Fed's December meeting noted that most of the FOMC judged that rate cuts are likely to be appropriate next year if inflation eases over time. Still, policymakers were divided in their assessment of risks between higher inflation and unemployment, with a part of the FOMC displaying greater concern that inflation becoming entrenched may require higher borrowing costs, while others preferred a greater magnitude of rate cuts to curb signs of a softening labor market. Further, the US Balance of Trade figures for November 2025 would be released on the same day. The US trade deficit narrowed sharply to $29.4 billion in October 2025, the smallest gap since June 2009, down from a revised $48.1 billion in September. On Friday (30 January 2026), the Producer Price Index for the month of December 2025 would be made public. The US producer prices rose 0.2% month over month in November 2025, accelerating from a 0.1% increase in October, according to delayed data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers slump on profit booking; Nifty tumbles below 25,100 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-slump-on-profit-booking-nifty-tumbles-below-25100-level/1667159</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667159</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key benchmark indices tumbled during the week, weighed down by profit booking, geopolitical tensions, and mixed Q3 earnings.

The key benchmark indices tumbled during the week, weighed down by profit booking, geopolitical tensions, and mixed Q3 earnings. Earnings for several companies were impacted by the implementation of the new labour code. Market sentiment remained subdued as the rupee touched a fresh record low of 91.99 against the US dollar, leading investors to adopt a risk-off stance. Market participants continued to monitor ongoing Q3 results, crude oil price movements, and geopolitical developments. The markets declined in four out of five trading sessions during the week. The Nifty settled below the 25,100 level, while the Sensex slipped below the 81,550 mark. Mid- and small-cap stocks underperformed the frontline indices. In the week ended on Friday, 23 January 2026, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 2,032.65 points or 2.43% to settle at 81,537.70. The Nifty 50 index dropped 645.70 points or 2.51% to settle at 25,048.65. The BSE Mid-Cap index fell 4.20% to close at 44,246.27. The BSE Small-Cap slumped 5.79% to end at 46,825.31. The rupee hit a fresh record low of 91.99 against the US dollar in intraday trade on Friday, pressured by weak global cues and persistent dollar demand. Weekly Index Movement: Equity benchmarks closed lower on Monday as investor sentiment turned cautious amid renewed global trade tensions and disappointing earnings from index heavyweights. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 324.17 points or 0.39% to 83,246.18. The Nifty 50 index declined 108.85 points or 0.42% to 25,585.50. Benchmark equity indices closed sharply lower on Tuesday, with the Nifty slipping below the 25,250 level as selling pressure intensified across the board. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,065.71 points or 1.28% to 82,180.47. The Nifty 50 index dropped 353 points or 1.38% to 25,232.50. Domestic equities extended losses for a third straight session on Wednesday as global shocks and weak earnings hit risk appetite. The S&P BSE Sensex dropped 270.84 points or 0.33% to 81,909.63. The Nifty 50 index lost 75 points or 0.30% to 25,157.50. In three trading sessions, the Sensex slipped 1.99% while the Nifty declined 2.09%. Domestic equities rebounded on Thursday after three consecutive sessions of losses, snapping the recent decline and restoring some investor confidence. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 397.74 points or 0.49% to 82,307.37. The Nifty 50 index rose 132.40 points or 0.53% to 25,289.90. In the previous three sessions, the Sensex slipped 1.99% while the Nifty declined 2.09%. The key equity benchmarks ended with major cuts on Friday, breaking a three-day losing streak as sentiment remained cautious with investors tracking global cues and awaiting further clarity on domestic triggers, keeping market moves range-bound. The S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 769.67 points or 0.94% to 81,537.70. The Nifty 50 index lost 241.25 points or 0.95% to 25,048.65. World economic Forum: Maharashtra Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis said Tata Sons has committed $11 billion to develop the proposed innovation city. While the location has been identified and broad contours finalized, the state expects the planning phase to take another six to eight months before execution begins. Britain will not sign US President Donald Trump’s proposed Board of Peace treaty on Thursday, Foreign Secretary Yvette Cooper said, citing concerns over Russia’s potential involvement in the initiative aimed at resolving global conflicts. She said the UK would not be among the signatories, as the legal treaty raises broader issues and because of concerns over President Vladimir Putin’s role in a peace initiative. At the 56th World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos, the Adani Group on Wednesday outlined a $66 billion investment blueprint for Maharashtra, spanning aviation, clean energy, urban infrastructure, digital platforms and advanced manufacturing, positioning itself as a long-term partner in the state’s infrastructure-led growth agenda. Economy: The International Monetary Fund (IMF) on Monday raised its economic growth forecast for India for the 2025-26 financial year, citing stronger-than-expected momentum in recent quarters. IMF has revised India's GDP growth estimate for FY26 upward by 0.7% to 7.3%, reflecting a better-than-anticipated performance in the third quarter and sustained strength heading into the fourth. However, the IMF expects growth to ease to 6.4% in 2026 and 2027 as temporary and cyclical factors supporting the economy begin to wane. Stocks in Spotlight: Wipro tumbled 11.03%. The company reported a 3.92% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,119 crore despite a 3.78% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 23,555.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Looking ahead, the company said that it expects revenue from IT Services business segment to be in the range of $2,635 million to $2,688 million. This translates to sequential guidance of 0% to 2.0% in constant currency terms. Reliance Industries (RIL) slipped 4.84%. The company reported a 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on a 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ICICI Bank slipped 4.65%. The bank reported a 4.02% fall in standalone net profit to Rs 11,318 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 11,792 crore in Q3 FY25. Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26. Net interest margin was 4.30% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.25% in Q3 FY25. Provisions (excluding provision for tax) were Rs 2,556 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 1,227 crore in Q3 FY25. HDFC Bank declined 1.64%. The company reported an 11.46% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 18,563.75 crore on a 2.91% increase in total income to Rs 90,005 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. LTIMindtree dropped 6.91%. The company reported a 30.73% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 970.6 crore despite a 3.72% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q2 September 2025. Persistent Systems slipped 4.14%. The company reported a 6.79% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 439.4 crore despite of 5.52% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3778.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Bajaj Consumer Care jumped 6.38%. The company’s net profit rose 83.2% YoY to Rs 46.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 25.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 32.7% YoY to Rs 306.1 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 230.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Dr Reddy’s Laboratories rallied 5.07%. The company reported a 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1209.8 crore despite a 4.4% jump in revenue to Rs 8,716.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Cipla tanked 5.94%. The company reported 56.96% decrease in consolidated net profit to Rs 675.80 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,570.51 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations marginally rose 0.02% to Rs 7,074.48 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7,072.97 crore in Q3 FY25. Global Market: The December Eurozone annual CPI figure is expected to be 2.0%, hitting the European Central Bank’s target for the first time since mid-2025, down from 2.1% in November. Japan’s central bank held its key policy rate at 0.75% as the country prepares to go into an election in which Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi, who advocates for monetary easing and fiscal support, will face voters for the first time. Japan’s headline inflation rate in December slowed sharply to 2.1%, its lowest level since March 2022. Its core inflation rate came in at 2.4% on the year. South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. China’s economic growth slowed to its weakest pace in nearly three years in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, though full-year growth matched Beijing’s target despite growing trade frictions with the U.S. and a prolonged real estate slump. China’s gross domestic product grew 4.5% in the October-to-December period, data from the National Statistics Bureau showed Monday. That marked a slowdown from 4.8% in the third quarter and was the weakest reading since the first quarter of 2023, when growth also came in at 4.5%. The full-year economic output came in at 5%, meeting the official target of around 5%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at a premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-a-premium/1667158</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667158</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,080, a premium of 31.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,048.65 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,080, a premium of 31.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,048.65 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index lost 241.25 points or 0.95% to 25,048.65. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.31% to 14.19. HDFC Bank, Reliance Industries and ICICI Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers ends with significant losses; Nifty settles below 25,050 marks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-ends-with-significant-losses-nifty-settles-below-25050-marks/1667156</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667156</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today as sentiment remained cautious with investors tracking global cues and awaiting further clarity on domestic triggers, keeping market moves range-bound.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today as sentiment remained cautious with investors tracking global cues and awaiting further clarity on domestic triggers, keeping market moves range-bound. The Nifty settled below the 25,050 mark. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 769.67 points or 0.94% to 81,537.70. The Nifty 50 index lost 241.25 points or 0.95% to 25,048.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index dropped 1.56%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 2.19%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.31% to 14.19. The rupee hit a fresh record low of 91.99 against the US dollar in intraday trade on Friday, pressured by weak global cues and persistent dollar demand. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty IT index (down 0.17%), the Nifty FMCG index (down 0.61%) and the Nifty Consumer Durables (down 0.82%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Realty index (down 3.34%), the Nifty Media index (down 2.51%) and the Nifty PSU Bank index (down 2.27%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. World Economic Forum: In a surprise appearance at the World Economic Forum in Davos, billionaire Elon Musk said artificial intelligence could become smarter than all of humanity combined within the next five years. India has emerged as a premier hub for artificial intelligence applications, leveraging its tech-positive population and strong software legacy to transition into a “full-on AI economy”, according to the World Economic Forum’s Cathy Li. “India is a fascinating market, particularly in terms of AI applications and services. It is a no-brainer to leverage these strengths, and the country is already using its strong building blocks to move toward a full-on AI economy,” she said. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was up 0.27% to 6.654 as compared with the previous close of 6.636. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.8950 compared with its close of 91.5800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement gained 0.25% to Rs 1,56,769. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.01% to 98.17. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.28% to 4.239. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement gained 80 cents or 1.25% to $64.86 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares declined on Friday as investors digest events at Davos, including Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy's excoriating speech about the continent. Asian indices ended higher, tracking Wall Street gains as geopolitical concerns eased. The Bank of Japan kept its key policy rate unchanged at 0.75% but raised Japan’s growth outlook ahead of the upcoming election. The central bank lifted its GDP growth forecast for FY26 to 0.9% from 0.7% and for FY27 to 1% from 0.7%, citing a moderate global recovery, rising wages and prices, supportive government measures, and accommodative financial conditions. Japan’s headline inflation rate in December slowed sharply to 2.1%, its lowest level since March 2022. Its core inflation rate came in at 2.4% on the year. Some tech stocks in Asia fell after shares of California-based Intel plummeted 13% in after-hours U.S. trading on its soft guidance for the current quarter, despite posting fourth-quarter earnings beats Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the main benchmarks extended their gains from the previous session after Greenland tensions eased. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 306.78 points, or 0.63%, and closed at 49,384.01. The 30-stock index recovered from the losses seen earlier this week following President Donald Trump’s new Europe tariffs announcement. The S&P 500 climbed 0.55% and ended at 6,913.35. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.91% and settled at 23,436.02, supported by gains in Nvidia, Microsoft, and Meta Platforms.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sona BLW slides after Q3 PAT falls 13% QoQ to Rs 151 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sona-blw-slides-after-q3-pat-falls-13-qoq-to-rs-151-crore/1667232</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667232</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 5.40% QoQ to Rs 1,199.76 crore during the quarter.

However, revenue from operations rose 5.40% QoQ to Rs 1,199.76 crore during the quarter. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit declined marginally by 0.27%, while revenue surged 38.23% for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 241.55 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of 15.74% YoY. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 40.14 crore during the quarter under review. EBITDA stood at Rs 304.60 crore, registering a growth of 30.05% from Rs 234.20 crore posted in the corresponding quarter last year. However, the EBITDA margin declined to 25.2% in Q3 FY26 from 27.0% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, revenue from battery electric vehicles (BEV) grew 38% YoY, reflecting strong momentum in the company’s EV business. Vivek Vikram Singh, MD & Group CEO, said, “In Q3 FY25, we achieved our highest-ever quarterly revenue, EBITDA, and adjusted net profit in Q3 FY26. Our revenue grew strongly by 39% year on year, primarily driven by the expansion of our electric vehicle traction motor and railway business in India. BEV revenue share improved meaningfully to 38% in Q3 from 32% in Q2FY26 and represents our second-best quarter till date in terms of absolute BEV revenue and share. We have commercialized a new product in this quarter, the hydraulic motor controller, leveraging our strengths in motors and controllers to develop the solution for a new application outside the current product portfolio. We continue to add new EV customers and win new EV programs from our existing EV customers. Moreover, we commenced sample production of in-cabin radar sensors in our new SMT line at Chennai facility in this quarter, making us one of the few automotive radar manufacturers in India with local SMT manufacturing capability.” Meanwhile, the company’s board has declared an interim dividend of Rs 1.60 per equity share for the financial year 2025–26. The record date has been fixed as Friday, 30 January 2026. Sona BLW Precision Forgings is one of the world's leading automotive technology companies. The company has emerged as a global supplier with nine manufacturing and assembly facilities across India, the USA, Mexico, and China. It is primarily engaged in designing, manufacturing, and supplying highly engineered, mission-critical automotive systems and components to automotive OEMs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SonaBLWPrecisionForgingsLtd_30715559_18341.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India Cements slumps on reporting dismal Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-cements-slumps-on-reporting-dismal-q3-performance/1667153</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667153</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations jumped by 18.55% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,114.264 crore in Q3 FY26.

However, revenue from operations jumped by 18.55% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,114.264 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 3.93 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to a pre-tax loss of Rs 306.45 crore recorded in the same period a year ago. The firm reported exceptional items of Rs 8.47 crore during the quarter The company achieved domestic sales volumes of 2.59 million tonnes, reflecting an 25% YoY growth. Cement realizations, net of logistics costs, also improved by 0.17% compared to the December 2025 quarter. Total expenses fell 9.89% to Rs 1,134.03 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,258.56 crore posted in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 247.83 crore (up 23.34% YoY), and employee benefits expense stood at Rs 69.89 crore (up 0.37% YoY) during the quarter under review. India Cements business is the manufacturing and sale of cement and cement-related products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndiaCements_6042944115_270.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index declines 3.34%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-declines-334/1667150</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667150</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index ended down 3.34% at 756.35 today.

Nifty Realty index ended down 3.34% at 756.35 today. The index is down 15.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Anant Raj Ltd slipped 6.75%, Godrej Properties Ltd fell 4.89% and Lodha Developers Ltd shed 4.78%. The Nifty Realty index is down 13.00% over last one year compared to the 7.94% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Media index is down 2.51% and Nifty PSU Bank index has slid 2.27% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has declined 0.95% to close at 25048.65 while the SENSEX is down 0.94% to close at 81537.7 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finance-background-picture-id625756386_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 770 pts lower; Nifty ends tad below 25,050; VIX spurts 6.31%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-770-pts-lower-nifty-ends-tad-below-25050-vix-spurts-631/1667149</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667149</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with major cuts today, marking a sharp reversal from the previous session’s gains, as broad-based selling pressure emerged across sectors.

The key equity benchmarks ended with major cuts today, marking a sharp reversal from the previous session’s gains, as broad-based selling pressure emerged across sectors. Investors turned cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026 amid rising domestic and global uncertainties. The Nifty ended a tad below the 25,050 mark. All the sectoral indices in the NSE traded in the red, with realty, media, and PSU bank shares losing the most. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 769.67 points or 0.94% to 81,537.70. The Nifty 50 index lost 241.25 points or 0.95% to 25,048.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index dropped 1.56%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 2.19%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,325 shares rose and 2,884 shares fell. A total of 152 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.31% to 14.19. The rupee hit a fresh record low of 91.99 against the US dollar in intraday trade on Friday, pressured by weak global cues and persistent dollar demand. The Indian stock market will remain shut on Monday, 26 January 2026, for Republic Day. World Economic Forum: In a surprise appearance at the World Economic Forum in Davos, billionaire Elon Musk said artificial intelligence could become smarter than all of humanity combined within the next five years. India has emerged as a premier hub for artificial intelligence applications, leveraging its tech-positive population and strong software legacy to transition into a “full-on AI economy,” according to the World Economic Forum’s Cathy Li. “India is a fascinating market, particularly in terms of AI applications and services. It is a no-brainer to leverage these strengths, and the country is already using its strong building blocks to move toward a full-on AI economy,” she said. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index dropped 3.35% to 756.30. The index tumbled 11.34% over the past five consecutive trading sessions. Anant Raj (down 6.74%), Lodha Developers (down 4.98%), Godrej Properties (down 4.88%), DLF (down 4.12%), Brigade Enterprises (down 2.56%), Phoenix Mills (down 2.56%), SignatureGlobal India (down 2.54%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 2.52%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.96%) jumped. Stocks in Spotlight: Adani Energy Solutions tumbled 10.70% after the company reported 1.68% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 552.31 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 561.78 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 15.73% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,729.65 crore in Q3 FY26. Cipla tanked 3.80% after the company reported 56.96% decrease in consolidated net profit to Rs 675.80 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,570.51 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations marginally rose 0.02% to Rs 7,074.48 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7,072.97 crore in Q3 FY25. InterGlobe Aviaition (Indigo) declined 4.01% after the company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 77.55% to Rs 549.8 crore despite 6.16% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 23,471.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atul added 1.04% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 47.82% to Rs 160.74 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 108.74 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 11.06% YoY to Rs 1,573.62 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Coforge declined 2.81% after the company reported 33.4% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 250.2 crore despite a 5.1% increase in gross revenues to Rs 4,188.1 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY26. Gujarat State Petronet (GSPL) fell 1.39% after its standalone net profit fell 15.70% to Rs 114.26 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 4.5% to Rs 272.19 crore compared with the same quarter last year. Computer Age Management Services declined 3.87%. The company reported 0.04% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 125.53 crore on a 5.52% increase in revenue from operations from operations to Rs 390.13 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. InfoBeans Technologies tumbled 9.27% after the company reported 15% drop in net profit to Rs 19 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 23 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue for the period under review was Rs 138 crore, up 6% QoQ. DLF fell 4.06%. The company reported an 13.66% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,203.36 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,058.73 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations surged 32.15% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 2,020.22 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Home First Finance Company India jumped 6.12% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 43.97% to Rs 140.20 crore on 18.8% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 482.24 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ideaforge Technology slipped 7.01% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 33.85 crore in Q3 FY26, widening from Rs 24.02 crore in Q3 FY25. Despite the wider loss, the company’s revenue from operations increased 79.15% year on year (YoY) to Rs 31.55 crore during the quarter. Innova Captab soared 3.28% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 23.11% to Rs 42.14 crore on 42.29% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 450.29 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Premier Energies fell 7.82%. The company reported a 53.44% year-on-year (YoY) surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 391.62 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 255.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.02% YoY to Rs 1,936.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: European shares declined on Friday as investors digested events at Davos, including Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy’s excoriating speech about the continent. Most Asian markets ended higher, tracking Wall Street gains as geopolitical concerns eased. The Bank of Japan kept its key policy rate unchanged at 0.75% but raised Japan’s growth outlook ahead of the upcoming election. The central bank lifted its GDP growth forecast for FY26 to 0.9% from 0.7% and for FY27 to 1% from 0.7%, citing a moderate global recovery, rising wages and prices, supportive government measures, and accommodative financial conditions. Japan’s headline inflation rate in December slowed sharply to 2.1%, its lowest level since March 2022. Its core inflation rate came in at 2.4% on the year. Some tech stocks in Asia fell after shares of California-based Intel plummeted 13% in after-hours U.S. trading on its soft guidance for the current quarter, despite posting fourth-quarter earnings beats Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the main benchmarks extended their gains from the previous session after Greenland tensions eased. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 306.78 points, or 0.63%, and closed at 49,384.01. The 30-stock index recovered from the losses seen earlier this week following President Donald Trump’s new Europe tariffs announcement. The S&P 500 climbed 0.55% and ended at 6,913.35. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.91% and settled at 23,436.02, supported by gains in Nvidia, Microsoft, and Meta Platforms.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Atul gains after Q3 PAT climbs 48% YoY to Rs 161 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/atul-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-48-yoy-to-rs-161-cr/1667135</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667135</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations increased 11.06% YoY to Rs 1,573.62 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations increased 11.06% YoY to Rs 1,573.62 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 28.91% to Rs 203.48 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 157.84 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses rose 10.32% to Rs 1,410.06 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,278.05 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of material consumed stood at Rs 744.15 crore (up 10.13% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 166.73 crore (up 48.30% YoY), while finance cost stood at Rs 3.70 crore (down 13.75% YoY) and power, fuel and water expenses were at Rs 148.65 crore (down 16.38% YoY) during the period under review. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 30.86% YoY to Rs 467.75 crore, while revenue increased 11.41% YoY to Rs 4,603.47 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Atul, a part of the Lalbhai Group (Gujarat), is a diversified and integrated Indian chemical company engaged in the manufacturing of life science chemicals and performance & other chemicals. The company, along with its subsidiaries, serves a wide range of industries including adhesives, agriculture, animal feed, automobiles, composites, construction, cosmetics, defence, dyestuffs, electrical and electronics, flavours and fragrances, food, footwear, glass, home care, horticulture, hospitality, paints and coatings, paper, personal care, pharmaceuticals, plastics, polymers, rubber, soaps and detergents, sports and leisure, textiles, tyres, and wind energy across global markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Atul_38989432980_43.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>