<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:45:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR edges lower amid dollar strength abroad and negative cues from equities ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-edges-lower-amid-dollar-strength-abroad-and-negative-cues-from-equities/1671707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671707</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee lost momentum in opening trades on Thursday but recovered thereafter.

The Indian rupee lost momentum in opening trades on Thursday but recovered thereafter. INR opened lower at Rs 90.52 against the dollar and rebounded to a high of 90.37 so far during the day. Negative cues from equities and broad dollar strength in limiting gians in the counter. Asian markets are trading mostly lower on Thursday, following the mixed cues from Wall Street overnight, reflecting the continued weakness in technology stocks which mirrored their peers on the tech-heavy Nasdaq amid valuation concerns. Yesterday, rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.43 against the US dollar, after a sharp rally in the previous trading session following India-US trade deal announcement and possible dollar buying by corporates and importers. However, caution still remains as there is no signed or officially released trade agreement yet, no framework text or final documentation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trent gains after Q3 PAT climbs 36% YoY to Rs 640 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trent-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-36-yoy-to-rs-640-cr/1671702</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671702</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Trent advanced 1.10% to Rs 4,057.15 after the company reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Trent_20841567073_345.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lloyds Engg rallies after Q3 PAT climbs 71% YoY to Rs 61 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lloyds-engg-rallies-after-q3-pat-climbs-71-yoy-to-rs-61-cr/1671700</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671700</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 38.11% YoY to Rs 66.61 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 38.11% YoY to Rs 66.61 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA for the quarter stood at Rs 76.99 crore, up 44.39% YoY while EBITDA margin expanded 664 bps to 25.96% in Q3 FY26 as against 19.32% in Q3 FY25. Revenue from engineering segment stood at Rs 19.78 crore, up 19.78% YoY, The electrical segment delivered strong growth, with revenue rising 28.75% YoY to Rs 47.29 crore. As on 31st December 2025, the order book stood at Rs 2011.22 crore. Lloyds Engineering Works specializes in the design and manufacture of heavy equipment and systems for the hydrocarbon, oil & gas, steel, power, naval and nuclear sectors. The company is engaged in design, engineering, manufacturing, fabrication, supply, erection and commissioning of all types of mechanical, hydraulic, structural, process plants, metallurgical, chemical plants equipment including marine loading/ unloading arms, truck/wagon loading/unloading arms, columns, pressure vessels, dryers, boilers, power plant, steel plant equipment, capital equipment and execution of turnkey, epc projects, manufacturer of elevator, motor, and submersible pump.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsSteelsIndustriesLtd_74513842593_67056.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Parag Milk Foods tumbles after Q3 PAT declines 18% YoY amid commodity inflation headwinds ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/parag-milk-foods-tumbles-after-q3-pat-declines-18-yoy-amid-commodity-inflation-headwinds/1671697</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671697</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a YoY basis in Q3 FY26, gross profit increased to Rs 262 crore, up 9%.

On a YoY basis in Q3 FY26, gross profit increased to Rs 262 crore, up 9%. However, gross margin declined by nearly 130 basis points, from 27.2% to 25.9% due to cost inflation offset by favourable portfolio mix. EBITDA declined 5% YoY to Rs 76 crore as against Rs 80 crore, with EBITDA margin contracting by 150 basis points to 7.5%, largely tracking the gross margin compression. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 33 crore, down by 14% from Rs 38 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Akshali Shah, executive director, PMFL, said: “Our value-added dairy engine continues to power ahead, reaffirming our dominance in core categories. At the same time, the acceleration of our New Age Business comprising of Pride of Cows and Avvatar, signals the emergence of Parag as a truly modern, consumer-centric FMCG brands driving premiumization with superior product offerings. The headwinds of commodity inflation are likely to continue in the foreseeable future. The company is well poised to navigate through these challenging times with the power of its brands, superior offerings and improved product mix.” Parag Milk Foods, established in 1992, is the largest private dairy FMCG company with a pan India presence.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ParagMilkFoodsLtd_60698755021_45144.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Force Motors gains as Q3 PAT soars 252% YoY to Rs 406 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/force-motors-gains-as-q3-pat-soars-252-yoy-to-rs-406-cr/1671696</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671696</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 12.7% to Rs 2,128.56 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,889.49 crore in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations rose 12.7% to Rs 2,128.56 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,889.49 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 331.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 177.15 crore a year ago, aided by exceptional items of Rs 211.24 crore comprising government incentives, partly offset by labour code–related employee benefits liabilities. Total expenses rose 5.48% year on year to Rs 1,827.43 crore in Q3 FY26. Employee benefit expense stood at Rs 167.45 crore (up 27.35% YoY), while finance costs were at Rs 0.16 crore (down 96.12% YoY) during the period under review. In a separate filing, the company announced plans to fully acquire Veera Tanneries by March 31, 2026. The proposed acquisition marks a strategic expansion move for the automotive manufacturer, signaling diversification beyond its core automotive business, with a clear timeline set for completion of the full buyout. Force Motors is engaged in manufacturing light commercial vehicles, utility vehicles, and engines. It is an automobile company with a focus on the design, development, and manufacture of a range of automotive components, aggregates, and vehicles.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ForceMotors_49967151331_53.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge drift in early trade; breadth negative]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-drift-in-early-trade-breadth-negative/1671693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671693</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor losses in early trade amid muted global cues, a day after extending gains for the third straight session.

The domestic equity indices traded with minor losses in early trade amid muted global cues, a day after extending gains for the third straight session. Sentiment remained cautious following volatility in global IT stocks, triggered by concerns over Anthropic’s latest AI tool and its potential impact on sector valuations. The Nifty traded below the 25,750 mark. FMCG, PSU bank and oil & gas shares advanced while metal, realty and auto shares declined. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 294.25 points or 0.35% to 85,523.44. The Nifty 50 index fell 33.80 points or 0.13% to 25,742.20. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.65% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.67%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,509 shares rose and 1,567 shares fell. A total of 156 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 29.79 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 249.54 crore in the Indian equity market on 04 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Trent fell 1.11%. The company reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Power Company fell 2.25% after it has reported 25.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 771.98 crore on 9.37% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 13,948.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JSW Cement added 4.38% after it has reported consolidated net profit of Rs 149.02 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 68.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.16% YoY to Rs 1621.22 crore in Q3 FY26. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel has started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.39% to 6.695 compared with previous session close of 6.721. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.4725 compared with its close of 90.4700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.25% to Rs 151,139. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.15% to 97.80. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.33% to 4.264. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell $1.36 or 1.96% to $68.19 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market mostly fell Thursday as the tech sell-off on Wall Street gained momentum, with cryptocurrencies also falling. Bitcoin declined more than 3%, hovering just above the $73,000 level, after falling below that mark earlier. The S&P 500 fell on Wednesday as the sell-off in technology stocks intensified. The broad market index slid 0.51% and closed at 6,882.72, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 260.31 points, or 0.53%, and settled at 49,501.30. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1.51% to end at 22,904.58. Meanwhile, ADP on Wednesday released its monthly look at private payroll growth for January, which showed an increase of just 22,000 on the month. That’s below the gain of 45,000 jobs that was forecasted and widely reported in the media.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd Spikes 2.65%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-petroleum-corporation-ltd-spikes-265/1671689</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671689</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd rose 2.65% today to trade at Rs 471.25.

Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd rose 2.65% today to trade at Rs 471.25. The BSE Oil & Gas index is up 0.49% to quote at 29164.89. The index is up 3.34 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Indian Oil Corporation Ltd increased 2.37% and Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd added 1.8% on the day. The BSE Oil & Gas index went up 14.73 % over last one year compared to the 7.01% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd has lost 2.09% over last one month compared to 3.34% gain in BSE Oil & Gas index and 1.54% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 48018 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 2.35 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 508.45 on 05 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 287.55 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HPCL_59291502793_2305.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd Falls 5.02%, BSE Metal index Drops 1.17%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-ltd-falls-502-bse-metal-index-drops-117/1671690</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671690</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd lost 5.02% today to trade at Rs 607.05.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd lost 5.02% today to trade at Rs 607.05. The BSE Metal index is down 1.17% to quote at 39177.46. The index is up 3.15 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Vedanta Ltd decreased 4.05% and National Aluminium Company Ltd lost 3.32% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 37.62 % over last one year compared to the 7.01% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Zinc Ltd has lost 5.58% over last one month compared to 3.15% gain in BSE Metal index and 1.54% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 17.23 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 732.6 on 28 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 378.65 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oberoi Realty emerges as highest bidder for lease land in Mumbai]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oberoi-realty-emerges-as-highest-bidder-for-lease-land-in-mumbai/1671686</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671686</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing post market hours yesterday, the company stated that it had participated in the bids invited by Railway Land Development Authority (RLDA), a statutory authority under the Ministry of Railways, Government of India.

In a regulatory filing post market hours yesterday, the company stated that it had participated in the bids invited by Railway Land Development Authority (RLDA), a statutory authority under the Ministry of Railways, Government of India. The actuion was for grant of lease for the development of approx. 45,371 square meters (approximately 11 acres) of railway land in Bandra East, adjoining Western Express Highway, Mumbai, for 99 years, with FSI potential of approximately 19.50 lakh square feet. The financial bids were opened by RLDA on Wednesday. The company’s bid, at Rs 5,400 crore, has emerged as the highest. “Communication from RLDA w.r.t. the next steps in the process is awaited,” the company said in a statement. Oberoi Realty is a real estate development company headquartered in Mumbai. It focuses on premium developments in the residential, office space, retail, hospitality and social infrastructure verticals. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 0.69% to Rs 622.64 crore on a 5.78% rise in net sales to Rs 1,492.64 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.15% to currently trade at Rs 1541.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OberoiRealty_76593607717_38025.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mishra Dhatu Nigam secures Rs 158-crore order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mishra-dhatu-nigam-secures-rs-158-crore-order/1671683</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671683</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mishra Dhatu Nigam is engaged in the business of manufacturing superalloys, titanium, special-purpose steel, and other special metals.

Mishra Dhatu Nigam is engaged in the business of manufacturing superalloys, titanium, special-purpose steel, and other special metals. The company reported a 45.6% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 12.96 crore, on a 19% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 207.76 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Mishra Dhatu Nigam rose 0.33% to Rs 363.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MishraDhatuNigamLtd_30871451450_14133.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at red opening for Nifty 50; Asian market trades lower]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-red-opening-for-nifty-50-asian-market-trades-lower/1671678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671678</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 44.50 points, suggesting a red start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 44.50 points, suggesting a red start for the Nifty 50 today. The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel has started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 29.79 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 249.54 crore in the Indian equity market on 04 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 2,815.48 so far in February (till 03 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia market mostly fell Thursday as the tech sell-off on Wall Street gained momentum, with cryptocurrencies also falling. Bitcoin declined more than 3%, hovering just above the $73,000 level, after falling below that mark earlier. The S&P 500 fell on Wednesday as the sell-off in technology stocks intensified. The broad market index slid 0.51% and closed at 6,882.72, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 260.31 points, or 0.53%, and settled at 49,501.30. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1.51% to end at 22,904.58. Meanwhile, ADP on Wednesday released its monthly look at private payroll growth for January, which showed an increase of just 22,000 on the month. That’s below the gain of 45,000 jobs that was forecasted and widely reported in the media. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks eked out modest gains on Tuesday, extending their rally to a third straight session. Sentiment remained supported by the landmark India-US trade agreement, which helped ease external uncertainty. Gains, however, were capped as rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran kept risk appetite in check. The Nifty 50 closed above the 25,750 level, led by buying in consumer durables, energy and auto stocks, while IT shares lagged amid a global technology selloff. The S&P BSE Sensex added 78.56 points or 0.09% to 83,817.69. The Nifty 50 index rose 48.45 points or 0.19% to 25,776. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.83% while the Nifty jumped 3.82%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waaree Energies secures 150 MW solar module order in the US]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waaree-energies-secures-150-mw-solar-module-order-in-the-us/1671610</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671610</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the supply of the solar modules will be executed over the years 2026 and 2027.

In an exchange filing, the company said the supply of the solar modules will be executed over the years 2026 and 2027. Waaree Energies clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the entity awarding the contract. The company also confirmed that the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction and is fully compliant with applicable regulatory norms. Mumbai-based Waaree Energies is a renewable energy company. It offers innovative solar solutions, including panel manufacturing, EPC services, project development, and rooftop systems. The company reported a 115.64% year-on-year (YoY) jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,062.46 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 492.69 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Revenue from operations soared 118.81% YoY to Rs 7,565.05 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter rose 0.03% to 3,103 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WaareeEnergiesLtd_42747859_39763.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Trent, Tata Power, JSW Cement, Cummins India, Marico]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-trent-tata-power-jsw-cement-cummins-india-marico/1671608</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671608</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on Thursday, 5 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on Thursday, 5 February 2026. Earnings to Watch: Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles, Bharti Airtel, Bharti Hexacom, Hero MotoCorp, Hindustan Copper, Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail, Allcargo Logistics, Alembic Pharmaceuticals, PVR Inox, Berger Paints India, Godrej Properties, FSN E-Commerce, Page Industries, Power Finance Corporation, Borosil, Caplin Point Laboratories, Cemindia Projects, Dalmia Bharat Sugar and Industries, Data Patterns (India), Dhanuka Agritech, Dredging Corporation of India, Eveready Industries India, FDC, Gokul Agro Resources, Goodyear India, Harsha Engineers International, HealthCare Global Enterprises, Rail Vikas Nigam will declare their results later today. Stocks to Watch: Trent reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Power Company reported 25.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 771.98 crore on 9.37% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 13,948.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JSW Cement reported consolidated net profit of Rs 149.02 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 68.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.16% YoY to Rs 1621.22 crore in Q3 FY26. Cummins India reported a 12.96% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 486.06 crore on a 1.5% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 3006.24 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Metorpolis Healthcare’s consolidated net profit jumped 31.97% to Rs 4138.56 crore on 25.76% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 40,590.97 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Apollo Tyres reported 39.52% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 470.51 crore on 11.77% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7743.07 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Marico has entered into definitive agreements to acquire a 60% stake in Cosmix Wellness, the company which owns the brand, Cosmix – one of India’s leading digital-first functional wellness brands, at an valuation of Rs 375 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>