<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Krishival Foods Ltd Partly Paidup leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/krishival-foods-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-losers-in-b-group/1665257</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665257</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[S.M.

S.M. Gold Ltd, Naksh Precious Metals Ltd, Landmark Cars Ltd and Fedbank Financial Services Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 16 January 2026. Krishival Foods Ltd Partly Paidup tumbled 9.99% to Rs 120.3 at 13:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 14 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3012 shares in the past one month. S.M. Gold Ltd lost 9.98% to Rs 18.14. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.04 lakh shares in the past one month. Naksh Precious Metals Ltd crashed 9.82% to Rs 5.14. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2320 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 60104 shares in the past one month. Landmark Cars Ltd corrected 8.76% to Rs 410.35. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9085 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12675 shares in the past one month. Fedbank Financial Services Ltd shed 8.73% to Rs 161. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.87 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 95617 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Indiamart Intermesh Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-indiamart-intermesh-ltd-counter/1665251</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665251</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Zen Technologies Ltd, Federal Bank Ltd, HBL Engineering Ltd, Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 16 January 2026.

Zen Technologies Ltd, Federal Bank Ltd, HBL Engineering Ltd, Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 16 January 2026. Indiamart Intermesh Ltd witnessed volume of 10.29 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.62 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 81530 shares. The stock increased 8.32% to Rs.2,290.50. Volumes stood at 3.4 lakh shares in the last session. Zen Technologies Ltd saw volume of 36.09 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.13 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.24 lakh shares. The stock increased 5.96% to Rs.1,301.30. Volumes stood at 2.34 lakh shares in the last session. Federal Bank Ltd recorded volume of 533.38 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.28 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 84.87 lakh shares. The stock gained 8.22% to Rs.267.15. Volumes stood at 112.88 lakh shares in the last session. HBL Engineering Ltd registered volume of 103.93 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.97 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 17.39 lakh shares. The stock slipped 9.36% to Rs.796.05. Volumes stood at 23.05 lakh shares in the last session. Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts Ltd notched up volume of 19.3 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.71 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.38 lakh shares. The stock slipped 0.38% to Rs.450.55. Volumes stood at 5.23 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndiaMARTInterMESH_51321124_68842.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade with moderate gains; private bank shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-with-moderate-gains-private-bank-shares-advance/1665256</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665256</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with small gains in mid-afternoon trade, supported by a rally in IT stocks after Infosys reported stronger-than-expected quarterly results and raised its full-year revenue growth guidance.

The domestic equity indices traded with small gains in mid-afternoon trade, supported by a rally in IT stocks after Infosys reported stronger-than-expected quarterly results and raised its full-year revenue growth guidance. Meanwhile, in the Maharashtra elections, the Bharatiya Janata Party–Shiv Sena alliance was leading in early trends, boosting investor sentiment as markets typically view political stability and continuity in governance as positive for economic and policy outlook. The Nifty traded above the 25,650 mark. Private bank shares advanced after declining in the past trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 198.87 points or 0.24% to 83,581.58. The Nifty 50 index added 30 points or 0.11% to 25,695.80. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.02% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.36%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,870 shares rose and 2,296 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. Maharashtra elections result 2026 updates: The Maharashtra civic body poll results indicated a favourable trend for the Bharatiya Janata Party–Shiv Sena alliance, according to early trends as votes were being counted for elections to 29 civic bodies. As of 2:15 pm, the BJP was leading in 1,014 wards, while its ally Shiv Sena was ahead in 290 wards. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Private Bank index rose 0.54% to 28,716.90. The index shed 0.03% in the past trading session. Nifty Private Bank index, Federal Bank (up 8.22%), RBL Bank (up 4.18%), Yes Bank (up 1.83%), IndusInd Bank (up 0.71%), HDFC Bank (up 0.64%) and IDFC First Bank (up 0.46%) advanced. On the other hand, Bandhan Bank (down 1.25%), Axis Bank (down 0.47%) and ICICI Bank (down 0.20%) edged lower. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.24% to 6.663 compared with previous session close of 6.647. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7600 compared with its close of 90.3400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement declined 0.07% to Rs 143,015. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 99.09. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.26% to 4.172. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement gained 9 cents or 0.14% to $63.85 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Anand Rathi Share and Stock Brokers rallied 5.39% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 71.77% to Rs 37 crore on 21.45% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 248.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Nelco tanked 3.46% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 1.19 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 4.95 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income declined 4.08% YoY to Rs 78.88 crore in Q3 FY26, from Rs 82.24 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Anand Rathi Share and Stock Brokers rallies after Q3 PAT climbs 72% YoY to Rs 37 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/anand-rathi-share-and-stock-brokers-rallies-after-q3-pat-climbs-72-yoy-to-rs-37-cr/1665249</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665249</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 73.44% YoY to Rs 49.76 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 73.44% YoY to Rs 49.76 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. During the quarter, consolidated EBITDA stood at Rs 101.15 crore, registering a growth of 31.5% compared with Rs 76.91 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 40.8% in Q3 FY26 from 37.6% in Q3 FY25. On the segmental front, revenue from broking-related services stood at Rs 128.66 crore (up 12% YoY), interest income from Margin Trading Facility (MTF) was Rs 43.83 crore (up 45.7% YoY), distribution income came in at Rs 25.06 crore (up 37.7% YoY) and other income from operations stood at Rs 50.65 crore (up 22.8% YoY) during the quarter. The Margin Trading Facility book stood at Rs 1,231.67 crore, reflecting a 46.1% YoY growth, highlighting strong investor appetite and platform engagement. Assets under management grew by 32.1% YoY to Rs 8,368.84 crore, creating an enduring revenue pipeline for the future. The company’s total client base increased 14.6% YoY to 9,92,531 clients in Q3 FY26. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit rose 2.95% YoY to Rs 87.72 crore, while revenue increased 4.71% YoY to Rs 676.50 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Pradeep Gupta, chairman and managing director, said, " The Indian capital markets had a rough ride in FY26, with the Sensex and Nifty delivering lacklustre gains; under-performing other significant global peers. There was pressure from sustained selling by foreign investors, citing concerns over weak earnings, stretched valuations and currency volatility, which resulted in the benchmark indices remaining subdued despite brief mid-year rallies. Despite this backdrop, our business continued to grow. We delivered strong broking revenues, with Assets under Custody rising 48% year-on-year to Rs 1.06 trillion, an affirmation of our clients' trust and our disciplined approach to financial stewardship. Our non-broking businesses also registered meaningful growth, with the MTF book expanding 46% YoY to Rs 12,317 million and Assets under Management increasing 32% Yo Y to Rs 83,688 million. We will continue our focus on de-risking and stabilizing our earnings through increased exposure in the non-broking segments. In the era of discount and algorithm broking, we remain customer-oriented and our approach will always be relationship-based which is why over 54% of our clients have been with us since longer than 3 years. We take great pride in the enduring relationships that we have built - an affirmation about the consistency of our service, the relevance of our offerings and the strength of our brand." Anand Rathi Share and Stock Brokers is an established full-service brokerage house in India with over 30 years of experience. The company offerings and services are categorized in 3 categories: broking services, margin trading facility and distribution of financial products. The company caters to a diverse set of clients across retail, high net worth individuals, ultra-high net worth individuals, and institutions. The investment offerings of the company span across a wide array of asset classes like equity, derivatives, commodities, and currency markets. The client base is spread across various age demographics, with 2.21 lakh active clients at the end of March 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AnandRathiShareStockBrokersLtd_10551968_29599.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index climbs to over one-month high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-climbs-to-over-one-month-high/1665236</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665236</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar index climbed to over a month high on Friday after yesterday’s improved jobless claims report reduced bets of a near term Fed rate cut.

The US dollar index climbed to over a month high on Friday after yesterday’s improved jobless claims report reduced bets of a near term Fed rate cut. Data from the US Department of Labor (DOL) showed Initial Jobless Claims unexpectedly fell to 198K in the week ended January 10, below market expectations of 215K and down from the prior week’s revised 207K. The data confirmed that layoffs remain limited and that the labor market is holding up despite an extended period of high borrowing costs. Moreover, market sentiment improved after US President Donald Trump reportedly said he has no plans to remove Fed Chair Jerome Powell. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 99.11, marginally lower on the day but extending gains for the third week in a row.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold edges lower post recent highs; poised for 3% weekly gain]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-edges-lower-post-recent-highs-poised-for-3-weekly-gain/1665235</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665235</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices edged down to around $4,600 per ounce in Asian electronic trading on Friday, extending Thursday’s modest losses as safe-haven demand softened and expectations of an imminent Federal Reserve rate cut faded.

Gold prices edged down to around $4,600 per ounce in Asian electronic trading on Friday, extending Thursday’s modest losses as safe-haven demand softened and expectations of an imminent Federal Reserve rate cut faded. Geopolitical concerns in Iran eased after President Donald Trump indicated a possible delay in military action, following Iran’s pledge not to execute protesters. The US dollar index remained steady around 99, supported by robust economic data that tempered bets on near-term interest rate reductions, pushing the next fully priced Fed rate cut from June to July. In India, MCX February delivery bullion futures traded little changed at Rs 1,43,074 per 10 grams, maintaining momentum for a weekly gain of over 3%, having touched fresh highs of Rs 1,43,590 earlier in the week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade near flat line; European mrkt decline ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-near-flat-line-european-mrkt-decline/1665233</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665233</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices pared most of their gains and traded marginally higher in afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking and continued foreign fund outflows.

The key equity indices pared most of their gains and traded marginally higher in afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking and continued foreign fund outflows. Investors remained cautious ahead of earnings announcements from Reliance Industries, ICICI Bank and HDFC Bank, as well as amid ongoing geopolitical developments. The Nifty slipped below the 25,700 mark after hitting an intraday high of 25,873.50 in mid-morning trade. IT, realty and PSU Bank shares advanced while Consumer Durables, pharma and metal shares declined. At 13:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 98.99 points or 0.11% to 83,480.41. The Nifty 50 index added 1.65 points or 0.01% to 25,662.80. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.26% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.24%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,135 shares rose and 1,964 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Infosys (up 5.41%), Tech Mahindra (up 4.66%), Wipro (up 3.02%), Tata Consultancy Service (TCS) (up 2.36%) and HCL Technologies (up 2.32%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Infosys jumped 5.22% after the company raised its FY26 revenue growth forecast to 3.0%-3.5% in constant currency terms in Q3 FY26, up from projected 2%-3% in Q2 FY26. The company reported a 9.6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,654 crore on a 2.22% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 45,479 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company's net profit declined 2.2%, while revenue increased 8.9% in Q3 FY26. Cipla (down 2.55%), Eternal (down 2.36%), Bharat Electronics (BEL) (down 1.96%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (down 1.88%) and Jio Financial Services (down 1.72%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Jio Financial Services (JFSL) declined 1.72% after the company reported 8.8% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 268.98 crore despite a 105.5% surge in total revenue from operations to Rs 900.90 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Stocks in Spotlight: L&T Technology Services tumbled 4.78% after the company reported 0.1% rise in net profit to Rs 329.1 crore as revenue fell by 1.9% to Rs 2923.5 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY26. Angel One rallied 8.42% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 26.89% to Rs 268.66 crore on 11.08% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 1334.89 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Fedbank Financial Services fell 7.79%. The company has reported a net profit of Rs 87.9 crore in Q3 FY26, which is significantly higher as compared with the PAT of Rs 18.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 318.9 crore, up 16.8% YoY. Net total income in the December 2025 period rose by 11.8% to Rs 347.8 crore from Rs 311.0 crore in the December 2024 period. Prestige Estates Projects added 1.93% after the company recorded pre-sales of Rs 4,183.6 crore in Q3 FY26, representing a 39% year-on-year growth. Sales volume during the quarter stood at 2.99 million square feet, with the sale of 1,811 units. Ahluwalia Contracts (India) added 1.97% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 3,069.70 crore from the Central Vista Project Division-12, Central Public Work Department, New Delhi. LTIMindtree jumped 4.56% after the company said it had won a large contract from the Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) to build the next phase of India's tax analytics system. The company said it has been awarded the "Insight 2.0" project, a seven-year mandate valued at around Rs 3,000 crore, to modernise the national tax analytics platform. Global Markets: European market declined as investors digest ongoing geopolitical tensions. Data released earlier on Friday showed that German consumer prices were unchanged in December, rising 1.8% year on year—below the European Central Bank’s 2.0% medium-term target. Asian market broadly traded mixed on Friday even as major chip stocks edged higher. Shares of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. rose in trade after the company delivered another record quarter, saying it expects to boost capital spending in 2026 to between $52 billion and $56 billion. Investors across the region were also watching chip-related stocks after the U.S. reached a trade deal with Taiwan. Under the agreement, Taiwanese semiconductor companies commited to invest at least $250 billion in U.S. production capacity in exchange for lower “reciprocal” tariffs. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.60%, while the S&P 500 rose 0.26% and the Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.25%. U.S. bank stocks also advanced after the latest raft of quarterly earnings. Goldman Sachs advanced more than 4% after its fourth-quarter profit topped widely reported earnings estimates. Morgan Stanley surged nearly 6% after its wealth management unit contributed to top- and bottom-line beats in the fourth quarter. The rally also came on the back of solid economic data. Jobless claims data for the week ending Jan. 10 came in at 198,000, lower than the 215,000 expected by economists polled by Dow Jones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sterling and Wilson Renewable clocks PAT of Rs 2 crore in Q3; raises orderbook guidance to Rs 11,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sterling-and-wilson-renewable-clocks-pat-of-rs-2-crore-in-q3-raises-orderbook-guidance-to-rs-11000-crore/1665232</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665232</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has, however, seen a significant sequential recovery, moving back into the black from a net loss of Rs 478 crore recorded in Q2 FY26.

The company has, however, seen a significant sequential recovery, moving back into the black from a net loss of Rs 478 crore recorded in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations rose by 13.9% YoY to Rs 2,092 crore during the period under review. EBITDA declined by 30.1% to Rs 51 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 73 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 was 2.4% as against 4.0% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 5 crore, which is significantly lower as compared with the pre-tax profit of Rs 41 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. During Q3 FY26, the company signed a 5-year framework agreement with Adani Green, and also secured its first BOS order from them. SWREL also secured its second South African order worth USD 147 million during the quarter, while also adding two more Indian RE projects including a pure BESS order from a leading Indian IPP. The company further said that its new order inflow have been very strong this fiscal, touching Rs 6,929 crore during 9M FY26. The company has revised its new order inflow guidance for Fiscal 2026 to more than Rs 11,000 crore (up 60% YoY) on the back of continued ordering momentum. C. K. Thakur, Global CEO, Sterling and Wilson Renewable Energy Group, said: “SWREL has delivered robust revenue growth displaying our strong execution skills in the domestic segment. The marquee order from Adani Green and signing a strategic 5-year framework agreement with them is an important milestone reflecting the strong faith placed in our company’s execution by globally renowned RE developers. Furthermore, our continued order inflows and growing opportunities across domestic and international markets underscore the strong potential of our business, reinforcing SWREL’s visibility and quality of its growth pipeline.” Sterling and Wilson Renewable Energy (SWREL) is a global pure-play, end-to-end renewable engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) solutions provider. The company provides EPC services for utility-scale solar, floating solar, hybrid & energy storage and wind solutions and has a total portfolio of over 26.1 GWp. SWREL also manages an operation and maintenance (O&M) portfolio of 10.1 GWp solar power projects. The scrip zoomed 9.74% to currently trade at Rs 217.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SterlingWilsonRenewableEnergyLtd_13546287_74090.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nelco slumps on reporting dismal Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nelco-slumps-on-reporting-dismal-q3-performance/1665231</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665231</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income declined 4.08% YoY to Rs 78.88 crore in Q3 FY26, from Rs 82.24 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

Total income declined 4.08% YoY to Rs 78.88 crore in Q3 FY26, from Rs 82.24 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. The company reported a loss before tax of Rs 1.73 crore in Q3 FY26, against a profit before tax of Rs 6.98 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses rose 2.83% YoY to Rs 70.48 crore, compared with Rs 68.54 crore in Q3 FY25. Purchase of stock-in-trade stood at Rs 14.72 crore, up 99.59% YoY during the quarter. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit declined 0.57% YoY to Rs 0.87 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 0.88 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income fell 4.52% YoY to Rs 50.23 crore during the quarter. Nelco provides domestic satellite communication services to closed user group networks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NELCO_96557056478_410.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Canara Bank up for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/canara-bank-up-for-third-consecutive-session/1665224</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665224</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Canara Bank is up for a third straight session today.

Canara Bank is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 155.6, up 1.11% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 25755.6. The Sensex is at 83702.57, up 0.38%. Canara Bank has gained around 3.59% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Canara Bank is a constituent, has gained around 1.86% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59580.15, up 0.74% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 193.44 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 231.73 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 155.6, up 1.01% on the day. Canara Bank is up 58.97% in last one year as compared to a 11% jump in NIFTY and a 23.65% jump in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 7.5 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CanaraBank_17338928867_5471.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shriram Finance Ltd spurts 2.96%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shriram-finance-ltd-spurts-296-gains-for-third-straight-session/1665225</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665225</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shriram Finance Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Shriram Finance Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 1010.15, up 2.96% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 25755.6. The Sensex is at 83702.57, up 0.38%. Shriram Finance Ltd has risen around 16.89% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Shriram Finance Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.23% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27501.4, up 0.31% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 84.89 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 100.18 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1011, up 2.89% on the day. Shriram Finance Ltd is up 91.86% in last one year as compared to a 11% spurt in NIFTY and a 22.02% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 20.45 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShriramFinanceLtd_71599469_1745.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Infosys Ltd up for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/infosys-ltd-up-for-third-consecutive-session/1665226</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665226</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Infosys Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Infosys Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1689.3, up 5.59% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 25755.6. The Sensex is at 83702.57, up 0.38%. Infosys Ltd has gained around 5.45% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Infosys Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.43% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37822.7, up 3.38% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 139.36 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 67.48 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1691.1, up 5.08% on the day. Infosys Ltd is down 6.95% in last one year as compared to a 11% jump in NIFTY and a 6.97% jump in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 24.18 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Infosys_56909713360_2806.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nazara-technologies-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1665227</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665227</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Nazara Technologies Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 272.2, up 1.25% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 25755.6. The Sensex is at 83702.57, up 0.38%. Nazara Technologies Ltd has gained around 14.83% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Nazara Technologies Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.22% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1415.45, down 0.09% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 9.81 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 43.51 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 373.54 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NazaraTechnologies_39505358.8300902_33311.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Biocon Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/biocon-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1665228</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665228</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Biocon Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Biocon Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 383.95, up 1.31% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 25755.6. The Sensex is at 83702.57, up 0.38%. Biocon Ltd has slipped around 0.56% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Biocon Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 1.33% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22505.4, down 0.86% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 17.89 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 26.3 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 384.45, up 1.33% on the day. Biocon Ltd is down 2.48% in last one year as compared to a 11% jump in NIFTY and a 1.13% jump in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Biocon_44501850463_14801.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of India gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-india-gains-for-third-straight-session/1665229</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665229</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bank of India gained for a third straight session today.

Bank of India gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 156.76, up 2.54% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 25755.6. The Sensex is at 83702.57, up 0.38%. Bank of India has gained around 10.43% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty PSU Bank index of which Bank of India is a constituent, has gained around 8.08% in last one month and is currently quoting at 8910.65, up 0.9% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 125.32 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 75.84 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 156.7, up 2.19% on the day. Bank of India is up 56.4% in last one year as compared to a 11% jump in NIFTY and a 42.84% jump in the Nifty PSU Bank index. The PE of the stock is 6.99 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofIndia_12067469065_5654.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBL Bank Ltd soars 4.21%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbl-bank-ltd-soars-421/1665230</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665230</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RBL Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

RBL Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 325.15, up 4.21% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 25755.6. The Sensex is at 83702.57, up 0.38%. RBL Bank Ltd has risen around 9.5% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Private Bank index of which RBL Bank Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.27% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28561.85, up 0.48% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 73.39 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 50.2 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 326.15, up 4.12% on the day. RBL Bank Ltd is up 109.61% in last one year as compared to a 11% spurt in NIFTY and a 21.19% spurt in the Nifty Private Bank index. The PE of the stock is 40.07 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RBLBankLtd_63443224104_5982.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank soars 2.5%, gains for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/punjab-national-bank-soars-25-gains-for-fifth-straight-session/1665218</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665218</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank is up for a fifth straight session today.

Punjab National Bank is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 131.9, up 2.5% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.37% on the day, quoting at 25759.55. The Sensex is at 83749.1, up 0.44%. Punjab National Bank has gained around 10.53% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Punjab National Bank is a constituent, has gained around 1.9% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59580.15, up 0.78% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 242.5 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 150.93 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 132.07, up 2.32% on the day. Punjab National Bank is up 31.73% in last one year as compared to a 11.02% jump in NIFTY and a 23.71% jump in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 9.45 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd spurts 0.87%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-ltd-spurts-087-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1665219</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665219</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Vedanta Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 681.65, up 0.87% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.37% on the day, quoting at 25759.55. The Sensex is at 83749.1, up 0.44%. Vedanta Ltd has gained around 19.63% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Vedanta Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 11.22% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11661.4, up 0.05% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 182.38 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 155.57 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 681.1, up 0.78% on the day. Vedanta Ltd is up 50.13% in last one year as compared to a 11.02% jump in NIFTY and a 36.91% jump in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 28.08 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of Maharashtra soars 0.74%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-maharashtra-soars-074-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1665220</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665220</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bank of Maharashtra gained for a fifth straight session today.

Bank of Maharashtra gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 66.39, up 0.74% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.37% on the day, quoting at 25759.55. The Sensex is at 83749.1, up 0.44%. Bank of Maharashtra has risen around 17.01% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty PSU Bank index of which Bank of Maharashtra is a constituent, has risen around 8.2% in last one month and is currently quoting at 8910.65, up 1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 174.36 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 228.23 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 7.8 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofMaha_49685557243_5607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IT stocks rally as Infosys outlook lifts sector, Nifty IT jumps over 3%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/it-stocks-rally-as-infosys-outlook-lifts-sector-nifty-it-jumps-over-3/1665216</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665216</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty IT index rose 3.44% to 39,122.20, rebounding from a 1.08% fall in the previous session.

The Nifty IT index rose 3.44% to 39,122.20, rebounding from a 1.08% fall in the previous session. Infosys jumped 5.61%, while LTIMindtree gained 5.55%. Oracle Financial Services Software rose 5.00% and Tech Mahindra advanced 4.98%. Mphasis climbed 4.74%, followed by Wipro, which added 3.31%. Persistent Systems moved up 2.67%, Coforge gained 2.57%, Tata Consultancy Services rose 2.46%, and HCL Technologies climbed 2.17%. Infosys reported a 9.6% sequential drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,654 crore for the December quarter (Q3 FY26), while revenue from operations rose 2.22% quarter-on-quarter to Rs 45,479 crore. On a year-on-year basis, net profit declined 2.2%, while revenue increased 8.9%. Profit before tax stood at Rs 9,229 crore, down 9.78% quarter-on-quarter and 4.56% year-on-year. Operating profit fell 10.7% sequentially and 6.3% year-on-year to Rs 8,355 crore, with operating margin easing to 18.4% from 21.3% a year ago. The company said its results were impacted by higher employee-related costs following the implementation of India’s new Labour Codes, notified on 21 November 2025. The changes, which consolidate 29 labour laws, led to higher gratuity and leave liabilities. Infosys recorded a one-time impact of $143 million (Rs 1,289 crore) in its consolidated statement of comprehensive income. Infosys raised its FY26 constant currency revenue growth forecast to 3.0-3.5%, from 2-3% earlier, while maintaining its operating margin guidance at 20-22%. Constant currency revenue grew 1.7% year-on-year and 0.6% quarter-on-quarter in Q3 FY26. Revenue in dollar terms rose 3.2% year-on-year to $5,099 million. The improved outlook helped lift sentiment across the IT sector, driving broad-based buying in frontline technology stocks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Infosys_56909713360_2806.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>