<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:17:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PGIM India Mutual Fund announces Monthly Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pgim-india-mutual-fund-announces-monthly-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1664992</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664992</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PGIM India Mutual Fund has announced 19 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW under the following schemes.

PGIM India Mutual Fund has announced 19 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: PGIM India Arbitrage Fund: Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.0452 Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.0460 PGIM India Aggressive Hybrid Equity Fund: Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.1587 Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.1782 PGIM India Equity Savings Fund: Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.0651 Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.0716

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1664981</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664981</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced 16 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following scheme.

UTI Mutual Fund has announced 16 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following scheme. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: UTI-Multi Asset Allocation Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 2.55 Direct Plan – IDCW: 2.55

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>