<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:56:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Saatvik Green Energy wins Rs 17-cr solar pump supply order from MSEDCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/saatvik-green-energy-wins-rs-17-cr-solar-pump-supply-order-from-msedcl/1661942</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661942</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order entails the supply of 1,000 solar photovoltaic water pumping systems, with an approximate value of Rs 16.74 crore.

The order entails the supply of 1,000 solar photovoltaic water pumping systems, with an approximate value of Rs 16.74 crore. The scope of work includes installation and commissioning of the systems, which are to be completed within 60 days from the date of issuance of the notice to proceed or work order by the concerned circle office. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not involve any promoter or promoter group interest. The company also clarified that the order does not fall under related party transactions. Saatvik Green Energy is an integrated solar energy solutions provider engaged in manufacturing high-efficiency photovoltaic (PV) modules and offering EPC services for utility-scale, commercial, and industrial projects. The company’s net profit rose 36% year-on-year to Rs 83.24 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 61.20 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 61.6% YoY to Rs 768.03 crore from Rs 475.30 crore in Q2 FY25. Shares of Saatvik Green Energy rose 0.13% to Rs 382.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SAATVIKGREENENERGYLIMITED_74895602_94178.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lenskart's subsidiary to acquire nearly 29% stake in Korea-based startup iiNeer ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lenskarts-subsidiary-to-acquire-nearly-29-stake-in-korea-based-startup-iineer/1661943</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661943</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[At an exchange rate of Rs 0.062 per Korean Won, the acquisition sum totals to Rs 18.6 crore.

At an exchange rate of Rs 0.062 per Korean Won, the acquisition sum totals to Rs 18.6 crore. iiNeer is a Korea-based startup, which is focused on developing technology-enabled eye-testing and lens-cutting equipment. It had recorded a turnover of 177.77 million Korean Won in the calendar year 2024. This acquisition enables the company to build in-house optical hardware capabilities, specifically for manufacturing lens edging systems that include edgers, tracers, and blockers. By investing in these proprietary core equipment capabilities, the company expects to enhance operating efficiencies and reduce long-term capital expenditure on equipment. Lenskart Solutions is a technology-led eyewear company involved in designing, manufacturing, branding and retailing prescription glasses, sunglasses, contact lenses and related accessories. The company's consolidated net profit rose 19.60% to Rs 102.22 crore on a 20.77% increase in revenue to Rs 2096.15 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip rose 0.87% to currently trade at Rs 455.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LENSKARTSOLUTIONSLIMITED_69247877_68840.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at muted opening for equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-muted-opening-for-equities/1661935</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661935</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 20.00 points, indicating a muted opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 20.00 points, indicating a muted opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,721.26 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,381.34 crore in the Indian equity market on 24 December 2025, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 23,830.77 crore so far in December. This follows their cash sales of Rs 17,500.31 crore in November and Rs 2,346.89 crore in October. Global Markets: Asia markets traded higher Friday, with several exchanges in the region closed for the Boxing Day holiday. Silver prices continued rising and hit another high, after notching a record Wednesday. Spot silver rose more than 4% on Friday to reach an all-time high of $74.89 per ounce. Silver has rallied over 159% year to date. Metal prices have soared this year amid shaky investor sentiment on riskier assets, as fears of an AI bubble and uncertainty over U.S. Fed rate cuts mount. Meanwhile, core consumer prices in Tokyo rose 2.3% in December from a year earlier, according to government data Friday. The core CPI, which strips out volatile fresh food costs, remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target, reinforcing the case for more interest rate hikes. The latest reading was below the 2.8% increase in November. Tokyo’s inflation numbers are widely considered to be a leading indicator of nationwide trends. Australia and Hong Kong markets were closed for the holiday. U.S. equity futures ticked slightly higher in early Asian hours, after the S&P 500 closed at a new record for the second straight day on Wednesday stateside. The broad market index advanced 0.32%, ending the session at 6,932.05. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 288.75 points, or 0.60%, and also posted a closing record of 48,731.16. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.22% and settled at 23,613.31. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks slipped into the red on Wednesday in a quiet, pre-Christmas session marked by light volumes and subdued risk-taking. Foreign investors turned net sellers, while the absence of fresh cues capped buying interest. Weakness in oil and gas and IT stocks weighed on sentiment. The Nifty gave up early gains after hitting an intraday high of 26,236.40 and ended the day below the 26,150 mark, as traders squared off positions ahead of the holiday break. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 116.14 points or 0.14% to 85,408.70. The Nifty 50 index fell 35.05 points or 0.13% to 26,142.10.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: NBCC (India), Ola Electric, Lenskart Solutions, Gujarat Gas]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-nbcc-india-ola-electric-lenskart-solutions-gujarat-gas/1661934</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661934</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital banned from F&O trading on 26 December 2025.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital banned from F&O trading on 26 December 2025. Stocks To Watch: NBCC (India) has signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Board of Mumbai Port Authority for the development of CGO Complex on 25 acres at Mumbai Port's land, as deposit work on turnkey basis. Ola Electric Mobility received a sanction order from the Ministry of Heavy Industries, Government of India, for the release of incentives amounting to Rs 366.78 crore under the Production Linked Incentive Scheme for Automobile and Auto Components (PLI-Auto Scheme) for claims pertaining to FY 2024-25. Lenskart Solutions’ Singapore arm approved an investment of KRW 3 billon (approximately Rs 18.6 crore ) for the acquisition of 29.24% of the share capital of iiNeer Corp. Gujarat Gas’ Milind Torawane, IAS has resigned as managing director with effect from 24 th December 2025, following his transfer and appoint as Principal Secretary to Government, Education Department (Primary & Secondary Education). It has appointed Avantika Singh Aulakh, IAS as managing director. Strides Pharma Sciences’ wholly owned subsidiary, Strides Pharma Inc. USA has received a Form 483 with four observations from US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) following an inspection of its formulations facility at Chestnut Ridge, New York.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oriental Rail Infra bags Rs 5-cr order from ICF, Chennai]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oriental-rail-infra-bags-rs-5-cr-order-from-icf-chennai/1661933</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661933</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order is for the manufacturing, supply and installation of 64 sets of one-coach chair assemblies.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order is for the manufacturing, supply and installation of 64 sets of one-coach chair assemblies. The total contract value stands at Rs 4,90,04,928 and the order is scheduled to be executed by 8 February 2026. As per the terms of the contract, delivery will be made to ICF. Up to 90% of the supply value will be paid upon submission of the inspection certificate and the provisional physical receipt certificate. The remaining 10% of the supply value, along with 100% of the installation charges, will be released after receipt and acceptance of the stores by the consignee, based on the installation certificate issued by the competent authority. The company also clarified that neither its promoters nor members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding authority. It added that the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. Oriental Rail Infrastructure is engaged in the manufacturing and supply of several diversified railway products and items for Indian Railways and other related industries. Its products include seat & berths, recorn, compreg board & articles thereof, furniture & parts, coated upholstery fabric, plywood, phenolic resin & hardener, silicon foam, etc. The firm reported a 2% growth in consolidated net profit to Rs 10.67 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 10.46 crore recorded in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 28.33% YoY to Rs 133.39 crore for the quarter ended 30 September 2025. The counter rallied 5.81% to Rs 162 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OrientalVeneerProductsLtd_6722154754_15746.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>