<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:58:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/biofil-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1670193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670193</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd, United Foodbrands Ltd, Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd and Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 February 2026.

Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd, United Foodbrands Ltd, Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd and Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 February 2026. Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd surged 17.88% to Rs 40.81 at 12:01 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 51521 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16624 shares in the past one month. Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd spiked 13.24% to Rs 135.95. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 6910 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5797 shares in the past one month. United Foodbrands Ltd soared 13.00% to Rs 245.1. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.89 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5029 shares in the past one month. Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd advanced 12.15% to Rs 107.88. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1192 shares in the past one month. Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd jumped 11.01% to Rs 25.2. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 203 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 769 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BiofilChemicals_25533397190_3284.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Agarwal Industrial Corp gains on bagging Rs 219-cr order from BPCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/agarwal-industrial-corp-gains-on-bagging-rs-219-cr-order-from-bpcl/1670192</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670192</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves the supply of bulk bitumen (VG-30 and VG-40 grades) to BPCL’s Kakinada and Mangalore locations.

The contract involves the supply of bulk bitumen (VG-30 and VG-40 grades) to BPCL’s Kakinada and Mangalore locations. The firm order comprises 32,000 metric tonnes for Kakinada and 10,800 metric tonnes for Mangalore, aggregating to a total quantity of around 42,800 metric tonnes. The estimated contract value includes firm orders of approximately Rs 166.68 crore for Kakinada and Rs 51.91 crore for Mangalore. The project is scheduled to be executed over a one-year period from January 23, 2026, to January 22, 2027. Agarwal Industrial Corporation is primarily engaged in the manufacturing of bitumen and bitumen products. It also transports liquefied petroleum gas (LPG) and bituminous product. The company also forayed into the ship operating and chartering business through its subsidiary in the UAE. The company reported a 35% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 11.99 crore on a 24.8% fall in revenue to Rs 244.80 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AgarwalIndustrialCorporationLtd_81781984596_7400.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sharda Cropchem Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sharda-cropchem-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1670190</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670190</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Latent View Analytics Ltd, Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd, KNR Constructions Ltd and Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 February 2026.

Latent View Analytics Ltd, Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd, KNR Constructions Ltd and Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 February 2026. Sharda Cropchem Ltd soared 7.80% to Rs 1067.15 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 56700 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 50896 shares in the past one month. Latent View Analytics Ltd spiked 5.80% to Rs 442.4. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 5.09 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15621 shares in the past one month. Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd surged 5.30% to Rs 771.05. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 9944 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15370 shares in the past one month. KNR Constructions Ltd spurt 5.05% to Rs 148.7. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 64052 shares in the past one month. Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd rose 4.26% to Rs 170.25. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 8.27 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10.69 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShardaCropchem_3864079388_35410.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index net speculators reduce net short position]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-net-speculators-reduce-net-short-position/1670188</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670188</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index speculators reduced net short position, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

US dollar index speculators reduced net short position, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of US dollar index futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 4405 contracts in the data reported through January 27, 2026, showing an decrease of 2013 net short positions compared to the previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cigarette stocks slide as excise-led price hike weighs on sentiment]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cigarette-stocks-slide-as-excise-led-price-hike-weighs-on-sentiment/1670187</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670187</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Against this backdrop, VST Industries fell 1.76%, ITC declined 2.34%, while Godfrey Phillips India slid 5.29%, as investors reacted to higher prices triggered by the revised tax structure.

Against this backdrop, VST Industries fell 1.76%, ITC declined 2.34%, while Godfrey Phillips India slid 5.29%, as investors reacted to higher prices triggered by the revised tax structure. From February 2026, cigarettes and tobacco products will attract additional excise duty and cess over and above the highest 40% GST slab, replacing the earlier regime of 28% GST plus compensation cess. The Central Excise Act has also been amended to impose a per-stick excise duty on cigarettes, with rates linked to cigarette length. According to media reports, the cost of a pack of 10 cigarettes has increased by around Rs 22-Rs 25, while premium 76 mm cigarettes are expected to cost Rs 50-Rs 55 more per pack. Revised maximum retail prices are likely to take effect from February 2 as fresh stock with updated MRPs reaches wholesale markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VSTInds_23522197115_598.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's manufacturing PMI rebounds, consumer goods see upbeat sentiments]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-manufacturing-pmi-rebounds-consumer-goods-see-upbeat-sentiments/1670186</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670186</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[After losing growth traction at the end of 2025, Indian goods producers reported faster increases in new orders, output, employment and buying levels during January.

After losing growth traction at the end of 2025, Indian goods producers reported faster increases in new orders, output, employment and buying levels during January. Input prices rose to the greatest extent in four months, albeit one that was negligible by historical standards, while charge inflation eased further. Stock trends were mixed, with holdings of finished items falling as orders were often fulfilled from warehouses and pre-production inventories expanding due to input purchasing growth. Rising from a two-year low of 55.0 in December to 55.4 in January, the seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) – a gauge of overall conditions derived from measures of new orders, output, employment, supplier delivery times and stocks of purchases – indicated a stronger improvement in the health of the sector. The PMI came in below the flash estimate released in late-January (56.8), but remained above its long-run average. Granular data showed consumer goods as the brightest area of India's manufacturing industry, with the slowest improvement in operating conditions seen in capital goods.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id5822566_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers pare gains; PSU bank shares decline for 2nd decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-pare-gains-psu-bank-shares-decline-for-2nd-decline/1670182</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670182</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks reversed all gains and traded with small cuts in the early afternoon trade, extending their Budget Day losses.

The key equity benchmarks reversed all gains and traded with small cuts in the early afternoon trade, extending their Budget Day losses. Major indices, which had opened modestly higher on Monday, turned lower as investors assessed the federal budget, which fell short of expectations on measures to boost foreign investment and ease trading costs. The Nifty traded below 25,750 mark. PSU Bank shares declined for previous two consecutive trading sessions. At 11:28 ST, the S&P BSE Sensex, fell 114.20 points or 0.14% to 80,606.51. The Nifty 50 index fell 102.30 points or 0.41% to 24,723.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 1.23% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index declined 1.55%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,173 shares rose and 2,687 shares fell. A total of 192 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. Politics: Sunetra Pawar was sworn in Maharashtra's first woman Deputy Chief Minister on 31 January 2026, days after her husband Ajit Pawar's fatal plane crash on January 28 near Baramati Airport. A former Rajya Sabha MP and social activist from Baramati, Sunetra Pawar took oath at Lok Bhavan in Mumbai and said she would carry forward Ajit Pawar’s legacy of public service, focusing on social equality, women and youth empowerment, rural upliftment, and administrative reform. She will work alongside Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis and Deputy Chief Minister Eknath Shinde, strengthening the Mahayuti alliance. Sunetra Pawar is expected to handle portfolios such as Excise, Sports, and Youth Welfare and Minorities Development, with the Finance portfolio temporarily retained by the chief minister. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index fell 2.29% to 8,322.35. The index declined 7.72% in the previous two consecutive trading session. Indian Bank (down 3.3%), Bank of Baroda (down 2.86%), UCO Bank (down 2.67%), Punjab & Sind Bank (down 2.43%) and State Bank of India (down 2.38%), Punjab National Bank (down 2.28%), Central Bank of India (down 1.74%), Indian Overseas Bank (down 1.51%), Union Bank of India (down 1.42%) and Bank of India (down 0.96%) fell. Stocks in Spotlight: Studds Accessories declined 2.62%. The company reported a 26.3% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 20.7 crore on 9.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 163 crore in Q3 FY265 over Q3 FY25. Gokaldas Exports dropped 5.79% after the company reported 70.97% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 14.61 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 50.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Lupin declined 2.37%. The company announced a strategic collaboration with TB Alliance, to advance the clinical development and commercialization of Telacebec for the treatment of mycobacterial diseases, such as tuberculosis (TB), leprosy, and Buruli ulcer. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 389 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. Asian equities slipped on Monday as investors digested fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold continued to slide after last week’s drop. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gokaldas Exports slides after Q3 PAT tumbles 71% YoY to Rs 15 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gokaldas-exports-slides-after-q3-pat-tumbles-71-yoy-to-rs-15-crore/1670174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670174</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations shed 0.92% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 978.65 crore during the quarter.

Revenue from operations shed 0.92% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 978.65 crore during the quarter. The company stated that the India operation continues to maintain its growth momentum of 8% YoY, weathering the first full impact of US tariffs in the current quarter. AGOA uncertainty and supply chain delays impacted African businesses during the quarter. While EBIDTA reduced by 18% YoY to Rs 96 crore, EBIDTA margin declined by 202 basis points YoY to 9.7% in Q3 FY26. The drop in EBIDTA margin was mainly impacted mainly due to US tariff rebates. Productivity gains, strong order book and better cost management helped in absorbing the above impact to a good extent. However, the African business improved sequentially and is positioned for a good growth in the coming periods. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 26.14 crore, down by 61.17% from Rs 67.32 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Sivaramakrishnan Ganapathi, vice chairman and managing director of Gokaldas Exports, said, “Our India operation delivered a growth of 8% YoY, even after absorbing the first full impact of US tariffs in this quarter, whereas apparel export from India remained flat. With a possible renewal of AGOA on the cards, there is a stronger order book for Africa improving the outlook. The EBITDA margin was tempered by US tariff, but was offset by higher productivity gain and diligent cost management measures.” On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit fell 39.27% YoY to Rs 64.17 crore in 9M FY26, while revenue from operations rose 2.45% YoY to Rs 2,918.79 crore. Gokaldas Exports is an apparel manufacturer, designing, manufacturing, and exporting a diverse range of apparel products for all seasons. The company exports to a number of the world's most prestigious fashion brands and retailers in more than 50 countries.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GokaldasExports_17758090823_12966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin joins hands with TB Alliance to accelerate clinical development of Telacebec ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-joins-hands-with-tb-alliance-to-accelerate-clinical-development-of-telacebec/1670175</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670175</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TB Alliance is a non-profit drug developer.

TB Alliance is a non-profit drug developer. Under the terms of the agreement, Lupin and TB Alliance will collaborate to support the clinical development and commercialization of Telacebec, to provide advanced treatment options for patients affected by these diseases. TB Alliance will continue to lead the development process, while Lupin will provide its expertise in global manufacturing, regulatory affairs, and supply chain to ensure global access to Telacebec. Ramesh Swaminathan, executive director, Global CFO, and Head of IT and API Plus SBU, Lupin, said, “This collaboration with TB Alliance underscores Lupin’s enduring commitment to improving patient outcomes in areas of significant unmet medical need. By leveraging our manufacturing scale and global distribution capabilities alongside TB Alliance’s deep expertise in drug development, we aim to enable timely and equitable access to Telacebec and contribute meaningfully to the global fight against tuberculosis, leprosy, and Buruli ulcer.” Mel Spigelman, managing director (MD), president and chief executive officer (CEO), TB Alliance, said, “Telacebec represents the kind of scientific innovation that has the potential to transform treatment for diseases that have long been neglected. By partnering with Lupin, we are combining deep scientific expertise with global Chemistry, Manufacturing and Controls and access capabilities to help move this promising compound forward as quickly and responsibly as possible, with the ultimate goal of delivering better treatment options to people affected by tuberculosis, leprosy, and Buruli ulcer around the world.” Lupin is a global pharmaceutical leader headquartered in Mumbai, India, with products distributed in over 100 markets. It specializes in pharmaceutical products, including branded and generic formulations, complex generics, biotechnology products, and active pharmaceutical ingredients. The company had reported a 73.33% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,477.92 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 852.63 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 24.27% year-on-year to Rs 6,831.43 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. The counter declined 1.77% to Rs 2100.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Aegis Logistics Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-aegis-logistics-ltd-counter/1670173</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670173</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Latent View Analytics Ltd, Delhivery Ltd, Craftsman Automation Ltd, Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 02 February 2026.

Latent View Analytics Ltd, Delhivery Ltd, Craftsman Automation Ltd, Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 02 February 2026. Aegis Logistics Ltd saw volume of 13.11 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 28.11 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 46623 shares. The stock increased 0.53% to Rs.703.15. Volumes stood at 9399 shares in the last session. Latent View Analytics Ltd saw volume of 2.61 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 15.38 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 16963 shares. The stock increased 8.33% to Rs.453.00. Volumes stood at 17104 shares in the last session. Delhivery Ltd clocked volume of 30.91 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 10.35 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.99 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.28% to Rs.435.10. Volumes stood at 7.84 lakh shares in the last session. Craftsman Automation Ltd registered volume of 22197 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.39 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 5053 shares. The stock slipped 1.95% to Rs.7,283.50. Volumes stood at 3493 shares in the last session. Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd registered volume of 20812 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.08 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 5106 shares. The stock slipped 1.90% to Rs.3,918.00. Volumes stood at 1795 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisLogistics_61348536029_9.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Hannah Joseph Hospital's market entry sees a measured heartbeat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-hannah-joseph-hospitals-market-entry-sees-a-measured-heartbeat/1670172</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670172</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 65, a 7.14% discount to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 65, a 7.14% discount to the issue price. The stock was currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% to the listing price. The stock touched a high of Rs 68.25 and a low of Rs 61.75, with around 18.24 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Hannah Joseph Hospital's IPO was subscribed 1.51 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 January 2026 and it closed on 27 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 67 to Rs 70 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 60,00,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter group shareholding diluted to 68.83% from 93.57% pre-issue. The company intends to utilise the net proceeds for funding of capital expenditure for establishing radiation oncology centre and general corporate purpose. Ahead of the IPO, Hannah Joseph Hospital on 21 January 2025, raised Rs 11.94 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 17.06 lakh shares at Rs 70 each to 7 anchor investors. Hannah Joseph Hospital is a multi-specialty healthcare provider in Madurai, operating a centrally air-conditioned, 150-bed facility spread across a two-acre campus, equipped with modern medical and surgical infrastructure. The hospital has recorded steady growth in complex surgeries, patient volumes, and turnover, and has emerged as a key centre for neurosciences in Madurai and South Tamil Nadu, supported by an advanced neuroradiology department aligned with international standards. It has also expanded into cardiac sciences with a cath lab and dedicated cardiac operating theatres, enabling procedures ranging from complex coronary angioplasties to open-heart surgeries. As of 30 November 2025, the company had total 364 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 42.55 crore and net profit of Rs 5.12 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HannahJosephHospitalLimited_21919019_94645.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Forex reserves hit record high yet again ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/forex-reserves-hit-record-high-yet-again/1670169</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670169</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s foreign exchange reserves hit a fresh record high in the week ended January 23, rising due to a sharp gain in gold holdings and foreign currency assets, according to the latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India.The country’s forex reserves jumped by USD 8.053 billion during the week to USD 709.413 billion, surpassing the earlier peak of USD 704.89 billion recorded in September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growing-from-coin-jar-picture-id622446130_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 148 pts; oil & gas shares in demand ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-148-pts-oil-gas-shares-in-demand/1670168</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670168</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with small gains in the morning trade, supported by value buying in blue-chip stocks, after suffering a sharp drubbing on Budget day.

The key equity benchmarks traded with small gains in the morning trade, supported by value buying in blue-chip stocks, after suffering a sharp drubbing on Budget day. The Nifty traded above the 24,800 level, while Oil & Gas shares advanced after declining in the previous trading session. At 10:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, rose 147.90 points or 0.17% to 80,865.23. The Nifty 50 index added 1.90 points or 0.01% to 24,823.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.41% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index declined 0.79%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,390 shares rose and 2,206 shares fell. A total of 191 shares were unchanged. Earnings to Watch: Huyundai Motor India (down 1.40%), PB Fintech (down 1.67%), Utkarsh Small Finance Bank (SFB) (down 1.61%), Campus Activewear (up 2.02%), Corona Remedies (down 0.25%), Bajaj Housing Finance (down 0.98%), Aether Energy (down 1.70%), Aarti Industries (down 0.98%), Akzo Nobel (up 0.47%), Mahindra Lifespace Developers (up 0.95%), Orectra Greentech (up 0.35%), Railtel Corporation of India (down 0.90%) and Tata Chemicals (down 2.34%) will announce their quarterly results later today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index fell 0.59% to 11,522. The index declined 2.86% in the two consecutive trading session. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (up 3.41%), Petronet LNG (up 1.16%), Reliance Industries (up 1.07%), Indian Oil Corporation (up 0.91%) and Aegis Logistics (up 0.06%) added. On the other hand, Oil India (down 4.42%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 1.97%) and GAIL (India) (down 1.59%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Maruti Suzuki India shed 0.13%. The company reported total sales of 236,963 units in January 2026, registering an 11.6% YoY growth compared with 212,251 units sold in January 2025. Latent View Analytics added 7.74% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 19.69% to Rs 50.14 crore on 22.02% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 278 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Godrej Properties rose 1% after the company reported sales of over Rs 2,000 crore in Phase 1 of its residential project Godrej Trilogy in Worli.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Properties climbs as Worli project clocks over Rs 2,000 crore sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-properties-climbs-as-worli-project-clocks-over-rs-2000-crore-sales/1670167</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670167</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project was launched in November 2025, with nearly 100 homes sold since launch.

The project was launched in November 2025, with nearly 100 homes sold since launch. Godrej Trilogy is spread across 2.63 acres and consists of three towers. In the initial phase, the company launched select floors in two towers, Seaturf and Seafront, with an opened inventory of approximately Rs 3,500 crore. The project offers 3-bedroom and 4-bedroom residences, with three apartments per floor. The development offers views of the Arabian Sea, the Mumbai skyline, and the Mahalaxmi Racecourse. Once completed, the towers are expected to be among the tallest residential buildings in India. The project is located on Dr. Annie Besant Road in Worli, with access to the Mumbai Coastal Road, the Bandra-Worli Sea Link, and Metro Line 3. Amenities at the project include a five-level clubhouse with a spa, racquet club, and fitness centres. Godrej Trilogy is an IGBC Platinum pre-certified project. In FY 2025, Godrej Properties retained its position as India’s largest developer by the value of residential sales achieved. The company's consolidated net profit jumped 20.84% to Rs 405.08 crore, despite a 32.27% fall in net sales to Rs 470.38 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejPropert_34796940031_15613.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki reports 12% YoY sales growth in January 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maruti-suzuki-reports-12-yoy-sales-growth-in-january-2026/1670163</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670163</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic passenger vehicle (PV) sales stood at 174,529 units, marginally higher by 0.5% YoY, while sales of light commercial vehicles (LCVs) declined 7.8% YoY to 3,771 units during the month.

Domestic passenger vehicle (PV) sales stood at 174,529 units, marginally higher by 0.5% YoY, while sales of light commercial vehicles (LCVs) declined 7.8% YoY to 3,771 units during the month. While the company’s total domestic sales (PV+LCV+OEM) rose 0.4% YoY to 185,943 units, export sales, however, surged 88.3% YoY to 51,020 units, marking an all-time monthly high. For the period from April to January of FY26, the company has registered total sales of 1,983,467 units, up 7.7% YoY. Maruti Suzuki India is engaged in the manufacture, purchase, and sale of motor vehicles, components, and spare parts (automobiles). The company reported a 4.08% YoY increase in net profit to Rs 3,879.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,726.9 crore in Q3 FY25, while revenue from operations rose 28.74% YoY to Rs 49,904.1 crore. Shares of Maruti Suzuki India rose 0.31% to Rs 14,244.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1670161</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670161</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Mutual Fund has announced 04 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option and under the Periodic IDCW Periodic-Payout/Reinvestment) of following schemes.

Tata Mutual Fund has announced 04 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option and under the Periodic IDCW Periodic-Payout/Reinvestment) of following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Tata Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan & Direct Plan: 0.36 each. Tata Equity Savings Fund – Regular Plan & Direct Plan: 0.059 each.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Latent View Analytics jumps after Q3 PAT climbs 20% YoY to Rs 50 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/latent-view-analytics-jumps-after-q3-pat-climbs-20-yoy-to-rs-50-cr/1670151</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670151</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 19.04% YoY to Rs 66.78 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 19.04% YoY to Rs 66.78 crore during the quarter. Rajan Sethuraman, chief executive officer, LatentView, said, “During the quarter, we added 6 new client logos, while renewing most of our existing contracts. Our Financial Services practice continued to be a key growth driver, witnessing sequential growth of 20.6% and reinforcing its strategic importance to our overall performance. As we enter FY27, we continue to see strong, sustained momentum in Financial Services, reflecting the deep strategic role LatentView plays in supporting our clients’ short-term priorities and long-term business goals.” 2026 marks our 20th anniversary, and our commitment to turn data into impactful business decisions is as strong as ever. Looking forward, we remain focused on scaling AI and Agentic AI frameworks across the organization and strengthening our position as a trusted AI consultant and thought partner of choice for our clients.” Rajan Venkatesan, chief financial officer, LatentView, said, “In Q3FY26, we reported revenue of Rs 278.0 crore, witnessing sequential growth of 7.9% in rupee terms and 5.7% in dollar terms, indicating strong momentum in topline performance. The growth was primarily led by the Financial Services and Technology practices, which grew by 20.6% and 6.2%, respectively. We maintained an adjusted EBITDA margin at 23.0%, supported by operational discipline, despite the impact of one time costs. Excluding these one time items, adjusted EBITDA margin for the quarter would have been 24.6%. Employee costs for the quarter included a one time catch up expense related to the implementation of the new labour code, with a total impact of Rs 4.6 crore at the group level. On a recurring basis, we expect this to result in an incremental impact of approximately 10-15 basis points on margins going forward. We are in the process of restructuring salary components to ensure full compliance with the new labour code and expect this exercise to be completed by March 31, 2026.” Latent View Analytics (LatentView) is a global data analytics company. The company provides a 360-degree view of the digital consumer, enabling companies to predict new revenue streams, anticipate product trends and popularity, improve customer retention rates, and optimize investment decisions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/latentviewanalytics_44641535_39858.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade with small gains; oil & gas shares advance; VIX jumps 1.52%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-small-gains-oil-gas-shares-advance-vix-jumps-152/1670149</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670149</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade after a sharp sell-off during a special trading session on Sunday.

The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade after a sharp sell-off during a special trading session on Sunday. Investor sentiment weakened after the Union Budget for FY 2026–27 fell short of market expectations, particularly on issues related to foreign investment and trading costs. The Nifty traded above the 24,800 level. Oil & Gas, metal and banks shares advanced while FMCG, IT and media shares declined. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 197.32 points or 0.24% to 80,921.92. The Nifty 50 index rose 32.80 points or 0.11% to 24,843.55. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.56% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index declined 0.94%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,297 shares rose and 1,651 shares fell. A total of 151 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 1.52% to 15.33. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 588.34 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 682.73 crore in the Indian equity market on 1 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Hero Motocorp rose 0.21%. The company’s total sales jumped 26% to 5,57,871 units in January 2026 compared with 442,873 units in January 2025. Latent View added 2.61% after the company reported a 19.68% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 501.42 crore on 22.02% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2780.09 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Studds Accessories declined 2.27%. The company reported a 26.3% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 20.7 crore on 9.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 163 crore in Q3 FY265 over Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.96% to 6.759 compared with previous session close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7300 compared with its close of 90.7875 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.95% to Rs 144,885. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.10% to 97.09. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.12% to 4.239. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell $2.84 or 4.10% to $64.21 a barrel. Brent crude prices slid after U.S. President Donald Trump said over the weekend that Iran was “seriously talking” with Washington, signaling a possible easing of tensions with the OPEC member. The comments helped temper fears of a potential military strike that had earlier pushed oil prices to multi-month highs. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 354 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. Asian equities slipped on Monday as investors digested fresh private data on China’s factory activity for January, while gold continued to slide after last week’s drop. China’s manufacturing momentum picked up pace in January, a private survey released on Monday showed, with producers ramping up output and shipping goods ahead of the long Lunar New Year break. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. Over in the US, stocks ended lower on Friday as technology shares stayed under pressure, even as markets broadly welcomed President Donald Trump’s choice of Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve chair. Despite the late-month wobble and choppy trading through January, the S&P 500 still managed to close the month in positive territory. On Friday, the index slipped 0.43% for its third straight decline, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.36%, and the Nasdaq Composite lagged with a sharper 0.94% drop. Warsh’s nomination helped calm nerves around the Fed’s independence, given his past experience as a central bank governor and his firm views on inflation. While he is expected to favour lower interest rates in the near term, in line with Trump’s preferences, markets see him as someone likely to retain policy credibility rather than simply take cues from the White House.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Patterns (India) Ltd Spurts 4.15%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/data-patterns-india-ltd-spurts-415/1670147</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670147</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Data Patterns (India) Ltd rose 4.15% today to trade at Rs 2573.

Data Patterns (India) Ltd rose 4.15% today to trade at Rs 2573. The BSE Capital Goods index is up 0.53% to quote at 64996.15. The index is down 4.24 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Cochin Shipyard Ltd increased 2.52% and Bharat Electronics Ltd added 2.22% on the day. The BSE Capital Goods index went up 3.86 % over last one year compared to the 3.93% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Data Patterns (India) Ltd has lost 1.84% over last one month compared to 4.24% fall in BSE Capital Goods index and 6.07% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1945 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 51904 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 3267.2 on 06 Jun 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 1350.5 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DataPatternsIndiaLtd_64674034_39972.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd Falls 10.65%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/optiemus-infracom-ltd-falls-1065/1670148</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670148</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd lost 10.65% today to trade at Rs 350.

Optiemus Infracom Ltd lost 10.65% today to trade at Rs 350. The BSE Telecommunication index is down 0.7% to quote at 2912.49. The index is down 8.57 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Tata Communications Ltd decreased 2.32% and Bharti Hexacom Ltd lost 1.63% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 5.35 % over last one year compared to the 3.93% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Optiemus Infracom Ltd has lost 31.01% over last one month compared to 8.57% fall in BSE Telecommunication index and 6.07% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 8471 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 712.95 on 25 Sep 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 02 Feb 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OptiemusInfra_38144306001_5004.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>