<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:21:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Worth Peripherals Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/worth-peripherals-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662437</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662437</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Pavna Industries Ltd, Deccan Gold Mines Ltd, California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup and Prakash Steelage Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 December 2025.

Pavna Industries Ltd, Deccan Gold Mines Ltd, California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup and Prakash Steelage Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 December 2025. Worth Peripherals Ltd lost 17.08% to Rs 139.3 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1684 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 986 shares in the past one month. Pavna Industries Ltd crashed 12.88% to Rs 21.1. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 14391 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5511 shares in the past one month. Deccan Gold Mines Ltd tumbled 12.04% to Rs 92.8. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 19.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9.78 lakh shares in the past one month. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup dropped 10.99% to Rs 4.13. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1737 shares in the past one month. Prakash Steelage Ltd fell 9.38% to Rs 5.41. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6.95 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 56860 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WorthPeripheralsLtd_81529932771_71405.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade near flat line; PSU Bank shares jump]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-near-flat-line-psu-bank-shares-jump/1662438</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662438</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices traded with minor cuts in mid-afternoon trade amid continued foreign institutional investor (FII) selling.

The key domestic indices traded with minor cuts in mid-afternoon trade amid continued foreign institutional investor (FII) selling. Trading activity remained range-bound in the absence of strong domestic triggers and ahead of the year-end holiday period. The Nifty traded below the 25,950 mark. PSU Bank shares witnessed buying demand for second straight session. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 3.75 points or 0.10% to 84,608.82. The Nifty 50 index lost 13.70 points or 0.05% to 25,928.40. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.10%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,828 shares rose and 2,263 shares fell. A total of 189 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU bank index jumped 1.46% to 8,412.90. The index rose 1.51% in the two trading sessions. Indian Bank (up 2.67%), Bank of Maharashtra (up 2.65%), Canara Bank (up 1.56%), Indian Overseas Bank (up 1.48%), Union Bank of India (up 1.23%), Bank of Baroda (up 1.2%), Punjab National Bank (up 1.16%), Bank of India (up 1.04%), UCO Bank (up 1.02%) and State Bank of India (up 0.85%) surged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.03% to 6.597 as compared with the previous close of 6.595. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8175 compared with its close of 89.9825 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.64% to Rs 135,829. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.01% to 98.02. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.07% to 4.120. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement advanced 15 cents or 0.24% to $62.09 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Concord Drugs rallied 3.48% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 14.71 crore for the supply of various pharmaceutical products. Waaree Renewable Technologies rose 0.53%. The company has secured a domestic order from India’s largest manufacturers of pig iron, castings, and seamless tubes to develop a 35 MWp ground-mount solar power project on a turnkey basis, including operation & maintenance (O&M).

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Honasa Consumer Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-honasa-consumer-ltd-counter/1662436</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662436</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd, The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd, Astrazeneca Pharma India Ltd, Maharashtra Seamless Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 30 December 2025.

Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd, The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd, Astrazeneca Pharma India Ltd, Maharashtra Seamless Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 30 December 2025. Honasa Consumer Ltd registered volume of 193.17 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 27.19 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7.11 lakh shares. The stock rose 5.34% to Rs.291.80. Volumes stood at 10.21 lakh shares in the last session. Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd witnessed volume of 3.98 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.98 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 44277 shares. The stock dropped 6.00% to Rs.1,780.00. Volumes stood at 41821 shares in the last session. The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd registered volume of 3.15 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.61 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 41410 shares. The stock rose 3.29% to Rs.1,888.80. Volumes stood at 19811 shares in the last session. Astrazeneca Pharma India Ltd clocked volume of 38380 shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.47 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 7020 shares. The stock lost 3.02% to Rs.8,770.00. Volumes stood at 8945 shares in the last session. Maharashtra Seamless Ltd notched up volume of 7.72 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.33 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.45 lakh shares. The stock slipped 0.02% to Rs.551.00. Volumes stood at 1.33 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HonasaConsumerLtd_60997811_77264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps India bags Rs 21-cr off-grid solar project from Jharkhand RE Agency]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shakti-pumps-india-bags-rs-21-cr-off-grid-solar-project-from-jharkhand-re-agency/1662435</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662435</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total order value stands at Rs 19.29 crore, which amounts to Rs 21 crore.

The total order value stands at Rs 19.29 crore, which amounts to Rs 21 crore. The project is expected to be completed within 120 days from the date of the notice to proceed (NTP). The company confirmed that neither its promoters nor promoter group have any interest in the entity awarding the order, and the contract does not qualify as a related party transaction. Shakti Pumps (India) manufactures solar pumps, energy-efficient stainless-steel submersible pumps, pressure booster pumps, pump motors, and other products. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 10.56% to Rs 90.71 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 101.42 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5% YoY to Rs 666.35 crore in Q2 Sept 2025. Shares of Shakti Pumps India fell 0.99% to Rs 706.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME EPW India plugs into Dalal Street with a premium market listing]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-epw-india-plugs-into-dalal-street-with-a-premium-market-listing/1662434</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662434</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock listed at Rs 111, a 14.43% premium to the IPO price, and is currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% over the listing price.

The stock listed at Rs 111, a 14.43% premium to the IPO price, and is currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% over the listing price. It touched a high of Rs 116.55 and a low of Rs 111, with 5.12 lakh shares traded on the exchange. EPW India's IPO was subscribed 1.29 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 95 to Rs 97 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 32,79,600 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds to meet working capital requirements, repayment of banking facilities availed by the company and general corporate purpose. Ahead of the IPO, EPW India on 19 December 2025, raised Rs 9.04 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 9.32 lakh shares at Rs 97 per share to 3 anchor investors. EPW India is an IT electronics refurbishing company that provides refurbished electronic products at significantly lower prices compared to new products, using two supply chain models: direct-to-consumer (D2C) and business-to-business (B2B). The company’s business model encompasses an end-to-end reverse supply chain for IT assets. This involves procuring used IT assets such as laptops, desktops, Chromebooks, and peripherals, refurbishing them to near-new condition, and selling them directly to end users, including businesses and retail customers. Currently, the company sells IT products such as laptops, desktops, Chromebooks, monitors, and accessories (keyboards, mouse, etc.) through its own retail stores and website. As of 30 September 2025, the company had a total of 84 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 44.03 crore and net profit of Rs 4.02 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EPWIndiaLimited_22699479_95846.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Dachepalli Publishers opens a new chapter with a subdued market debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-dachepalli-publishers-opens-a-new-chapter-with-a-subdued-market-debut/1662429</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662429</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 81.60, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 81.60, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently down 1.96% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 85.65 and a low of Rs 77.55. About 12.41 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Dachepalli Publishers' IPO was subscribed 1.90 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 100 to Rs 102 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 39,60,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 73.56% from 100% pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds to meet working capital requirements, repayment of certain borrowing availed by company, in part or full and for general corporate purpose. Dachepalli Publishers is an Indian educational publishing company engaged in the development and distribution of textbooks, reference books, and academic materials for school and college curricula. As of 2025, the company has a catalogue of more than 600 titles across six publishing brands and operates in 10 states and union territories. The company distributes its products through a network of over 300 distributors and dealers, supported by an in-house sales team of more than 60 professionals. In FY25, Dachepalli Publishers sold over 4 million books and employed 205 people, delivering curriculum-aligned content in both print and digital formats. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 40.36 crore and net profit of Rs 7.61 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DachepalliPublishersLimited_68103588_95587.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Steel Exchange board OKs proposal to raise funds up to Rs 700 crore via equity route]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/steel-exchange-board-oks-proposal-to-raise-funds-up-to-rs-700-crore-via-equity-route/1662431</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662431</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Board has further delegated the powers to a Fund-Raising Committee constituted for this purpose, which shall have the authority to determine the structure, form of issuance, instrument, price, terms and conditions of the issue.

The Board has further delegated the powers to a Fund-Raising Committee constituted for this purpose, which shall have the authority to determine the structure, form of issuance, instrument, price, terms and conditions of the issue. The amount of fund raise is nearly 62% of the company’s full market capitalization, which currently stands at Rs 1,128.73 crore. Steel Exchange India is primarily engaged in the manufacturing of TMT bars, apart from billets, ingots, and power generation. The company also deals in the sale and purchase of steel products through its trading division and is recognized as one of the largest dealers for Rashtriya Ispat Nigam. The company’s standalone net profit declined 22.43% to Rs 2.11 crore on a 11.22% fall in revenue to Rs 231.76 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip tumbled 4.03% to currently trade at Rs 9.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SteelExchange_99094797223_21196.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-bank-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1662414</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662414</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

ICICI Bank Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1338.9, down 0.33% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.ICICI Bank Ltd has lost around 3.68% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which ICICI Bank Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.23% in last one month and is currently quoting at 58932.35, up 0.02% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 36.81 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 82.01 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1340, down 0.29% on the day. ICICI Bank Ltd jumped 4.47% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 15.9% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 19.39 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIBank_93786457618_5418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aegis-logistics-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1662415</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662415</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Aegis Logistics Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 704.9, down 1.02% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Aegis Logistics Ltd has eased around 8.15% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Aegis Logistics Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34868.75, down 0.42% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 72234 shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.22 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 47.44 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisLogistics_61348536029_9.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Finserv Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-finserv-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1662416</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662416</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bajaj Finserv Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Bajaj Finserv Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1990.9, down 1.05% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Bajaj Finserv Ltd has lost around 4.37% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Bajaj Finserv Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.97% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27363.5, down 0.35% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 13.99 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 8.93 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1992.1, down 0.74% on the day. Bajaj Finserv Ltd jumped 26.96% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 15.97% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 224.27 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajFinservLtd_81833438_28075.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1662417</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662417</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[BSE Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

BSE Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2591.6, down 1.4% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.BSE Ltd has lost around 10.22% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which BSE Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.97% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27363.5, down 0.35% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 17.72 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 41.15 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2591.2, down 1.4% on the day. BSE Ltd jumped 46% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 15.97% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 64.2 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BSELtd_11315994_21236.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Wipro Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wipro-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1662418</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662418</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Wipro Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Wipro Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 263.82, down 0.16% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Wipro Ltd has gained around 5.41% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Wipro Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.57% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38282.7, down 0.38% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 23.65 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 76.06 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 264.47, down 0.04% on the day. Wipro Ltd tumbled 12.6% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 12% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 23 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Wipro_36546468_614.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/persistent-systems-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1662419</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662419</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Persistent Systems Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 6203.5, down 0.4% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Persistent Systems Ltd has lost around 3.16% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Persistent Systems Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.57% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38282.7, down 0.38% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.2 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.14 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 6217.5, down 0.16% on the day. Persistent Systems Ltd tumbled 3.94% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 12% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 67.26 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PersistentSys_70071143_18286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oracle-financial-services-software-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1662420</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662420</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 7655, down 0.47% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd has lost around 6.07% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.57% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38282.7, down 0.38% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 78654 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.03 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 7644, down 0.51% on the day. Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd tumbled 40.15% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 12% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 19.87 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OracleFinServ_27814195267_13105.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Infosys Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/infosys-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1662421</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662421</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Infosys Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Infosys Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1635.9, down 0.54% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Infosys Ltd has gained around 4.6% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Infosys Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.57% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38282.7, down 0.38% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 16.69 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 75.61 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1638.6, down 0.5% on the day. Infosys Ltd tumbled 12.98% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 12% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 24.88 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Infosys_56909713360_2806.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zee-entertainment-enterprises-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1662422</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662422</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 90.06, down 0.75% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd has lost around 10.05% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.46% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1424.05, up 0.33% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 28.18 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 61.86 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 16.28 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZeeEntertainmen_48983040733_3126.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1662423</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662423</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1712.2, down 0.29% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd has eased around 5.27% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22578.3, down 0.72% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 9.85 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 20.24 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1714.9, up 0.02% on the day. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd tumbled 9.23% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 4.26% fall in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 88.17 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SunPharmaInds_69091260890_4325.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alkem Laboratories Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alkem-laboratories-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1662424</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662424</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Alkem Laboratories Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Alkem Laboratories Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5418, down 1.58% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Alkem Laboratories Ltd has eased around 3.41% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Alkem Laboratories Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22578.3, down 0.72% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 38116 shares today, compared to the daily average of 62815 shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5422.5, down 1.44% on the day. Alkem Laboratories Ltd tumbled 3.83% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 4.26% fall in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 29.41 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlkemLab_4180671424_19299.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yes Bank Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yes-bank-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1662425</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662425</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Yes Bank Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Yes Bank Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 21.34, down 0.09% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25897.6. The Sensex is at 84563.41, down 0.16%.Yes Bank Ltd has lost around 4.94% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Private Bank index of which Yes Bank Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.38% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28352.3, up 0.04% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 531.28 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 687.65 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 21.31, down 0.33% on the day. Yes Bank Ltd jumped 8.93% in last one year as compared to a 9.53% rally in NIFTY and a 14.46% spurt in the Nifty Private Bank index. The PE of the stock is 24 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/YesBank_75840425465_25267.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,900 level; broader mrkt underperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25900-level-broader-mrkt-underperforms/1662426</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662426</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate cuts in the afternoon trade as as muted year-end activity and continued concerns over foreign fund flows kept investors on the sidelines.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate cuts in the afternoon trade as as muted year-end activity and continued concerns over foreign fund flows kept investors on the sidelines. The Nifty traded below the 25,900 level. Realty, healthcare and pharma shares declined, while metal, PSU bank and auto shares advanced. At 13:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 141.25 points or 0.17% to 84,554.29. The Nifty 50 index lost 51.25 points or 0.20% to 25,890.85. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.42%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 0.58%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,658 shares rose and 2,340 shares fell. A total of 206 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Shriram Finance (up 1.98%), Hindalco Industries (up 1.77%), Axis Bank (up 1.34%), Bajaj Auto (up 1.19%) and Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.06%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Max Healthcare Institute (down 2.66%), Eternal (down 2.21%), Apollo Hospitals Enterprise (down 1.98%), SBI Life Insurance Company (down 1.79%) and InterGlobe Aviation (down 1.50%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharat Electronics (BEL) shed 0.81%. The company said that it has received additional orders worth Rs 569 crore since December 12. These orders include radars, tank overhauls, communication equipment, fire control systems, simulators, antenna stabilisation systems, security software, components, upgrades, and spares. Prime Focus advanced 2.83% after the company announced that its indirect subsidiary, Brahma AI Holdings (Brahma), has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, Brahma AI ME, on 29 December 2025 in the Abu Dhabi Global Market, UAE. NTPC Green Energy slipped 1.34%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary, NTPC Renewable Energy, has declared commercial operations of an additional 13.98 MW solar power capacity at the Khavda-I Solar PV Project in Gujarat. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers & Chemicals (GNFC) declined 1.76% after the company announced that managing director (MD) T Natarajan will resign effective 29 December 2025, following an order from the Government of Gujarat. Waaree Energies fell 1.24% after its whole time director (WTD) & chief executive officer (CEO), Amit Paithankar, resigned to pursue opportunities outside the organisation. Lemon Tree Hotels rose 1.09% after the company announced the execution of a Hotel Operation Agreement (HOA) for an upcoming property in Tirupati, Andhra Pradesh. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) lost 1.37%. The company said it has emerged as the lowest bidder (L1) for a contract worth Rs 201.23 crore from East Coast Railway. Niraj Cement Structurals advanced 2.65% after the company has secured a Rs 34.86-crore contract from Mumbai Metropolitan Region Development Authority (MMRDA) for building linkway foot overbridges (FOBs) at the Metro Line-7 Goregaon (East) station. Lupin shed 0.44%. The company said that it has entered into an exclusive License, Supply, and Distribution Agreement with China-based Gan & Lee Pharmaceuticals for a novel fortnightly GLP-1 receptor agonist, Bofanglutide. Bofanglutide injection is indicated for the treatment of type 2 diabetes and for weight management in overweight or obese individuals. Global Markets: European and Asian markets traded mixed on Tuesday, after the tech sell-down on Wall Street continued on AI bubble fears. Investors will be focused on China’s military exercises around Taiwan, after the world’s second-largest economy announced new drills surrounding the island Monday. Overnight in the U.S., stocks fell on Monday, spurred by losses in technology, after the S&P 500 scaled to record levels last week. The S&P 500 dropped 0.35% and closed at 6,905.74, while the Nasdaq Composite shed 0.50% and settled at 23,474.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back by 249.04 points, or 0.51%, and ended at 48,461.93. Meanwhile, silver pulled back more than 6% after reaching $80 per ounce for the first time ever overnight. This comes as the precious metal has had a massive run-up in 2025, surging almost 150% to become one of the year’s hottest trades.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>