<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:53:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tijaria Polypipes Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tijaria-polypipes-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1671815</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671815</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Loyal Textile Mills Ltd, Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd, Bartronics India Ltd and Diligent Media Corporation Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 February 2026.

Loyal Textile Mills Ltd, Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd, Bartronics India Ltd and Diligent Media Corporation Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 February 2026. Tijaria Polypipes Ltd surged 20.00% to Rs 6.36 at 11:54 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 2.41 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19895 shares in the past one month. Loyal Textile Mills Ltd soared 19.98% to Rs 254. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 217 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1254 shares in the past one month. Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd spiked 17.23% to Rs 27.69. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 3 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 905 shares in the past one month. Bartronics India Ltd exploded 17.22% to Rs 14.02. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 6.84 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.94 lakh shares in the past one month. Diligent Media Corporation Ltd jumped 15.92% to Rs 3.86. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 22653 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 28356 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TijariaPoly_63547462691_40460.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indo Tech Transformers posts over 29% YoY increase in Q3 PAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indo-tech-transformers-posts-over-29-yoy-increase-in-q3-pat/1671814</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671814</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PBIDT improved 15.4% YoY to Rs 35.29 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 30.59 crore in Q3 FY25.

PBIDT improved 15.4% YoY to Rs 35.29 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 30.59 crore in Q3 FY25. PBIDT margin expanded by 73 basis points YoY to 17.98% in the third quarter. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 33.50 crore, up by 16.1% from Rs 28.85 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Indo Tech Transformers is engaged in the business of manufacturing power and distribution transformers and various special application transformers, mobile substation transformers, and substations. The scrip tumbled 5.63% to currently trade at Rs 1414.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndoTechTrans_24423190996_19825.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Keystone Realtors drops after Q3 PAT slumps 77% YoY to Rs 3 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/keystone-realtors-drops-after-q3-pat-slumps-77-yoy-to-rs-3-cr/1671813</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671813</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) tumbled 76.55% YoY to Rs 10.48 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) tumbled 76.55% YoY to Rs 10.48 crore during the quarter. EBITDA stood at Rs 39.1 crore in Q3 FY26, registering de-growth of 37.84%, compared with Rs 62.9 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. EBITDA margin improved to 13.3% in Q3 FY26 as against 12.9% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, pre-sales fell 3.01% YoY to Rs 837 crore, while collection dropped 3.32% YoY to Rs 524 crore. Gross Debt stands at Rs 625 crore and Gross Debt/Equity ratio is 0.22 as on Q3 FY26. During Q3FY26 the company launched 1 project with an estimated GDV of Rs 919 crore. With this launch, the total number of projects launched in YTD FY26 increased to five, with an estimated GDV of Rs 5,835 crore. About 83% of the full-year FY26 launches guidance of Rs 7,000 crore has already been achieved in YTD FY26. Boman Irani, chairman and managing director, Keystone Realtors, said, “We are delighted with the company’s strong performance in Q3 FY25-26, which reflects both the commitment of our teams and the continued trust of our customers. Building on the momentum from FY25, our pre-sales reached Rs 837 crore in Q3 FY26 and Rs 2,676 crore for YTD FY26, representing a robust 23% year-on-year growth. During the quarter, we successfully launched a new project with an estimated GDV of Rs 919 crore, taking our cumulative launches for YTD FY26 to five projects with a total GDV of Rs 5,835 crore. In line with our proactive business development strategy, we added another project with an estimated GDV of Rs 382 crore, bringing our cumulative additions for YTD FY26 to four new projects, including two cluster redevelopment initiatives, with a combined GDV of Rs 8,649 crore surpassing our full-year guidance.” Keystone Realtors is one of the prominent real estate developers in the Mumbai Metropolitan Region (MMR).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KeystoneRealtorsLtd_68331064_42751.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Westlife Foodworld Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/westlife-foodworld-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1671812</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671812</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Devyani International Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd, Jai Balaji Industries Ltd and Jubilant Foodworks Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 February 2026.

Devyani International Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd, Jai Balaji Industries Ltd and Jubilant Foodworks Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 February 2026. Westlife Foodworld Ltd surged 11.95% to Rs 534 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 75211 shares in the past one month. Devyani International Ltd spiked 8.88% to Rs 134.25. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 30.41 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.34 lakh shares in the past one month. Sapphire Foods India Ltd soared 6.41% to Rs 215.75. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.57 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21873 shares in the past one month. Jai Balaji Industries Ltd advanced 5.84% to Rs 75. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 89984 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 92641 shares in the past one month. Jubilant Foodworks Ltd rose 5.06% to Rs 542.5. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 76020 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WestlifeDevelop_24138693598_1543.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NHPC Q3 PAT slips 3% YoY to Rs 321 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nhpc-q3-pat-slips-3-yoy-to-rs-321-cr/1671786</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671786</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income declined 4.74% year-on-year to Rs 2,492.83 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total income declined 4.74% year-on-year to Rs 2,492.83 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Loss before tax and regulatory deferral account balances widened to Rs 282.20 crore in Q3 FY26 from a profit of Rs 400.57 crore in Q3 FY25. During Q3 FY26, total expenses increased 25.19% YoY to Rs 2,775.99 crore. Depreciation and amortization expenses stood at Rs 456.61 crore (up 53.89% YoY), and employee benefits expenses were Rs 346.41 crore (down 49.55% YoY) during the period under review. On the margins front, the company’s operating margin declined to 26.38% in Q3 FY26 from 33.62% in Q3 FY25. The net profit margin remained flat at 14.44% in Q3 FY26, unchanged from the corresponding quarter last year. Separately, the board approved an interim dividend of 14% (Rs 1.40 per equity share of face value Rs 10) for FY26. February 10, 2026, has been fixed as the record date, and the dividend will be paid within the statutory timeline. The company also proposed the cancellation of the MoU and Promoters’ Agreement with Green Energy Development Corporation of Odisha (GEDCOL) for setting up floating solar power projects in Odisha. Further, NHPC proposed the withdrawal of its nominee director from the board of PTC India Ltd and the relinquishment of its promoter status in PTC, in line with the Ministry of Power’s office memorandum dated 16 January 2026. NHPC, a Navratna Ratna public sector utility, is the Government of India’s flagship hydroelectric generation company. The company is primarily involved in the generation and sale of bulk power to various power utilities. Its other business includes providing project management/construction contracts/consultancy assignment services and trading of power. Shares of NHPC rose 0.80% to currently trade at Rs 78.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NHPCLtd_36439171799_12584.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hexaware Tech drops on softer Q4CY25 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hexaware-tech-drops-on-softer-q4cy25-performance/1671747</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671747</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, reported profit declined 9.1% YoY to Rs 291.6 crore in Q4CY25, compared with Rs 320.7 crore in Q4CY24.

On a consolidated basis, reported profit declined 9.1% YoY to Rs 291.6 crore in Q4CY25, compared with Rs 320.7 crore in Q4CY24. On a sequential basis, reported profit fell 21.2% QoQ from Rs 369.9 crore in Q3CY25. The quarter was impacted by an expense of Rs 111.1 crore related to the implementation of new labour codes, which weighed on reported profitability. Revenue in rupee terms rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 3,478.2 crore in Q4CY25, compared with Rs 3,154.4 crore in Q4CY24. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue was marginally lower by 0.2% from Rs 3,483.6 crore in Q3CY25. Revenue in dollar terms stood at $389 million, down 1.5% QoQ and up 4.5% YoY. Constant currency revenue declined 1.4% QoQ and rose 3.5% YoY. Profit before tax stood at Rs 325.5 crore in Q4CY25, down 34.5% vs Q3CY25 and down 21.9% vs Q4CY24. EBITDA stood at Rs 591.5 crore in Q4CY25, down 3.3% vs Q3CY25 and up 15.1% vs Q4CY24. EBITDA margin stood at 17.0% in Q4CY25, compared with 17.6% in Q3CY25 and 16.3% in Q4CY24. Employee benefits expense stood at Rs 2,040.3 crore in Q4CY25, up 12.1% YoY and 2.9% QoQ. Other expenses rose 25.5% YoY and 17.9% QoQ to Rs 1,060 crore. Finance costs increased 50.7% YoY to Rs 31.2 crore. Depreciation and amortisation rose sharply to Rs 123.7 crore, up 62.1% YoY. During the quarter, the company added one customer in the $100 million-plus revenue category and one customer in the $50 million-plus category, taking the $50 million-plus customer count to four in CY25 from three in CY24. The top 10 customers accounted for 36.4% of revenue in CY25. Closing headcount stood at 33,844, with a net addition of 1,535 employees since Q4CY24. Voluntary attrition for IT was at 11.0%, while utilisation for IT stood at 80.8% in Q4CY25. Days sales outstanding including billed and unbilled stood at 67 days, with billed DSO at 38 days. Adjusted cash conversion for CY25 was reported at 75.8%. Cash and cash equivalents stood at $237 million as of 31 December 2025. The management stated that the company is focusing on speed and agility, with a strategy to launch one AI-enabled service every month, while noting that CY25 was a challenging year for the industry but deal wins improved in the latter part of the year. Hexaware Technologies is a global digital and technology services company. It serves a diverse range of customers, including 30+ Fortune 500 organizations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HexawareTechnologiesltd_74145797_12111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Network Planning Group evaluates seven road projects for their conformity to PM GatiShakti principles]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/network-planning-group-evaluates-seven-road-projects-for-their-conformity-to-pm-gatishakti-principles/1671748</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671748</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Commerce & Industry has stated in a latest update that 108th meeting of the Network Planning Group (NPG) was held at Department for Promotion of Industry and Internal Trade (DPIIT).

Ministry of Commerce & Industry has stated in a latest update that 108th meeting of the Network Planning Group (NPG) was held at Department for Promotion of Industry and Internal Trade (DPIIT). The meeting was convened to evaluate infrastructure projects. The meeting focused on enhancing multimodal connectivity and logistics efficiency in alignment with the PM GatiShakti National Master Plan (PMGS NMP). The NPG evaluated seven road projects for their conformity to the PM GatiShakti principles of integrated multimodal infrastructure, last-mile connectivity to economic and social nodes and ‘Whole of Government’ approach.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/transport-3366421__340_silver.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty slides below 25,650 mark; consumer durables share decline ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-slides-below-25650-mark-consumer-durables-share-decline/1671746</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671746</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the early afternoon, snapping a three-day rally as investors resorted to profit booking at higher levels.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the early afternoon, snapping a three-day rally as investors resorted to profit booking at higher levels. Broader market indices mirrored the weak trend and traded under pressure. The Nifty traded below the 25,650 mark. Consumer Durables shares declined after advancing for previous three consecutive trading sessions. At 11:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, slipped 405.66 points or 0.48% to 83,412.03. The Nifty 50 index fell 134.95 points or 0.52% to 25,641.05. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.81% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 1.01%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,449 shares rose and 2,345 shares fell. A total of 190 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel has started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index fell 1.38% to 35,883.80. The index added 4.82% in the previous three consecutive trading session. Dixon Technologies (India) (down 4.02%), Kalyan Jewellers India (down 3.49%), Cera Sanitaryware (down 3.2%), Titan Company (down 1.54%), PG Electroplast (down 1.48%), Blue Star (down 1.47%), V-Guard Industries (down 0.96%), Amber Enterprises India (down 0.96%), Bata India (down 0.84%) and Kajaria Ceramics (down 0.81%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Cummins India added 2.78%. The company has reported an 11.84% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 453.10 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 514crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations shed 1.15% year-on-year to Rs 3,006.24 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Tata Power Company declined 2.30% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 25.1% to Rs 771.98 crore on 9.37% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 13,948.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Mitsu Chem Plast rose 5.29% after the company entered into a global supplier agreement with Poland's Arjohuntleigh Polska Sp. z o.o., following a year-long validation and approval process. Trent advanced 2.22% after the company reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asia market mostly fell Thursday as the tech sell-off on Wall Street gained momentum, with cryptocurrencies also falling. Bitcoin declined more than 3%, hovering just above the $73,000 level, after falling below that mark earlier. The S&P 500 fell on Wednesday as the sell-off in technology stocks intensified. The broad market index slid 0.51% and closed at 6,882.72, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 260.31 points, or 0.53%, and settled at 49,501.30. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1.51% to end at 22,904.58. Meanwhile, ADP on Wednesday released its monthly look at private payroll growth for January, which showed an increase of just 22,000 on the month. That’s below the gain of 45,000 jobs that was forecasted and widely reported in the media.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen slips near 157 as fiscal concerns and Fed outlook support dollar]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-slips-near-157-as-fiscal-concerns-and-fed-outlook-support-dollar/1671744</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671744</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen slipped toward 157 per dollar in electronic trading on Thursday, hovering near its weakest level in almost two weeks as concerns mounted over Japan’s fiscal outlook under Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s expansionary spending plans.

The Japanese yen slipped toward 157 per dollar in electronic trading on Thursday, hovering near its weakest level in almost two weeks as concerns mounted over Japan’s fiscal outlook under Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s expansionary spending plans. With snap elections scheduled for Sunday, expectations that the ruling Liberal Democratic Party may gain more seats have raised fears of increased debt-funded spending, weighing on the currency. Meanwhile, the dollar remained firm after US President Donald Trump nominated Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve Chair. Hopes that Warsh may favor maintaining higher interest rates boosted the greenback, adding further pressure on the yen in the near term.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cummins India Q3 PAT slides 12% YoY to Rs 453 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cummins-india-q3-pat-slides-12-yoy-to-rs-453-crore/1671734</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671734</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations shed 1.15% year-on-year to Rs 3,006.24 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations shed 1.15% year-on-year to Rs 3,006.24 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Domestic sales stood at Rs 2,535 crore, marginally softening by 2% compared with the same quarter last year and declining 2% sequentially. Export sales came in at Rs 471 crore, up 2% year-on-year but down 14% compared with the previous quarter. Total expenses declined 2.41% YoY to Rs 2,475.59 crore during the quarter. Cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 1,676.17 crore (up 2.37% YoY), while employee expenses came in at Rs 200.30 crore (down 14.12% YoY). Profit before exceptional items and tax rose 7.29% year-on-year to Rs 719.06 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 670.16 crore in the same quarter last year. On a nine-month basis, the company reported a 21.35% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,680.06 crore in 9M FY26, compared with Rs 1,384.41 crore in 9M FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 15.92% YoY to Rs 8,986.53 crore during the period. Shveta Arya, managing director, Cummins India, said, “I am pleased to share that Cummins India has recorded a revenue of over Rs 3,000 crore and continues steady execution on our profitable growth strategy, supported by volume leverage and operational efficiencies. The Consumer Price Index (CPI) remains stable compared to the last quarter, which shows rapid momentum. Other macroeconomic indicators, like Index of Industrial Production (IIP), crude oil price, show supportive trends. With indirect taxation reforms and further reduction in repo rate, we believe the Indian economy continues to be positioned for an estimated 7.4% GDP growth.” On its outlook, the company stated, "Domestic demand continues to demonstrate resilience, supported by sustained capital expenditure across key sectors. While exports face near-term pressures amid ongoing geopolitical uncertainties, we expect greater stability over the medium to long term. We remain watchful of policy developments and see continued collaboration with trade partners as a key enabler of growth across our end markets. Against this backdrop, we are executing with discipline maintaining prudent capital allocation, strong cost controls, and a healthy balance sheet and cash position. Customer satisfaction and shareholder value creation continue to be our primary focus. Backed by reliable technology, talent capabilities, a dependable brand, diverse products, strong manufacturing capabilities, and a wide distribution and service network, the Company is well-positioned to serve customers efficiently.” Meanwhile, the company’s board has approved and declared an interim dividend of Rs 20 per equity share for FY26 on 27.72 crore equity shares. The board has fixed Wednesday, 11 February 2026, as the record date for determining shareholder eligibility for the interim dividend. The dividend will be paid on or around Monday, 2 March 2026. Cummins India is one of the leading manufacturers of diesel and natural gas engines in India. As one of the seven legal entities under the Cummins Group in the country, the company operates through three core business units: Engine, Power Systems and Distribution. The counter rose 0.36% to Rs 4,215.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CumminsIndia_11953924793_337.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Power drops after Q3 PAT slips 25% YoY to Rs 772 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-power-drops-after-q3-pat-slips-25-yoy-to-rs-772-cr/1671735</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671735</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) rose 5.69% YoY to Rs 1,539.63 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) rose 5.69% YoY to Rs 1,539.63 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA stood at Rs 3,913 crore in Q3 FY26, up 12% YoY. During the quarter, revenue from renewable energy (RE) business surged 78% YoY to Rs 3,785 crore. Revenue from the transmission and distribution segment rose 8.76% YoY to Rs 9,626.24 crore while revenue from thermal & Hydro business tumbled 58.94% YoY to Rs 2,022.04 crore The company’s total installed capacity stands at 16.3 GW during the quarter. Praveer Sinha, CEO & managing director, Tata Power, said, “Q3 FY26 marked strong execution and all-round performance across Generation, Transmission, Distribution, Renewables, and Manufacturing. We crossed 10 GW of cumulative renewable EPC execution, delivered record solar cell and module output with industry-leading yields, scaled Rooftop Solar, cumulative installations, beyond 4 GWp. We now serve over 13 million Distribution customers nationwide - the largest base among private utilities. Our Odisha Discoms delivered strong financial and operational performance, earning A+ and A grades in the Ministry of Power’s 14th Integrated Ratings. In Transmission, we commissioned key projects strengthening green energy corridors. The World Bank’s financing for Bhutan’s largest PPP hydropower project further strengthens our clean energy portfolio and regional cooperation. Our nine-month performance positions us strongly as we enter 2026, supported by favourable macro conditions and rising power demand from manufacturing, urbanisation, and AI-led digital infrastructure. As India enters a decisive phase of power sector expansion, Tata Power remains focused on responsibly scaling clean energy capacity, strengthening system resilience, and delivering long-term, reliable growth.” Tata Power Company is a part of the Tata Group and primarily engaged in the generation, transmission, and distribution of electricity. It aims to produce electricity entirely through renewable sources.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataPowerCo_38377109932_554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-icici-prudential-life-insurance-company-ltd-counter/1671729</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671729</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Metropolis Healthcare Ltd, Devyani International Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 05 February 2026.

Metropolis Healthcare Ltd, Devyani International Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 05 February 2026. ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd saw volume of 1.49 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 10 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 14919 shares. The stock dropped 0.33% to Rs.657.95. Volumes stood at 12676 shares in the last session. Metropolis Healthcare Ltd clocked volume of 8978 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.97 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1503 shares. The stock gained 1.53% to Rs.1,920.10. Volumes stood at 2152 shares in the last session. Devyani International Ltd clocked volume of 16.37 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.94 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3.32 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.93% to Rs.131.85. Volumes stood at 19.17 lakh shares in the last session. BLS International Services Ltd witnessed volume of 26.99 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.66 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5.79 lakh shares. The stock increased 2.47% to Rs.296.35. Volumes stood at 36.62 lakh shares in the last session. Sapphire Foods India Ltd notched up volume of 1.17 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.55 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 25794 shares. The stock rose 5.87% to Rs.214.65. Volumes stood at 93319 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIPrudentialLifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_18603840404_22005.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1671731</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671731</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 05 February 2026.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 05 February 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name List of Existing Fund Manager(s) List of Revised Fund Manager(s) ICICI Prudential Smallcap Fund • Anish Tawakley • Aatur Shah • Rajat Chandak • Aatur Shah • Sakshat Goel • Gaurav Jain ICICI Prudential Large Cap Fund • Anish Tawakley • Vaibhav Dusad • Sankaran Naren • Vaibhav Dusad ICICI Prudential Business Cycle Fund • Anish Tawakley • Manish Banthia • Manan Tijoriwala • Divya Jain • Manish Banthia • Manan Tijoriwala • Divya Jain ICICI Prudential Equity Minimum Variance Fund • Vaibhav Dusad • Nitya Mishra • Aatur Shah • Nitya Mishra

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concord Control Systems jumps after bagging Rs 185 crore KAVACH 4.0 order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concord-control-systems-jumps-after-bagging-rs-185-crore-kavach-40-order/1671726</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671726</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order is for the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of KAVACH 4.0 on-board loco equipment.

The order is for the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of KAVACH 4.0 on-board loco equipment. The contract has been awarded by Indian Railways. The order has been routed through Progota India, an associate of Concord Control Systems. The project is scheduled to be executed within 12 months. KAVACH 4.0 is India's indigenous Automatic Train Protection system. It is designed to prevent collisions, over-speeding and signal violations. Concord Control Systems is India's leading manufacturer of embedded electronics systems and critical electronic solutions supporting India’s next-generation rail infrastructure. The company is an RDSO-approved OEM and technology leader delivering advanced electrical and electronic systems for Indian Railways. On a consolidated basis, the company had reported 93.48% jump in net profit to Rs 16.02 crore on a 63.92% increase in revenue to Rs 81.55 crore in H1 FY26 over H1 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ConcordControlSystemsLtd_63232532_77868.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1671718</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671718</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 05 February 2026.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 05 February 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager New Fund Manager Mirae Asset Liquid Fund Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni Mirae Asset Money Market Fund Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni Mirae Asset CRISIL IBX Gilt Index – April 2033 Index Fund Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni Mirae Asset Nifty AAA PSU Bond Plus SDL Apr 2026 50:50 Index Fund Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni Mirae Asset Nifty SDL Jun 2027 Index Fund Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni Mirae Asset Nifty SDL June 2028 Index Fund Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni Mirae Asset Nifty 8-13 yr G-Sec ETF Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni Mirae Asset CRISIL-IBX Financial Services 9-12 Months Debt Index Fund Mr. Basant Bafna Ms. Pranavi Kulkarni

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,700; metal shares slump]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25700-metal-shares-slump/1671716</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671716</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity indices traded with modest losses in the morning trade amid muted global cues.

The headline equity indices traded with modest losses in the morning trade amid muted global cues. The Nifty traded below the 25,700 mark. Metal shares corrected after advancing in the past three consecutive trading session. At 10:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, slipped 278.32 points or 0.33% to 83,539.46. The Nifty 50 index fell 88.45 points or 0.34% to 25,687.75. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.65% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.81%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,540 shares rose and 2,061 shares fell. A total of 206 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel has started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Earnings to Watch: Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles, Bharti Airtel, Bharti Hexacom, Hero MotoCorp, Hindustan Copper, Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail, Allcargo Logistics, Alembic Pharmaceuticals, PVR Inox, Berger Paints India, Godrej Properties, FSN E-Commerce, Page Industries, Power Finance Corporation, Borosil, Caplin Point Laboratories, Cemindia Projects, Dalmia Bharat Sugar and Industries, Data Patterns (India), Dhanuka Agritech, Dredging Corporation of India, Eveready Industries India, FDC, Gokul Agro Resources, Goodyear India, Harsha Engineers International, HealthCare Global Enterprises, Rail Vikas Nigam will declare their results later today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index tanked 2.33% to 11,763.30. The index rallied 6.12% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Zinc (down 5.37%), Vedanta (down 5.07%), National Aluminium Company (down 3.99%), Hindalco Industries (down 3.21%), NMDC (down 2.59%), Hindustan Copper (down 2.58%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 1.62%), Steel Authority of India (down 1.57%), Tata Steel (down 1.16%) and Jindal Steel (down 0.68%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Trent rose 0.63%. The company reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Lloyds Engineering Works added 0.73%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 70.86% to Rs 61.03 crore on 2.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 272.45 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Parag Milk Foods slumped 6.58% after the company reported 18% drop in consolidated to Rs 30 crore despite a 14% rise in revenue to Rs 1,013 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Government has taken care of its sensitive sectors like fertiliser and agriculture in the India-US trade deal: Piyush Goyal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/government-has-taken-care-of-its-sensitive-sectors-like-fertiliser-and-agriculture-in-the-india-us-trade-deal-piyush-goyal/1671713</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671713</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal clarified that the Indian government has taken care of its sensitive sectors like fertiliser and agriculture in the India-US trade deal.

Union Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal clarified that the Indian government has taken care of its sensitive sectors like fertiliser and agriculture in the India-US trade deal. Making a statement in the Rajya Sabha, Piyush Goyal said this Agreement will provide new opportunities to small and medium businessmen, MSMEs, industrialists, skilled workers and industries. He said the deal will act as a catalyst to strengthen manufacturing, expand employment opportunities, and propel economic growth, while unlocking new business avenues for both nations. Mr Goyal said both sides will work together to fulfil important processes related to the trade agreement and finalise the paperwork so that its full capability can be taken at the earliest. He further informed that the details of the Agreement will be announced soon after the conclusion of these processes. He also clarified that safeguarding the energy requirements of 140 Crore Indians is the biggest priority of the Modi government. He said President Trump announced a reduction in the tariff on Indian exports to the United States to 18%, which is lower than the tariffs imposed by the United States on many competing countries. He said this will increase India’s export competitiveness in the American market.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/agriculture-1551086__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mitsu Chem Plast gains after being onboarded as global supplier to Arjo]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mitsu-chem-plast-gains-after-being-onboarded-as-global-supplier-to-arjo/1671712</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671712</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agreement onboards Mitsu Chem Plast as a global supplier to the Arjo Group, one of the world’s top medical equipment manufacturers.

The agreement onboards Mitsu Chem Plast as a global supplier to the Arjo Group, one of the world’s top medical equipment manufacturers. Under the pact, Mitsu Chem Plast will supply hospital furniture parts and related plastic accessories designed to support patient safety, caregiver ergonomics and risk management in healthcare settings. The partnership strengthens the company’s position in the global hospital furniture supply chain, enhances international brand visibility and opens up long-term export-led growth opportunities. The development comes amid improving India-EU trade ties following the recently concluded trade agreement, which is expected to ease market access and boost export competitiveness for specialised polymer and healthcare component makers. Mitsu Chem Plast said the agreement reinforces its strategic focus on high-value medical applications and its commitment to delivering globally compliant polymer solutions. Sanjay Dedhia, managing director of Mitsu Chem Plast said, "We are feeling proud and pleased to enter into a Global Supplier Agreement with Arjohuntleigh Polska Sp. z o.o., which marks an important milestone for Mitsu Chem Plast. Successfully completing a year-long validation process reflects the strength of our product quality, manufacturing discipline, and ability to meet stringent global standards. This partnership positions Mitsu as a trusted supplier in the global healthcare ecosystem and strengthens our presence in the hospital furniture and medical equipment components vertical. It also supports our strategy of expanding exports, diversifying our customer base, and building long-term, sustainable relationships with global leaders. We believe this association will enhance our brand credibility and create meaningful growth opportunities over the coming years." Mitsu Chem Plast is a certified manufacturer of polymer-based moulded products, offering technically advanced solutions across industrial packaging, healthcare, infrastructure and emergency handling segments. The company’s portfolio includes plastic drums, jerry cans, bottles and caps, hospital and infrastructure furniture components, and rescue and safety equipment, serving OEM clients in sectors such as chemicals, pharmaceuticals, agrochemicals, diagnostics and healthcare. On a standalone basis, net profit of Mitsu Chem Plast rose 218.24% to Rs 4.71 crore while net sales rose 6.89% to Rs 86 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MitsuChemPlastLtd_48975116_68583.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR edges lower amid dollar strength abroad and negative cues from equities ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-edges-lower-amid-dollar-strength-abroad-and-negative-cues-from-equities/1671707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671707</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee lost momentum in opening trades on Thursday but recovered thereafter.

The Indian rupee lost momentum in opening trades on Thursday but recovered thereafter. INR opened lower at Rs 90.52 against the dollar and rebounded to a high of 90.37 so far during the day. Negative cues from equities and broad dollar strength in limiting gians in the counter. Asian markets are trading mostly lower on Thursday, following the mixed cues from Wall Street overnight, reflecting the continued weakness in technology stocks which mirrored their peers on the tech-heavy Nasdaq amid valuation concerns. Yesterday, rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.43 against the US dollar, after a sharp rally in the previous trading session following India-US trade deal announcement and possible dollar buying by corporates and importers. However, caution still remains as there is no signed or officially released trade agreement yet, no framework text or final documentation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trent gains after Q3 PAT climbs 36% YoY to Rs 640 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trent-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-36-yoy-to-rs-640-cr/1671702</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671702</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 829.80 crore, up 34.19% compared with Rs 618.36 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 829.80 crore, up 34.19% compared with Rs 618.36 crore in Q3 FY25. Exceptional items during the quarter amounted to Rs 25.79 crore and were related to labour code charges. Adjusted PAT jumped 41% YoY to Rs 660 crore during the quarter. Operating EBITDA climbed 23% YoY to Rs 822 crore. In Q3FY26, the company opened 17 Westside and 48 Zudio stores (including 1 store in the UAE). As of 31st December 2025, the company operated with a footprint of over 15 million sqft. across its fashion brands. The company said that it believes that, given its approach to merchandise sourcing, price architecture, distribution, and disciplined inventory provisioning, the full-year results are more representative of the underlying health of the business. The gross margin profile of Westside and Zudio remained stable. Operating EBIT margin for Q3 FY26 stood at 13.8%, compared with 13.2% in Q3 FY25. On consolidated basis, net profit jumped 2.73% to Rs 510.11 crore on 14.79% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5345.06 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company clarified that its consolidated revenue excludes sales from the Trent Hypermarket business due to accounting standards, though its share of profit from the venture is included under the equity method. The Star business consists of 79 stores including the addition of 6 stores and closure of 5 stores during the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company said it is pursuing multiple initiatives, including technology-led interventions, to enhance differentiation and improve customer convenience. Noel N Tata, chairman, Trent said, “On a higher base, our fashion business registered category leading growth during the quarter. The customer sentiment is gradually improving and our business outlook for the medium term continues to remain positive. Our focus continues to be on portfolio growth, elevating products and enhancing store experience for our customers. We have consistently delivered a differentiated consumer proposition that appeals to a wider audience across diverse markets. We believe an unwavering focus on being relevant to our customers and building resilience with our business model choices will continue to hold us in good stead. We are excited and remain committed to building out a sizable pure play direct-to-customer business across customer segments in the context of the market size and opportunity. In our Star business, we continue to apply Trent’s playbook and the contribution of our own brands is now trending over 74% of revenues. We recognize that the expansion program for Star stores has been slower vis-à-vis our expectations and we are looking to accelerate this agenda in the coming periods. The opportunity in the food space for the Star proposition is exciting at the same time it is intensely competitive and we are calibrating our store portfolio to be more future-ready. We remain convinced that this business is well poised to deliver growing consumer value in the years ahead.” As of 31st December 2025, the company’s store portfolio included 278 Westside, 854 Zudio (including 4 stores in the UAE) and 32 stores across other lifestyle concepts. Trent is part of the Tata Group and operates a portfolio of retail concepts. The primary customer propositions of Trent include Westside, one of India's leading chains of fashion retail stores, Zudio, a one stop destination for great fashion at great value and Star, which operates in the competitive food, grocery and daily needs segment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Trent_20841567073_345.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>