<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:54:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Biopol Chemicals enters the market lab, but momentum evaporates]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-biopol-chemicals-enters-the-market-lab-but-momentum-evaporates/1676564</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676564</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 111, a premium of 2.78% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 111, a premium of 2.78% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its lower limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 111 and a low of Rs 105.45. About 18.59 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Biopol Chemicals' IPO was subscribed 21.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 6 February 2026 and it closed on 10 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was set between Rs 102 to Rs 108 per equity share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 28,94,400 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 65.81% from 89.88% pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for acquisition of industrial land, repayment or prepayment, in full or in part, of borrowings availed by company from banks, financial institutions and non-banking financial companies and for general corporate purposes. Biopol Chemicals is a B2B manufacturer and distributor of specialty chemicals with a portfolio of 66 products across silicones, emulsifiers, biochemicals and polyelectrolytes, serving industries such as textiles, home care, agriculture and industrial chemicals. The company operates four establishments across Gujarat and West Bengal, including a manufacturing facility with an installed capacity of 18,25,000 litres per annum. Its product range includes textile auxiliaries, silicone fluids, emulsifiers, agricultural adjuvants and specialty industrial chemicals, designed to meet sector-specific performance and application requirements. As of 31 December 2025, the company had a total of 24 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 48.97 crore and net profit of Rs 6 crore for the period ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BIOPOLCHEMICALSLIMITED_52903502_95994.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Power India Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-power-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1676562</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676562</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kalyani Forge Ltd, Delphi World Money Ltd, Chamanlal Setia Exports Ltd and Anmol India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026.

Kalyani Forge Ltd, Delphi World Money Ltd, Chamanlal Setia Exports Ltd and Anmol India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026. GE Power India Ltd soared 18.26% to Rs 473 at 13-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 19.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18829 shares in the past one month. Kalyani Forge Ltd spiked 14.34% to Rs 698.6. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 491 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 173 shares in the past one month. Delphi World Money Ltd surged 13.26% to Rs 17.25. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11869 shares in the past one month. Chamanlal Setia Exports Ltd gained 12.50% to Rs 309.2. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.96 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2097 shares in the past one month. Anmol India Ltd exploded 11.97% to Rs 13.47. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 46404 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4404 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GEPower_62970729410_20944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME PAN HR Solution makes a quiet debut, treads water at issue price]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-pan-hr-solution-makes-a-quiet-debut-treads-water-at-issue-price/1676561</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676561</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 78.35, a 0.45% premium to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 78.35, a 0.45% premium to the issue price. The stock was currently down 0.45% to the listing price. The stock touched a high of Rs 80 and a low of Rs 78, with around 6.32 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. PAN HR Solutions' IPO was subscribed 9.51 times. The issue opened for bidding on 6 February 2026 and it closed on 10 February 2025. The price band of the IPO was between Rs 74 to Rs 78 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 18,00,000 equity shares and offer for sale (OFS) of 3,84,000 equity shares by existing shareholders. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for funding for working capital requirements and for general corporate purpose. Ahead of the IPO, PAN HR Solutions on 5 February 2026, raised Rs 4.19 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 5.37 lakh shares at Rs 78 per share to 3 anchor investor. PAN HR Solutions is a B2B service provider offering end-to-end human resource and workforce management solutions across industries. The company provides services spanning manpower recruitment, staffing, payroll processing, facility management, compliance audits and e-commerce logistics support, catering to unskilled, semi-skilled and skilled blue-collar workforce requirements. Positioned as a one-stop HR solutions provider, it manages the entire employee lifecycle from hiring and onboarding to payroll administration and statutory compliance, including EPF, ESIC and professional tax regulations, while also delivering housekeeping, office support and delivery staffing services along with independent compliance audits. As of 30 November 2026, the company had 10,374 employees at different client locations. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 153.98 crore and net profit of Rs 5.13 crore for the period ended 30 November 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PANHRSOLUTIONLIMITED_43086913_95963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineers India Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/engineers-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1676548</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676548</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd and Goldiam International Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026.

TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd and Goldiam International Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026. Engineers India Ltd soared 14.49% to Rs 207 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 39.5 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.78 lakh shares in the past one month. TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd spiked 5.73% to Rs 132.71. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 6.81 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.5 lakh shares in the past one month. SignatureGlobal India Ltd surged 5.64% to Rs 1037.5. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 66050 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 51494 shares in the past one month. Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd exploded 3.79% to Rs 1387. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.78 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35887 shares in the past one month. Goldiam International Ltd rose 3.52% to Rs 397.2. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 36094 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 95991 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EngineersIndia_47008482189_12029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Honasa Consumer rises after Q3 PAT climbs 93% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/honasa-consumer-rises-after-q3-pat-climbs-93-yoy/1676549</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676549</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a reported basis, consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% YoY from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a reported basis, consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% YoY from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. On a like-for-like basis, revenue came in at Rs 630 crore, marking the company’s highest-ever quarterly revenue and reflecting 21.7% YoY growth. Gross profit rose 13.9% YoY to Rs 412 crore, although gross margin moderated to 68.5% from 70.0% in the year-ago period. Profit after tax stood at Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, up 92.9% YoY from Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY25. PAT margin improved to 8.3% from 5.0%. Before exceptional items, PAT was reported at Rs 55 crore, nearly doubling year-on-year. Profit before tax increased 128% YoY to Rs 67 crore, while PBT margin expanded to 11.2% from 5.7%. EBITDA surged 150.7% YoY to Rs 66 crore from Rs 26 crore, with EBITDA margin expanding sharply to 10.9% from 5.0% in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses rose to Rs 71 crore, accounting for 11.8% of revenue, compared with 10.0% in the year-ago quarter. Advertisement expenses stood at Rs 186 crore, representing 30.9% of revenue, lower than 34.3% in Q3 FY25. Underlying Volume Growth (UVG) for the quarter stood at 30.2%, indicating steady consumer demand across core categories. Focus categories delivered over 25% growth, while flagship brand Mamaearth returned to double-digit growth, driven by product re-innovation and sharper investments. Younger brands recorded over 25% growth, and The Derma Co. maintained a double-digit EBITDA profile while scaling efficiently. Offline execution improved with direct outlet coverage crossing 1 lakh outlets, and total distribution expanding over 25% YoY to 2.7 lakh outlets, with a strong focus on the top 100 towns. Management highlighted continued investment in product re-innovation, with offerings such as Mamaearth Rice Face Wash and BBlunt Intense Moisture Shampoo performing strongly against leading national and international competitors. The company reiterated its focus on strengthening margins, improving capital efficiency and building a structurally stronger business for sustainable long-term growth. Honasa Consumer is India's largest digital-first beauty and personal care company, with a diverse portfolio of eight brands.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HonasaConsumerLtd_60997811_77264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's vegetable oil imports jump 20% on year in Jan-26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-vegetable-oil-imports-jump-20-on-year-in-jan-26/1676547</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676547</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Solvent Extractors’ Association of India (SEA) has released import data for vegetable oils (edible & non-edible) for January, 2026.

The Solvent Extractors’ Association of India (SEA) has released import data for vegetable oils (edible & non-edible) for January, 2026. Imports during the month totalled 1,339,375 tons compared to 1,119,893 tons in January., 2025 i.e. up by 20%. This includes 1,311,847 tons of edible oils and 27,528 tons of non-edible oils. In first quarter of the oil year 2025-26(Nov’25-Jan.’26), total vegetable oil imports reached 3,960,102 tons, down by 2% from 4,046,423 tons in the same period last year. Edible oil import in January 2026 marginally declined to 13.12 lakh tons from 13.62 lakh tons in December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Hotels Q3 PAT rallies 55% YoY to Rs 903 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-hotels-q3-pat-rallies-55-yoy-to-rs-903-cr/1676541</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676541</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax increased 44.29% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,203.46 crore in the quarter ended December 2025.

Profit before tax increased 44.29% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,203.46 crore in the quarter ended December 2025. EBITDA stood at Rs 1,076 crore in December 2025 quarter, registering the growth of 12%, compared with Rs 962 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin declined to 37.9% in Q3 FY26 as against 38% in Q3 FY25. Indian Hotels Company’s consolidated same-store hotels reported a 9% growth in RevPAR. Management fee income rose 15% to Rs 203 crore, driven by not-like-for-like growth. In Q3 FY26, IHCL signed 239 hotels across its brandscape, including strategic acquisitions and partnerships with Clarks Group, Madison, Rajdarbar Group, Ambuja Neotia, and Atmantan. The company opened and onboarded 120 hotels, taking its operating portfolio to 361 hotels with an inventory of over 32,000 rooms. Puneet Chhatwal, MD & CEO, IHCL, said, “Q3 FY2026 marks fifteenth consecutive quarter of record performance with a Consolidated revenue of Rs 2,900 crores, a 12% growth over the previous year, EBITDA of 1,134 crores and an EBITDA margin of 39.1%. The revenue in the quarter was driven by a strong same store performance, not like for like growth, supported by a 17% growth in airline and institutional catering and 31% growth in New Businesses. The hotel segment reported a revenue of Rs 2,579 crores resulting in the best ever quarterly EBITDA of Rs 1,050 crores.” He added, “IHCL continued its growth momentum in FY2026 with 239 signings to reach a portfolio of 617 hotels and opened and onboarded 120 hotels, led by strategic partnerships and acquisitions. Under Accelerate 2030, IHCL expanded its brandscape with the acquisition of controlling stake in Atmantan, an integrated wellness brand and entered into definitive agreements to acquire 51% stake in Brij, a boutique experiential leisure offering and scaled the Ginger brand with 51% acquisition in ANK & Pride Hospitality. IHCL Consolidated continues to maintain a healthy balance sheet with a gross cash balance of INR 3,877 crores as on 31st December 2025. IHCL is well placed to deliver sustained performance enabled by a diversified topline across brands, geographies and contract types.” Ankur Dalwani, executive vice president & chief financial officer (CFO), IHCL said, “For Q3 FY2026, IHCL Standalone reported a revenue of Rs 1,654 crores, clocking a strong EBITDA margin of 48.2%, an expansion of 40 basis points and a PAT of Rs 921 crores post Exceptional Items.” He added, “During the nine months ending December 2025, IHCL Consolidated generated cash of about INR 1,600 crores and undertook capital expenditure to the tune of INR 750 crores towards greenfield projects at Ekta Nagar, Taj Frankfurt, brownfield expansion at Taj Ganges Varanasi and the upcoming Taj Bandstand project along with renovations to key hotels such as Taj Palace Delhi, Taj Fort Aguada Goa, President Mumbai and St James Court London among others.” The Indian Hotels Company (IHCL) and its subsidiaries bring together a group o brands and businesses that offer a fusion of warm Indian hospitality and world-class service. Shares of Indian Hotels Company declined 2.87% to Rs 691.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndianHotels_18642202460_282.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NIBE slides after reporting dismal Q3 numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nibe-slides-after-reporting-dismal-q3-numbers/1676538</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676538</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 60.3% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 59.08 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations fell 60.3% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 59.08 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company reported a pre-tax loss of Rs 21.81 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared to a profit before tax of Rs 1.91 crore reported in the same quarter last year. Total expenses fell 45.15% YoY to Rs 81.39 crore during the quarter. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 13.15 crore (up 40.49% YoY), while employee benefit expenses fell 11.02% YoY to Rs 6.70 crore during the period under review. NIBE operates in manufacturing critical components for the defence sector, electric vehicles (E-Vehicles), and software development. The company is engaged in the fabrication and machining of components used in the defence sector, as well as the assembly of components for E-vehicles.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KavitaFabrics_98715753806_43224.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/USD eases to one-week low near 1.3600 as tepid UK economic activity weighs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpusd-eases-to-one-week-low-near-13600-as-tepid-uk-economic-activity-weighs/1676537</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676537</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound is witnessing tepid moves amid firm action in the US dollar index and sustained tepid pace of economic growth in the UK.

British Pound is witnessing tepid moves amid firm action in the US dollar index and sustained tepid pace of economic growth in the UK. Britain's economy barely expanded in the final quarter of ⁠2025. Gross domestic product (GDP) grew by a mere 0.1% in the October-to-December period, the same slow pace as in ⁠the third quarter, the Office for National Statistics (ONS) said. The UK economy is estimated to have grown 1.3% in 2025, the ONS noted, following growth of 1.1% in 2024. Month-on-month, the economy expanded 0.1% in December, down from a 0.2% expansion, keeping the GBP/USD pair under stress as it neared one-week low of 1.3600. On NSE, GBP/INR futures are quoting at 123.5, down 0.17% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/concept-money-tree-on-grass-picture-id462171033_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CMS Info Systems slips after recording over 38% YoY fall in Q3 PAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cms-info-systems-slips-after-recording-over-38-yoy-fall-in-q3-pat/1676540</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676540</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the segmental front, Cash Management Services revenue was Rs 384.27 crore, Managed Services revenue was Rs 270.09 crore and Card Services revenue was Rs 24.91 crore in the December’25 quarter.

On the segmental front, Cash Management Services revenue was Rs 384.27 crore, Managed Services revenue was Rs 270.09 crore and Card Services revenue was Rs 24.91 crore in the December’25 quarter. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 77.03 crore, down by 38.6% from Rs 125.42 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company said that it has bagged a 10-year contract from SBI worth Rs 1,000 crore. This would translate into incremental revenues of Rs 500 crore. The ICICI Bank and India Post deals are nearing full execution. The company’s HAWKAI enterprise solution is now live at a leading PSU bank, deploying 16 advanced AI use cases for the entity. The company has signed term sheet for business transfer agreement with a leading managed services provider and the estimated deal value of the same is expected to be around Rs 100-125 crore. The board of CMS Info Systems has approved an interim dividend of Rs 2.75 apiece for the financial year 2025-26. Rajiv Kaul, executive VC & CEO, said: “FY26 has been an intensely volatile year following a strong growth CAGR of 18% between FY22 and FY25. Wage inflation, industry-related issues, and macro events have affected revenue growth in the last two quarters and significantly impacted margins. We have made one-time investments in new delivery models to increase network productivity and drive profitable growth. With high-quality, long-duration, large order wins at SBI and ICICI of over Rs 1500 crore, we feel confident that we have bottomed out with Q3 and are well-positioned to see strong QoQ gains to reach our FY27 revenue goal of Rs 2,800 crore.” CMS Info Systems is India’s leading business services company providing logistics and technology solutions to banks, financial institutions, organized retail, and e-commerce companies with a presence across cash logistics, managed services, and technology solutions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/cms-info-systems_80678221_44662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty drops below 25,550 mark; realty shares slump]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-drops-below-25550-mark-realty-shares-slump/1676524</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676524</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with sharp losses in mid-morning trade, mirroring weak global cues amid newly introduced Anthropic AI model, raising concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models.

The key equity benchmarks traded with sharp losses in mid-morning trade, mirroring weak global cues amid newly introduced Anthropic AI model, raising concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models. Sentiment remained cautious and shifting towards risk-off stance. The Nifty traded below the 25,550 mark. Realty shares plunged for the three straight sessions. At 11:25 AM IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 856.28 points or 1.02% to 82,822.20. The Nifty 50 index tanked 261.40 points or 1.02% to 25,545.30. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index dropped 1.70% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.63%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1080 shares rose and 2,800 shares fell. A total of 169 shares were unchanged. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.75% to Rs 153,979. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 2.78% to 818.90. The index declined 4.19% in the three consecutive trading session. Prestige Estates Projects (down 4.37%), DLF (down 3.71%), Godrej Properties (down 3.61%), Brigade Enterprises (down 3.38%), Oberoi Realty (down 2.66%), Lodha Developers (down 2.42%), Phoenix Mills (down 2.25%), Sobha (down 1.65%), Anant Raj (down 1.52%) tumbled. Stocks in Spotlight: Whirlpool of India advanced 1.09%. The company has reported 39.7% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 26.49 crore despite a 4.0% rise in net sales to Rs 1,773.84 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Concord Enviro Systems declined 7.18% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 8.18 crore in Q3 FY26, marginally lower than the net loss of Rs 8.56 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 1.4% YoY to Rs 124.58 crore in Q3 FY26. Global Markets: The Asia-Pacific market declined Friday, tracking Wall Street declines, as fears over artificial intelligence disruption drove the S&P 500 to a third straight day of losses. Certain pockets of the U.S. stock market have been hit this year by the release of AI tools that threaten to automate tasks performed by some companies—or at least risk eating into their profit margins. Overnight on Wall Street, US stocks fell sharply Thursday as the market punished companies seen as potential losers from artificial-intelligence technology. The S&P 500 fell 108.71 points to 6,832.76. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 669.42 to 49,451.98, and the Nasdaq Composite sank 469.32 to 22,597.15.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sundaram MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sundaram-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1676519</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676519</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced 17 February 2026 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes.

Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced 17 February 2026 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) will be: Sundaram Aggressive Hybrid Fund - Regular Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.250 Sundaram Aggressive Hybrid Fund - Direct Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.350 Sundaram Balanced Advantage Fund - Regular Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.115 Sundaram Balanced Advantage Fund - Direct Plan-Monthly-IDCW Option: 0.140

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Whirlpool of India posts nearly 40% YoY drop in Q3 PAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/whirlpool-of-india-posts-nearly-40-yoy-drop-in-q3-pat/1676511</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676511</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The increase in revenue was mainly due to share gains in Washers and growth in Aircon categories.

The increase in revenue was mainly due to share gains in Washers and growth in Aircon categories. The refrigerator business remained muted due to soft industry and continuing competitive pricing and promotions. Despite facing competitive and regulatory headwinds for the industry, the company said that it has made strong progress in its core strategic areas of driving premiumization, executional excellence and cost productivity. While EBITDA improved by 31.2% YoY to Rs 90.9 crore, EBITDA margin expanded by 106 basis points YoY to 5.1% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 32.86 crore, down by 44.5% from Rs 59.19 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Narasimhan Eswar, managing director, Whirlpool of India, said: “Q3 was a historic period for Whirlpool of India Ltd (WOIL). We declared the securing of our future in mid October 2025 with a long term deal signed with Whirlpool Corporation (WHR) that ensured multi-decadal rights to usage of the Whirlpool brand, long term technological licensing agreements for accessing world class WHR technology across current and future categories and a 3 year plus TSA (transitional services agreement) that will allow us the interim systems stability needed to drive strongly forward into the future. We held volume market shares in total refrigerator and washer MBO (Multi-brand outlets) market for the quarter versus year ago, despite intense competition while showing an improvement of 70 basis points share points vs Q2, clearly consolidating our position amongst top 3 brands in refrigerator and washer business.” Whirlpool of India (WOIL), headquartered in Gurugram, is one of the leading manufacturers and marketers of major home appliances in the country. It operates three manufacturing facilities at Faridabad, Puducherry and Pune. The scrip rose 1.05% to currently trade at Rs 898.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WhirlpoolIndia_58904292456_328.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concord Enviro net loss narrows to Rs 8 crore in Q3 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concord-enviro-net-loss-narrows-to-rs-8-crore-in-q3/1676510</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676510</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 1.4% YoY to Rs 124.58 crore in Q3 FY26.

However, revenue from operations rose 1.4% YoY to Rs 124.58 crore in Q3 FY26. Loss before tax stood at Rs 8.57 crore in Q3 FY26, widening from a loss of Rs 7.77 crore in the same period last year. EBITDA surged 150.7% to Rs 43 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 17.15 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 3.5% in Q3 FY26 as against 1.4% in Q3 FY25. The company's order book currently stands at Rs 594.7 crore. Meanwhile, the company said that its board has approved the appointment of Anish Goel as a chief financial officer (CFO) with effect from 12 February 2026. Concord Enviro Systems (CESL) is a global provider of water and wastewater treatment and reuse solutions, including zero liquid discharge (ZLD) technology. CESL has in-house capabilities to develop solutions across the entire value chain, including designing, manufacturing, installation and commissioning, operation and maintenance (O&M), and digitalization solutions, including the Internet of Things (IoT). Shares of Concord Enviro Systems fell 6.96% to Rs 383 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ConcordEnviroSystemsLtd_80266234_77163.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Honasa Consumer Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-honasa-consumer-ltd-counter/1676508</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676508</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TBO Tek Ltd, L&T Technology Services Ltd, Engineers India Ltd, Muthoot Finance Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 13 February 2026.

TBO Tek Ltd, L&T Technology Services Ltd, Engineers India Ltd, Muthoot Finance Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 13 February 2026. Honasa Consumer Ltd witnessed volume of 9.9 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 59.07 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 16759 shares. The stock increased 3.16% to Rs.308.50. Volumes stood at 67641 shares in the last session. TBO Tek Ltd saw volume of 2.03 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 50.74 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3998 shares. The stock dropped 5.23% to Rs.1,394.45. Volumes stood at 11242 shares in the last session. L&T Technology Services Ltd recorded volume of 1.55 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 35.09 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4409 shares. The stock lost 4.40% to Rs.3,539.95. Volumes stood at 4735 shares in the last session. Engineers India Ltd notched up volume of 33.36 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 25.12 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.33 lakh shares. The stock rose 14.68% to Rs.207.35. Volumes stood at 73128 shares in the last session. Muthoot Finance Ltd recorded volume of 2.39 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.78 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 35191 shares. The stock lost 11.03% to Rs.3,620.25. Volumes stood at 57149 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HonasaConsumerLtd_60997811_77264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin Q3 PAT soars 37% YoY to Rs 1,176 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-q3-pat-soars-37-yoy-to-rs-1176-crore/1676507</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676507</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 1,522.04 crore during the quarter, up 4207% from Rs 1,071.27 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 2,376.6 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 68.6% growth compared with Rs 1,409.80 crore in Q3 FY25. The EBITDA margin improved 840 basis points to 33.5% in Q3 FY26 from 25.1% in Q3 FY25. U.S. sales for Q3 FY26 rose 54% to Rs 3,113.2 crore ($350 million) from Rs 2,022.1 crore ($240 million) in Q3 FY25, accounting for 44% of the company’s global sales. During the quarter, the company received 1 ANDA approval from the U.S. FDA and launched 3 products in the U.S., taking its total generic portfolio to 149 products. Lupin continues to be the 3rd largest pharmaceutical player in both U.S. generic market and U.S. total market by prescriptions (IQVIA Qtr. TRx Dec 2025). Lupin is the leader in 55 of its marketed generics in the U.S. and amongst the Top 3 in 116 of its marketed products (IQVIA Qtr Dec 2025 by extended units). India sales for Q3 FY26 were Rs 2,038.7 crore, up 5.6% from Rs 1,930.5 crore in Q3 FY25, accounting for 29% of the company’s global sales. India Region Formulation sales rose 10.9% in the quarter compared to Q3 FY25. During the quarter, the company launched 3 brands across therapies. Lupin is the 8th largest company in the Indian pharmaceutical market (IQVIA MAT Dec 2025). Lupin’s Other Developed Markets sales for Q3 FY26 were Rs 812.1 crore, up 10.8% from Rs 732.8 crore in Q3 FY25, accounting for 11% of the company’s global sales. The company’s Emerging Markets sales for Q3 FY26 were Rs 917.0 crore, up 42.4% from Rs 644.1 crore in Q3 FY25, accounting for 13% of the company’s global sales. Global API sales for the quarter were Rs 219.5 crore, down 24.1% from Rs 289.1 crore in Q3 FY25, accounting for 3% of global sales. Investment in Research & Development stood at Rs 535.2 crore (7.5% of sales) for Q3 FY26, up from Rs 441.2 crore (7.9% of sales) in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, Lupin received approval for 1 ANDA from the U.S. FDA, taking its cumulative ANDA filings to 431 as of December 31, 2025, with 341 approvals received to date. The company now has 52 First-to-File (FTF) filings, including 22 exclusive FTF opportunities. Cumulative U.S. DMF filings stand at 93 as of December 31, 2025. Commenting on the Q3FY26 results, Nilesh Gupta, MD, Lupin, said “We are happy to deliver another quarter of strong growth led by our highest ever quarterly sales in the US and double-digit growth in India and all other regions. We are on track to deliver a strong close to FY26." Lupin is a global pharmaceutical leader headquartered in Mumbai, India, with products distributed in over 100 markets. It specializes in pharmaceutical products, including branded and generic formulations, complex generics, biotechnology products, and active pharmaceutical ingredients. Shares of Lupin declined 1.55% to Rs 2,175.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[H.G. Infra Engg Q3 PAT fall 18% YoY to Rs 94 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hg-infra-engg-q3-pat-fall-18-yoy-to-rs-94-cr/1676504</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676504</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) fell 22.8% to Rs 139.01 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 179.97 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax (PBT) fell 22.8% to Rs 139.01 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 179.97 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA rose 7.6% to Rs 308.78 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 286.90 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin reduced to 21.7% in Q3 FY26 as against 22.7% in Q3 FY25. The company’s total expenses rose 18.05% YoY to Rs 1,285.61 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed was at Rs 521.55 crore (up 13.39%), employee benefits expense stood at Rs 84.08 crore (down 2.02% YoY), while finance costs stood at Rs 129.18 crore (up 72.54% YoY) during the period under review. H.G. Infra Engineering is an Indian road infrastructure company engaged in the business of Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) services and maintenance of roads, bridges, flyovers, and other infrastructure contract works. Shares of H.G. Infra Engineering rose 0.30% to Rs 674.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HGInfraEngineeringLtd_52714149365_71631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Technology has become the core architecture of modern securities markets, says SEBI Chair]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/technology-has-become-the-core-architecture-of-modern-securities-markets-says-sebi-chair/1676502</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676502</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tuhin Kanta Pandey, Chairman, SEBI has stated that technology has become the core architecture of modern securities markets.

Tuhin Kanta Pandey, Chairman, SEBI has stated that technology has become the core architecture of modern securities markets. Trading, clearing, settlement, surveillance - all are now deeply digital. We are also witnessing the emergence of data-driven supervision. SupTech and RegTech tools are changing how regulators and intermediaries monitor risk and compliance. SEBI’s approach has been to encourage innovation, while remaining vigilant about market integrity and investor protection. He noted that artificial intelligence and advanced analytics offer powerful tools. They can strengthen surveillance. They can help detect misconduct patterns. They can identify fraud. They can also deepen our understanding of investor behaviour. But in novation is not risk-free. Algorithmic markets can create feedback loops. AI models can introduce opacity and technology can amplify errors at speed. is where research becomes indispensable. We need rigorous work on market microstructure in digital environments, he opined.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI-DPI index improves further in H1FY26: RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-dpi-index-improves-further-in-h1fy26-rbi/1676490</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676490</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Payment digitisation improved further in the six months to September 2025, continuing a year-long trend, the Reserve Bank said on Thursday.

Payment digitisation improved further in the six months to September 2025, continuing a year-long trend, the Reserve Bank said on Thursday. The composite Reserve Bank of India - Digital Payments Index (RBI-DPI), which has been published since January 2021 with March 2018 as the base year to capture the extent of digitisation of payments across the country, showed an improvement in the first half of FY26, it said. The index for September 2025 stands at 516.76 as against 465.33 for September 2024 and 493.22 for March 2025, the RBI said in a statement. The increase in RBI-DPI index was driven by significant growth in parameters viz. Payment Performance and Payment Enablers across the country over the period, RBI noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Net direct tax collection soars 9.4% this fiscal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/net-direct-tax-collection-soars-94-this-fiscal/1676489</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676489</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 trillion so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from previous year.

The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 trillion so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from previous year. Latest data released by the Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) showed that tax receipts from corporations and individuals between 1 April and 10 February were over 80% of the revised direct tax target of Rs 24.21 trillion for FY26. The initial target was Rs 25.2 trillion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-calculator-tax-return-taxes-1241517_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>