<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:25:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SIP AuM rises to Rs 16.63 lakh crore in December with 9.79 crore SIP accounts: AMFI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sip-aum-rises-to-rs-1663-lakh-crore-in-december-with-979-crore-sip-accounts-amfi/1664616</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664616</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The net assets under the management (AUM) of the Indian mutual fund industry at the end of December 2025 stood at Rs 80.23 lakh crore, according to data from the Association of Mutual Funds of India (AMFI).

The net assets under the management (AUM) of the Indian mutual fund industry at the end of December 2025 stood at Rs 80.23 lakh crore, according to data from the Association of Mutual Funds of India (AMFI). This is slightly lower as compared with the figure of Rs 80.80 lakh crore recorded in November 2025. The AUM of open-ended plans fell to Rs 79.98 lakh crore in December 2025 from Rs 80.55 lakh crore in November 2025. Investors continued to be drawn to equity plans in this category, with net inflows of Rs 28,054.06 crore. Within equity, Flexi Cap Fund drew the most significant inflows in December, attracting Rs 10,019.27 crore. Mid Cap Funds followed suit with inflows of Rs 4,175.81 crore, while ELSS saw net outflows of Rs 717.73 crore. Debt funds witnessed net outflows in December, totaling Rs 1,32,410.37 crore. This category had recorded net outflows of Rs 25,692.63 crore in November. Liquid Funds recorded maximum outflows of Rs 47,307.95 crore. Other debt segments like Money Market Funds, Overnight Funds and Ultra Short Duration Funds also saw significant inflows. Hybrid schemes, offering a mix of equity and debt exposure, recorded net inflows of Rs 10,755.57 crore in December 2025. This was largely driven by Arbitrage Funds, which attracted Rs 26,411.54 crore. The systematic investment plan (SIP) contributions rose to Rs 31,002 crore in December 2025, up by 0.53% from Rs Rs 29,445 crore in November 2025. The number of contributing SIP accounts also rose from 9.42 crore in November to 9.79 crore in December, while SIP assets under management (AUM) climbed to Rs 16.63 lakh crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Karma Energy Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/karma-energy-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1664609</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664609</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd, Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd, Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 January 2026.

Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd, Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd, Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 January 2026. Karma Energy Ltd crashed 10.00% to Rs 47.25 at 14:20 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1113 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1744 shares in the past one month. Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd lost 8.87% to Rs 685. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 25750 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4498 shares in the past one month. Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd tumbled 8.48% to Rs 2200. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1307 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 154 shares in the past one month. Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd slipped 7.04% to Rs 865.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 343 shares in the past one month. Shyam Telecom Ltd corrected 6.83% to Rs 12. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9064 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7014 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KarmaEner_72744909020_39082.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops 505 pts; consumer durables shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-505-pts-consumer-durables-shares-tumble/1664604</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664604</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with substantial losses in the mid-afternoon trade, amid profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

The key equity indices traded with substantial losses in the mid-afternoon trade, amid profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. Investors remained cautious as they tracked developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical developments. The Nifty slipped below the 25,650 mark. Consumer durables share extended losses for the fourth consecutive trading session. At 14:32 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex fell 505.31 points or 0.60% to 83,333.17. The Nifty 50 index dropped 148.50 points or 0.58% to 25,646.60. In the broader market. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.45% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.21%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,866 shares rose and 2,110 shares fell. A total of 220 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index dropped 1.46% to 36,958.45. The index fell 3.59% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Dixon Technologies (India) (down 5.17%), PG Electroplast (down 2.07%), Kalyan Jewellers India (down 1.87%), Whirlpool of India (down 1.87%), Havells India (down 1.75%), Voltas (down 1.34%), Amber Enterprises India (down 0.88%), Blue Star (down 0.76%), V-Guard Industries (down 0.65%) and Kajaria Ceramics (down 0.56%) declined. On the other hand, Century Plyboards (India) (up 0.41%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (up 0.24%) and Cera Sanitaryware (up 0.24%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.35% to 6.628 compared with previous session close of 6.605. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2875 compared with its close of 90.1750 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement shed 0.18% to Rs 141,769. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.11% to 98.73. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.195. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement gained 56 cents or 0.88% to $64.43 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Indo Thai Securities rose 1.95% after the company reported a 1,629.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.12 crore on a 400.18% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 27.71 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Puravankara shed 0.26%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary Starworth Infrastructure & Construction (SICL) has received a letter of intent (LoI) for the construction of an East Bangalore-based proposed residential project "Sattva AANGANE". Anand Rathi Wealth shed 0.03%. The company reported 29.6% rise in net profit to Rs 100.1 crore on a 22.2% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 289.6 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at ITI Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-iti-ltd-counter/1664602</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664602</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Authum Investment & Infrastructure Ltd, Maharashtra Scooters Ltd, Oil India Ltd, IFCI Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 13 January 2026.

Authum Investment & Infrastructure Ltd, Maharashtra Scooters Ltd, Oil India Ltd, IFCI Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 13 January 2026. ITI Ltd saw volume of 133.81 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 31.47 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4.25 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.83% to Rs.307.45. Volumes stood at 5.31 lakh shares in the last session. Authum Investment & Infrastructure Ltd notched up volume of 26.9 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 26.98 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 99684 shares. The stock rose 8.69% to Rs.673.60. Volumes stood at 1.44 lakh shares in the last session. Maharashtra Scooters Ltd recorded volume of 39341 shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.88 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4990 shares. The stock gained 5.33% to Rs.13,642.00. Volumes stood at 17234 shares in the last session. Oil India Ltd notched up volume of 98.66 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.53 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 21.80 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.19% to Rs.443.45. Volumes stood at 14.06 lakh shares in the last session. IFCI Ltd witnessed volume of 1530.3 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 3.83 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 399.37 lakh shares. The stock increased 1.81% to Rs.57.45. Volumes stood at 2730.36 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITI_63692350660_2334.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures climb above $60 per barrel in Asia ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-oil-futures-climb-above-60-per-barrel-in-asia/1664600</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664600</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures climbed above $60 per barrel in early Asia trade on Tuesday, hitting the highest level in over a month after US President Donald Trump announced fresh tariffs targeting countries trading with Iran.

WTI crude oil futures climbed above $60 per barrel in early Asia trade on Tuesday, hitting the highest level in over a month after US President Donald Trump announced fresh tariffs targeting countries trading with Iran. Trump warned of a 25% tariff on any nation doing business with Tehran and hinted at possible military action, raising fears of supply disruptions from one of the world’s major oil producers. Market focus also turned to a pending US Supreme Court ruling on the legality of Trump’s tariff policies, expected Wednesday, adding to uncertainty. In currency markets, the dollar firmed after recent weakness linked to concerns over Federal Reserve independence. In India, MCX January crude futures rose 1.4% to ₹5,413 per barrel, with gains amplified by a weaker rupee, which slipped to around 90.2 per dollar amid escalating global trade tensions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indo Thai Securities gains as Q3 PAT soars 1,629% YoY to Rs 17 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indo-thai-securities-gains-as-q3-pat-soars-1629-yoy-to-rs-17-crore/1664599</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664599</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) rose sharply to Rs 22.62 crore in Q3 FY26, up 1,769.42% from Rs 1.21 crore in the year-ago quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) rose sharply to Rs 22.62 crore in Q3 FY26, up 1,769.42% from Rs 1.21 crore in the year-ago quarter. Total expenses increased 19.18% to Rs 5.22 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4.38 crore in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, fees and commission expenses stood at Rs 0.87 crore (down 25% YoY), employee benefit expenses at Rs 2.04 crore (up 28.3% YoY), and finance costs at Rs 0.61 crore (up 90.62% YoY). Separately, the company announced that Deepak Sharma has resigned from the position of chief financial officer (CFO) and key managerial personnel with effect from 13 January 2026, after the close of business hours. The board has appointed Nishit Doshi as chief financial officer and key managerial personnel, effective 14 January 2026. Indo Thai Securities, the flagship company of the Indo Thai Group, is a growing financial services provider based in Indore. The company caters to corporate clients, high-net-worth individuals, and retail investors and offers comprehensive broking and clearing services across equity, derivatives, and commodity segments as a member of NSE, BSE, MSEI, MCX, and NCDEX.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndoThaiSec_94679781016_41238.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade lower; European mrkt  advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-lower-european-mrkt-advance/1664592</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664592</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in afternoon trade, amid profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in afternoon trade, amid profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. Investors remained cautious as they tracked developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical developments. The Nifty slipped below the 25,700 mark. Consumer durables, realty and pharma shares declined while media, FMCG and PSU Bank shares advanced. At 13:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 419.07 points or 0.50% to 83,459.10. The Nifty 50 index fell 139.10 points or 0.54% to 25,651.15. In the broader market. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.45% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.21%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,866 shares rose and 2,110 shares fell. A total of 220 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) (up 2.80%), Eternal (up 2%), ICICI Bank (up 1.68%), Hindalco Industries (up 1.24%) and Tech Mahindra (up 1.14%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Trent (down 4.04%), Larsen & Tourbo (L&T) (down 3.57%), Indigo (down 2.10%), Reliance Industries (down 1.96%) and Dr Reddy Laboratories (down 1.69%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) rose 0.69%. The company reported an 11.74% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 10,657 crore, despite 1.96% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,087 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 13.92%, while revenue from operations increased 4.87% in Q3 FY26. The decline in profitability was impacted due to one-time exceptional charges including Rs 2,120 crore related to the statutory impact of new labour codes and it also made a provision towards a legal claim of of Rs 1,010 crore during the December quarter. HCL Technologies fell 0.41%. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 3.75% to Rs 4,076 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,235 crore in Q2 FY26. However, revenue from operations increased 6.04% to Rs 33,872 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 31,942 crore posted in Q2 FY26. For FY26, HCLTech expects revenue growth of 4–4.5% YoY in constant currency, services revenue growth of 4.75–5.25% YoY, and an EBIT margin of 17–18%. Kalpataru surged 4.12% after the company’s collections jumped 17% to Rs 1,101 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 943 crore in Q3 FY25. Maharashtra Scooters rallied 5.49% after the company reported a 24.84% surge in standalone net profit to Rs 4.12 crore on a 11.22% rise in total income to Rs 6.44 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Omaxe soared 16.19% after the company unveiled plans to invest Rs 500 crore in a new mixed-use development project, Omaxe Chowk, in Ludhiana. Lotus Chocolate Company slumped 8.21% after the company’s standalone net profit tumbled 96.22% to Rs 0.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3.71 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 18.90% to Rs 133.63 crore in the third quarter of FY26 from Rs 146.69 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. GTPL Hathway shed 0.57% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 8.3% to Rs 11.01 crore on 5.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 932.62 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Global Markets: European market advanced as investors keeping an eye on geopolitical developments and data. Most Asian markets advanced on Tuesday as traders shrugged off geopolitical flashpoints in Iran and Venezuela, as well as a criminal investigation into U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Japan’s benchmark Nikkei 225 jumped 3.13% to lead gains in the region. Japan’s ruling Liberal Democratic Party is expected to dissolve the country’s Lower House later this month and opt for a snap election likely in February, according to media reports. Traders will also be keeping a close eye on oil prices amid ongoing protests in Iran. President Donald Trump is reportedly weighing options for intervention in Iran, according to multiple media reports. Trump in a social media post on Monday stateside reportedly said any country doing business with Iran will face a 25% tariff “on any and all business being done with the United States of America.” That new tariff on imports from Iran’s trading partners is “effective immediately.” Overnight in the U.S., stocks rallied off their session lows, with the S&P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average hitting new all-time highs. The S&P 500 rose 0.16% to end at 6,977.27, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average ticked up 86.13 points, or 0.17%, and settled at 49,590.20. Both indexes touched fresh all-time intraday highs and closed at records. The Nasdaq Composite was up 0.26% and closed at 23,733.90.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Puravankara's subsidiary bags LoI for residential project in Bangalore worth Rs 311.18 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/puravankaras-subsidiary-bags-loi-for-residential-project-in-bangalore-worth-rs-31118-crore/1664593</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664593</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project has an approximate built-up area of 30,36,458 square feet and it has an approximate contract value of Rs 311.18 crore.

The project has an approximate built-up area of 30,36,458 square feet and it has an approximate contract value of Rs 311.18 crore. The project has to be executed within a period of 37 months. The Puravankara Group is one of India's most trusted realty majors, headquartered in Bengaluru with a pan-India presence. Over the past five decades, the company has established three distinct and successful residential brands – Puravankara, Provident Housing (PHL), and Purva Land - catering to the entire spectrum of housing and plotted development needs. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 41.79 crore in Q2 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 16.78 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales jumped 30% year on year to Rs 644.20 crore in Q2 FY26. The scrip rose 0.26% to currently trade at Rs 232.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Puravankara_83213463793_25459.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1664586</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664586</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Hero MotoCorp Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5694, down 0.57% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.52% on the day, quoting at 25656.75. The Sensex is at 83440.78, down 0.52%.Hero MotoCorp Ltd has lost around 4.46% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Hero MotoCorp Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28011.75, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.72 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.03 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5702.5, down 0.63% on the day. Hero MotoCorp Ltd jumped 38.79% in last one year as compared to a 10.7% rally in NIFTY and a 21.67% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 23.86 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Motor Company Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-motor-company-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664587</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664587</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TVS Motor Company Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

TVS Motor Company Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3718.6, down 0.96% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.52% on the day, quoting at 25656.75. The Sensex is at 83440.78, down 0.52%.TVS Motor Company Ltd has gained around 2.18% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which TVS Motor Company Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28011.75, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 8.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.57 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3728.8, down 1.09% on the day. TVS Motor Company Ltd jumped 66.38% in last one year as compared to a 10.7% rally in NIFTY and a 21.67% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 56.51 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSMotorCo_68147319859_8029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tube-investments-of-india-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664588</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664588</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Tube Investments of India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2383, down 1.07% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.52% on the day, quoting at 25656.75. The Sensex is at 83440.78, down 0.52%.Tube Investments of India Ltd has lost around 10% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Tube Investments of India Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28011.75, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.49 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.91 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2387.6, down 1.06% on the day. Tube Investments of India Ltd tumbled 28.25% in last one year as compared to a 10.7% rally in NIFTY and a 21.67% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 34.7 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TubeInvestmentsofIndiaLtd_81529932771_40963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siemens-energy-india-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664589</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664589</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Siemens Energy India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2372.7, down 0.04% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.52% on the day, quoting at 25656.75. The Sensex is at 83440.78, down 0.52%.Siemens Energy India Ltd has eased around 19.45% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Siemens Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.05% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34473.55, down 0.47% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.12 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 9.23 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 76.89 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiemensEnergyIndiaLtd_11731431_93274.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Anand Rathi Wealth gains after PAT jumps nearly 30% in Q3; AUM rises to Rs 99,008 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/anand-rathi-wealth-gains-after-pat-jumps-nearly-30-in-q3-aum-rises-to-rs-99008-crore/1664584</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664584</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total costs rose by 21.7% YoY to Rs 170.4 crore during the period under review, primarily due to higher employee costs (up 20.9% YoY) and higher other expenses (up 23.6% YoY).

Total costs rose by 21.7% YoY to Rs 170.4 crore during the period under review, primarily due to higher employee costs (up 20.9% YoY) and higher other expenses (up 23.6% YoY). Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 135.3 crore, up 30% from Rs 104.1 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Assets under management (AUM) as on 31 December 2025 stood at Rs 99,008 crore, up by 30% from Rs 76,402 crore as on 31 December 2024. Rakesh Rawal, CEO and Feroze Azeez, joint CEO, said: “We recorded net inflows of Rs 10,078 crore during the nine months of FY26 and on boarded 1,800+ clients during last one year bringing our total client base to 13,262 families. The client attrition — measured by AUM lost — remained low at 0.31% for nine months of FY26, reflecting continued trust in our uncomplicated, client-centric approach. We are confident of delivering long-term growth of 20–25%, driven by the uncomplicated and scalable nature of our business model, while creating sustainable value for all stakeholders.” Anand Rathi Wealth is among India’s leading wealth management firms, catering to high and ultra-high-net-worth individuals with a unique and differentiated client strategy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Anand-Rathi-Wealth_80898926_67729.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[A B Infrabuild gains after bagging Rs 55-cr order from East Coast Railways]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/a-b-infrabuild-gains-after-bagging-rs-55-cr-order-from-east-coast-railways/1664583</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664583</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order pertains to the construction of a Road Over Bridge (ROB) in lieu of Level Crossing No.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order pertains to the construction of a Road Over Bridge (ROB) in lieu of Level Crossing No. 341, located between Jhadupudi and Sompeta railway stations on the main line under the Khurda Road Division. The project involves a composite girder structure with proposed spans of 1x36 metres, 2x24 metres and 4x18.75 metres RCCT-beam girders at railway kilometre 641/19–21. The total contract value stands at Rs 55,26,31,365.74 and the project is scheduled to be completed within 24 months. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity and that the contract does not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. A B Infrabuild engaged in construction, alter, improve, maintain, enlarge, pull down, remove, replace and develop, work, manage, and roads, railways, branches and sidings, bridges; and other constructions related to civil works. The company’s standalone net profit tumbled 43.6% to Rs 2.11 crore, while revenue from operations declined 21% to Rs 37.30 crore in Q2 FY26 compared to Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABInfrabuild_38628776_73120.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[B.R. Goyal Infrastructure gains on securing Rs 87-cr NHAI work order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/br-goyal-infrastructure-gains-on-securing-rs-87-cr-nhai-work-order/1664581</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664581</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order covers user fee collection at Simliya Fee Plaza (km 409.680) and Fatehpur Fee Plaza (km 461.290) on the Kota–Baran section (km 388.263–492.322) of NH-76, along with upkeep and maintenance of adjacent toilet blocks, including recouping of consumable items.

The order covers user fee collection at Simliya Fee Plaza (km 409.680) and Fatehpur Fee Plaza (km 461.290) on the Kota–Baran section (km 388.263–492.322) of NH-76, along with upkeep and maintenance of adjacent toilet blocks, including recouping of consumable items. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is to be executed over a period of one year. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding authority and that the order does not fall under related party transactions. B.R. Goyal Infrastructure is engaged in constructing infrastructure projects such as roads, highways, bridges, and buildings. On a full-year basis, the company's consolidated net profit increased 15.1% to Rs 25.18 crore on a 13.4% drop in net sales to Rs 509.80 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/B.R.GoyalInfrastructureLtd_81707004_93579.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil India Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-india-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1664574</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664574</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil India Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Oil India Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 443.75, up 4.26% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.41% on the day, quoting at 25685. The Sensex is at 83470.88, down 0.49%. Oil India Ltd has gained around 9.96% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Oil India Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34473.55, down 0.26% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 80.07 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 16.22 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 442.1, up 3.86% on the day. Oil India Ltd is down 4.6% in last one year as compared to a 10.83% jump in NIFTY and a 2.43% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 14.83 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OilIndia_41919311821_5452.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd spurts 3.01%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-natural-gas-corpn-ltd-spurts-301-up-for-third-straight-session/1664575</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664575</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 242.8, up 3.01% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.41% on the day, quoting at 25685. The Sensex is at 83470.88, down 0.49%. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd has added around 3.17% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd is a constituent, has added around 1.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34473.55, down 0.26% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 115.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 83.44 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 242.52, up 2.56% on the day. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd is down 6.75% in last one year as compared to a 10.83% gain in NIFTY and a 2.43% gain in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 9.11 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ONGC_65712746772_6068.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tech-mahindra-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1664576</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664576</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Tech Mahindra Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1604.8, up 1.18% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.41% on the day, quoting at 25685. The Sensex is at 83470.88, down 0.49%. Tech Mahindra Ltd has gained around 1.87% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Tech Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.92% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37988.25, up 0.12% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 11.1 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.63 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1604.1, up 0.85% on the day. Tech Mahindra Ltd is down 2.59% in last one year as compared to a 10.83% jump in NIFTY and a 11.68% jump in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 39.6 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TechMahindra_28047796713_17215.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd soars 1.5%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/national-aluminium-company-ltd-soars-15-gains-for-third-straight-session/1664577</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664577</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

National Aluminium Company Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 355.3, up 1.5% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.41% on the day, quoting at 25685. The Sensex is at 83470.88, down 0.49%. National Aluminium Company Ltd has added around 27.48% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which National Aluminium Company Ltd is a constituent, has added around 7.49% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11315.75, up 0.24% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 128.25 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 172.08 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 354.55, up 0.85% on the day. National Aluminium Company Ltd is up 78.09% in last one year as compared to a 10.83% gain in NIFTY and a 37.2% gain in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 10.44 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NatlAluminium_39819539035_2304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1664578</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664578</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Vedanta Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 634.1, up 1.08% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.41% on the day, quoting at 25685. The Sensex is at 83470.88, down 0.49%. Vedanta Ltd has gained around 15.42% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Vedanta Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 7.49% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11315.75, up 0.24% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 111.61 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 147.77 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 632.65, up 0.48% on the day. Vedanta Ltd is up 47.26% in last one year as compared to a 10.83% jump in NIFTY and a 37.2% jump in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 26.08 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>