<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd Surges 1.46%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/national-aluminium-company-ltd-surges-146/1662880</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662880</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd gained 1.46% today to trade at Rs 319.1.

National Aluminium Company Ltd gained 1.46% today to trade at Rs 319.1. The BSE Metal index is up 0.28% to quote at 37218.88. The index is up 9.35 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, NMDC Ltd increased 1.23% and Hindalco Industries Ltd added 0.99% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 27.69 % over last one year compared to the 6.65% surge in benchmark SENSEX. National Aluminium Company Ltd has added 19.76% over last one month compared to 9.35% gain in BSE Metal index and 0.18% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 29771 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 6.14 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 319.95 on 31 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 140 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NatlAluminium_39819539035_2304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITC Ltd Falls 4.33%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itc-ltd-falls-433/1662881</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662881</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITC Ltd lost 4.33% today to trade at Rs 348.2.

ITC Ltd lost 4.33% today to trade at Rs 348.2. The BSE Fast Moving Consumer Goods index is down 0.24% to quote at 19694.68. The index is down 2.39 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd decreased 3.69% and Tasty Bite Eatables Ltd lost 2.14% on the day. The BSE Fast Moving Consumer Goods index went down 6.61 % over last one year compared to the 6.65% surge in benchmark SENSEX. ITC Ltd has lost 13.07% over last one month compared to 2.39% fall in BSE Fast Moving Consumer Goods index and 0.18% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 10.43 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 36.76 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 471.3 on 01 Feb 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 346.6 on 02 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITC_29088800077_301.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at green start for equities; Singapore’s GDP rises 5.7% YoY in Q4]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-green-start-for-equities-singapores-gdp-rises-57-yoy-in-q4/1662873</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662873</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 54.50 points, indicating a positive opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 54.50 points, indicating a positive opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,268.60 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,525.89 crore in the Indian equity market on 01 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. This follows their cash sales of Rs 17,500.31 crore in November and Rs 2,346.89 crore in October. Global Markets: South Korea’s Kospi hit a new record Friday as the Asia markets kicked off the new year on a mixed trading note. Some Asian markets were still closed for the holidays, including Japan and mainland China. Meanwhile, Singapore’s economy expanded 5.7% year-on-year for the fourth quarter, driven mainly by strong manufacturing growth in the three months through December. The latest reading is faster than the revised 4.3% growth in the previous quarter. On Wednesday, Prime Minister Lawrence Wong announced in his New Year message that the country had clocked a stronger-than-expected 4.8% expansion for the full year of 2025. U.S. stock futures were looking up in early Asian hours, with S&P futures up by 0.15% and Nasdaq-100 futures climbing 0.12%. Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 0.16% higher. On Wednesday stateside, the S&P 500 dipped 0.74%, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and the Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 0.63%. Domestic Market: Benchmark equity indices ended nearly flat on Thursday as the expiry of weekly Sensex derivatives contracts capped gains in the absence of major economic cues. The Nifty closed below the 25,150 mark after giving up early advances, with auto and metal stocks rising while pharma and healthcare shares declined, as investors shifted focus to the upcoming earnings season. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 32 points or 0.04% to 85,188.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 16.95 points or 0.06% to 26,146.55.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: RailTel Corporation of India, Aurobindo Pharma, Olectra Greentech]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-railtel-corporation-of-india-aurobindo-pharma-olectra-greentech/1662872</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662872</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: SAIL shares are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025.

Securities in F&O Ban: SAIL shares are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025. Stocks to Watch: RailTel Corporation of India has received a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) from the Assam Health Infrastructure Development & Management Society (AHIDMS) for procurement, implementation, and maintenance of a Hospital Management Information System (HMIS). The estimated order value is Rs 56.71 crore. Aurobindo Pharma announced that its subsidiary, Auro Pharma, has approved the acquisition of the non-oncology prescription formulations business of Khandelwal Laboratories on a going-concern basis through a Business Transfer Agreement for Rs 325 crore. Time Technoplast has received approvals from the Petroleum and Explosives Safety Organisation (PESO) and TÜV Rheinland (India) for the manufacture and supply of high-pressure Type-3 fully wrapped fiber-reinforced composite cylinders of 2-liter capacity for compressed gas applications. Olectra Greentech declared the commercial operation date (COD) for its greenfield electric vehicle (EV) manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. The Phase-I per-shift annual production capacity stands at 2,500 electric buses, representing 50% of the planned per-shift capacity of 5,000 buses. Prataap Snacks said manufacturing operations at its Bengaluru unit ceased from 1 January 2026 as part of strategic consolidation. Production has been shifted to another facility in the region, ensuring continuity of supply. The company expects no adverse impact on its overall production capacity. Indegene announced the merger of its step-down arms—Indegene Aptilon Services and Trilogy Writing & Consulting—to form Indegene Healthcare Canada Inc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel bags Rs 57-cr HMIS contract from Assam health agency]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-bags-rs-57-cr-hmis-contract-from-assam-health-agency/1662871</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662871</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, has an estimated value of Rs 56.71 crore, as per the LoA.

The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, has an estimated value of Rs 56.71 crore, as per the LoA. The project is scheduled to be executed up to January 31, 2032. The company added that neither its promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in AHIDMS, and the contract does not fall under related-party transactions. RailTel Corporation, a "Navratna" PSU, is one of the largest neutral telecom infrastructure providers in the country, owning a Pan-India optical fiber network. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 4.72% to Rs 76.07 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 72.64 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 12.78% YoY to Rs 951.36 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of RailTel Corporation of India shed 0.23% to Rs 370.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>