<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shankara Building Products Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shankara-building-products-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1664043</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664043</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[N K Industries Ltd, Naksh Precious Metals Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 January 2026.

N K Industries Ltd, Naksh Precious Metals Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 January 2026. Shankara Building Products Ltd crashed 13.06% to Rs 110.15 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 47486 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 25093 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd lost 9.99% to Rs 66.96. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 127 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62 shares in the past one month. Naksh Precious Metals Ltd tumbled 9.98% to Rs 5.77. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4821 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 68353 shares in the past one month. Rollatainers Ltd fell 9.60% to Rs 1.79. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.4 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.96 lakh shares in the past one month. JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd pared 9.48% to Rs 10.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 33363 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22423 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShankaraBuildingProductsLtd_44449259665_28590.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tanvi Foods jump on incorporation of UK subsidiary]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tanvi-foods-jump-on-incorporation-of-uk-subsidiary/1664044</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664044</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the UK subsidiary was incorporated on 8 January 2026, with an initial paid up capital of GBP 1,000.

The company said the UK subsidiary was incorporated on 8 January 2026, with an initial paid up capital of GBP 1,000. Tanvi Foods (India) will hold a 51% stake by subscribing to 510 shares of GBP 1 each, with the investment to be made in cash. The new subsidiary will focus on frozen and ready to eat Indian food products, including frozen samosas, and is aimed at tapping the growing demand for ethnic and convenience foods in the UK. The company said the move will help strengthen its international presence and replicate the business model of its US arm, Tanvi Foods USA Inc., in the UK market. Tanvi Foods said the incorporation does not involve any acquisition and that there is no promoter interest in the subsidiary. The company added that all future transactions between the parent and the subsidiary will be conducted at arm’s length and in compliance with applicable laws in India and the UK. Tanvi Foods (India) is engaged in the processing and manufacture of corn based food products such as corn samosas, corn patties and spring rolls, and also trades in fresh and frozen corn and related products. On a consolidated basis, Tanvi Foods (India)'s net profit surged 282.35% to Rs 0.65 crore on 9.33% increase in net sales to Rs 48.29 crore in H1FY26 over H1FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TanviFoodsIndiaLtd_33349110964_69448.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AuSom Enterprise jumps 21% in four days]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ausom-enterprise-jumps-21-in-four-days/1664045</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664045</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of AuSom Enterprise surged 21.1% in four trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 109 on 5 January 2026.

Shares of AuSom Enterprise surged 21.1% in four trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 109 on 5 January 2026. The stock hit an all-time high of Rs 132 today. On the BSE, 0.89 lakh shares have been traded so far, compared with an average daily volume of 7,431 shares over the past two weeks. The stock had outperformed the market over the past month, rising 20.82% as against the Sensex's 1.37% drop. The stock had outperformed the market over the three months, rising 22.85% as against the Sensex's 1.62% jump. The counter had also outperformed the market in the past year, soaring 30.56% as against Sensex's 7.58% rise. On the technical front, the stock's daily RSI (relative strength index) stood at 83.352. The RSI oscillates between zero and 100. Traditionally, the RSI is considered overbought when above 70 and oversold when below 30. On the daily chart, the stock was trading above its 50-day, 100-day, and 200-day simple moving average (SMA), placed at 80.80, 77.33, and 42.35, respectively. These levels will act as crucial support zones in the near term. AuSom Enterprise is engaged in trading in the financial and commodity markets, along with the manufacturing and trading of jewellery. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 6.7% to Rs 1.81 crore on a 5014.2% surge in total income to Rs 122.23 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AusomEnter_45506933337_2386.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 651 pts; consumer durables shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-651-pts-consumer-durables-shares-decline/1664039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664039</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in the mid- afternoon as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S.

The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in the mid- afternoon as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on the legality of U.S. tariffs, which have weighed on markets in recent sessions. The Nifty traded near the 25,650 mark. Consumer durables shares extended losses for second consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 651.25 points or 0.77% to 83,539.71. The Nifty 50 index dropped 223.30 points or 0.87% to 25,653.95. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 1.13% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.79%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 965 shares rose and 3,126 shares fell. A total of 180 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index declined 1.28% to 37,548.90. The index fell 2.05% in for the two consecutive trading session. Amber Enterprises India (down 2.7%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (down 2.68%), V-Guard Industries (down 2.23%), PG Electroplast (down 1.69%), Kajaria Ceramics (down 1.3%), Blue Star (down 1.3%), Whirlpool of India (down 1.23%), Kalyan Jewellers India (down 1.22%), Cera Sanitaryware (down 1.19%) and Titan Company (down 0.92%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.15% to 6.640 compared with previous session close of 6.630. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2275 compared with its close of 89.9025 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.46% to Rs 138,364. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.16% to 99.03. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.12% to 4.190. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 57 cents or 0.92% to $62.56 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Indo Tech Transformers fell 2.13%. The company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 64.99 crore from ReNew Wind Energy (Jamb) for the manufacture and supply of six 220 kV–165 MVA transformers. Waaree Energies shed 2.68%. The company said that it has received a one-time order from a renowned domestic customer engaged in owning, developing, and operating renewable power projects in India for the supply of 105 MW solar modules in FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Indian Energy Exchange Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-indian-energy-exchange-ltd-counter/1664038</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664038</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd, Elecon Engineering Company Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, Cera Sanitaryware Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 09 January 2026.

Hitachi Energy India Ltd, Elecon Engineering Company Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, Cera Sanitaryware Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 09 January 2026. Indian Energy Exchange Ltd notched up volume of 1992.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.31 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 272.70 lakh shares. The stock slipped 6.92% to Rs.139.70. Volumes stood at 241.7 lakh shares in the last session. Hitachi Energy India Ltd notched up volume of 6.35 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.16 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.03 lakh shares. The stock slipped 5.12% to Rs.17,500.00. Volumes stood at 1.82 lakh shares in the last session. Elecon Engineering Company Ltd witnessed volume of 107.41 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.99 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 21.52 lakh shares. The stock dropped 15.86% to Rs.423.50. Volumes stood at 24.19 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd saw volume of 27.53 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.54 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.07 lakh shares. The stock dropped 5.33% to Rs.418.15. Volumes stood at 5.09 lakh shares in the last session. Cera Sanitaryware Ltd registered volume of 48470 shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.23 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 11453 shares. The stock slipped 1.25% to Rs.5,123.50. Volumes stood at 18631 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndianEnergyExchangeLtd_3642743015_70961.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index fast approaching next crucial 99 mark; All eyes on US non farms report]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-fast-approaching-next-crucial-99-mark-all-eyes-on-us-non-farms-report/1664036</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664036</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Dollar index is staying elevated around a one-month high and seen fast approaching the next crucial 99 mark.

Dollar index is staying elevated around a one-month high and seen fast approaching the next crucial 99 mark. All eyes are now glued to upcoming US nonfarm payrolls (NFP) report that could shed some light on Federal Reserve interest rate stance for the year. On Thursday, the US Department of Labor (DOL) reported that initial jobless claims rose modestly to 208,000 in the week ended January 3, slightly below market expectations of 210,000 but above the previous week’s revised 200,000. Continuing jobless claims increased to 1.914 million from 1.858 million, indicating a gradual rise in the number of people remaining on unemployment benefits. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is trading higher by the fourth consecutive day and quoting for now at 98.79, up 0.10% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures climb above $58 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-oil-futures-climb-above-58-per-barrel/1664037</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664037</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures climbed above $58 per barrel on Friday, extending gains for a third straight week as concerns over a potential surge in Venezuelan supply eased.

WTI Crude oil futures climbed above $58 per barrel on Friday, extending gains for a third straight week as concerns over a potential surge in Venezuelan supply eased. The move came after the US Congress advanced measures aimed at limiting military intervention in Venezuela, reducing the likelihood of abrupt policy actions that could disrupt global oil flows. At the same time, ongoing political unrest in Iran injected fresh geopolitical risk into the market, supporting prices amid fears of broader regional instability. In the domestic market, MCX crude futures tracked global strength, rising over 2%, as sentiment remained underpinned by easing supply fears and heightened geopolitical uncertainty.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/steel-long-pipes-in-crude-oil-factory-during-sunset-picture_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indo Tech Transformers bags Rs 65-cr order from ReNew Wind Energy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indo-tech-transformers-bags-rs-65-cr-order-from-renew-wind-energy/1664031</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664031</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order is domestic in nature and involves the supply of power transformers, with deliveries scheduled between February 2027 and May 2027.

The order is domestic in nature and involves the supply of power transformers, with deliveries scheduled between February 2027 and May 2027. The company said that neither the promoter nor the promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions. Indo Tech Transformers is engaged in the business of manufacturing power and distribution transformers and various special application transformers, mobile substation transformers, and substations. The company's standalone net profit surged 39.8% to Rs 24.78 crore on a 25% increase in net sales to Rs 182.86 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip dropped 2.15% to currently trade at Rs 1,507 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndoTechTrans_24423190996_19825.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,700 level; European mrkt advance ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25700-level-european-mrkt-advance/1664030</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664030</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on the legality of U.S. tariffs, which have weighed on markets in recent sessions. The Nifty traded below the 25,700 level. Realty, private bank and auto shares declined, while PSU bank and IT shares advanced. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 596.05 points or 0.71% to 83,584.91. The Nifty 50 index dropped 185.60 points or 0.72% to 25,688.65. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.63% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 1.23%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,059 shares rose and 2,955 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Asian Paints (up 2%), Bharat Electronics (up 1.14%), Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (up 1.11%), HCL Technologies (up 1.07%) and ETERNAL (up 0.35%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. NTPC (down 2.73%), ICICI Bank (down 2.09%), Adani Enterprises (down 2.10%), Bajaj Auto (down 1.72%) and Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (down 1.45%) were the major Nifty50 losers. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 1,88,18,40,600 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 13:40 IST on Friday (9 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 5.42 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Stocks in Spotlight: Elecon Engineering Company dropped 15.56% to Rs 441.80 after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 33.1% to Rs 71.99 crore despite a 4.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 551.74 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Waaree Renewable Technologies declined 3.27% after the company announced reduction of the capacity and the corresponding contract value of a previously received commercial order from its subsidiary, Waaree Forever Energies (WFEPL). Power grid Corporation of India shed 0.40%. The company has been declared as successful bidder under tariff based competitive bidding (TBCB) for the development of 3GW transmission system in Davanagere, Karnataka. Brahmaputra Infrastructure added 0.48%. The company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from the Office of the Chief Engineer, PWD (R&B), Jammu, for balance work related to the construction of the new Legislature Complex at Jammu. Highway Infrastructure rallied 2.23% after the company announced that it has entered into a contract agreement worth Rs 328.77 crore with the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI). Global Markets: European shares opened higher on Friday as investors assessed evolving economic cues and rising social pressures across the region. Asian markets traded mixed, even as China’s consumer prices rose 0.8% year-on-year, according to data from the National Bureau of Statistics, following a 0.7% increase in November. In the U.S., investors are awaiting two key catalysts on Friday. First, the Supreme Court could issue a ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump’s tariffs, which could have an impact on trade policy and the nation’s fiscal situation. Second, the December jobs report will be out on Friday morning. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose while the Nasdaq Composite came under pressure as investors moved away from technology stocks. The Dow Jones Industrial Average climbed 270.03 points, or 0.55%, and ended at 49,266.11; the S&P 500 advanced 0.01% and closed at 6,921.46, while The tech-heavy Nasdaq dropped 0.44% and settled at 23,480.02

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-bank-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664017</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664017</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

HDFC Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 936.95, down 1.03% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.HDFC Bank Ltd has lost around 5.34% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which HDFC Bank Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.58% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59686.5, down 0.64% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 282.56 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 187.84 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 940.75, down 1.04% on the day. HDFC Bank Ltd jumped 13.11% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 21.68% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 20.47 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCBank_24534281400_4987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1664018</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664018</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3677.5, down 1.25% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd has gained around 1.31% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 2.83% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28414.95, down 0.99% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.41 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 14.13 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3688.6, down 1.37% on the day. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd jumped 18.9% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 22.22% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 33.07 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/exide-industries-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664019</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664019</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Exide Industries Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 348.35, down 1.26% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Exide Industries Ltd has eased around 5.95% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Exide Industries Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 2.83% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28414.95, down 0.99% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 7.35 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.14 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 349.4, down 1.15% on the day. Exide Industries Ltd tumbled 10.47% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 22.22% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 28.82 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ExideInds_97756038201_111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahanagar Gas Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahanagar-gas-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664020</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664020</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahanagar Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Mahanagar Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1054.4, down 0.51% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Mahanagar Gas Ltd has lost around 5.47% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Mahanagar Gas Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.15 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.67 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 10.56 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahanagarGasLtd_64664984058_13369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indraprastha Gas Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indraprastha-gas-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1664021</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664021</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indraprastha Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Indraprastha Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 184.07, down 0.85% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Indraprastha Gas Ltd has lost around 0.37% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Indraprastha Gas Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 7.75 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 33.01 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 19.06 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndraprasthaGas_19895507695_20703.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Reliance Power Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/reliance-power-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1664022</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664022</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reliance Power Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Reliance Power Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 33.93, down 1.19% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Reliance Power Ltd has lost around 0.15% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Reliance Power Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 183.89 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 565.94 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ReliancePower_71756580176_12653.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Power Company Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-power-company-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1664023</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664023</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Power Company Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Tata Power Company Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 367.3, down 1.84% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Tata Power Company Ltd has eased around 3.3% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Tata Power Company Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 31.64 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 38.54 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 368, down 1.87% on the day. Tata Power Company Ltd jumped 3.07% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 2.08% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 51.12 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataPowerCo_38377109932_554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suzlon Energy Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suzlon-energy-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664024</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664024</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Suzlon Energy Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Suzlon Energy Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 49.67, down 2.47% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Suzlon Energy Ltd has eased around 3.63% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Suzlon Energy Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 557.62 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 435.16 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 49.84, down 2.37% on the day. Suzlon Energy Ltd tumbled 10.62% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 2.08% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 22.94 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuzlonEnergy_13614358127_13872.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Green Energy Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-green-energy-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1664025</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664025</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Adani Green Energy Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Adani Green Energy Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 964.2, down 2.49% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Adani Green Energy Ltd has eased around 2.59% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Adani Green Energy Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 12.03 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 17.14 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 966, down 2.43% on the day. Adani Green Energy Ltd jumped 2.24% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 2.08% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 134.17 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniGreenEnergyLtd_74416007001_70666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Energy Solutions Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-energy-solutions-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664026</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664026</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Adani Energy Solutions Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Adani Energy Solutions Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 968.8, down 2.56% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.Adani Energy Solutions Ltd has eased around 1.4% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Adani Energy Solutions Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.28 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.9 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 970, down 2.59% on the day. Adani Energy Solutions Ltd jumped 32.85% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 2.08% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 192.99 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniTransmissi_50439587268_66273.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cg-power-industrial-solutions-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664027</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664027</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 593.5, down 3.38% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.67% on the day, quoting at 25702.5. The Sensex is at 83622.68, down 0.66%.CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd has lost around 10.81% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34729.65, down 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 104.37 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 23.21 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 599.45, down 2.27% on the day. CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd tumbled 8.72% in last one year as compared to a 9.69% rally in NIFTY and a 2.08% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 86.65 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CGPowerIndu_42121517029_125.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>