<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[H.G. Infra Engineering bags LOA from NHAI for Odisha road project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hg-infra-engineering-bags-loa-from-nhai-for-odisha-road-project/1679950</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679950</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package III, stretching from Gobindpur on NH-55 to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza on NH-16.

The project involves the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package III, stretching from Gobindpur on NH-55 to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza on NH-16. The total project length stands at 40.33 km. The project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode. While the estimated project cost is Rs 1,827.33 crore, HGINFRA's bid project cost stands at Rs 1,582.11 crore, excluding applicable GST. The construction period for the project is 910 days. HGINFRA is an infrastructure development company. The company specialises in executing end-to-end Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) services and Hybrid Annuity Model (HAM) projects across transport infrastructure, renewable energy, and Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) including Transmission. On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit fell 18.1% to Rs 94.28 crore on a 12.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,421.16 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HGInfraEngineeringLtd_52714149365_71631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta declared preferred bidder for Karnapodikonda bauxite block in Odisha]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-declared-preferred-bidder-for-karnapodikonda-bauxite-block-in-odisha/1679949</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679949</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said it received a 'Declaration of Preferred Bidder' notification from the Directorate of Mines and Geology, Government of Odisha, on 27 February 2026.

In a regulatory filing, the company said it received a 'Declaration of Preferred Bidder' notification from the Directorate of Mines and Geology, Government of Odisha, on 27 February 2026. The tender process was initiated through a Notice Inviting Tender dated 4 December 2025 for grant of a mining lease for the block. After qualifying at the initial bid stage, Vedanta participated in the live e-auction process and emerged as the preferred bidder. According to the tender document, the Karnapodikonda bauxite block is classified at the G2 level of exploration and spans a total area of 532.747 hectares. The company said the acquisition aligns with its strategic objective of backward integration for its aluminium business, strengthening long-term raw material security. Vedanta is a global producer of critical minerals, energy transition metals, power, and technology, with operations across India, South Africa, Namibia, Liberia, the UAE, Saudi Arabia, Korea, Taiwan, and Japan. It is the world’s largest integrated zinc producer, the fourth-largest silver producer, and among the top aluminium producers globally. Vedanta is also India’s only private oil and gas producer and one of the country’s largest private power generators. On a consolidated basis, Vedanta's net profit surged 60.98% to Rs 5,710 crore while revenue from operations jumped 36.95% YoY to Rs 23,369 crore in Q3 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>