<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gillette India gains as Q3 PAT climbs 37% YoY to Rs 172 cr; declares dividend of Rs 180/share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gillette-india-gains-as-q3-pat-climbs-37-yoy-to-rs-172-cr-declares-dividend-of-rs-180share/1668890</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668890</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PAT growth was fueled by double-digit revenue expansion and a favorable product pricing mix, reflecting a strong quarterly performance.

PAT growth was fueled by double-digit revenue expansion and a favorable product pricing mix, reflecting a strong quarterly performance. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 232.14 crore in the December quarter, up 38.89% from Rs 167.14 crore reported in the corresponding quarter the previous year. During the quarter, the company's revenue from grooming was at Rs 647.06 crore (up 13.39% YoY), and revenue from oral care stood at Rs 142.94 crore (up 24.39% YoY). Kumar Venkatasubramanian, managing director of Gillette India, said, “We have delivered strong, balanced growth once again this quarter. This performance was enabled by our teams’ commitment to execute our integrated growth strategy. This includes a focused product portfolio of daily use categories, where performance drives brand choice; superiority (of product performance, packaging, brand communication, retail execution, and consumer and customer value); productivity; constructive disruption; and an agile and accountable organization. We remain committed to this strategy, which continues to drive our results, guiding us to deliver sustainable, balanced growth and value creation.” Meanwhile, the board of directors also declared an interim dividend of Rs 180 per equity share, including a one-time special dividend of Rs 60 per share, for FY26. The record date has been fixed as 4 February 2026, and the dividend will be paid on or before 26 February 2026. Gillette India is engaged in the manufacturing and sale of branded packaged fast-moving consumer goods in the grooming, portable power, and oral care businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GilletteIndia_17228255119_288.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drop in early trade; breadth weak]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drop-in-early-trade-breadth-weak/1668884</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668884</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks opened sharply lower in early trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors turned cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, slated for presentation on February 1.

Domestic equity benchmarks opened sharply lower in early trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors turned cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, slated for presentation on February 1. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments for fresh direction. Investor focus is also on quarterly results due later today from key companies such as Bajaj Auto, NTPC, Power Grid Corporation of India, Nestlé India, and Ambuja Cements. Reflecting the subdued sentiment, the Nifty slipped below the 25,250 level during morning trade. Metal, IT and oil & gas shares witnessed selling pressure, while FMCG, consumer durables and pharma stocks advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 520.26 points or 0.63% to 82,046.11. The Nifty 50 index fell 179.25 points or 0.69% to 25,239.25. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.20%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 996 shares rose and 2,121 shares fell. A total of 162 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 393.97 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,638.76 crore in the Indian equity market on 29 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: ITC rose 0.82%. The company reported a 0.07% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 4,931.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,934.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 6.7% YoY to Rs 21,706.6 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Tata Motors added 0.13%. The company reported a 48% YoY drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 705 crore, while revenue from operations increased 16.1% to Rs 21,847 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. REC slipped 2.45%. The company reported a 0.3% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 4,043 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,029.1 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 2.8% YoY to Rs 5,275.5 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper advanced 0.12% to 6.707 as compared with previous close of 6.699. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9000 compared with its close of 91.9950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement dropped 3.53% to Rs 1,63,420. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.30% to 96.43. The United States 10-year bond yield advanced 0.92% to 4.267. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement lost 1.23 cents or 1.77% to $68.36 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump said that he will announce his choice for the next Federal Reserve chair on Friday. Speaking at the premiere of Melania, a film about first lady Melania Trump, he said the five-month search to replace current chair Jerome Powell was nearing its conclusion. The process for selecting Powell’s replacement began in September with an 11-candidate field that included past and current Fed officials, economists, and Wall Street investment professionals. Trump also endorsed a Senate deal to fund the vast majority of the federal government through the remainder of the fiscal year, easing near-term political uncertainty for investors. Senators clinched a deal with just over a day until a partial government shutdown. They agreed to remove funding for the Department of Homeland Security from the package and pass the other five bills, while DHS will be funded by a stopgap. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index slipped 0.13% to close at 6,969.01, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 0.72% to end at 23,685.12. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.11%, or 55.96 points, and settled at 49,071.56.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dabur India rises after Q3 PAT jumps 7% YoY to Rs 554 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dabur-india-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-7-yoy-to-rs-554-cr/1668886</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668886</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax rose to Rs 726.16 crore from Rs 657.58 crore, including a one-time exceptional charge of Rs 15.05 crore for employee benefits under the new labour codes.

Profit before exceptional items and tax rose to Rs 726.16 crore from Rs 657.58 crore, including a one-time exceptional charge of Rs 15.05 crore for employee benefits under the new labour codes. The company reported net profit before exceptional items surged 10.1% to Rs 575 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 522 crore a year earlier, while operating profit grew 7.7% to Rs 734 crore during the quarter. Total expenses were at Rs 2,972.83 crore, up 5.19% in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 2,826.20 crore in the year ago period. The India FMCG business reported 6% growth during the quarter, with rural demand outperforming urban markets for the eighth consecutive quarter. Syndicated data showed a 330-basis-point growth gap in favour of rural markets, a trend mirrored in Dabur’s internal numbers. Dabur said its total reach expanded by 50,000 outlets during the quarter, taking distribution to over 8.5 million outlets, making it the second most distributed FMCG company in India. Its rural footprint now spans more than 133,000 villages. Category performance remained strong in Q3 FY26, led by a 19.1% surge in the Hair Oils business, which helped Dabur gain 193 basis points in market share, taking its overall share to around 20%—the highest ever. The Foods business grew 14%, while Toothpaste, led by Dabur Red and Meswak, rose around 10%. Juices & Nectars gained 195 basis points in market share, with the 100% juices segment up around 646 basis points, and Air Fresheners touched a 44% share after a 131-basis-point gain. The Skin & Salon business grew 6.6%, while Hajmola reported 7% growth during the quarter. Dabur’s international business delivered 11.1% year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26, driven by strong performances across key geographies. The company reported 20.2% growth in Bangladesh, 19.3% in the US, 15.4% in Turkey, and 12.5% in MENA during the quarter. Mohit Malhotra, chief executive officer, Dabur India, said, "Dabur delivered a steady quarter, with healthy volume-led growth across our key business verticals and geographies. We have sharpened our competitive edge through stronger innovation and focused brand building, leading to healthy market share gains. As demand conditions improve, the combination of favorable macroeconomic indicators and expectations of supportive policy measures, reinforced by recent GST changes, positions us well for the quarters ahead, and we remain confident of delivering sustainable growth, resilient profitability, and continued shareholder value." Dabur is one of India’s leading FMCG companies, specializing in Ayurveda and natural health care, with an extensive distribution network spanning India and key international markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DaburIndia_45461479947_3392.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd Slides 3.56%, BSE Telecommunication index Shed 1.31%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/optiemus-infracom-ltd-slides-356-bse-telecommunication-index-shed-131/1668879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668879</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd fell 3.56% today to trade at Rs 385.6.

Optiemus Infracom Ltd fell 3.56% today to trade at Rs 385.6. The BSE Telecommunication index is down 1.31% to quote at 2873.55. The index is down 7.98 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, HFCL Ltd decreased 1.69% and ITI Ltd lost 1.61% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 5.18 % over last one year compared to the 6.76% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Optiemus Infracom Ltd has lost 23.69% over last one month compared to 7.98% fall in BSE Telecommunication index and 3.84% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 3 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 8355 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 712.95 on 25 Sep 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 366.05 on 27 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OptiemusInfra_38144306001_5004.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Swiggy slumps as Q3 net loss widens to Rs 1,065 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/swiggy-slumps-as-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-1065-cr/1668881</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668881</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Despite the loss, the company recorded strong top-line growth, with revenue from operations rising 53.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,148 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Despite the loss, the company recorded strong top-line growth, with revenue from operations rising 53.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,148 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Total expenses climbed 48.99% YoY to Rs 7,298 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,898 crore in Q3 FY25. Advertising and sales promotion expenses surged 47.53% YoY to Rs 1,108 crore, while delivery and related charges increased 36.02% YoY to Rs 1,533 crore. Employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 673 crore (up 2.43% YoY) and finance costs climbed 111.53% YoY to Rs 55 crore during the quarter. The company’s pre-tax loss also stood at Rs 1,065 crore in Q3 FY26, against a pre-tax loss of Rs 799 crore in Q3 FY25. Swiggy said its Food Delivery business saw an acceleration in growth, with gross order value (GOV) rising 20.5% year-on-year to Rs 8,959 crore. Monthly transacting users (MTUs) increased 22% YoY to 18.1 million. Adjusted EBITDA margin improved to 3.0% of GOV, up 56 basis points YoY and 22 bps sequentially, the highest in the last two years, reflecting stronger user engagement through new use cases and improved affordability without compromising growth or profitability. Instamart’s GOV more than doubled, rising 103% YoY to Rs 7,938 crore. The company added 34 dark stores during the quarter, taking the total network to 1,136 stores across 131 cities, covering 4.8 million sq ft. Average order value rose 39.7% YoY to Rs 746, driven by traction in the Maxxsaver basket-building proposition and expansion of non-grocery categories. Contribution margin improved to -2.5% sequentially, aided by larger basket sizes, optimisation of customer incentives and operating leverage. Overall, the quick commerce business reported a loss of Rs 908 crore for the quarter, while adjusted EBITDA margin improved to -11.4% from -12.1% in Q2. Sriharsha Majety, MD & Group CEO of Swiggy, said, “the company continues to accelerate user growth and gross order value in food delivery, defying broader concerns of a sector slowdown, while significantly improving operating margins. He said the quick commerce opportunity remains in its early stages, with Swiggy focused on deepening wallet share and expanding differentiated assortments to drive engagement and order values. Majety added that the successful qualified institutional placement has strengthened the balance sheet and provides long-term capital to support sustained investments in growth and innovation, with the company maintaining a disciplined approach to capital allocation as it works towards contribution margin breakeven.” Swiggy is India’s pioneering on-demand convenience platform, catering to millions of consumers each month. Founded in 2014, its mission is to elevate the quality of life for the urban consumer by offering unparalleled convenience, enabled by over 6.9 lakh delivery partners. With an extensive footprint in food delivery, Swiggy Food collaborates with over 2.7 lakh restaurants across 720+ cities.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SwiggyLtd_23318367_68148.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests red start for equities; Trump to announce Powell's replacement]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-red-start-for-equities-trump-to-announce-powells-replacement/1668866</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668866</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 93.50 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 93.50 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 393.97 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,638.76 crore in the Indian equity market on 29 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 43,686.59 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump said that he will announce his choice for the next Federal Reserve chair on Friday. Speaking at the premiere of Melania, a film about first lady Melania Trump, he said the five-month search to replace current chair Jerome Powell was nearing its conclusion. The process for selecting Powell’s replacement began in September with an 11-candidate field that included past and current Fed officials, economists, and Wall Street investment professionals. Trump also endorsed a Senate deal to fund the vast majority of the federal government through the remainder of the fiscal year, easing near-term political uncertainty for investors. Senators clinched a deal with just over a day until a partial government shutdown. They agreed to remove funding for the Department of Homeland Security from the package and pass the other five bills, while DHS will be funded by a stopgap. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index slipped 0.13% to close at 6,969.01, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 0.72% to end at 23,685.12. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.11%, or 55.96 points, and settled at 49,071.56. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks closed with modest gains on Thursday, rising for the third straight session, as bargain buying and supportive economic signals helped offset expiry-led volatility. Both the Sensex and the Nifty bounced back sharply from intraday lows to finish higher on the Sensex monthly F&O expiry day. Sentiment was buoyed by the Economic Survey’s FY27 growth outlook of 6.8%-7.2% and by foreign institutional investors turning buyers on Wednesday after a 15-session selling streak. With investor attention squarely on the Union Budget 2026 due on February 1, the Nifty ended above the 25,400 level, supported by strength in metal and private banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 221.69 points or 0.27% to 82,566.37. The Nifty 50 index added 76.15 points or 0.30% to 25,418.90. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 1.26% while the Nifty rose 1.48%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: ITC, Tata Motors, One 97 Communications, Swiggy, Colgate-Palmolive]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-itc-tata-motors-one-97-communications-swiggy-colgate-palmolive/1668862</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668862</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Listing In the SME segment, BSE SME Shayona Engineering is set to list today.

Listing In the SME segment, BSE SME Shayona Engineering is set to list today. The issue price is set at Rs 144 per share. The issue was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue was open between 22 and 27 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 140 to Rs 144 per equity share. Result Today: Bajaj Auto, NTPC, Power Grid Corporation of India, Nestle India, Bank of Baroda, Meesho, Ajanta Pharma, Ambuja Cements, Ashoka Buildcon, Aster DM Healthcare, Antony Waste Handling Cell, Brigade Enterprises, Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company, Exide Industries, Glenmark Pharmaceuticals, Jindal Steel, KEC International, Dr. Lal PathLabs, LIC Housing Finance, National Aluminium Company, New India Assurance Company, Steel Authority of India, and Welspun Corp will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: ITC reported a 0.07% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 4,931.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,934.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 6.7% YoY to Rs 21,706.6 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Tata Motors reported a 48% YoY drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 705 crore, while revenue from operations increased 16.1% to Rs 21,847 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. REC reported a 0.3% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 4,043 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,029.1 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 2.8% YoY to Rs 5,275.5 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. One 97 Communications reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 225 crore as compared with a net loss of Rs 208 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operation jumped 20% YoY to Rs 2,194 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Swiggy reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 1,065 crore in Q3 FY26, widening from a net loss of Rs 799 crore in Q3 FY25. Despite the loss, the company recorded strong top-line growth, with revenue from operations rising 53.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,148 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Colgate-Palmolive (India) reported consolidated net profit rose 0.3% to Rs 323.9 crore on a 1.66% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,486.1 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Vedanta reported a 60.98% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 5,710 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,547 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 36.95% YoY to Rs 23,369 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Atlanta Electricals said it has bagged two orders worth Rs 146 crore from Karnataka Power Transmission Corporation and three additional orders worth Rs 142 crore from Datta Power Infra, which is executing projects for NTPC. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (HPCL) said it has signed an MoU with Oil India to collaborate on a compressed biogas (CBG) project. Under the pact, Oil India will set up a CBG plant using HPCL’s indigenously developed HP RAMP technology.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HAL wins Rs 1,800-cr order from Pawan Hans for 10 Dhruv NG helicopters]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hal-wins-rs-1800-cr-order-from-pawan-hans-for-10-dhruv-ng-helicopters/1668805</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668805</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The estimated value of the contract exceeds Rs 1,800 crore, with the delivery of helicopters scheduled to be completed by 2027.

The estimated value of the contract exceeds Rs 1,800 crore, with the delivery of helicopters scheduled to be completed by 2027. The order has been awarded by Pawan Hans, Noida, and is classified as a domestic contract. HAL clarified that neither its promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in Pawan Hans. The company also stated that the contract does not fall under related-party transactions. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 10.8% to Rs 1,669.07 crore on 10.9% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,628.61 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hindustan Aeronautics is engaged in the business of Manufacture of Aircraft and Helicopters and Repair, Maintenance of Aircraft and Helicopters. Shares of Hindustan Aeronautics shed 0.73% to Rs 4,567.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindustanAeronauticsLtd_47098929559_12030.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>