<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:29:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Armour Security (India)'s market debut fails to stand watch]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-armour-security-indias-market-debut-fails-to-stand-watch/1666617</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666617</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 45.60, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 45.60, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently down 4.93% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 45.60 and a low of Rs 43.35. About 18,000 shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Armour Security (India)'s IPO was subscribed 1.77 times. The issue opened for bidding on 14 January 2026 and it closed on 19 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 55 to Rs 57 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 46,50,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter group shareholding diluted to 70.12% from 96.80% pre-issue. The company intends to utilized the net proceeds for funding of working capital requirements, funding capital expenditure requirements for purchasing of machinery equipment and vehicles, pre-payment/re-payment of, in part or full, certain outstanding borrowings of the company and general corporate purposes. Armour Security (India) specializes in comprehensive private security solutions, offering services such as security planning and management, integrated facility management, housekeeping and manpower provision, including skilled, semi-skilled, and unskilled personnel, to cater to clients’ diverse needs. With over two decades of experience, the company has established a strong presence in the security manpower services and integrated facility management sector. Starting from a single office in Defence Colony, Delhi, it has expanded its operations to various states across India, ensuring the consistent delivery of quality services. As of 9 December 2025, the company had a total of 37 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 19.68 crore and net profit of Rs 2.90 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ARMOURSECURITYINDIALTD_70957373_94589.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TANFAC Industries edges lower after weak Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tanfac-industries-edges-lower-after-weak-q3-performance/1666616</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666616</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total operating expenditure for the December’25 quarter was Rs 147.42 crore, up by 15.3% YoY.

Total operating expenditure for the December’25 quarter was Rs 147.42 crore, up by 15.3% YoY. During Q3 FY26, PBIDT was Rs 26.15 crore as against Rs 50.52 crore in the same quarter of the previous year, up 39.1% YoY. PBIDT margin in Q3 FY26 declined to 15.09% from 28.35% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 20.33 crore, down by 56.3% from Rs 46.47 crore in Q3 FY25. Afzal Malkani, managing director, stated: “The company had recorded good revenue and profitability during the quarter and nine month ended 31st December 2025 despite pressures on margin due to steep increase in one of the key input costs and reduction in production due to plant shut down (annual maintenance and activities relating to commissioning of Solar Grade DHF).” He further noted the timely commissioning of the two phases of the Solar Grade DHF project with an annual capacity of 10,000 metric tonnes in June & October 2025 respectively would help the company improve both top and bottom lines during the subsequent quarters Tanfac Industries is a joint sector company promoted by Anupam Rasayan India and Tamil Nadu Industrial Development Corporation (TIDCO) and is amongst the leading producers of hydrofluoric acid and its derivatives.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TanfacInds_95252622_548.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MSME sector contributes nearly 30% to national GDP, accounts for approximately 46% of exports]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/msme-sector-contributes-nearly-30-to-national-gdp-accounts-for-approximately-46-of-exports/1666614</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666614</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NITI Aayog has stated in a latest report that India's Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs) form the backbone of the nation's industrial landscape, contributing nearly 30% to national GDP, employing over 250 million people and accounting for approximately 46% of exports.

NITI Aayog has stated in a latest report that India's Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs) form the backbone of the nation's industrial landscape, contributing nearly 30% to national GDP, employing over 250 million people and accounting for approximately 46% of exports. The Roadmap for Green Transition of MSMEs focuses on three key levers: deployment of energy-efficient equipment, adoption of alternative fuels, and integration of green electricity. Suman Bery, Vice Chairperson, NITI Aayog observed that MSMEs are important members of domestic and international supply chains. He urged prioritizing technology adoption, access to affordable finance, skilling & regulatory reforms, and increased participation of female workforce to achieve overall competitiveness of MSMEs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/auto-mechanic-service-and-repair-picture-id652660470_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sundaram Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sundaram-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1666612</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666612</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Notice is hereby given that Mr.

Notice is hereby given that Mr. Siddarth Mohta has been appointed as Associate Fund Manager – Equity, with effect from January 16, 2026. Accordingly, his details shall be added under “Information on Key Personnel” in the Statement of Additional Information (SAI) of Sundaram Mutual Fund. Details of Mr. Siddarth Mohta Age: 45 years Designation: Associate Fund Manager - Equity Qualification: Qualification: - MBA, CFA (ICFAI), FRM B.Com

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cement production likely to increase sevenfold to around 2100 million tonnes in 2070, says NITY Aayog]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cement-production-likely-to-increase-sevenfold-to-around-2100-million-tonnes-in-2070-says-nity-aayog/1666611</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666611</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NITI Aayog has stated in a latest report that India's cement production is likely to increase sevenfold to 2100 million tonnes in 2070, from the level of 391 million tonnes in 2023.

NITI Aayog has stated in a latest report that India's cement production is likely to increase sevenfold to 2100 million tonnes in 2070, from the level of 391 million tonnes in 2023. Under the decarbonisation strategy, the cement sector must reduce its carbon intensity from 0.63 tCO₂e per tonne of cement to approximately 0.09-0.13 tCO₂e per tonne by 2070. The report proposes to prioritize the use of refuse-derived fuels, clinker substitution, scaling up of Carbon Capture, Utilisation and Storage (CCUS) and effective implementation of Carbon Credit Trading Scheme to enable deep decarbonisation in this sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/mortgage-concept-by-money-house-from-the-coins-picture-id51_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 297 pts; media shares in demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-297-pts-media-shares-in-demand/1666610</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666610</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade, tracking a rally in global markets amid improved investor sentiment.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade, tracking a rally in global markets amid improved investor sentiment. The Nifty traded above the 25,200 level. Media stocks advanced after declining in the previous three trading sessions. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 296.81 points or 0.36% to 82,206.44. The Nifty 50 index rose 91.90 points or 0.37% to 25,246.85. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.83% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.74%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,763 shares rose and 1,126 shares fell. A total of 188 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 1.41% to 13.98. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 5,74,91,640 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:20 IST on Thursday (22 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.65 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index added 1.84% to 1,378.90. The index rose 2.11% after declining over the previous three trading sessions. Prime Focus (up 5.29%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 4.08%), Saregama India (up 2.3%), Network 18 Media & Investments (up 1.53%), PVR Inox (up 1.5%), Sun TV Network (up 1.15%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (up 0.91%), and Nazara Technologies (up 0.67%) rose. Stocks in Spotlight: Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (HPCL) shed 0.44%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 34.72% to Rs 4,072.49 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3,022.90 crore in Q3 FY25. The company's total income (excluding excise duty) rose 5.23% YoY to Rs 1,15,740.02 crore during the December 2025 quarter. Zydus Lifesciences rose 1.08% after the company announced the launch of the world’s first biosimilar of Nivolumab in India under the brand name Tishtha, aimed at treating multiple types of cancer. Global Markets: Asian markets traded mixed on Thursday, tracking overnight gains on Wall Street after U.S. President Donald Trump dialed back his threat to impose tariffs on European countries over Greenland. Trump also said at the World Economic Forum in Davos that he would not use force to acquire the Arctic island, calming nerves over a possible U.S. military action, adding that he had “formed the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland,” along with NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. Meanwhile, South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. U.S. equities leaped on Wednesday after President Donald Trump called off new Europe tariffs, saying a deal framework has been reached over Greenland. The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged 588.64 points, or 1.21%, to end at 49,007.23. The S&P 500 gained 1.16% and closed at 6,875.62, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.18% to settle at 23,224.82. Back in Washington, Supreme Court justices expressed skepticism about whether Trump has the authority to fire Lisa Cook as a Federal Reserve governor. During oral arguments Wednesday, Justice Brett Kavanaugh told a Trump administration lawyer that arguments the president can fire Cook without judicial review “would weaken, if not shatter, the independence of the Federal Reserve."

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1666608</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666608</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Notice is hereby given that Mr.

Notice is hereby given that Mr. Pranav Gupta has been appointed as Research Analyst – Equity for the Mutual Fund business and designated as Key Personnel at Axis Asset Management Company Limited, with effect from January 08, 2026. Details of Mr. Pranav Gupta Age: 44 years Designation: Research Analyst - Equity Qualification: Chartered accountant & FRM

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KEI Industries posts nearly 43% YoY jump in Q3 PAT; EBITDA improves to Rs 354 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kei-industries-posts-nearly-43-yoy-jump-in-q3-pat-ebitda-improves-to-rs-354-crore/1666604</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666604</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total operating expenditure for the period under review was Rs 2,634.61 crore, up by 18.3% YoY.

Total operating expenditure for the period under review was Rs 2,634.61 crore, up by 18.3% YoY. During Q3 FY26, EBITDA was Rs 353.90 crore as against Rs 254.45 crore in the same quarter of the previous year, up 39.1% YoY. EBITDA margin in Q3 FY26 improved to 11.98% from 10.29% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 314.67 crore, up by 42.3% from Rs 221.20 crore in Q3 FY25. KEI Industries manufactures wires and cables (W&C) like EHV cables, HT cables, and LT cables and sells them in India and overseas. The scrip declined 3.51% to currently trade at Rs 3802 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KEIInds_55284114961_4679.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee: Weak equities pull INR to record low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-weak-equities-pull-inr-to-record-low/1666576</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666576</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee tanked to a new low on Wednesday, witnessing sustained losses and breaking beyond 91 per US dollar mark.

Indian Rupee tanked to a new low on Wednesday, witnessing sustained losses and breaking beyond 91 per US dollar mark. INR has lost around 70 paise to reach 91.65 per US dollar as local equities extended downward trajectory. Meanwhile, Local stocks stayed slippery as headline index NIFTY tested lowest in three and half months, adding to recent losses. NSE Nifty 50 index broke under 25000 mark. The index has lost more than 3% this month so far.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growth-on-coin-pile-business-conceptual-picture-id489_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Abbott India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-abbott-india-ltd-counter/1666554</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666554</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd, NTPC Ltd, V-Guard Industries Ltd, Triveni Turbine Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 22 January 2026.

HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd, NTPC Ltd, V-Guard Industries Ltd, Triveni Turbine Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 22 January 2026. Abbott India Ltd clocked volume of 4115 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 12.24 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 336 shares. The stock gained 0.41% to Rs.27,717.00. Volumes stood at 499 shares in the last session. HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd saw volume of 6.65 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.56 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 77681 shares. The stock increased 0.18% to Rs.725.00. Volumes stood at 67359 shares in the last session. NTPC Ltd saw volume of 31.03 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.39 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4.86 lakh shares. The stock increased 0.47% to Rs.340.25. Volumes stood at 2.99 lakh shares in the last session. V-Guard Industries Ltd registered volume of 1.57 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 4.84 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 32516 shares. The stock slipped 0.61% to Rs.307.20. Volumes stood at 15558 shares in the last session. Triveni Turbine Ltd recorded volume of 10.57 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 4.48 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.36 lakh shares. The stock gained 0.44% to Rs.471.40. Volumes stood at 3.32 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AbbottIndia_90273760573_90.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of India gains as Q3 PAT jumps 8% YoY to Rs 2,705 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-india-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-8-yoy-to-rs-2705-cr/1666552</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666552</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income stood at Rs 21,205.95 crore in Q3 FY26, up 6.25% as against Rs 19,956.9 crore in Q3 FY25.

Total income stood at Rs 21,205.95 crore in Q3 FY26, up 6.25% as against Rs 19,956.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) rose 6.41% YoY to Rs 3,616.8 crore in Q3 December 2025. Net interest income (NII) fell 1.24% to Rs 5,912 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 5,986 crore in Q2 FY25. Net interest margin (NIM) slipped to 2.41% in Q2 FY26, compared with 2.81% in Q2 FY25 Global deposits jumped 11.64% to Rs 8,87,288 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 7,94,788 crore in Q3 FY25. Domestic deposits increased 12.80% YoY to Rs 7,65,499 crore in Q3 FY26. Global advances stood at Rs 7,40,314 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 13.63% compared with Rs 6,51,507 crore in Q3 FY25. Domestic advances climbed 15.16% YoY to Rs 6,29,080 crore in Q3 FY26. On asset quality front, gross non-performing assets (GNPA) reduced by 143 bps to 2.26% in Q3 FY26 as against 3.69% in Q3 FY25. Net non-performing assets (NNPA) declined by 25 bps to 0.60% in Q3 FY26, compared with 0.85% in Q3 FY25. Capital Adequacy Ratio (CRAR) as of Q3 FY26 stood at 17.09%. Tier 1 CRAR stood at 14.36% while CET -1 ratio stood at 13.76% in Q3 FY26. The bank reported robust growth across its lending segments, with Retail Advances leading the way, growing by 20.64% YoY, followed by Agriculture Advances at 16.69% and MSME Advances at 15.77%. Corporate Advances grew at a relatively moderate pace of 11.32% YoY. The focus on high-growth segments is reflected in the increase of RAM (Retail, Agriculture, and MSME) share in total advances to 58.54%, highlighting the bank’s strategy of prioritizing diversified and high-potential lending over large corporate exposure. Bank of India is an India-based bank. The Bank's segments include Treasury Operations, Wholesale Banking and Retail Banking. The Treasury operations segment includes the entire investment portfolio, which is dealing in government and other securities, money market operations and foreign exchange operations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofIndia_12067469065_5654.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI AMC records PAT of Rs 121 crore in Q3; AUM rises to Rs 3.93 lakh crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-amc-records-pat-of-rs-121-crore-in-q3-aum-rises-to-rs-393-lakh-crore/1666551</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666551</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operations jumped by 24% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 517 crore during the quarter.

Total revenue from operations jumped by 24% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 517 crore during the quarter. Profit before tax stood at Rs 178 crore in Q3 FY26, down 19% from Rs 221 crore in Q3 FY25. The total assets under management (AUM) for UTI Asset Management Company stood at Rs 23,14,828 crore at the end of December 2025. As on 31 December 2025, UTI MF's quarterly average assets under management (QAAUM) was Rs 3,93,809 crore. Equity assets (active + passive) contributed 70% to UTI MF's total average AUM. The ratio of equity-oriented QAAUM to non-equity-oriented QAAUM stood at 70:30, compared to the industry ratio of 61:39. The total number of live folios as of 31 December 2025 was 1.38 crore. Gross inflow mobilized through SIP for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 stood at Rs 2,387 crore. SIP AUM as of the quarter-end stood at Rs 44,752 crore, reflecting a growth of 16.64% compared to 31 December 2024. Digital purchase transactions increased to 53.83 lakh for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, marking a 5.61% rise compared to the same quarter in 2024. Imtaiyazur Rahman, managing director & chief executive officer, UTI AMC, said: "We are pleased to announce that during our Q3 FY25-26, we have continued to record steady growth in AUM as well as gross SIP inflows. This performance reflects the growing participation and trust of retail investors, supported by our focus on product innovation and digital initiatives. With effect from 1st February 2026, Mr. Vetri Subramaniam will function as the MD & CEO of UTI AMC Ltd." UTI Asset Management Company (UTI AMC) is the investment manager to UTI Mutual Fund. UTI AMC is registered as Portfolio Manager with SEBI and through its subsidiary it acts as Fund manager for AIF, among others. It also has a countrywide network of branches along with a diversified distribution network. The scrip advanced 2.62% to currently trade at Rs 1060.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UTIAssetManagementCompanyLtd._39082514_23412.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waaree Energies rallies after Q3 PAT climbs 116% YoY to Rs 1,062 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waaree-energies-rallies-after-q3-pat-climbs-116-yoy-to-rs-1062-crore/1666549</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666549</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations soared 118.81% YoY to Rs 7,565.05 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations soared 118.81% YoY to Rs 7,565.05 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 1,763.80 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a growth of 155.69% from Rs 689.81 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 294.78 crore during the quarter. EBITDA for the quarter stood at Rs 1,928.15 crore, registering a growth of 167.16% compared with Rs 721.73 crore in Q3 FY25. The EBITDA margin improved significantly to 25.49% in Q3 FY26 from 20.88% in the corresponding quarter last year. During the quarter, the company achieved module production of 3.51 GW, driven by strong operational execution. Cell production stood at 0.75 GW in Q3 FY26. On a nine-month basis, Waaree Energies’ consolidated net profit jumped 112.27% YoY to Rs 2,650.21 crore, while revenue increased 72.94% YoY to Rs 18,056.52 crore in 9M FY26 compared with the same period last year. Amit Paithankar, Whole Time Director & CEO, Waaree Energies, said, “Waaree Energies has delivered another exceptional quarter, with Q3 FY26 marking record revenue and profitability. Over the nine months, we have achieved significant growth in both topline and EBITDA, reflecting the resilience of our business model and the trust our customers place in us. I am pleased to share that Waaree is First Indian Manufacturer to achieve 1 GW+ of module production and sales in single month with 52 modules produced per minute. We have secured a record order inflow, strengthening our order book of around Rs 60,000 crore ensuring sustained visibility for the years ahead. Also, we have secured bankable PPAs backed by land and connectivity. We are accelerating our transformation into an integrated clean energy solutions provider by strengthening adjacencies across BESS, inverter, transformer, Renewable Power Infrastructure and green hydrogen electrolyser creating a resilient and future-ready portfolio. Additionally, our recent acquisition strengthens our supply chain by ensuring secure and fully traceable access to polysilicon, supporting Waaree’s rapidly expanding manufacturing footprint in the U.S.A. and global markets. With disciplined execution, prudent capital allocation and strategic diversification, we are confident of closing FY26 on a strong note. Waaree is on track to achieve its EBITDA target of Rs 5,500–6,000 crore while creating long-term value for stakeholders and contributing meaningfully to India’s clean energy transition.” Mumbai-based Waaree Energies is a renewable energy company. It offers innovative solar solutions, including panel manufacturing, EPC services, project development, and rooftop systems.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WaareeEnergiesLtd_42747859_39763.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Consumer Care jumps on strong Q3 earnings ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-consumer-care-jumps-on-strong-q3-earnings/1666532</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666532</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net profit rose 83.2% YoY to Rs 46.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 25.3 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net profit rose 83.2% YoY to Rs 46.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 25.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 32.7% YoY to Rs 306.1 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 230.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross profit stood at Rs 183.6 crore in Q3 FY26, up 53.1% YoY from Rs 119.9 crore. Gross margin improved sharply to 60.0% of sales from 52.0% a year ago. Profit before tax stood at Rs 56.4 crore in Q3 FY26, up 81.4% vs year-ago quarter. EBITDA stood at Rs 56.9 crore in Q3 FY26, surging 109.5% YoY from Rs 27.2 crore. EBITDA margin expanded to 18.6% from 11.8% in Q3 FY25. Employee costs rose 32.1% YoY to Rs 35.8 crore. Advertisement and sales promotion expenses increased 36.7% YoY to Rs 46.9 crore, reflecting higher brand spends. Other expenses grew 25.6% YoY to Rs 43.9 crore. Bajaj Consumer Care operates in the personal care segment with a focus on hair oils and related products. The company’s portfolio includes established brands such as Bajaj Almond Drops Hair Oil and Nomarks, and it has expanded over time into a broader range of personal care products, including skincare, lotions, soaps and haircare items.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajConsumerCareLtd_68216011_38716.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Stainless gains after Q3 PAT climbs 27% YoY to Rs 829-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-stainless-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-27-yoy-to-rs-829-cr/1666548</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666548</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax jumped 24.98% YoY to Rs 1,112.33 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional items and tax jumped 24.98% YoY to Rs 1,112.33 crore during the quarter. Exceptional items for the period included labour code charges amounting to Rs 30.05 crore. In Q3 FY26, EBITDA stood at Rs 1,408 crore, recording the growth of 17% compared with Rs 1,208 crore posted in Q3 FY25. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit jumped 7.63% to Rs 665.85 crore on 5.63% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 10,632.35 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sales volumes climbed 11% YoY to 650 metric tonnes (MT) in Q3 FY26. The domestic market contributed 95% of total revenue, while exports accounted for the remaining 5% during the quarter. Meanwhile, the company's board declared a interim dividend of Re 1 per equity share of face value Rs 2 for FY26. The record date has been fixed as Thursday, 29 January 2026. The dividend will be paid on or before 19 February 2026. Jindal Stainless is India’s leading stainless-steel manufacturer of stainless steel flat products, in austenitic, ferritic, martensitic and duplex grades in India used in a variety of industries like automobile, railways, construction, consumer goods, etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalStain_15230115440_24610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/motilal-oswal-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1666607</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666607</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 21 January 2026.

Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 21 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund management Structure Revised Fund management Structure Motilal Oswal Midcap Fund Niket Shah Ajay Khandelwal Ajay Khandelwal Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma Motilal Oswal Balanced Advantage Fund Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Niket Shah Sandeep Jain Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Sandeep Jain Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma Motilal Oswal Flexi Cap Fund Niket Shah Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma Motilal Oswal Small Cap Fund Ajay Khandelwal Niket Shah Ajay Khandelwal Bhalchandra Shinde Motilal Oswal Large Cap Fund Ajay Khandelwal Niket Shah Atul Mehra Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Motilal Oswal Multi Cap Fund Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Niket Shah Sandeep Jain Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Sandeep Jain Motilal Oswal Business Cycle Fund Ajay Khandelwal Niket Shah Atul Mehra Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma Motilal Oswal Digital India Fund Varun Sharma Niket Shah Atul Mehra Varun Sharma Atul Mehra Motilal Oswal Arbitrage Fund Vishal Ashar Niket Shah Atul Mehra Vishal Ashar Atul Mehra Motilal Oswal Innovation Opportunities Fund Niket Shah Atul Mehra Varun Sharma Atul Mehra Varun Sharma Motilal Oswal Consumption Fund Aliasgar Shakir Niket Shah Varun Sharma Varun Sharma Aliasgar Shakir

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sundaram Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sundaram-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1666527</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666527</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 21 January 2026.

Sundaram Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 21 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager New Fund Manager Sundaram Infrastructure Advantage Fund Clyton Richard Fernandes Siddarth Mohta Sundaram Dividend Yield Fund Clyton Richard Fernandes Shalav Saket (Overseas Investments) Siddarth Mohta Shalav Saket (Overseas Investments)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty tad above 25,300 level; PSU bank shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-tad-above-25300-level-psu-bank-shares-advance/1666523</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666523</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in the morning trade, tracking a rally in global markets amid improved investor sentiment.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in the morning trade, tracking a rally in global markets amid improved investor sentiment. The Nifty traded a tad above the 25,300 level. PSU bank stocks advanced after declining in the previous three trading sessions. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 458.54 points or 0.56% to 82,368.17. The Nifty 50 index rose 150.10 points or 0.60% to 25,306.55. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 1.08% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.04%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,870 shares rose and 838 shares fell. A total of 197 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC (up 0.24%), Adani Energy Solutions (up 3.23%), Alivus Life Sciences (down 0.78%), APL Apollo Tubes (up 3.71%), Adani Total Gas (up 2.18%), Bandhan Bank (up 1.20%), BlueStone Jewellery and Lifestyle (up 5.41%), Borana Weaves (up 3.23%), Computer Age Management Services (up 1.83%), Cigniti Technologies (up 4.27%), Coforge (up 2.91%), Cyient (up 0.24%), DLF (down 0.13%), Go Digit General Insurance (up 1.73%), Gujarat State Petronet (up 1.87%), Home First Finance Company India (up 0.09%), Ideaforge Technology (up 0.97%), Indian Bank (up 2.36%), InterGlobe Aviation (up 1.18%), Infobeans Technologies (up 10.04%), Le Travenues Technology (down 2.13%), Mphasis (up 2.99%), Orient Electric (up 2.88%), Premier Energies (up 2.60%), Radico Khaitan (up 1.02%), Steel Strips Wheels (up 2.33%), Syngene International (up 0.61%), Tanla Platforms (up 1.67%), Ujjivan Small Finance Bank (up 3.60%), V‑Mart Retail (up 0.54%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 3.37%), Zensar Technologies (up 2.71%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index advanced 2.54% to 9,002.55. The index rose 2.11% after declining over the previous three trading sessions. Bank of India (up 4.61%), Punjab & Sind Bank (up 2.63%), Canara Bank (up 2.58%), Bank of Baroda (up 2.47%), Indian Bank (up 1.95%), Union Bank of India (up 1.92%), State Bank of India (up 1.86%), UCO Bank (up 1.36%), Punjab National Bank (up 1.33%) and Indian Overseas Bank (up 1.22%) rose. Stocks in Spotlight: Dr Reddy’s Laboratories rose 5.50%. The company reported a 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1209.8 crore despite a 4.4% jump in revenue to Rs 8,716.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Eternal shed 0.99%. The company reported a 72.88% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 102 crore on a 201.85% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 16,315 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HPCL Q3 PAT jumps 35% YoY to Rs 4,072 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hpcl-q3-pat-jumps-35-yoy-to-rs-4072-cr/1666484</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666484</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company's total income (excluding excise duty) rose 5.23% YoY to Rs 1,15,740.02 crore during the December 2025 quarter.

The company's total income (excluding excise duty) rose 5.23% YoY to Rs 1,15,740.02 crore during the December 2025 quarter. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 5,412.68 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of 34.96% compared to the same quarter last year. The gross refining margin (GRMs) jumped to US $8.85 per barrel in Q3 FY26 from US $6.01 per barrel in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, HPCL’s refineries recorded a crude throughput of 6.38 million metric tonnes (MMT) in Q3 FY26, representing a 1.39% growth over 6.47 MMT in Q3 FY25. The company’s Q3 FY26 sales, including exports, stood at 13.34 MMT, registering a 3.7% year-on-year increase, while domestic sales grew 3.1%. Combined sales of petrol (MS) and diesel (HSD) reached 8.07 MMT, up 2.6% YoY, and total LPG sales (domestic and non-domestic) rose 8.9% to 2.52 MMT. Pipeline throughput during the quarter was 6.24 MM. On the margins front, the operating margin improved to 4.34% in Q3 FY26 from 3.76% in Q3 FY25. Similarly, the net profit margin rose to 3.27%, up from 2.54% in the corresponding quarter of the previous fiscal year. Capital expenditure in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 4,976 crore, taking cumulative capex for the first nine months of FY26 to Rs 11,094 crore. The spending was focused on strengthening refining and marketing infrastructure, including investments in subsidiaries and joint ventures to add capacities, develop new business lines and improve operating efficiencies. Under its network expansion and outreach initiatives, the company commissioned 321 retail outlets in Q3 FY26, taking the total network to 24,572 outlets. It also added five new LPG distributors during the quarter, raising the total to 6,389. In the city gas distribution (CGD) segment, the company laid 793 inch-km of steel pipelines and 194 km of MDPE pipelines in Q3 FY26, taking cumulative lengths to 14,026 inch-km and 4,593 km, respectively, and added 12,457 domestic PNG connections, with the total reaching 1,45,867. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation is mainly engaged in the business of refining of crude oil and marketing of petroleum products, production of hydrocarbons as well as providing services for management of E&P Blocks. Shares of Hindustan Petroleum Corporation shed 0.12% to Rs 428.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HPCL_59291502793_2305.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zydus Lifesciences rises after launching nivolumab biosimilar]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zydus-lifesciences-rises-after-launching-nivolumab-biosimilar/1666483</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666483</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The product is available in 100 mg and 40 mg strengths, priced at Rs 28,950 and Rs 13,950 respectively.

The product is available in 100 mg and 40 mg strengths, priced at Rs 28,950 and Rs 13,950 respectively. The company said the prices are approximately one-fourth of the reference drug. According to the company, the lower pricing is expected to improve affordability and reduce the overall cost of immunotherapy, with potential benefits for more than 5 lakh patients. The availability of two dosage strengths is intended to help clinicians optimise dosing and minimise drug wastage, which is a key cost factor in immuno-oncology treatments. Zydus stated that Tishtha has been developed and manufactured in India, with an emphasis on ensuring consistent and long-term availability for patients who require therapy over multiple treatment cycles. The company highlighted affordability, consistency of supply, and reach as critical factors influencing access to modern cancer therapies. Zydus Lifesciences is a global life sciences company with operations across pharmaceuticals, consumer wellness, and medical technology. It posted a 38.12% YoY rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,258.6 crore in Q2 FY26, while revenue grew 18.07% to Rs 6,037.9 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CadilaHealth_93490673476_20883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>