<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RACL Geartech Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/racl-geartech-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678009</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678009</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Anuroop Packaging Ltd, Precision Wires India Ltd, Bharat Seats Ltd and Pavna Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 16 February 2026.

Anuroop Packaging Ltd, Precision Wires India Ltd, Bharat Seats Ltd and Pavna Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 16 February 2026. RACL Geartech Ltd soared 18.36% to Rs 1422.6 at 12:01 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 51815 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12005 shares in the past one month. Anuroop Packaging Ltd spiked 15.65% to Rs 12.12. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.69 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9324 shares in the past one month. Precision Wires India Ltd surged 15.04% to Rs 300.9. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 4.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35206 shares in the past one month. Bharat Seats Ltd jumped 14.96% to Rs 187.5. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 68651 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12190 shares in the past one month. Pavna Industries Ltd rose 11.82% to Rs 24.88. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 37043 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 20089 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RACLGeartech_62161473686_1194.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EFC (I) Q3 PAT jumps 54% YoY to Rs 62 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/efc-i-q3-pat-jumps-54-yoy-to-rs-62-cr/1678008</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678008</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 82.30 crore in Q3 FY26, up by 57.45% from Rs 52.27 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 82.30 crore in Q3 FY26, up by 57.45% from Rs 52.27 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 111.6 crore in December 2025 quarter, up 20.45%, compared with Rs 92.6 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin declined to 41.4% in Q3 FY26 as against 52.3% in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 50.25% to Rs 194.18 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. During the quarter, cost of raw materials & components consumed stood at Rs 125.99 crore, up 87.45% YoY, while employee benefits expense was at Rs 12.83 crore, up 61.18% YoY. On segmental front, revenue from rental stood at Rs 135.08 crore (up 40.22% YoY), revenue from interior stood at Rs 135.08 crore (up 13.49% YoY) and revenue from furniture stood at Rs 15.47 crore (up 16.14% YoY), during the quarter. Umesh Kumar Sahay, chairman & MD of EFC (I), said, “Our Q3 FY26 performance reflects steady execution and the growing acceptance of our integrated workspace ecosystem. With nine-month profitability already surpassing FY25 levels, we remain confident about sustaining growth momentum. The leasing business continues to remain strong. We now operate across 11 cities with more than 73,000 seats under management, serving 720+ clients with occupancy above 90%. Our Interiors division delivered strong growth in Q3, while the Furniture business saw sharp expansion over nine months, highlighting the effectiveness of our unified workspace solutions strategy. A key focus area this year has been successful completion of our NCLT-approved merger with “Whitehills Interior Limited” which marks an important milestone in our strategic growth journey. Our Furniture division has also demonstrated remarkable progress as “Ek Design Industries Limited” achieved major milestones by securing multiple certifications from TÜV-NORD, a globally recognized technical inspection and certification organization based in Germany. As we move ahead, our focus remains unwavering, to create value through innovation, operational excellence, and a unified service model that transforms workplaces for the future”. EFC (I) is a real estate-as-a-service company engaged in providing managed office spaces, interior designing and furniture manufacturing. Shares of EFC (I) fell 3.11% to Rs 260 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AmaniTradExp_85433749601_1690.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KFin Tech climbs after Q3 PAT rises 2% YoY to Rs 92 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kfin-tech-climbs-after-q3-pat-rises-2-yoy-to-rs-92-cr/1678005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678005</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax rose 9.56% YoY to Rs 133.76 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before exceptional items and tax rose 9.56% YoY to Rs 133.76 crore in Q3 FY26. The company reported exceptional loss of Rs 8.55 crore due to the impact of the new labour code. EBITDA stood at Rs 151.62 crore, up 16.1% YoY, EBITDA margin reduced to 40.9% as against 45.0% in Q3 FY25. Revenue from value added services (VAS) stood at Rs 25.20 crore, registering the growth of 11.5% YoY. Asset under management (AUM) jumped 30.9% YoY to Rs 1,80,000 crore. Cash and Cash equivalents stood at Rs 507.27 crore as on 31st December 2025. Sreekanth Nadella, managing director and CEO, KFin Technologies, said, “KFintech continues to deliver yet another strong quarter, reinforcing the strength of our diversified business model amidst uncertain global macro environment. We witnessed strong growth in revenue and profitability across our line of businesses, supported by new deal wins, differentiated service excellence, and strong operational control. During the quarter, we have made significant strides in our joint efforts to integrate with Ascent Fund Services and have seen fast progress in terms of business synergies. It is exciting to see Ascent’s flagship EKYC, AML, CFT compliance platform, “OneConstellation”, being selected by one of the largest multinational banks as their global investor onboarding and compliance platform, reinforcing Ascent’s commitment to combine fund administration with institutional-grade RegTech infrastructure. KFintech’s maiden pension administration platform deal from one of the largest banks in the Philippines validates our multi-geography strategy and platform strength. As we look forward, we remain focused on our integration plan, disciplined execution, harnessing technology to enhance operating leverage, and capturing emerging opportunities across geographies to deliver sustainable growth, profitability, and cash flows for all stakeholders. KFin Technologies (KFintech) is a leading technology-driven financial services platform. The company provides services and solutions to asset managers and corporate issuers across asset classes in India and provides several investor solutions, including transaction origination and processing for mutual funds and private retirement schemes to global asset managers across 18 jurisdictions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KFinTechnologiesLtd_30241335_73556.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Earkart bags Rs 4-cr government order via GeM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/earkart-bags-rs-4-cr-government-order-via-gem/1678004</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678004</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to the company, the order pertains to the supply of BTE hearing aids.

According to the company, the order pertains to the supply of BTE hearing aids. The contract is a one-time order and is expected to contribute positively to the company’s revenue during the execution period. Earkart manufactures and distributes modern hearing aids and related accessories at affordable prices across India. Along with its own manufactured hearing aids, the company also trades in hearing aids, parts, and accessories of other brands, both domestic and international. In addition, Earkart offers products such as adjustable foldable walkers and Multi-Sensory Integrated Educational Development (MSIED) and Teaching Learning Material (TLM) kits to support the mobility and daily needs of physically challenged individuals. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 43.11 crore and a net profit of Rs 6.88 crore for the year ended 31 March 2025. The counter slipped 1.99% to Rs 150 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EarkartLimited_52328300_95537.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Easy Trip Planners Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/easy-trip-planners-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1678003</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678003</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Natco Pharma Ltd, Cartrade Tech Ltd, KFin Technologies Ltd and Engineers India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 16 February 2026.

Natco Pharma Ltd, Cartrade Tech Ltd, KFin Technologies Ltd and Engineers India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 16 February 2026. Easy Trip Planners Ltd soared 11.95% to Rs 7.4 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 34.75 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11.75 lakh shares in the past one month. Natco Pharma Ltd surged 8.70% to Rs 893.65. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 12.11 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 40895 shares in the past one month. Cartrade Tech Ltd spiked 7.51% to Rs 2083.45. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 41903 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 31425 shares in the past one month. KFin Technologies Ltd spurt 6.27% to Rs 1028.8. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.04 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35506 shares in the past one month. Engineers India Ltd added 6.07% to Rs 214.1. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 30.9 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.66 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EasyTripPlanners_83237855.6888425_74649.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index speculative shorts edge lower]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-speculative-shorts-edge-lower/1677999</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677999</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index speculators marginally reduced net short positions, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

US dollar index speculators marginally reduced net short positions, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of US dollar index futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 729 contracts in the data reported through February 10, 2026, showing a decrease of 123 net short positions compared to the previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI tightens capital market exposure norms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-tightens-capital-market-exposure-norms/1678000</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678000</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has notified Commercial Banks – Credit Facilities Amendment Directions, 2026, updating norms for how banks extend credit to stockbrokers and other capital market intermediaries.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has notified Commercial Banks – Credit Facilities Amendment Directions, 2026, updating norms for how banks extend credit to stockbrokers and other capital market intermediaries. Banks must provide credit to SEBI regulated stockbrokers and similar intermediaries only on a fully secured basis. Collateral for such credit can include cash, government or eligible securities, immovable property and other approved financial assets, but partial unsecured guarantees or promoter only guarantees will no longer suffice. Bank guarantees issued in favour of exchanges or clearing houses must be backed by at least 50 percent collateral, of which 25 percent must be in cash, and equity shares accepted as collateral will attract a minimum 40 percent haircut for prudential valuation. RBI has tightened guidelines that govern lending activities of banks to capital market intermediaries (CMIs) such as brokers, mandating that all credit facilities to CMIs shall be provided on a fully secured basis. This indicates that for a bank to provide a Rs 100 loan to a broker, the broker must provide collateral equalling that amount to the bank. The RBI has updated limits on loans against capital market securities, directly impacting retail and institutional borrowing. Loans against listed shares and convertible debt are capped at 60% loan-to-value (LTV). Central bank noted that banks cannot fund proprietary trading by brokers. Loans against mutual funds, ETFs, REITs, and InvITs are capped at 75% LTV. Loans against debt mutual funds capped at 85% LTV. Loans against eligible securities are limited to Rs. 1 crore per individual borrower. Loans up to Rs. 25 lakh will be allowed for secondary market share purchases, while banks may also finance IPO, FPO, and ESOP subscriptions up to Rs. 25 lakh.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/debt-loan-credit-money-financial-problem-concept-picture-id_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Banks allowed to finance acquisitions up to 20% of their eligible capital base, says RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/banks-allowed-to-finance-acquisitions-up-to-20-of-their-eligible-capital-base-says-rbi/1677998</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677998</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian lenders will be allowed to finance acquisitions up to 20% of their eligible capital base, the Reserve Bank of India said in its final rules following a ‌review of ⁠bank ⁠exposure to capital markets.

Indian lenders will be allowed to finance acquisitions up to 20% of their eligible capital base, the Reserve Bank of India said in its final rules following a ‌review of ⁠bank ⁠exposure to capital markets. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI), has issued amended directions on capital market exposure and acquisition financing, introducing tighter eligibility norms, lending caps, and borrower requirements. The central bank noted that banks are permitted to extend acquisition finance for strategic stake purchases. However, total bank funding is capped at 75% of the deal value, ensuring that acquiring entities retain meaningful skin in the game. Acquiring companies must contribute at least 25% equity from their own funds. Minimum net worth of Rs. 500 crore is mandatory to access acquisition finance. Listed acquirers must report profits in the last three consecutive years. Unlisted acquirers must hold a BBB- or higher credit rating.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 149 pts; pharma shares in demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-149-pts-pharma-shares-in-demand/1677994</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677994</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest gains in mid-morning trade, recovering from early losses amid volatile conditions as value buying in select sectors lent support.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest gains in mid-morning trade, recovering from early losses amid volatile conditions as value buying in select sectors lent support. The Nifty traded above the 25,500 level. Pharma shares advanced after declining in the previous two trading sessions. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 149.12 points or 0.18% to 82,775.88. The Nifty 50 index rose 58 points or 0.23% to 25,528.40. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.28% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index shed 0.20%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,628 shares rose and 2,364 shares fell. A total of 198 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves fell to $717.6 billion as of February 6, 2026, dropping by $6.71 billion, data from the Reserve Bank of India showed. Meanwhile, data showed a dip in foreign currency assets (FCAs), which declined by $7.66 billion to $570.05 billion during the week. Gold holdings also recorded a sharp drop by $14.2 billion to $123.47 billion. Meanwhile, Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) decreased by $132 million to $18.82 billion. India’s reserve tranche position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) edged down by $32 million to $4.71 billion. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index rose 0.85% to 22,382.50. The index shed 0.23% over the previous two trading sessions. J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals (up 5.43%), Torrent Pharmaceuticals (up 5.26%), Aurobindo Pharma (up 1.93%), Biocon (up 1.43%), Alkem Laboratories (up 1.21%), Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (up 1.15%), Cipla (up 0.9%), Mankind Pharma (up 0.85%), Lupin (up 0.81%) and Zydus Lifesciences (up 0.67%) jumped. Stocks in Spotlight: Tenneco Clean Air India declined 3.69% after the company’s consolidated net profit dropped 5.21% to Rs 118.68 crore despite 14.23% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1285.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Natco Pharma surged 12.03% after the company received approval for Semaglutide from Central Drug Standard Control Organization (CDSCO) to manufacture and market generic Semaglutide Injection in India. HFCL shed 0.60%. The company announced that it has secured an export order worth approximately $4.67 million (around Rs 42.34 crore) from a reputed international customer for the supply of optical fiber cables. Global Markets: Asian shares consolidated recent gains on Monday amid thin trading due to the Lunar New Year holiday, while weak economic data from Japan weighed on sentiment in that market. Markets in China, South Korea, Taiwan, and the United States were closed, keeping activity in currencies, commodities, and bond markets largely subdued. Japan reported that its economy grew just 0.1% on an annualized basis in the December quarter, much lower than expectations, mainly due to lower government spending. The weak data highlights the challenges facing Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and may strengthen the case for additional government spending to support growth. Wall Street markets were mostly steady on Friday after January inflation data came in largely in line with expectations. The S&P 500 ended flat at 6,836.17 points. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.2%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average edged up 0.1% to 49,500.93 points. Data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that consumer prices rose 0.2% in January compared to the previous month and increased 2.4% compared to a year earlier. The inflation numbers offered only limited support to stocks, as hopes of lower interest rates were offset by ongoing concerns about the impact of artificial intelligence on businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Desco Infratech spurts on bagging Rs 40-cr power & solar orders ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/desco-infratech-spurts-on-bagging-rs-40-cr-power-solar-orders/1677993</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677993</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has secured an order from KP Energy for cable laying with digging work in Gujarat.

The company has secured an order from KP Energy for cable laying with digging work in Gujarat. The contract value stands at Rs 1.09 crore and will be executed as per the terms of the contract. The order was awarded by a domestic entity, and there is no promoter or group interest involved. Additionally, Desco Infratech has been awarded a large EPC supply and services contract by Sun Drops Energia valued at Rs. 39.34 crore. This domestic order will also be executed as per contract terms and does not involve any related party transaction. With these orders, Desco Infratech continues to strengthen its presence in the power and solar infrastructure sectors. Desco Infratech is an infrastructure company focused on engineering, planning, & construction, particularly in city gas distribution, renewable energy, water, and power sectors. On a full-year basis, the company's net profit surged 172.9% to Rs 9.06 crore on a 102.3% rise in revenue to Rs 59.45 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DescoInfratechLtd_59821997_94075.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI’s tighter lending norms rattle capital market stocks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbis-tighter-lending-norms-rattle-capital-market-stocks/1677988</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677988</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty Capital Markets index declined 2.02% to 4,691.80, reflecting broad weakness across capital market stocks.

The Nifty Capital Markets index declined 2.02% to 4,691.80, reflecting broad weakness across capital market stocks. BSE plunged 7.22%, while Angel One fell 4.57% and Groww declined 3.12%. Multi Commodity Exchange of India slipped 2.63% and Nuvama Wealth Management dropped 2.33%. UTI Asset Management Company lost 0.87%, 360 One WAM edged down 0.28%, and Motilal Oswal Financial Services was marginally lower by 0.04%. The RBI has tightened rules on loans taken by firms engaged in proprietary trading and those offering leverage to clients, aiming to curb speculative activity. Under the new guidelines, effective April 1, all credit extended to brokers must be fully collateralised. Lending for proprietary trading will be barred, and bank guarantees for such trades must be backed by at least 50% cash collateral. The move comes after a recent hike in Securities Transaction Tax (STT). Market participants fear the tighter regulations could reduce trading volumes, given that proprietary firms account for a significant share of equity options and cash market turnover.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at C.E. Info Systems Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-ce-info-systems-ltd-counter/1677962</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677962</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Natco Pharma Ltd, Ambuja Cements Ltd, RHI Magnesita India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 16 February 2026.

J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Natco Pharma Ltd, Ambuja Cements Ltd, RHI Magnesita India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 16 February 2026. C.E. Info Systems Ltd notched up volume of 1.52 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 53.98 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2820 shares. The stock slipped 5.66% to Rs.1,165.00. Volumes stood at 6144 shares in the last session. J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd saw volume of 76141 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 23.01 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3308 shares. The stock increased 5.55% to Rs.1,997.80. Volumes stood at 3964 shares in the last session. Natco Pharma Ltd witnessed volume of 6.56 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 14.9 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 44074 shares. The stock increased 11.41% to Rs.915.90. Volumes stood at 82829 shares in the last session. Ambuja Cements Ltd recorded volume of 9.85 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 12.57 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 78368 shares. The stock gained 0.12% to Rs.519.90. Volumes stood at 2.05 lakh shares in the last session. RHI Magnesita India Ltd saw volume of 56167 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.65 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 5821 shares. The stock increased 7.37% to Rs.469.30. Volumes stood at 3035 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/C.E.-Info-Systems-Ltd_18725708_75882.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Fabtech Tech secures $7.05 million order from West Africa]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fabtech-tech-secures-705-million-order-from-west-africa/1677959</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677959</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the contract involves the supply, installation, and commissioning of infrastructure for an Oral Solid Dosage (OSD) facility.

According to an exchange filing, the contract involves the supply, installation, and commissioning of infrastructure for an Oral Solid Dosage (OSD) facility. The project is scheduled to be executed within 23–27 months from the date of receipt of the advance payment. The company stated that it received the order on 14 February 2026. Fabtech Technologies Cleanrooms (FTCL) is an India-focused cleanroom infrastructure company, offering in-house manufactured modular partitions, HVAC, and MEP systems for pharma, biotech, semiconductor, and green energy sectors. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 37.83% to Rs 3.32 crore despite of 23.03% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 76.18 crore in H1 FY26 over H1 FY25. The counter shed 0.53% to Rs 160.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FabtechTechnologiesLtd_49634289_93987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Keystone Realtors wins Om Nagar CHS redevelopment in Andheri, Mumbai]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/keystone-realtors-wins-om-nagar-chs-redevelopment-in-andheri-mumbai/1677957</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677957</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project entails the redevelopment of eight housing societies spread across a strategically located land parcel admeasuring approximately 20,569.90 square metres.

The project entails the redevelopment of eight housing societies spread across a strategically located land parcel admeasuring approximately 20,569.90 square metres. Upon completion, the project will rehouse 637 existing members across the societies. The redevelopment is expected to unlock a free sale potential of around 5 lakh sq ft of RERA carpet area, with an estimated gross development value (GDV) of about Rs 1,775 crore, according to the company. The addition strengthens Rustomjee’s footprint in Mumbai’s high-growth western suburbs and aligns with its strategy of building a diversified portfolio across ticket sizes and micro-markets. The project is also in line with the developer’s focus on creating gated communities and integrated lifestyle offerings through large-format redevelopment initiatives. With this project, the company has further augmented its development pipeline for the current financial year, continuing its momentum of adding strategically located redevelopment projects in key urban clusters. Boman Irani, chairman and MD, Keystone Realtors, commented, “We are pleased to have been selected as the preferred Developer for the Om Nagar redevelopment project in Andheri (East), which represents an important addition to Rustomjee’s growing redevelopment portfolio. With a GDV of nearly Rs. 1,775 Crores and a significant development footprint, this project exemplifies our focus on scale, location, and value creation. This project underscores the confidence placed in our ability to execute large-scale, complex urban redevelopment assignments and deliver well-planned communities. The Company is increasing its focus on large society redevelopment, and this project further enhances our presence in a strategically important suburban market. We believe that urban redevelopment is not just about creating real estate, but about revitalizing communities and transforming the way people live in the city. We remain focused on disciplined execution and value creation as we continue to strengthen our project pipeline and pursue sustainable long-term growth.” Keystone Realtors is one of the prominent real estate developers in the Mumbai Metropolitan Region (MMR). The company’s consolidated net profit fell 77.57% to Rs 3.38 crore on 42.64% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 266.17 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Shares of Keystone Realtors fell 5.07% to Rs 466.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KeystoneRealtorsLtd_68331064_42751.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aye Finance lists at par; slips below IPO price]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aye-finance-lists-at-par-slips-below-ipo-price/1677956</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677956</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at 129, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at 129, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 132.75 and a low of 120.60. On the BSE, over 4.37 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. The initial public offer (IPO) of Aye Finance received bids for 4,42,21,288 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.97 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. The issue also consists of offer for sale (OFS) of Rs 300 crore through issuance of 2.33-2.46 crore equity shares. The OFS from investor selling shareholders was Rs 30 crore from Alpha Wave India I LP, Rs 139.763 crore from MAJ Invest Financial Inclusion Fund II K/S, Rs 82.5 crore from CapitalG L P, Rs 30 crore from LGT Capital Invest Mauritius PCC with Cell E/VP and Rs 17.737 crore from Vikram Jetley. The company proposed to utilize the net proceeds from the fresh issue towards augmenting the capital base to meet future capital requirements. Ahead of the IPO, Aye Finance on 8 February 2026, the company raised Rs 454.49 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 3. 52 crore shares at Rs 129 each to 19 anchor investors. Aye Finance incorporated in 1993 is Delhi based non-banking financial company – middle layer (NBFC-ML) focused on providing loans to micro scale micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMEs) across India. It offers a range of small ticket business loans with average ticket size on disbursement at Rs 1.8 lakh for working capital and business expansion needs, against hypothecation of working assets or against security of property to customers across manufacturing, trading, service and allied agriculture sectors. Gross NPA ratio has increased from 2.49% at end March 2023 to 4.21% at end March 2025 and 4.85% end September 2025. The capital adequacy ratio was 32.27%, with Tier I capital comprising 32.27% and Tier II capital comprising Nil at end September 2025. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 64.6 crore and income from operations of Rs 733.83 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AyeFinanceLtd_52229670_71135.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty above 25,500 level; realty shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-above-25500-level-realty-shares-advance/1677955</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677955</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,500 level. Realty shares advanced after declining in the previous two trading sessions. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 162.76 points or 0.20% to 82,789.52. The Nifty 50 index rose 53.80 points or 0.21% to 25,528.95. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap index added 0.14% and the BSE 250 SmallCap index shed 0.15%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,607 shares rose and 2,187 shares fell. A total of 239 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves fell to $717.6 billion as on February 6, 2026, dropping by $6.71 billion, data from the Reserve Bank of India showed. Meanwhile, data showed a dip in foreign currency assets (FCAs) which declined by $7.66 billion to $570.05 billion during the week. Gold holdings also recorded a sharp drop by $14.2 billion to $123.47 billion. Meanwhile, Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) decreased by $132 million to $18.82 billion. India’s reserve tranche position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) edged down by $32 million to $4.71 billion. New listing: Shares of Fractal Analytics were currently trading at Rs 878.10 at 10:15 IST on the BSE, representing a discount of 2.43% as compared with the issue price of Rs 900. The scrip was listed at 900, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 900 and a low of 855.15. On the BSE, over 2.39 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Shares of Aye Finance were currently trading at Rs 122.45 at 10:15 IST on the BSE, representing a discount of 5.08% as compared with the issue price of Rs 129. The scrip was listed at 129, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 132.75 and a low of 120.60. On the BSE, over 3.01 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index rose 0.94% to 831.35. The index fell 2.74% over the previous two trading sessions. SignatureGlobal India (up 5.11%), DLF (up 1.48%), Godrej Properties (up 1.23%), Lodha Developers (up 0.98%), Oberoi Realty (up 0.54%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.33%), Phoenix Mills (up 0.27%), Anant Raj (up 0.26%) rose. Stocks in Spotlight: Shakti Pumps India slumped 9.18% after its consolidated net profit declined 69.53% to Rs 31.70 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 104.05 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Titagarh Rail Systems fell 1.81% after its consolidated net profit tanked 23.48% to Rs 48.03 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.77 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HFCL secures $4.67 million export order for optical fiber cables]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hfcl-secures-467-million-export-order-for-optical-fiber-cables/1677954</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677954</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to a regulatory filing, the order entails the supply of optical fiber cables in line with customer specifications.

According to a regulatory filing, the order entails the supply of optical fiber cables in line with customer specifications. The contract is scheduled to be executed by May 2026. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It also confirmed that the contract does not fall under the category of related-party transactions, in line with regulatory norms. HFCL is a diversified telecom infrastructure enabler with businesses spanning telecom infrastructure development, system integration, and the manufacture and supply of high-end telecom equipment, optical fiber, and optical fiber cables (OFC). The company reported a 41.04% jump in consolidated profit to Rs 102.37 crore on a 19.65% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,210.79 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HFCL_23392864533_1189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Natco Pharma soars as CDSCO clears diabetes drug Semaglutide ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/natco-pharma-soars-as-cdsco-clears-diabetes-drug-semaglutide/1677952</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677952</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Semaglutide is indicated for the treatment of adults with insufficiently controlled type 2 diabetes mellitus as an adjunct to diet and exercise.

Semaglutide is indicated for the treatment of adults with insufficiently controlled type 2 diabetes mellitus as an adjunct to diet and exercise. The company will launch the product in the India market in March 2026. NATCO Pharma, headquartered in Hyderabad, India, develops, manufactures and distributes generic and branded pharmaceuticals, specialty pharmaceuticals, active pharmaceutical ingredients and crop protection products. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 13.9% to Rs 151.50 crore on 36.3% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 647.30 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Fractal Analytics is off to a flat start]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fractal-analytics-is-off-to-a-flat-start/1677950</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677950</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at 900, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at 900, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 900 and a low of 855.15. On the BSE, over 2.39 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Fractal Analytics was subscribed 2.66 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. The Rs 2,833.9 crore IPO comprised a fresh issue of 11,372,222 equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,023.5 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 20,115,556 equity shares worth Rs 1,810.4 crore at the upper price band of Rs 900. Fractal had stated that it would utilize Rs 264.9 crore from the net fresh issue proceeds to invest in its unit, Fractal USA, for repayment of its borrowings; Rs 57.1 crore for the purchase of laptops; Rs 121.1 crore for setting up new office premises in India; and Rs 355.1 crore for investment in R&D and sales and marketing under Fractal Alpha. The remaining funds had been earmarked for general corporate purposes. Fractal Analytics is an enterprise AI company providing end-to-end artificial intelligence solutions to global enterprises to support data-driven decision-making. With over 25 years of experience, the company operates through Fractal.ai and Fractal Alpha, serving clients across CPG and retail, TMT, healthcare and life sciences, and BFSI, with a customer base that includes several leading global corporations. Ahead of the IPO of Fractal Analytics on 6 February 2026, the company raised Rs 474.99 crore from anchor investors by allotting 52.77 lakh shares at Rs 900 each to 22 anchor investors. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 70.90 crore and sales of Rs 1,559 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FractalAnalyticsLtd_67528280_67414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ola Electric slumps as Q3 revenue drops 55% YoY; net loss narrows to Rs 487 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ola-electric-slumps-as-q3-revenue-drops-55-yoy-net-loss-narrows-to-rs-487-crore/1677947</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677947</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Deliveries stood at 32,680 units in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% YoY from 84,029 units and down 37.9% QoQ from 52,666 units.

Deliveries stood at 32,680 units in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% YoY from 84,029 units and down 37.9% QoQ from 52,666 units. Premium deliveries fell 79.3% YoY to 6,065 units and declined 54.8% QoQ. Mass segment deliveries dropped 51.4% YoY and 32.2% QoQ to 26,612 units. However, cells produced rose sharply to 72,418 units, up 90.2% QoQ from 38,080 units. On a consolidated basis, revenue from operations stood at Rs 470 crore, declining 55.0% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and 31.9% QoQ from Rs 690 crore. Automotive and cell sales dropped 53.1% YoY and 35.5% QoQ to Rs 433 crore. Production-linked incentive income declined 69.4% YoY, though increased 94.7% QoQ to Rs 37 crore. Gross profit came in at Rs 161 crore, down 17.0% YoY and 24.4% QoQ. However, gross margin improved to 34.3%, compared with 30.9% in Q2 FY26 and 18.6% in Q3 FY25. Total operating expenses stood at Rs 432 crore, down 33.9% YoY, but up 3.8% QoQ. R&D expenses rose 124.1% YoY and 8.3% QoQ to Rs 65 crore. SG&A expenses declined 38.1% YoY and 4.4% QoQ, while other operating expenses fell 42.2% YoY but increased 5.6% QoQ. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss stood at Rs 323 crore, widening from Rs 258 crore in Q2 FY26 but improving from Rs 494 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA margin was -68.7%, compared with -37.4% in Q2 FY26 and -47.3% a year ago. Net loss for the quarter stood at Rs 487 crore, widening from Rs 418 crore in Q2 FY26 but narrowing compared with Rs 564 crore in Q3 FY25. Cash flow from operations remained negative at Rs 575 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a negative Rs 255 crore in Q2 FY26 and negative Rs 851 crore in Q3 FY25. Free cash flow stood at negative Rs 781 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with negative Rs 405 crore in Q2 FY26 and negative Rs 1,076 crore in Q3 FY25. In the automotive segment, revenue from operations stood at Rs 467 crore, down 55.3% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and lower by 32.1% QoQ from Rs 688 crore. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss stood at Rs 167 crore, improving significantly from a loss of Rs 373 crore in Q3 FY25 but widening from a loss of Rs 102 crore in Q2 FY26. Adjusted EBITDA margin was -35.8%, broadly in line with -35.7% YoY, but weaker than -14.8% in Q2 FY26. In the cell segment, revenue from operations stood at Rs 9 crore, up from Rs 3 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 4 crore in Q2 FY26, reflecting scaling up of cell operations. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss widened to Rs 39 crore, compared with losses of Rs 8 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 27 crore in Q2 FY26. Adjusted EBITDA margin deteriorated sharply to -228.5%, versus -29.6% YoY and -100.0% QoQ. Ola Electric spokesperson said, "Q3 FY26 marks a structural reset for Ola Electric. We chose to fix the fundamentals by restoring service execution, resetting our cost structure, and deepening vertical integration. The result is a leaner operating model with materially lower breakeven and industry-leading gross margins. With service metrics stabilising and our Gigafactory transitioning into commercial scale deployment, we are positioned to enter the next phase of growth with significantly improved operating leverage." Ola Electric Mobility is India's leading electric vehicle (EV) manufacturer. It specialises in the vertical integration of technology and manufacturing for EVs and their components, including battery cells.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlaElectricMobilityLtd_81720871_75559.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>