<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Consumer price inflation stood at 2.75% in Jan-26 under new series]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/consumer-price-inflation-stood-at-275-in-jan-26-under-new-series/1676063</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676063</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation has released the first update of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) with Base 2024=100.

The Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation has released the first update of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) with Base 2024=100. The item basket and the corresponding weights are based on Household Consumption Expenditure Survey 2023-24. The exercise is being done for enhancing the coverage and representativeness of the inflation measure. Year-on-year inflation rate based on All India Consumer Price Index (CPI) with base year 2024 for the month of January, 2026 over January, 2025 is 2.75% (Provisional). Corresponding inflation rates for rural and urban are 2.73% and 2.77%, respectively. Year-on-year inflation rate based on All India Consumer Food Price Index (CFPI) for the month of January, 2026 over January, 2025 is 2.13% (Provisional). Corresponding inflation rates for rural and urban are 1.96% and 2.44%, respectively. Year-on-year Housing inflation rate for the month of January, 2026 is 2.05% (Provisional)and the corresponding inflation rates for rural and urban are 2.39% and 1.92%, respectively. Detailed data showed that Food and beverages inflation stood at 2.11% while inflation for Personal care, social protection and miscellaneous goods and services was elevated at 19.02%. Inflation for Transport was tepid at 0.09%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/food-vinegar-eat-fruit-52999_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles higher as foreign fund investments lift investor sentiments]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-higher-as-foreign-fund-investments-lift-investor-sentiments/1675990</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675990</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee appreciated 17 paise to settle for the day at 90.61 (provisional) against the US dollar on Thursday, as foreign fund investments lifted investor sentiments.

The Indian rupee appreciated 17 paise to settle for the day at 90.61 (provisional) against the US dollar on Thursday, as foreign fund investments lifted investor sentiments. However, domestic shares ended the session lower as IT stocks extended their slide from the previous session on renewed concerns about the disruption AI start-ups will have on established companies. The benchmark BSE Sensex dropped 558.72 points, or 0.66 percent, to 83,674.92 on its weekly derivatives expiry day. The broader NSE Nifty index fell 146.65 points, or 0.57 percent, to 25,807.20. Rising oil prices on heightened U.S.-Iran tensions also dented investor sentiment. At the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 90.55 against the US dollar, and touched an intraday high of 90.40 and a low of 90.65 during the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper sees modest gains, European equities edge higher]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-sees-modest-gains-european-equities-edge-higher/1675991</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675991</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures are edging up today but overall mood is cautious after the metal hit a one-week high yesterday.

COMEX Copper futures are edging up today but overall mood is cautious after the metal hit a one-week high yesterday. The counter currently trades at $5.98 per pound, up 0.32% on the day. In Asia, Shanghai Composite index closed slightly higher while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index fell 0.86%. Japanese NIKKEI 225 index closed marginally lower after briefly testing 58000 mark. European stocks gained impressively with German and French indices rallying around 1%. The US stocks ended marginally lower in last session. Dow fell 0.1%, the Nasdaq dipped 0.2% and the S&P 500 ended flat. Copper saw good gains in last session but eased in intraday moves and dipped under $6 per pound mark. Modest gains in the US dollar index after testing two-week low are capping Copper.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Currency in circulation jumps 11% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/currency-in-circulation-jumps-11-on-year/1675951</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675951</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation rose 0.5% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 40 lakh crore as on January 31, 2026.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation rose 0.5% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 40 lakh crore as on January 31, 2026. The central bank stated further that the overall reserve money gained 1.2% in the same period to Rs 49.23 lakh crore. Currency in circulation soared 11.1% on a year ago basis compared to 5.3% rise at the same time last year. In the current fiscal year, the currency in circulation rose 7.4% so far while the reserve money has moved up 1.9%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IT selloff drags benchmarks lower; Sensex sheds 559 pts, Nifty holds 25,800]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/it-selloff-drags-benchmarks-lower-sensex-sheds-559-pts-nifty-holds-25800/1675948</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675948</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Benchmark indices closed sharply lower on Thursday, weighed down by intense selling in IT stocks amid rising concerns over AI-led disruption and an uncertain global environment.

Benchmark indices closed sharply lower on Thursday, weighed down by intense selling in IT stocks amid rising concerns over AI-led disruption and an uncertain global environment. Weekly expiry-related volatility in BSE derivatives reinforced the risk-off mood. Sentiment deteriorated further after stronger-than-expected US jobs data tempered hopes of near-term rate cuts. The Nifty regained the 25,800 mark after hitting an intraday low of 25,752.40 in late trade, with technology stocks at the forefront of the decline. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 558.72 points or 0.66% to 83,674.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 146.65 points or 0.57% to 25,807.20. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.46% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.86%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,676 shares rose and 2,530 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.53% to 11.73. Economy: India's retail inflation stood at 2.75% in January 2026 under the new Consumer Price Index (CPI) series with base year 2024=100. The corresponding inflation rates were 2.73% for rural areas and 2.77% for urban areas. This is the first retail inflation released by the government under the new CPI series. Meanwhile, the central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.13% to 6.701 compared with previous session close of 6.710. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.5825 compared with its close of 90.7800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 0.47% to Rs 158,002. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.10% to 96.82. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.05% to 4.170. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement declined 39 cents or 0.56% to $69.01 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently up by 155 points, signaling a strong opening for US stocks today. European market advanced on Thursday as investors awaited for U.K. fourth quarter GDP and industrial production figures. Most Asian market ended higher, buoyed by Japan's post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Japanese stocks extending its post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Media reports noted that Takaichi’s snap-election landslide gives her an unusually strong, multi-year mandate to execute policy, which they view as broadly supportive for Japan’s markets and corporate sector. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day win streak after a better-than-expected January jobs report. The blue-chip index lost 66.74 points, or 0.13%, and closed at 50,121.40. The S&P 500 was nearly flat at 6,941.47. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 0.16% to end at 23,066.47. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000. Strong labor market has reduced the odds for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The jobs report follows weaker-than-expected consumer data released on Tuesday. That report showed that consumer spending in December was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain expected from economists polled by Dow Jones. Stocks in Spotlight: The Nifty IT index declined 5.51% to 33,160.20 amid concerns over artificial intelligence-led disruption and global macro uncertainty. The sharp fall followed the launch of a new artificial intelligence tool by US-based startup Anthropic, which recently introduced a product tailored for corporate legal teams. The sector was also weighed down by stronger-than-expected US jobs data, which dampened expectations of near-term interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve and added to investor caution toward export-oriented technology stocks. Meanwhile, the index is down 7.17% in the two consecutive sessions. Coforge slumped 6.61%, Tech Mahindra declined 6.40%, and Oracle Financial Services Software dropped 6.35%. Infosys and LTIMindtree each slipped 5.97%, while Tata Consultancy Services fell 5.77%. HCL Technologies lost 5.20%, Mphasis declined 4.93%, Wipro was down 4.79%, and Persistent Systems dropped 4.70%. Hindalco Industries fell 0.14%. The company said its wholly owned subsidiary Novelis Inc. has provided an update on the twin fire incidents at its Oswego plant in New York that occurred in September and November 2025. Novelis estimates the total free cash flow impact at $1.3-1.6 billion, which includes repair costs, operational downtime, working capital timing and other related expenses. The company said 70-80% of the free cash flow and adjusted EBITDA impact is expected to be recoverable through insurance, subject to policy terms, conditions and potential coverage disputes. No firm estimate for insurance recovery has been accrued at this stage. The Oswego hot mill is expected to restart by late Q2 calendar 2026. Meanwhile, Novelis reported its Q3 earnings. The Hindalco subsidiary reported a net loss attributable to common shareholders of $160 million, compared with a net income of $110 million in the prior year, Net sales rose 3% YoY to $4.2 billion. Ceigall India gained 1% after the company said its wholly owned subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects, has received a Letter of Award from the National Highways Authority of India for a highway project in Bihar. The bid project cost is approximately Rs 2,160 crore, and the project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). The construction period is 730 days, followed by a 15-year operation and maintenance period. Zydus Lifesciences rose 2.22% after the company announced a settlement agreement with Astellas Pharma Inc. in relation to Myrbetriq (generic name: Mirabegron) in the United States. The company, along with its wholly owned subsidiary Zydus Pharmaceuticals USA, has entered into a settlement that concludes all ongoing patent litigations with Astellas concerning Myrbetriq and Mirabegron. Redtape rose 1.40% after the company reported strong growth in revenue and profitability for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 104.53 crore in Q3 FY26, up 43.05% YoY from Rs 73.07 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit surged 279.56% from Rs 27.54 crore in Q2 FY26. Net sales increased 18.98% YoY to Rs 786.55 crore, compared with Rs 661.05 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue jumped 59.74% from Rs 492.40 crore in Q2 FY26. SJVN rose 2.34% after the company reported a 50.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 224.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 149.03 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations surged 61.2% year-on-year to Rs 1,081.97 crore during the quarter under review, up from Rs 670.99 crore in the corresponding period last year. Zydus Lifesciences rose 2.22% after the company announced a settlement agreement with Astellas Pharma Inc. in relation to Myrbetriq (generic name: Mirabegron) in the United States. Lenskart Solutions surged 10% after the company reported 237.9% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 132.7 crore on a 37.4% rise in revenue to Rs 2,307.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. LG Electronics India slipped 3.17% after the company reported 61.6% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 89.67 crore on a 6.4% fall in net sales to Rs 4,114.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Patanjali Foods rose 0.27%. The company has reported 60.0% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 593.44 crore on a 16.5% increase in net sales to Rs 10,483.71 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Jupiter Wagons slipped 3.59% after its consolidated net profit tanked 35.28% to Rs 62.99 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 97.33 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 13.54% YoY to Rs 890.36 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Bombay Dyeing & Manufacturing Company declined 2.84% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 9.85 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 70.06 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 21.9% year-on-year to Rs 324.02 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concepts-picture-id519261614_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1675943</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675943</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,849.10 a premium of 41.9 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,807.20 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,849.10 a premium of 41.9 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,807.20 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index fell 146.65 points or 0.57% to 25,807.20. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 1.53% to 11.73. Infosys (Infy), Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and HDFC Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Q3 PAT rises 28% YoY to Rs 273 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-forge-q3-pat-rises-28-yoy-to-rs-273-cr/1675944</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675944</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations soared 24.96% YoY to Rs 4,342.93 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations soared 24.96% YoY to Rs 4,342.93 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 462.93 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 347 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 55.72 crore during the quarter, primarily on account of the impact of newly notified labour codes, resulting in higher gratuity and leave liabilities. Total expenses rose 23.79% YoY to Rs 3,918.51 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of material consumed stood at Rs 1,841.79 crore (up 28.02% YoY), finance cost was at Rs 76.64 crore (down 20.13% YoY), and employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 534.56 crore (up 22.56% YoY) during the period under review. Segment-wise, revenue from forgings rose 10.01% to Rs 3,367.09 crore, while the defence segment saw a sharp 102.36% surge to Rs 681.99 crore. The "Other" segment revenue surged 158.84% to Rs 570.06 crore. The operating margin rose to 17.18% in Q3 FY26, down from 17.92% a year ago, while the net profit margin increased to 6.28% from 6.12%. B.N. Kalyani, chairman & managing director of Bharat Forge, said, “The quarterly performance continued to be impacted by the de-stocking in the North American CV market. Standalone revenues were up 7.0% sequentially to Rs 2,084 crores, and EBITDA at Rs 569 crore was up 4.6% QoQ, translating to an EBITDA margin of 27.3%. The performance was aided by the strong growth in the domestic automotive business and execution of the defense order book. Export revenues witnessed a 3% sequential decline, with the auto sector down 13% and industrials showing an 11% increase. In Q3, the company secured new orders worth Rs 2,388 crores, including Rs 1,878 crores in Defence. As of Dec 31st, 2025, the defence order book stood at Rs 11,130 crores. We signed the CQB Carbine contract with the Ministry of Defence for the supply of more than 250,000 units to the Indian armed forces. This order unlocks significant growth opportunities for our small arms vertical within the defence business. In the quarter gone by, JS Autocast (JSA) recorded revenue of Rs 203 Crore and EBITDA of Rs 32 Crore (15.7% EBITDA margin), representing a 22% and 39% YoY jump, respectively. K-Drive Mobility, a supplier of axle assembly across segments, witnessed a muted topline but a sharp jump in their profitability, with EBITDA margins moving up from 3.1% in Q2 FY26 to 5.1% in this quarter. We expect the margin profile to continue to improve over a 3-year time frame. The US & European operations reported modest operating profits despite seasonal weakness in the PV market. Review of the European steel manufacturing footprint is on track, and we expect to have concrete measures in place by the end of this fiscal year. Looking ahead into Q4 FY26 and FY27, it is fair to say that the worst is behind us and things are starting to look up. With both domestic and export markets looking strong across sectors and the commencement of ATAGS execution in H2 FY27, we expect high double-digit top-line growth and a commensurate impact on profitability.” Meanwhile, the board declared an interim dividend of Rs 2 per equity share (face value Rs 2 each). The dividend will be paid on or before 12 March 2026 to shareholders on record as of 18 February 2026. The board also approved the reappointment of B. P. Kalyani and S. E. Tandale as whole-time directors, designated as executive directors, for a further term of five years from 23 May 2026 to 22 May 2031, subject to shareholders’ approval by way of postal ballot. In addition, the board approved the merger of Ferrovia Transrail Solutions (FTSPL), a step-down wholly owned subsidiary, with BF Infrastructure (BFIL), a wholly owned subsidiary and the holding company of FTSPL. Bharat Forge manufactures an extensive array of critical and safety components for several sectors, including automobiles (across commercial & passenger vehicles), oil & gas, aerospace, locomotives, marine, energy (across renewable and non-renewable sources), construction, mining, and general engineering. Shares of Bharat Forge rose 3.33% to close at Rs 1,732.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatForge_36016338711_69.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices end with sharp losses; IT index underperforms; VIX jumps 1.53% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-end-with-sharp-losses-it-index-underperforms-vix-jumps-153/1675942</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675942</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with sharp losses today, amid IT stocks slumped on worries about artificial intelligence-led disruption and fragile global macro outlook.

The key equity benchmarks ended with sharp losses today, amid IT stocks slumped on worries about artificial intelligence-led disruption and fragile global macro outlook. Sentiment further dented due to expiry of BSE derivatives contracts, leading investors to adopt a risk-off stance. The Nifty closed near the 25,800 level after hitting an intraday low of 25,752.40 in the final leg of trade. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 558.72 points or 0.66% to 83,674.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 146.65 points or 0.57% to 25,807.20. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.46% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.86%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.53% to 11.73. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 0.40%), the Nifty Financial Services index (up 0.38%) and the Nifty Metal index (up 0.02%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 5.51%), the Nifty Realty index (down 1.45%) and the Nifty Media index (down 1.31%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Direct Tax Collection : The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.13% to 6.701 compared with previous session close of 6.710. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.5825 compared with its close of 90.7800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 0.47% to Rs 158,002. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.10% to 96.82. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.05% to 4.170. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement declined 39 cents or 0.56% to $69.01 a barrel. Global Markets: European market advanced on Thursday as investors awaited for U.K. fourth quarter GDP and industrial production figures. Most Asian market ended higher, buoyed by Japan’s post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Japanese stocks extending its post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Media reports noted that Takaichi’s snap-election landslide gives her an unusually strong, multi-year mandate to execute policy, which they view as broadly supportive for Japan’s markets and corporate sector. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day win streak after a better-than-expected January jobs report. The blue-chip index lost 66.74 points, or 0.13%, and closed at 50,121.40. The S&P 500 was nearly flat at 6,941.47. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 0.16% to end at 23,066.47. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000. Strong labor market has reduced the odds for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The jobs report follows weaker-than-expected consumer data released on Tuesday. That report showed that consumer spending in December was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain expected from economists polled by Dow Jones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index registers a drop of 5.51%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-registers-a-drop-of-551/1675941</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675941</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index closed down 5.51% at 33160.2 today.

Nifty IT index closed down 5.51% at 33160.2 today. The index has lost 13.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Coforge Ltd fell 6.50%, Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd slipped 6.28% and Tech Mahindra Ltd dropped 5.98%. The Nifty IT index has decreased 21.00% over last one year compared to the 11.98% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Realty index has slid 1.45% and Nifty Media index is down 1.31% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 is down 0.57% to close at 25807.2 while the SENSEX has declined 0.66% to close at 83674.92 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-789114__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market tumble amid IT sell-off; Nifty settles near 25,800 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-tumble-amid-it-sell-off-nifty-settles-near-25800-level/1675940</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675940</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with sharp losses today, amid IT stocks slumped on worries about artificial intelligence-led disruption and fragile global macro outlook.

The key equity benchmarks ended with sharp losses today, amid IT stocks slumped on worries about artificial intelligence-led disruption and fragile global macro outlook. Sentiment further dented due to expiry of BSE derivatives contracts, leading investors to adopt a risk-off stance. The Nifty closed near the 25,800 level after hitting an intraday low of 25,752.40 in the final leg of trade. IT, realty and media stocks tumbled while metal and consumer durables shares managed to advance. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 558.72 points or 0.66% to 83,674.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 146.65 points or 0.57% to 25,807.20. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.46% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.86%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,679 shares rose and 2,532 shares fell. A total of 174 shares were unchanged. Direct Tax Collection Data: The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 5.73% to 33,083.45 amid concerns over artificial intelligence-led disruption and global macro uncertainty. The sharp fall followed the launch of a new artificial intelligence tool by US-based startup Anthropic, which recently introduced a product tailored for corporate legal teams. The sector was also weighed down by stronger-than-expected US jobs data, which dampened expectations of near-term interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve and added to investor caution toward export-oriented technology stocks. Meanwhile, the index tanked 7.39% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Coforge (down 6.48%), Tech Mahindra (down 6.25%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 6.23%), Infosys (down 5.77%) and LTIMindtree (down 5.5%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 5.43%), Mphasis (down 4.83%), HCL Technologies (down 4.82%), Wipro (down 4.7%) and Persistent Systems (down 4.69%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Hindalco Industries rose 0.06%. The company said its wholly owned subsidiary Novelis Inc. has provided an update on the twin fire incidents at its Oswego plant in New York that occurred in September and November 2025. Novelis estimates the total free cash flow impact at $1.3-1.6 billion, which includes repair costs, operational downtime, working capital timing and other related expenses. The company said 70-80% of the free cash flow and adjusted EBITDA impact is expected to be recoverable through insurance, subject to policy terms, conditions and potential coverage disputes. No firm estimate for insurance recovery has been accrued at this stage. The Oswego hot mill is expected to restart by late Q2 calendar 2026. Meanwhile, Novelis reported its Q3 earnings. The Hindalco subsidiary reported a net loss attributable to common shareholders of $160 million, compared with a net income of $110 million in the prior year, Net sales rose 3% YoY to $4.2 billion. SJVN rose 1.18% after the company reported a 50.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 224.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 149.03 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations surged 61.2% year-on-year to Rs 1,081.97 crore during the quarter under review, up from Rs 670.99 crore in the corresponding period last year. Zydus Lifesciences rose 2.22% after the company announced a settlement agreement with Astellas Pharma Inc. in relation to Myrbetriq (generic name: Mirabegron) in the United States. Lenskart Solutions surged 13.67% after the company reported 237.9% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 132.7 crore on a 37.4% rise in revenue to Rs 2,307.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Jupiter Wagons slipped 3.69% after its consolidated net profit tanked 35.28% to Rs 62.99 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 97.33 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 13.54% YoY to Rs 890.36 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Bombay Dyeing & Manufacturing Company declined 2.84% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 9.85 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 70.06 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 21.9% year-on-year to Rs 324.02 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. LG Electronics India slipped 3.04% after the company reported 61.6% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 89.67 crore on a 6.4% fall in net sales to Rs 4,114.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Patanjali Foods shed 0.05%. The company has reported 60.0% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 593.44 crore on a 16.5% increase in net sales to Rs 10,483.71 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Global Market: European market advanced as investors awaited for U.K. fourth quarter GDP and industrial production figures. Most Asian market ended higher on Thursday, buoyed by Japan’s post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Japanese stocks extending its post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Media reports noted that Takaichi’s snap-election landslide gives her an unusually strong, multi-year mandate to execute policy, which they view as broadly supportive for Japan’s markets and corporate sector. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day win streak after a better-than-expected January jobs report. The blue-chip index lost 66.74 points, or 0.13%, and closed at 50,121.40. The S&P 500 was nearly flat at 6,941.47. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 0.16% to end at 23,066.47. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000. Strong labor market has reduced the odds for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The jobs report follows weaker-than-expected consumer data released on Tuesday. That report showed that consumer spending in December was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain expected from economists polled by Dow Jones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI digital payment index continues to edge higher]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-digital-payment-index-continues-to-edge-higher/1675887</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675887</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released latest edition of a composite Reserve Bank of India – Digital Payments Index (RBI-DPI).

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released latest edition of a composite Reserve Bank of India – Digital Payments Index (RBI-DPI). The index captures the extent of digitisation of payments across the country. The index for September 2025 stands at 516.76 as against 493.22 for March 2025 which was announced on July 28, 2025. The increase in RBI-DPI index was driven by significant growth in parameters viz. Payment Performance and Payment Enablers across the country over the period.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/smartphone-2453603__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Redtape jumps after Q3 PAT climbs 43% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/redtape-jumps-after-q3-pat-climbs-43-yoy/1675882</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675882</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 104.53 crore in Q3 FY26, up 43.05% YoY from Rs 73.07 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit stood at Rs 104.53 crore in Q3 FY26, up 43.05% YoY from Rs 73.07 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit surged 279.56% from Rs 27.54 crore in Q2 FY26. Net sales increased 18.98% YoY to Rs 786.55 crore, compared with Rs 661.05 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue jumped 59.74% from Rs 492.40 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax rose 38.78% YoY to Rs 137.35 crore from Rs 98.97 crore in Q3 FY25. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PBT more than tripled, rising 228.82% from Rs 41.77 crore in Q2 FY26. Total expenditure increased 15.07% YoY to Rs 656.58 crore, while rising 42.68% sequentially. Raw material cost declined 14.33% YoY to Rs 12.43 crore, while employee benefit expenses rose 4.51% YoY to Rs 33.83 crore. Redtape manufactures and markets sports and athleisure footwear along with a wide range of garments and accessories, catering to consumers across economy, mid and premium price segments. The company serves diverse age groups and occasions, positioning itself as a one-stop fashion retailer with offerings spanning both casual and formal footwear. Its products are distributed through multiple channels, including e-commerce platforms, the company’s own website and exclusive brand outlets across Tier 1, Tier 2 and Tier 3 cities in India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RedtapeLtd_27371920_76297.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Safari Industries (India) Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/safari-industries-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1675880</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675880</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[KPIT Technologies Ltd, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Birlasoft Ltd and Ashapura Minechem Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 February 2026.

KPIT Technologies Ltd, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Birlasoft Ltd and Ashapura Minechem Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 February 2026. Safari Industries (India) Ltd crashed 6.93% to Rs 1840 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 11704 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1980 shares in the past one month. KPIT Technologies Ltd tumbled 6.66% to Rs 895.2. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62107 shares in the past one month. AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd lost 6.51% to Rs 360.95. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6543 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11698 shares in the past one month. Birlasoft Ltd slipped 6.16% to Rs 436.25. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.06 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 96252 shares in the past one month. Ashapura Minechem Ltd shed 6.16% to Rs 587.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 41881 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 66563 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SafariInds_98893928962_710.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian AI market expected to grow to US$131.31 billion by 2032 from US$7.63 billion in 2024]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-ai-market-expected-to-grow-to-us13131-billion-by-2032-from-us763-billion-in-2024/1675879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675879</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Government stated in a latest update that India is in the first group of AI-ready nations, with systematic progress across all five layers of the AI architecture applications, models, chips, infrastructure and energy.

Government stated in a latest update that India is in the first group of AI-ready nations, with systematic progress across all five layers of the AI architecture applications, models, chips, infrastructure and energy. The report published by CCI (Competition Commission of India) cites that the global market size of AI has increased from USD 103.6 billion in 2020 to USD 288.8 billion in 2024. During the same period, the AI market in India has expanded from USD 2.97 billion to USD 7.63 billion. The Indian AI market is expected to grow to USD 131.31 billion by 2032 at a CAGR of 42.2%. India’s rapid digital transformation is being underpinned by strong foundational infrastructure, with data centres and widespread internet connectivity emerging as critical enablers of cloud adoption, AI deployment, and data-driven governance across the country.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-1549702_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bullion dips below $5100; consolidation seen ahead]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bullion-dips-below-5100-consolidation-seen-ahead/1675881</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675881</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices lost steam and slipped below $5100 per ounce in the Asia electronic trades, with the metal seen consolidating in a narrow range after hitting historical highs of $ 5626.8 on January 29th.

Gold prices lost steam and slipped below $5100 per ounce in the Asia electronic trades, with the metal seen consolidating in a narrow range after hitting historical highs of $ 5626.8 on January 29th. The counter trimmed yesterday’s gains as investors pared back expectations for Federal Reserve policy easing. Strength in the US dollar post stronger-than-expected US labor market data that reduced the likelihood of near-term Federal Reserve rate cuts also pulled the yellow metal lower today. Data released Wednesday showed nonfarm payrolls increased by 130,000 in January, the largest gain in more than a year, while the unemployment rate unexpectedly declined to 4.3%. MCX April 2 delivery futures were down 0.3% at Rs 158211 per 10 grams. More losses can be expected in the yellow metal and other precious metals, following the consolidation phase going on post the historic highs attained late last month. Investors are now awaiting Friday’s US consumer price index report for further insights.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suryalakshmi-cotton-mills-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1675845</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675845</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Khandwala Securities Ltd, Unitech Ltd, Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd and Network People Services Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 February 2026.

Khandwala Securities Ltd, Unitech Ltd, Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd and Network People Services Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 February 2026. Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd crashed 16.31% to Rs 61 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1228 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 694 shares in the past one month. Khandwala Securities Ltd tumbled 11.71% to Rs 18.7. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1553 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5679 shares in the past one month. Unitech Ltd lost 10.58% to Rs 5.58. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 25.68 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.95 lakh shares in the past one month. Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd slipped 9.26% to Rs 332.75. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1942 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1071 shares in the past one month. Network People Services Technologies Ltd shed 8.75% to Rs 1252.95. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3320 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1083 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuryalakCott_55522786721_1952.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade with significant losses; media shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-with-significant-losses-media-shares-tumble/1675843</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675843</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking. Sentiment remained subdued due to the expiry of BSE derivatives contracts and FII selling, prompting a shift toward a risk-off approach. The Nifty hovered below the 25,850 mark. Oil & gas shares tumbled after rallying for four consecutive trading sessions. Media shares declined after advancing in the past three trading sessions. At 14:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 455.46 points or 0.54% to 83,772.58. The Nifty 50 index fell 127.90 points or 0.49% to 25,824.55. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.55% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.67%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,675 shares rose and 2,448 shares fell. A total of 187 shares were unchanged. Direct Tax Collection : The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index declined 1.13% to 1476.70. the index increased 7.4% in the past three trading sessions. Network 18 Media & Investments (down 2.96%), PVR Inox (down 2.86%), Saregama India (down 2.52%), Prime Focus (down 2.41%) and Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 1.97%) were the top losers. Among the other losers were Sun TV Network (down 1.48%), Tips Music (down 1.09%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 1.07%), D B Corp (down 0.84%) and Nazara Technologies (down 0.07%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.01% to 6.709 compared with previous session close of 6.710. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6125 compared with its close of 90.7800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 0.42% to Rs 158,083. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.05% to 96.87. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.17% to 4.179. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 11 cents or 0.16% to $69.51 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Hindalco Industries shed 0.48%. The company said its wholly owned subsidiary Novelis Inc. has provided an update on the twin fire incidents at its Oswego plant in New York that occurred in September and November 2025. Novelis estimates the total free cash flow impact at $1.3-1.6 billion, which includes repair costs, operational downtime, working capital timing and other related expenses. The company said 70-80% of the free cash flow and adjusted EBITDA impact is expected to be recoverable through insurance, subject to policy terms, conditions and potential coverage disputes. No firm estimate for insurance recovery has been accrued at this stage. The Oswego hot mill is expected to restart by late Q2 calendar 2026. Meanwhile, Novelis reported its Q3 earnings. The Hindalco subsidiary reported a net loss attributable to common shareholders of $160 million, compared with a net income of $110 million in the prior year, Net sales rose 3% YoY to $4.2 billion. Jupiter Wagons slipped 3.60% after its consolidated net profit tanked 35.28% to Rs 62.99 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 97.33 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 13.54% YoY to Rs 890.36 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Bombay Dyeing & Manufacturing Company declined 2.32% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 9.85 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 70.06 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 21.9% year-on-year to Rs 324.02 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Abbott India Q3 PAT jumps 4% YoY to Rs 376 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/abbott-india-q3-pat-jumps-4-yoy-to-rs-376-cr/1675842</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675842</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 508.98 crore in Q3 FY26, up 4.38% year on year (YoY).

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 508.98 crore in Q3 FY26, up 4.38% year on year (YoY). Total expenses increased 7.20% to Rs 1,284.82 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,198.44 crore posted in same quarter last year. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 147.31 crore (up 26.88% YoY), employee benefit expense was at Rs 196.07 crore (up 45.58% YoY) and finance cost was at Rs 5.48 crore (up 142.47% YoY) during the period under review. Abbott India is one of the leading multinational pharmaceutical companies in India and sells its products through independent distributors primarily within India. Shares of Abbott India fell 1.06% to currently trade at Rs 26,609.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AbbottIndia_90273760573_90.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IT stocks tumble as AI disruption fears deepen; Nifty IT down over 5%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/it-stocks-tumble-as-ai-disruption-fears-deepen-nifty-it-down-over-5/1675841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675841</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The sharp decline followed the launch of a new artificial intelligence tool by US-based startup Anthropic, which recently introduced a product tailored for corporate legal teams.

The sharp decline followed the launch of a new artificial intelligence tool by US-based startup Anthropic, which recently introduced a product tailored for corporate legal teams. The company, known for its Claude chatbot, said the tool can automate functions such as contract reviews, non-disclosure agreement triage, compliance workflows, legal brief preparation and standardised responses. The development intensified investor concerns about the potential impact of AI automation on outsourcing-driven business models. Among major IT stocks, Coforge declined 6.31%, Oracle Financial Services Software fell 5.65%, and LTIMindtree dropped 5.63%. Infosys lost 5.58%, while Tata Consultancy Services fell 5.39%. Tech Mahindra declined 5.30%, Persistent Systems slipped 4.87%, and Mphasis dropped 4.56%. Wipro fell 4.25%, while HCL Technologies declined 3.99%. The sector was also weighed down by stronger-than-expected US jobs data, which dampened expectations of near-term interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve and added to investor caution toward export-oriented technology stocks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude nears $65 per barrel in Asia]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-nears-65-per-barrel-in-asia/1675840</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675840</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil prices edged higher toward $65 per barrel in early electronic trade on Thursday, as rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran sparked fresh supply concerns.

Oil prices edged higher toward $65 per barrel in early electronic trade on Thursday, as rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran sparked fresh supply concerns. Markets remain alert to the risk of disruptions to Iranian output or key shipping routes amid heightened rhetoric from Washington. US President Donald Trump said talks with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu produced no definitive agreement on the Iran issue, though negotiations with Tehran would continue. Earlier this week, Trump said the US may consider deploying a second aircraft carrier to the Middle East if talks fail, even as indirect US-Iran discussions resumed in Oman. The timing of the next round of talks remains unclear. Meanwhile, OPEC kept its global oil demand growth forecasts unchanged at 1.38 million bpd for 2026 and 1.34 million bpd for 2027, while maintaining its non-OPEC supply outlook. Investors now await the IEA’s monthly report later in the day, which could again point to a global supply surplus. In the domestic market, MCX February crude oil futures slipped below Rs 5,900 per barrel, down 0.34%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-in-morning-picture-id637134984_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>