<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Titan Company Ltd Spikes 2.55%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/titan-company-ltd-spikes-255/1663484</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663484</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Titan Company Ltd rose 2.55% today to trade at Rs 4215.8.

Titan Company Ltd rose 2.55% today to trade at Rs 4215.8. The BSE Consumer Durables index is up 0.62% to quote at 61885.4. The index is up 3.36 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd increased 1.34% and PG Electroplast Ltd added 0.5% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went down 5.28 % over last one year compared to the 8.21% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Titan Company Ltd has added 11.97% over last one month compared to 3.36% gain in BSE Consumer Durables index and 0.57% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 8570 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 27946 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 4264.8 on 07 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 2947.55 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TitanCompany_20146423894_1016.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd Slips 1.23%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-bank-ltd-slips-123/1663485</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663485</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd fell 1.23% today to trade at Rs 950.6.

HDFC Bank Ltd fell 1.23% today to trade at Rs 950.6. The BSE BANKEX index is down 0.82% to quote at 66998.4. The index is up 0.83 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd decreased 0.34% and ICICI Bank Ltd lost 0.2% on the day. The BSE BANKEX index went up 17.49 % over last one year compared to the 8.21% surge in benchmark SENSEX. HDFC Bank Ltd has lost 5.23% over last one month compared to 0.83% gain in BSE BANKEX index and 0.57% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 42898 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 7.23 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 1020.35 on 23 Oct 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 812.13 on 13 Jan 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCBank_24534281400_4987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Banks' supervisory data quality index score improves in Sep 2025 quarter, says RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/banks-supervisory-data-quality-index-score-improves-in-sep-2025-quarter-says-rbi/1663483</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663483</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RBI’s Supervisory Data Quality Index score of scheduled commercial banks has improved to 90.7 in the September 2025 quarter compared to 89.9 in the April-June period, the RBI said on Tuesday.

RBI’s Supervisory Data Quality Index score of scheduled commercial banks has improved to 90.7 in the September 2025 quarter compared to 89.9 in the April-June period, the RBI said on Tuesday. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has created the Supervisory Data Quality Index (sDQI) to measure data quality in terms of accuracy, timeliness, completeness and consistency in submission of returns. The objective of the index is to assess the adherence to the principles enunciated in the RBI's Master Direction on Filing of Supervisory Returns 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR under renewed pressure as dollar stays firm overseas]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-under-renewed-pressure-as-dollar-stays-firm-overseas/1663477</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663477</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee came under renewed pressure after dollar firmed back above 98 mark awaiting US data for further cues on interest rates.

The Indian rupee came under renewed pressure after dollar firmed back above 98 mark awaiting US data for further cues on interest rates. INR opened at Rs 90.20 per dollar and hit a low of 90.23 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee recovered some lost ground, snapping a four-day losing streak and appreciated 12 paise to settle at 90.18 against the American currency. Weak domestic equity markets and geopolitical tensions between the US and Venezuela however capped sharp gains for the domestic unit. Indian shares ended lower on Tuesday to extend losses from the previous session as investors weighed the risk of fresh U.S. tariffs and rising geopolitical tensions. The benchmark S&P/BSE Sensex dropped 376.28 points, or 0.44 percent, to 85,063.34 despite mostly firm cues from global markets. The broader NSE Nifty index fell 71.60 points, or 0.27 percent, to 26,178.70. Foreign investors net sold shares worth Rs 106 crore on Tuesday, while domestic institutional investors added strength to the market, buying shares to the extent of Rs. 1,749 crore, according to exchange provisional data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty indicates flat opening for key indices]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-indicates-flat-opening-for-key-indices/1663473</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663473</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 14.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 14.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 107.63 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,749.35 crore in the Indian equity market on 06 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 3,122.68 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asian market traded mixed, with regional defense stocks snapping two-day winning streak on Wednesday, as investors continued to assess geopolitical risks after the U.S. attack on Venezuela and renewed rhetoric over Greenland. White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt reportedly said on Tuesday that President Donald Trump and his team were considering “a range of options” in order to acquire Greenland — including “utilizing the U.S. Military.” The statement further escalates the Trump administration’s already aggressive rhetoric about Greenland, which the president has long sought to make a part of the United States. U.S. crude futures fell 1.3% to $56.39 per barrel after U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro. Overnight in the United States, stocks advanced as investors appeared to look past the Venezuela operation. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks ended lower for a second straight session on Tuesday as risk sentiment weakened across markets. Sentiment was hit by renewed tariff concerns after US President Donald Trump warned of higher tariffs on India if it failed to curb purchases of Russian oil. Foreign institutional investors also turned net sellers, adding to liquidity pressure. Geopolitical tensions further weighed on sentiment following the arrest of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro, while volatility edged higher. The Nifty 50 settled below the 26,200 mark, dragged down by private bank stocks. In contrast, healthcare and pharmaceutical shares saw buying interest. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 376.28 points or 0.44% to 85,063.34. The Nifty 50 index dropped 71.60 points or 0.27% to 26,178.70. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.81% while the Nifty fell 0.56%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Biocon, Senco Gold, Jubilant Foodworks, Titan Company]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-biocon-senco-gold-jubilant-foodworks-titan-company/1663469</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663469</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 7 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 7 January 2026. Stocks to Watch: Biocon’s subsidiary, Biocon Biologics will introduce three new oncology biosimilars at a US event. Titan Company’s consumer business registered a growth of 40% YoY in Q3FY26. A total of 56 stores (net) were added during the quarter expanding Titan’s combined retail network presence to 3,433 stores. Lodha Developers’ pre sales jumped 25% to Rs 56,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 45,100 crore in Q3 FY25. Collections declined 17% YoY to Rs 35,600 crore in Q3 FY26. Jubilant Foodworks’ consolidated revenue stood at Rs 2,438.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 13.4% YoY. Domino’s recorded a Like-For-Like (LFL) growth of 5%. Senco Gold reported a 51% revenue growth in Q3 FY26, driven by robust performances across its businesses. The retail business reported around 49% growth while SSSG growth stood at 39%. Godrej Consumer Products said that its standalone business is well positioned to deliver double-digit revenue growth for the quarter, underpinned by close to double-digit underlying volume growth (UVG), albeit on a supportive comparator. Personal Care is expected to record mid-single-digit value growth, driven by a marked recovery in the soaps category.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lodha Developers achieves 25% YoY growth in Q3 FY26 pre-sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lodha-developers-achieves-25-yoy-growth-in-q3-fy26-pre-sales/1663468</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663468</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sequentially, the company registered a 23% growth in pre-sales.

Sequentially, the company registered a 23% growth in pre-sales. The growth was supported by strong momentum in sustenance sales, and a significant launch pipeline in Q4 is expected to support the achievement of its annual pre-sales guidance of Rs 21,000 crore. Collections in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 3,560 crore, down 17% YoY but up 2% quarter-on-quarter (QoQ). The company added that collections were lower than Q3 FY25, which had one-off inflows from large land and office sales. Collections are expected to scale up significantly in the coming quarters. On a nine-month basis, the company’s pre-sales rose 14% YoY to Rs 14,640 crore, while collections declined 1% to Rs 9,930 crore in 9M FY26 compared to 9M FY25. The company said that in Q3 FY26, it added five projects with a gross development value (GDV) of Rs 33,800 crore across MMR, NCR, and Bengaluru. This takes total business development in 9M FY26 to Rs 58,800 crore, which is 2.35 times its annual guidance of Rs 25,000 crore. This significant business development is expected to enhance visibility of future growth and support higher profitability in upcoming acquisitions. The company also said its pilot in NCR has commenced with two projects on a joint development basis, reflecting its risk-calibrated approach to capital deployment. NCR is the second-largest housing market in the country, with a shortage of trusted quality developers and a fragmented supply landscape. The NCR entry will enable the company to serve nearly 80% of the housing demand across the top seven Indian cities. Despite the significant investment in business development during the first nine months, the company’s net debt stood at Rs 61.7 billion, well below its ceiling of 0.5x net debt-to-equity. Lodha Developers is primarily engaged in the business of real estate development. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 86.5% to Rs 788.70 crore on a 44.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3,798.50 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.78% to Rs 1,111.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MacrotechDevelopers_6058417.4681086_35713.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>