<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks jumps on inking agreement with NEC to manufacture 5G massive MIMO radios]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-jumps-on-inking-agreement-with-nec-to-manufacture-5g-massive-mimo-radios/1679607</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679607</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Masayuki Kayahara, Corporate Senior Vice President of Global Network Division at NEC Corporation said, “Today’s milestone furthers our collaboration with Tejas Networks for 5G massive MIMO radio and to achieve supply-chain diversification which helps in mitigating risks to our customers by building a resilient, flexible globalized ecosystem.” Arnob Roy, Chief Operating Officer and Executive Director of Tejas Networks said, “Our partnership with NEC will accelerate wireless innovation by leveraging our respective expertise in carrier-class product development for global telcos.

Masayuki Kayahara, Corporate Senior Vice President of Global Network Division at NEC Corporation said, “Today’s milestone furthers our collaboration with Tejas Networks for 5G massive MIMO radio and to achieve supply-chain diversification which helps in mitigating risks to our customers by building a resilient, flexible globalized ecosystem.” Arnob Roy, Chief Operating Officer and Executive Director of Tejas Networks said, “Our partnership with NEC will accelerate wireless innovation by leveraging our respective expertise in carrier-class product development for global telcos. We will continue to work closely with NEC to co-create leading-edge 5G/5G-Advanced solutions that meet the evolving needs of customers worldwide.” Sanjay Malik, Chief Strategy and Business Officer of Tejas Networks said, “We are delighted to win this deal in partnership with NEC as we expand our business internationally. We are looking forward to building on this momentum and replicate this success in other 4G/5G mobile networks across emerging and established markets.” Tejas Networks designs and manufactures wireline and wireless networking products, with a focus on technology, innovation, and R&D. TNL carrier-class products are used by telecom service providers, utilities, governments, and defense networks in 75+ countries. Tejas Networks is a part of the Tata Group, with Panatone Finvest (a subsidiary of Tata Sons) being the majority shareholder. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 196.55 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 165.67 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baroda-bnp-paribas-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1679608</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679608</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 27 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes.

Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 27 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.12 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.14 per unit Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.39 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.41 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.17 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Balanced Advantage Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.18 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[E2E Networks rises after launching QIP issue for raising capital ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/e2e-networks-rises-after-launching-qip-issue-for-raising-capital/1679609</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679609</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company's board had authorized and declared the opening of the issue on Wednesday, 25 February 2026.

The company's board had authorized and declared the opening of the issue on Wednesday, 25 February 2026. The floor price of Rs 2,630.60 is at a premium of 2.73% to the scrip’s previous closing price of Rs 2,560.60 recorded on the NSE. The company may offer a discount of not more than 5% on the floor price so calculated for the issue. The final issue price will be determined in consultation with the book running lead managers appointed for the issue. According to NSE data, the company intends to issue a total of 150 crore shares in the said issue. As per the E2E Networks’ offer document, the purpose of the said QIP issue to raise capital for funding the capital expenditure of the company towards procurement of cloud compute infrastructure, including cloud GPUs and traditional compute and other related IT equipment. The proceeds would also be used for general corporate purposes. E2E Networks operates as a cloud infrastructure provider in India, offering GPU computing, enterprise cloud solutions and managed services for artificial intelligence and machine learning workloads. On a standalone basis, E2E Networks reported net loss of Rs 5.70 crore in Q3 December 2025 as against net profit of Rs 11.59 crore in Q3 December 2024. Net sales rose 68.32% YoY to Rs 70.02 crore in Q3 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/E2ENetworksLtd_43382383477_72373.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shree Ram Twistex IPO ends with 43.66 times subscription]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shree-ram-twistex-ipo-ends-with-4366-times-subscription/1679605</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679605</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 46,28,41,632 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer.

The initial public offer (IPO) of Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 46,28,41,632 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 43.66 times. The Non-Institutional Investors category was subscribed 220.30 times, the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 76.63 times, and the Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 3.94 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026, and it closed on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 144 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The offer consisted entirely of a fresh issue of 1.06 crore equity shares. At the upper price band of Rs 104, the company intended to raise Rs 110.24 crore. Shree Ram Twistex will utilize the IPO proceeds to set up a 4.2 MW wind power plant for captive use at an estimated cost of Rs 39 crore. Additionally, Rs 14.89 crore will be allocated towards repayment of certain borrowings, Rs 44 crore for working capital requirements, and the remaining amount for general corporate purposes. Shree Ram Twistex manufactures cotton yarns, including compact ring spun, combed, and carded varieties for knitting, weaving, and value-added yarns like slub and lycra blends. Operating on a B2B model, it supplies domestic textile manufacturers and exporters, with exports contributing 6–10% of revenue. The Gujarat-based facility has 17 spinning machines and five warehouses with 9,855 MT storage capacity. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 7 crore and income from operations of Rs 132.08 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KSB jumps after Q3 PAT climbs 11% YoY to Rs 81 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ksb-jumps-after-q3-pat-climbs-11-yoy-to-rs-81-cr/1679606</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679606</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax climbed 36.43% YoY to Rs 133.7 crore during the quarter ended 31st December 2025.

Profit before exceptional item and tax climbed 36.43% YoY to Rs 133.7 crore during the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company reported an exceptional item of Rs 255 crore during the period, attributed to labour code compliance. Total expenses increased 4.36% YoY to Rs 670.8 crore in Q3 December 2025. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 348.8 crore (up 2.29% YoY), employee benefit expenses was at Rs 91 crore(up 9.9% YoY) during the period under review. Revenue from pumps segment jumped 9.08% YoY to Rs 656.9 crore while revenue from valves segment rose 2.64% YoY to Rs 128.5 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025.. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared a dividend of Rs 4.40 per share with a face value of Rs 2 each fully paid up for the year ended 31st December 2025. The record date for payment of dividend is 08 May, 2026. Additionally, the company’s board approved the re-appointment of Rajeev Jayantiprasad Jain as managing director for a further period of 5 years with effect from 01st July, 2026. KSB is engaged in the business of manufacture of different types of power-driven pumps and industrial valves.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KSB_11705810441_342.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Government of India announces the switch auction for an aggregate amount of &#8377;25,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/government-of-india-announces-the-switch-auction-for-an-aggregate-amount-of-837725000-crore/1679602</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679602</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) on Wednesday announced that it will conduct a switch auction of government securities worth Rs 25,000 crore on March 2.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) on Wednesday announced that it will conduct a switch auction of government securities worth Rs 25,000 crore on March 2. The auction will take place between 10:30 AM and 11:30 AM. The result of the auction will be announced on the same day, and settlement will take place on March 4, RBI said in a release. This is the third switch auction announced by the RBI this month. This operation is expected to reduce the redemption pressure in FY27, when government bonds worth Rs 5.47 lakh crore are due to mature.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Websol Energy gains on securing Rs 172-cr solar orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/websol-energy-gains-on-securing-rs-172-cr-solar-orders/1679603</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679603</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders, received from Bekem Infra Projects, Sri Avantika Contractors, and Kosol Energie, are currently under production and are scheduled for delivery by May 2026.

The orders, received from Bekem Infra Projects, Sri Avantika Contractors, and Kosol Energie, are currently under production and are scheduled for delivery by May 2026. The company clarified that the recently imposed US tariffs on solar imports will not have any impact on its operations, as it does not currently export to the United States. Commenting on the business updates, Sohan Lal Agarwal, managing director of Websol Energy System, said: “These new orders reflect the confidence our partners place in Websol’s capabilities and reinforce our position in the Indian solar market. We are committed to timely execution of our client orders and to supporting India’s renewable energy goals.” Websol Energy System is engaged in the business of manufacturing photovoltaic crystalline solar cells and related modules in India. The company reported a standalone net profit of Rs 64.98 crore in Q3 FY26, up 56.4% from Rs 41.56 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 77.2% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 261.02 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WebsolEnergy_85060500051_4320.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[All India House Price Index grows by 3.6% annually in Q3: RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/all-india-house-price-index-grows-by-36-annually-in-q3-rbi/1679600</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679600</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[All India House Price Index grew by 3.6 per cent year-on-year in Q3:2025-26, compared with a growth of 6.9 per cent in the same quarter last year, an RBI report showed.

All India House Price Index grew by 3.6 per cent year-on-year in Q3:2025-26, compared with a growth of 6.9 per cent in the same quarter last year, an RBI report showed. The increase was primarily driven by cities such as Nagpur, Chandigarh, and Jaipur. The House Price Index rose to 115.6 in Q3:2025-26, from 114.2 in the previous quarter, driven by rise in housing prices across major cities – Jaipur, Kanpur and Chennai – reflecting a quarter-on-quarter growth of 1.2 per cent. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) compiles the House Price Index (HPI) on a quarterly basis using transaction-level data received from the registration authorities.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/home-loans-market-picture-id499602755_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Revenue growth of India private non-financial companies comes at 12-quarter high in Oct-Dec 2025: RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/revenue-growth-of-india-private-non-financial-companies-comes-at-12-quarter-high-in-oct-dec-2025-rbi/1679594</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679594</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank on Wednesday said private listed non-financial companies' revenue growth came at 10.1 per cent in the third quarter of FY26.

The Reserve Bank on Wednesday said private listed non-financial companies' revenue growth came at 10.1 per cent in the third quarter of FY26. For the last 11 quarters, the revenue growth was coming in single-digits, data from 3,188 such companies analysed by the central bank pointed out, attributing the acceleration to the performance of the manufacturing sector. Sales of 1,794 listed private manufacturing companies expanded by 11.4 per cent on-year during the quarter, up from 8.5 per cent in the previous quarter, mainly driven by higher sales growth in automobiles, electrical machinery and non-ferrous metals industries, it said.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/illustration-of-a-graph-and-men-maintaining-profits-vector-_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shaily Engineering rises after bagging Rs 423-cr pen injector supply contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shaily-engineering-rises-after-bagging-rs-423-cr-pen-injector-supply-contract/1679581</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679581</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The customer’s name has not been disclosed due to confidentiality reasons, stated the exchange filing.

The customer’s name has not been disclosed due to confidentiality reasons, stated the exchange filing. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and involves the manufacturing and commercial supply of pen injectors over a period of four years. The company clarified in the filing that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity. It also stated that the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Shaily Engineering Plastics is engaged in the manufacture and sale of injection-molded precision plastic components and sub-assemblies for various requirements of Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEM). The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 48.3% to Rs 37.38 crore on a 26.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 250.50 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShailyEngineer_43007281636_6740.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers nudge higher in early trade; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-nudge-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-strong/1679578</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679578</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the early trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the early trade. The Nifty traded near the 25,500 level. PSU bank, IT and healthcare shares advanced, while realty, metal and consumer durables stocks declined. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, rose 29.73 points or 0.05% to 82,305.80. The Nifty 50 index gained 14.70 points or 0.05% to 25,499.90. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.18% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.05%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 1,828 shares rose and 1,037 shares fell. A total of 177 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 2,991.64 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,118.57 crore in the Indian equity market on 24 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Reliance Industries rose 0.03%. The company said that its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, Reliance Enterprise Intelligence (REIL), has allotted 59.66 crore equity shares worth Rs 596.6 crore to Reliance Intelligence, a wholly owned subsidiary of the company, and 25.65 crore equity shares worth Rs 256.6 crore to Facebook Overseas Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of Meta Platforms, Inc. Rail Vikas Nigam added 0.66%. The company announced that the company has received an LOA from the National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) for the development of a township in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh. The project cost is Rs 371.69 crore. KFin Technologies shed 0.48%. The company said that MFC Technologies, the joint venture between Computer Age Management Services (CAMS) and KFin Technologies, announced key leadership appointments as MF Central transitions into a professionally governed stand-alone entity serving India’s mutual fund ecosystem. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper declined 0.12% to 6.677 compared with previous session close of 6.699. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.8475 compared with its close of 90.9100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement lost 0.30% to Rs 160,656. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.09% to 97.54. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.15% to 4.043. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 13 cents or 0.18% to $70.82 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia markets rose on Thursday, tracking Wall Street gains as strong earnings from Nvidia and Oracle lifted investor sentiment. Japan's Nikkei 225 index rose 1.1%, to hit an all-time high of 59,199.31, extending its winning streak of record highs to a third straight session. The broader Topix added 1.45%, also scaling a new peak. On Wednesday, the Japanese government tapped Ayano Sato of Aoyama Gakuin University and Toichiro Asada of Chuo University as central bank board members, both dovish in their policy stance which aligns with Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s approach as well. The two will succeed outgoing central bank board members Asahi Noguchi and Junko Nakagawa, whose terms expire at the end of March and in June, respectively. Japanese equities have scaled multiple record highs recently, buoyed by the so-called "Takaichi trade,” as investors bet that the prime minister’s growth-oriented policies will lift stocks while pressuring the yen through looser monetary policy and increased fiscal spending. Meanwhile, South Korea’s central bank stood pat on interest rates on Thursday and signalled policy would stay unchanged for the next six months as a chip boom in exports and steady inflation allow policymakers more time to assess financial stability risks. The Bank of Korea’s seven-member monetary policy board voted to keep its benchmark interest rate unchanged at 2.50%. The central bank raised this year’s growth forecast to 2.0% from 1.8% previously. Overnight in the U.S., equities rose, supported by Nvidia and Oracle, as stocks built on the gains from the prior trading day. The S&P 500 added 0.81% to close at 6,946.13, and the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.26% to 23,152.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 307.65 points, or 0.63%, to settle at 49,482.15. Nvidia posted fiscal fourth-quarter results that topped widely reported expectations, fueled by a 75% surge in revenue from its core data center segment. Shares gained as much as 2% in extended trading following the release. The company reported adjusted earnings per share of $1.62, beating the $1.53 forecast that was widely reported in the media. Revenue totaled $68.13 billion, above widely reported estimates of $66.21 billion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR recovers ground as dollar stays pressured ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-recovers-ground-as-dollar-stays-pressured/1679573</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679573</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee recovered some lost momentum in opening trades on Thursday tracking weakness in dollar overseas and positive cues from equities.

The Indian rupee recovered some lost momentum in opening trades on Thursday tracking weakness in dollar overseas and positive cues from equities. Indian shares commenced higher on Thursday after U.S. chipmaker Nvidia forecast first-quarter revenue above market estimates, helping ease concerns that momentum in artificial intelligence spending was cooling. INR opened at Rs 90.86 per dollar and climbed to a high of 90.81 so far during the day. Meanwhile, ongoing uncertainty regarding US tariff policies is keeping the dollar pressured. Yesterday, rupee ended the day almost flat at 90.91 against the US dollar amid higher global crude oil prices and foreign fund outflows. The benchmark indices ended the session up 50.15 points, or 0.06 percent, at 82,276.07, after having surged to a high of 82,957.91 earlier on the back of firm cues from global markets as new U.S. tariffs came into effect at 10 percent under a different legal framework. The broader NSE Nifty index hit an intraday high of 25,652.60 before closing up 57.85 points.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Subex Ltd Surges 3.94%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/subex-ltd-surges-394/1679571</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679571</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Subex Ltd gained 3.94% today to trade at Rs 9.77.

Subex Ltd gained 3.94% today to trade at Rs 9.77. The BSE Information Technology index is up 0.66% to quote at 29844.9. The index is down 19.65 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Aurionpro Solutions Ltd increased 2.58% and KPIT Technologies Ltd added 2.17% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 22.49 % over last one year compared to the 10.48% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Subex Ltd has added 8.8% over last one month compared to 19.65% fall in BSE Information Technology index and 0.69% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 515 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 1.92 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 17.3 on 12 Jun 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 8.86 on 27 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Subex_27448607361_14155.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RVNL bags orders worth Rs 656 crore from NMDC for projects in Chhattisgarh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rvnl-bags-orders-worth-rs-656-crore-from-nmdc-for-projects-in-chhattisgarh/1679569</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679569</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The first contract pertains to the construction of a residential tower in Kirandul at a cost of Rs 284.52 crore.

The first contract pertains to the construction of a residential tower in Kirandul at a cost of Rs 284.52 crore. The project is to be executed within 16 months. The second order involves the development of a township in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh. The project cost stands at Rs 371.69 crore and is scheduled to be completed within 21 months. Both contracts have been awarded by NMDC, a domestic entity, under general contract conditions. The nature of the contracts includes residential and township infrastructure development. RVNL clarified that neither the promoter nor promoter group companies have any interest in NMDC. The company further stated that the contracts do not fall under related party transactions. Rail Vikas Nigam is engaged in executing a wide range of railway infrastructure projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, cable-stayed bridges, and institutional buildings. The company reported a 3.65% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 322.83 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 311.44 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 2.56% YoY to Rs 4,684.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of Rail Vikas Nigam fell 1.29% to end at Rs 317.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at green opening for equities; South Korea central bank keeps rates unchanged]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-green-opening-for-equities-south-korea-central-bank-keeps-rates-unchanged/1679559</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679559</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty March 2026 futures were up 37.00 points, suggesting a green start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty March 2026 futures were up 37.00 points, suggesting a green start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 2,991.64 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,118.57 crore in the Indian equity market on 24 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have bought shares worth Rs 4,361.57 crore in the cash market so far in February (till 25 February 2026). This is in contrast to their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia markets rose on Thursday, tracking Wall Street gains as strong earnings from Nvidia and Oracle lifted investor sentiment. Japan's Nikkei 225 index rose 1.1%, to hit an all-time high of 59,199.31, extending its winning streak of record highs to a third straight session. The broader Topix added 1.45%, also scaling a new peak. On Wednesday, the Japanese government tapped Ayano Sato of Aoyama Gakuin University and Toichiro Asada of Chuo University as central bank board members, both dovish in their policy stance which aligns with Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s approach as well. The two will succeed outgoing central bank board members Asahi Noguchi and Junko Nakagawa, whose terms expire at the end of March and in June, respectively. Japanese equities have scaled multiple record highs recently, buoyed by the so-called "Takaichi trade,” as investors bet that the prime minister’s growth-oriented policies will lift stocks while pressuring the yen through looser monetary policy and increased fiscal spending. Meanwhile, South Korea’s central bank stood pat on interest rates on Thursday and signalled policy would stay unchanged for the next six months as a chip boom in exports and steady inflation allow policymakers more time to assess financial stability risks. The Bank of Korea’s seven-member monetary policy board voted to keep its benchmark interest rate unchanged at 2.50%. The central bank raised this year’s growth forecast to 2.0% from 1.8% previously. Overnight in the U.S., equities rose, supported by Nvidia and Oracle, as stocks built on the gains from the prior trading day. The S&P 500 added 0.81% to close at 6,946.13, and the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.26% to 23,152.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 307.65 points, or 0.63%, to settle at 49,482.15. Nvidia posted fiscal fourth-quarter results that topped widely reported expectations, fueled by a 75% surge in revenue from its core data center segment. Shares gained as much as 2% in extended trading following the release. The company reported adjusted earnings per share of $1.62, beating the $1.53 forecast that was widely reported in the media. Revenue totaled $68.13 billion, above widely reported estimates of $66.21 billion. Domestic Market: The Indian equity benchmarks managed to claw back some ground on Wednesday, ending marginally in the green after a highly volatile session. The Sensex finished with a slight gain of 50.15 points or 0.06% to settle at 82,276.07, while the Nifty 50 advanced 57.70 points or 0.23% to close at 25,482.35. The day began with a strong relief rally, with the Sensex surging 732 points in morning trade as global market nerves eased following a 10% universal tariff implementation in the U.S., which was less severe than the 15% rate previously feared. However, the indices surrendered most of these intraday gains due to heavy profit booking and persistent selling in heavyweights like Reliance Industries (down 2.23%) and State Bank of India (down 1.93%). The recovery was primarily spearheaded by the Nifty Metal index, which soared on the back of strong performances from Tata Steel and National Aluminium Company. The IT sector, which had faced a brutal "Claude Code" rout in the previous session, staged a partial rebound, buoyed by value buying in Infosys and TCS. Despite the positive close for the benchmarks, the broader market sentiment remained mixed as sectors such as FMCG, PSU Banks, and Realty ended in the red. Investors remained cautious ahead of the upcoming February 27th GDP data release, even as volatility, measured by the India VIX, cooled by nearly 5% to reflect a temporary stabilization in market sentiment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Highway Infras bags Rs 16-cr contract for Katiyara Fee Plaza in Bihar]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/highway-infras-bags-rs-16-cr-contract-for-katiyara-fee-plaza-in-bihar/1679544</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679544</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves engaging a user fee agency through e-tender for the four-laning project of the Pararia-Mohania section of NH-319 (old NH-30).

The contract involves engaging a user fee agency through e-tender for the four-laning project of the Pararia-Mohania section of NH-319 (old NH-30). The scope also covers upkeep and maintenance of adjacent toilet blocks, including replenishment of consumables. The order, awarded by a domestic entity, pertains to the operation and collection of user fees at the plaza. The contract is to be executed within 90 days. The promoter and promoter group have no interest in the entity awarding the contract, and the deal is not a related party transaction. Highway Infrastructure is an infrastructure development and management company. The company is engaged in the business of tollway collection, EPC Infra, and real estate businesses. The company reported a 96% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 6.41 crore for Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations declined 9.2% to Rs 126.86 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Shares of Highway Infrastructure rose 0.81% to Rs 56 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HighwayInfrastructureLtd_53703943_66257.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Lupin, Zydus Life, Shaily Engineering, KSB, Sanofi India, KP Energy, RVNL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-lupin-zydus-life-shaily-engineering-ksb-sanofi-india-kp-energy-rvnl/1679543</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679543</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 26 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 26 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Reliance Industries said that its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, Reliance Enterprise Intelligence (REIL), has allotted 59.66 crore equity shares worth Rs 596.6 crore to Reliance Intelligence, a wholly owned subsidiary of the company, and 25.65 crore equity shares worth Rs 256.6 crore to Facebook Overseas Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of Meta Platforms, Inc. After the allotment, Reliance Intelligence holds a 70% stake in REIL, and the balance of 30% is held by Facebook. Consequently, REIL has ceased to be a wholly owned step-down subsidiary and has become a step-down subsidiary of the company. Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) said that the Government of India, the promoter, is not exercising the oversubscription option to the extent of 26.13 crore equity shares (2% of paid-up equity) since there is an under subscription of 1.18 crore equity shares of the company as of T Day (February 25). Hence, accordingly, the total offer size will be the base offer size of up to 26.13 crore shares (2 percent equity). Additionally, the company has signed a loan agreement with the consortium of Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation and MUFG Bank (Gift City branches) in New Delhi for raising an External Commercial Borrowing loan of JPY equivalent to $400 million. Shaily Engineering Plastics has received an order worth Rs 423 crore from a domestic pharma company to supply pen injectors. Lupin said that the Goods & Service Tax Department, Maharashtra on February 25, has initiated Inspection and Search proceedings at the registered office of the company, seeking documents related to payment of GST and claim of input tax credit, etc. Initiation of this inspection and search doesn’t have any impact on the company’s financials, operations, or other activities. KFin Technologies said that MFC Technologies, the joint venture between Computer Age Management Services (CAMS) and KFin Technologies, announced key leadership appointments as MF Central transitions into a professionally governed stand-alone entity serving India’s mutual fund ecosystem. SBI Life Insurance Company said that the Board has declared an interim dividend on equity shares of the company of Rs 2.7 per share for FY26. Zydus Lifesciences said that the company plans to launch Semaglutide injection under the brand names SEMAGLYNTM, MASHEMATM, and ALTERMETM upon patent expiry in India. The Drug Controller General of India (DCGI) had earlier provided its approval for manufacturing and marketing Semaglutide injection for the treatment of Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus and Obesity. KP Energy said that it has received a Letter of Award (LoA) from Enerparc Energy for the development of a 40.8 MW wind-solar hybrid power project in Gujarat, comprising approximately 20.2 MW of wind capacity and 20.6 MWp of solar capacity. Rail Vikas Nigam announced that the company has received an LOA from the National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) for the development of a township in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh. The project cost is Rs 371.69 crore. ACME Solar Holdings said that the company, through its subsidiary ACME Suryodaya, has commissioned the first phase of 19 MW/38 MWh out of 285 MW/600 MWh capacity of the battery energy storage system (BESS) project at Jaisalmer, Rajasthan. This project will currently be deployed as a merchant capacity while ACME Solar Holdings retains flexibility to shift to a long-term PPA in the future. The commercial operation date for the said Phase I will be February 27. NTPC Green Energy announced that the first part capacity of 50 MW out of 200 MW of the Dayapar Wind Energy Project Phase II in Gujarat of the company's subsidiary NTPC Renewable Energy has been declared in commercial operation. The current commercial capacity of the NTPC Green Energy group stands at 9,151.08 MW. With the addition of this capacity, the total installed capacity of the NTPC Green Energy Group will increase to 9201.08 MW. Sanofi India reported a net profit of Rs 61.7 crore for Q4, down 32.4% from Rs 91.3 crore in the same period last year. Revenue for the quarter declined 18.5% to Rs 419.8 crore from Rs 514.9 crore a year ago. KSB reported a net profit of Rs 81 crore for the quarter, up 10.8% year-on-year from Rs 73.1 crore in the same period last year. Revenue grew 8% to Rs 784 crore, compared with Rs 726.4 crore a year ago, driven by steady demand across its key segments. Solarworld Energy’s subsidiary has signed a non-binding memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Intelenergi Global for potential collaboration in solar photovoltaic (PV) module projects. The MoU outlines preliminary cooperation on technology, manufacturing, and deployment in the renewable energy segment. Emmvee Photovoltaic has stated that it remains insulated from the recently announced US solar import duties, as its manufacturing is primarily aligned with domestic demand.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>