<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:27:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Orient Tech soars after shareholders nod for 1:10 bonus issue]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/orient-tech-soars-after-shareholders-nod-for-110-bonus-issue/1662393</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662393</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eligible shareholders will receive 10 equity shares for every one share held.

Eligible shareholders will receive 10 equity shares for every one share held. The record date for determining eligibility will be announced separately in due course. The approval, received through a postal ballot process with strong shareholder participation, reflects continued investor confidence in the company’s financial discipline, resilient operating model, and its strategic positioning in high-growth technology segments that are driving enterprise transformation across India. The bonus issue will be implemented through the capitalisation of Rs 4.16 crore from the securities premium account. Ajay Sawant, said: “The approval of the bonus issue is a clear endorsement of the confidence our shareholders have in Orient Technologies’ fundamentals, governance standards, and long-term vision. It reflects the strength of our balance sheet and the consistency of our execution, even as we continue to invest in futureready capabilities across cloud, cybersecurity, and managed services. Our focus remains on building a scalable, resilient, and differentiated technology services platform that delivers sustainable value to all stakeholders over the long term.” Orient Technologies is a leading IT Infrastructure, Cloud, Cybersecurity, and Digital Transformation services provider with over 30 years of industry expertise. With deep domain specializations across Data Centre Solutions, IT Enabled Services, Cybersecurity, Cloud & DevOps, and Application Services, the company designs and delivers technology solutions that drive business outcomes for enterprises across India and beyond. On standalone basis, the company’s net profit fell 5.9% to Rs 14.17 crore despite a 22.3% jump in net sales to Rs 272.80 crore in Q2 Sept 2025 over Q2 Sept 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OrientTechnologiesLtd_43426305_92883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prime Focus rises after subsidiary sets up AI arm in UAE]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prime-focus-rises-after-subsidiary-sets-up-ai-arm-in-uae/1662391</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662391</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The new subsidiary will focus on technology and artificial intelligence in the film, television, and gaming sectors, aiming to facilitate Prime Focus’s AI business in the UAE.

The new subsidiary will focus on technology and artificial intelligence in the film, television, and gaming sectors, aiming to facilitate Prime Focus’s AI business in the UAE. Brahma AI ME is a subsidiary (indirect) of the PFL and has taken required approvals from relevant authorities as applicable. Brahma AI ME is an indirect subsidiary of Prime Focus and has obtained all necessary approvals from relevant authorities. Brahma AI Holdings, the parent company, subscribed for one share at $1 at the time of incorporation. Prime Focus offers motion picture post production and visual effects services. The company offers visual effects, digital film lab, telecine, editing, and motion control to high-definition production services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PrimeFocus_61388003233_27264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NTPC Green arm declares commercial operations of 13.98 MW at Khavda-I project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ntpc-green-arm-declares-commercial-operations-of-1398-mw-at-khavda-i-project/1662392</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662392</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said that the ninth part capacity of 13.98 MW out of the total 1,255 MW Khavda-I Solar PV project, being implemented under the CPSU Scheme Phase-II Tranche-III, has been declared commercially operational with effect from 30 December 2025.

In an exchange filing, the company said that the ninth part capacity of 13.98 MW out of the total 1,255 MW Khavda-I Solar PV project, being implemented under the CPSU Scheme Phase-II Tranche-III, has been declared commercially operational with effect from 30 December 2025. With the commissioning of this capacity, the current commercial capacity of the NTPC Green Energy group stands at 7,996.30 MW, while the total installed capacity of the NGEL group has increased to 8,010.28 MW. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 130.3% to Rs 87.59 crore on a 21.5% rise in revenue to Rs 612.29 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of NTPC Green Energy shed 0.84% to Rs 94.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NTPCGreenEnergyLtd_60513344_94008.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mastek's US subsidiary appoints Google tech leader Marc Berson to its board ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/masteks-us-subsidiary-appoints-google-tech-leader-marc-berson-to-its-board/1662390</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662390</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Based in the United States, Marc currently serves as the head of Google Internal Systems (CIO).

Based in the United States, Marc currently serves as the head of Google Internal Systems (CIO). His appointment signals Mastek’s commitment to deepening its North American footprint and integrating world class Silicon Valley expertise into its strategic oversight. Marc’s career spans leadership roles at Gilead Sciences, HP, IBM, and Philips, where he spearheaded massive enterprise transformations. His expertise bridges the gap between complex processes, systems, and cutting-edge digital innovation, making him a pivotal asset for Mastek’s "Lead with AI" roadmap. Marc holds a Bachelor of Science in Finance and International Business from Penn State University and a Master’s in Project Management from George Washington University. Umang Nahata, CEO of Mastek, said: “Marc brings a rare combination of deep technology insight and practitioner-led experience in navigating the complexities of global scale. His counsel will be invaluable as we solidify Mastek’s position to lead with AI as the preferred partner for delivering best-in-class ROI to clients. By integrating his Silicon Valley perspective, we are better positioned to accelerate our mission of driving high-impact, AI-driven business outcomes for the modern enterprise.” Mastek is an IT company providing enterprise digital and cloud transformation services to the Government/public sector, healthcare, life science, retail, and financial services sectors. The company’s service offerings include application development, Oracle suite and cloud migration, digital commerce, application support & maintenance, BI & analytics, assurance & testing and agile consulting. The scrip fell 1.13% to currently trade at Rs 2087.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Mastek_31982240985_2732.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Sundrex Oil Company sputters on debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-sundrex-oil-company-sputters-on-debut/1662389</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662389</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock listed at Rs 68.80, a 20% discount to the IPO price, and is currently down 5% over the listing price.

The stock listed at Rs 68.80, a 20% discount to the IPO price, and is currently down 5% over the listing price. It touched a high of Rs 68.80 and a low of Rs 65.40, with 16,000 shares traded on the exchange. Sundrex Oil Company's IPO was subscribed 1.50 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 81 to Rs 86 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 37,50,400 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds to meet working capital expenses, to meet capital expenditure, for prepayment and repayment of all or a portion of certain secured and unsecured loan, general corporate purposes and to meet the offer-related expenses. Sundrex Oil Company manufactures and wholesales lubricants, greases, and related industrial products across India, catering to both B2B and B2C customers. Its revenue is overwhelmingly B2B-driven, contributing about 99% of total sales, with the B2C segment accounting for the remaining 1%. The company’s portfolio spans industrial and automotive lubricants, transformer oils, metalworking fluids, bituminous products, and other specialised formulations. As of 30 June 2025, the company employed approximately 73 people across various levels of the organization. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 18.71 crore and a net profit of Rs 1.94 crore for the period ended 30 June 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SundrexOilCompanyLtd_25039735_94304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade near flat line; auto shares pick up pace]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-near-flat-line-auto-shares-pick-up-pace/1662388</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662388</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded near flat line in mid-morning trade.

The key equity barometers traded near flat line in mid-morning trade. Trading activity remained rangebound due to absence of strong domestic triggers and the year-end holiday period. The Nifty traded below the 25,950 mark while volatility may persist owing to the Nifty F&O expiry. Auto shares jumped, snapping a three-session losing streak. At 11:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 96.27 points or 0.11% to 84,599.27. The Nifty 50 index lost 26.30 points or 0.09% to 25,918.25. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.30%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.51%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,697 shares rose and 2,084 shares fell. A total of 232 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index rose 0.74% to 27,795.45. The index dropped 1.07% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Hero MotoCorp (up 1.66%), Bajaj Auto (up 1.31%), Ashok Leyland (up 1.28%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.21%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 0.98%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 0.85%), Bharat Forge (up 0.8%), TVS Motor Company (up 0.66%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (up 0.54%) and Samvardhana Motherson International (up 0.22%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Waaree Energies fell 1.46% after its whole time director (WTD) & chief executive officer (CEO), Amit Paithankar, resigned to pursue opportunities outside the organisation. Lemon Tree Hotels rose 0.87% after the company announced the execution of a Hotel Operation Agreement (HOA) for an upcoming property in Tirupati, Andhra Pradesh. Global Markets: Asian market traded mixed on Tuesday, after the tech sell-down on Wall Street continued on AI bubble fears. Investors will be focused on China’s military exercises around Taiwan, after the world’s second-largest economy announced new drills surrounding the island Monday. Overnight in the U.S., stocks fell on Monday, spurred by losses in technology, after the S&P 500 scaled to record levels last week. The S&P 500 dropped 0.35% and closed at 6,905.74, while the Nasdaq Composite shed 0.50% and settled at 23,474.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back by 249.04 points, or 0.51%, and ended at 48,461.93. Meanwhile, silver pulled back more than 6% after reaching $80 per ounce for the first time ever overnight. This comes as the precious metal has had a massive run-up in 2025, surging almost 150% to become one of the year’s hottest trades.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GNFC slides after MD T Natarajan steps down]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gnfc-slides-after-md-t-natarajan-steps-down/1662387</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662387</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of Gujarat has nominated Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS, as managing director with effect from 29 December 2025.

The Government of Gujarat has nominated Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS, as managing director with effect from 29 December 2025. Beniwal, a 2004 batch Gujarat cadre IAS officer, brings nearly two decades of administrative experience. He holds a B.Tech in Mechanical Engineering from IT (BHU), Varanasi, and a Master’s degree in Public Administration from Duke University, USA. His career spans multiple key administrative roles, including Collector and District Magistrate of Mehsana and Ahmedabad, District Development Officer in Kutch, and coordination of the Vibrant Gujarat Global Summits in 2017 and 2018. He has also served as Vice-Chairman and CEO of the Gujarat Maritime Board, Managing Director of Gujarat Urban Development Company Limited, Additional CEO of the Gujarat Urban Development Mission, and Commissioner of Municipalities Administration. In these roles, Beniwal has played a pivotal role in urban development initiatives, governance reforms, and strengthening the administration of Urban Local Bodies across Gujarat. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fert. & Chem is leading entities engaged in the manufacturing and selling of fertilizers, industrial chemical products and providing IT services. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 70.5% to Rs 179 crore on 2.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,968 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GNFC_11816154185_213.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin signs exclusive licensing deal with Gan & Lee for novel GLP-1 receptor agonist]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-signs-exclusive-licensing-deal-with-gan-lee-for-novel-glp-1-receptor-agonist/1662385</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662385</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the agreement strengthens Lupin’s diabetes portfolio and expands its presence in the obesity segment.

According to an exchange filing, the agreement strengthens Lupin’s diabetes portfolio and expands its presence in the obesity segment. Bofanglutide, developed by Gan & Lee, is intended for adults with type 2 diabetes and for weight management in overweight or obese individuals. As a potential first-in-class fortnightly GLP-1 agonist, clinical data indicate that Bofanglutide delivers weight loss results comparable to or better than existing GLP-1 alternatives, with the added convenience of once-every-two-weeks dosing compared to weekly injections, while maintaining safety and tolerability consistent with the GLP-1 class. The drug also helps reduce blood glucose levels and body weight. The company said obesity is emerging as a major health concern in India, with an estimated 174 million adults overweight and around 50 million classified as obese. Diabetes affects approximately 90 million adults in the country. Under the terms of the agreement, Lupin will have exclusive rights to commercialize and distribute Bofanglutide in India. Nilesh Gupta, Managing Director, Lupin, said, “We are committed to offering the best solutions for managing chronic metabolic diseases like diabetes, and addressing obesity is one of the most urgent global health challenges. This partnership demonstrates our strategic focus on the GLP-1 class of drugs and highlights our dedication to delivering high-quality, innovative therapies for our patients.” Rajeev Sibal, President of India Region Formulations at Lupin, said, “Bofanglutide offers a significant advantage with its convenient fortnightly dosing, thus reducing the number of injections by 50% while delivering outcomes and clinically proven efficacy that matches or surpasses existing weekly formulations. This strategic alliance marks a pivotal step in strengthening Lupin’s leadership in metabolic health, expanding our innovative portfolio, and reaffirming our commitment to delivering transformative solutions.” Gan & Lee Executive Vice President & Chief Commercial Officer (EVP & CCO) Kai Du and Key Accounts Director, Dr Dhaval Soneji commented and believed, “On the heels of the Latin American exclusive agreement signed in November, this new partnership with Lupin for the Indian market further underscores Gan & Lee’s rapid global strategic advancement. Our goal is to provide superior treatment options for patients with metabolic diseases worldwide, while showcasing the value of Chinese biopharmaceutical innovation on the global stage.” Lupin is a global pharmaceutical leader headquartered in Mumbai, India, with products distributed in over 100 markets. It specializes in pharmaceutical products, including branded and generic formulations, complex generics, biotechnology products, and active pharmaceutical ingredients. The company had reported a 73.33% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,477.92 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 852.63 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 24.27% year-on-year to Rs 6,831.43 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. The counter rose 0.11% to currently trade at Rs 2,081.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Honasa Consumer jumps after promoter Varun Alagh raises stake]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/honasa-consumer-jumps-after-promoter-varun-alagh-raises-stake/1662384</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662384</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Alagh on 29 December 2025 acquired 18.52 lakh shares, or 0.57% of the company’s total equity, at Rs 270 per share, aggregating to about Rs 50 crore.

Alagh on 29 December 2025 acquired 18.52 lakh shares, or 0.57% of the company’s total equity, at Rs 270 per share, aggregating to about Rs 50 crore. Following the transaction, his shareholding climbed to 32.45%, while the aggregate promoter and promoter group stake increased to 35.54%. As of September 2025, Alagh held a 31.88% stake in the company, with total promoter holding at 34.97%. The stock move reflected positive investor sentiment around the promoter’s confidence in the company’s long-term prospects. Honasa Consumer is a brand house focused on the personal care and beauty market. The company operates a portfolio of digital-first brands including Mamaearth, The Derma Co., Aqualogica, Bblunt, Dr Sheth's, Staze and Luminéve, developed through a customer insights–driven product strategy. Honasa’s distribution network covers more than 100,000 FMCG retail outlets and spans over 18,000 pin codes, making its products available across more than 700 districts in India. The company reported a net profit of Rs 39 crore in Q2 FY26 as against a net loss of Rs 19 crore recorded in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose by 16.5% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 538 crore during the quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HonasaConsumerLtd_60997811_77264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cupid gains after board approves FMCG unit in Saudi Arabia]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cupid-gains-after-board-approves-fmcg-unit-in-saudi-arabia/1662381</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662381</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the proposed plant will be its first manufacturing facility outside India, marking a key milestone in its international expansion journey.

In an exchange filing, the company said the proposed plant will be its first manufacturing facility outside India, marking a key milestone in its international expansion journey. The new facility is aimed at supporting Cupid’s FMCG growth strategy and strengthening its presence in overseas markets, starting with the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) region. The plant is expected to enhance regional supply capabilities, improve speed to market, and ensure better product availability across KSA and other GCC countries. The project is proposed to be funded through the company’s internal accruals and will be taken forward after completing detailed evaluations and obtaining necessary regulatory and statutory approvals. Cupid said that establishing a manufacturing base closer to key international markets will help deepen its global FMCG footprint and improve service efficiency across the region. CUPID is India's premier manufacturer and brand of male and female condoms, water-based personal lubricants, IVD kits, deodorants, perfumes, almond hair oil, body oils, petroleum jelly and other FMCG products. The company operates with a strong commitment to public health and well-being, maintaining ethical business practices aligned with international standards. The company reported a 140.47% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 24.12 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 10.03 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 103.22% YoY to Rs 84.44 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cupid_16723626520_5185.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Paradeep Phosphates Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-paradeep-phosphates-ltd-counter/1662380</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662380</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Honasa Consumer Ltd, Rashtriya Chemicals & Fertilizers Ltd, The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 30 December 2025.

Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Honasa Consumer Ltd, Rashtriya Chemicals & Fertilizers Ltd, The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 30 December 2025. Paradeep Phosphates Ltd registered volume of 10.2 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.14 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.99 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.02% to Rs.168.00. Volumes stood at 2.81 lakh shares in the last session. Vishal Mega Mart Ltd registered volume of 12.58 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 3.47 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.62 lakh shares. The stock slipped 1.65% to Rs.134.00. Volumes stood at 77167 shares in the last session. Honasa Consumer Ltd recorded volume of 4.78 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 3.14 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.52 lakh shares. The stock gained 3.72% to Rs.287.05. Volumes stood at 38910 shares in the last session. Rashtriya Chemicals & Fertilizers Ltd recorded volume of 1.75 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 2.21 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 79168 shares. The stock gained 1.88% to Rs.146.15. Volumes stood at 2.48 lakh shares in the last session. The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd saw volume of 5690 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 2.11 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2699 shares. The stock increased 5.19% to Rs.1,924.00. Volumes stood at 1819 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Paradeep-Phosphates-Ltd_66677477_12375.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GoI announces the sale of one dated security for a notified amount of &#8377;32,000 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/goi-announces-the-sale-of-one-dated-security-for-a-notified-amount-of-837732000-crore/1662376</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662376</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.48% Government Security 2035” for a notified amount of ₹32,000 crore (nominal) through price based auction using multiple price method.

The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.48% Government Security 2035” for a notified amount of ₹32,000 crore (nominal) through price based auction using multiple price method. GoI will have the option to retain additional subscription up to ₹2,000 crore against the security mentioned above. The auction will be conducted by the Reserve Bank of India, Mumbai Office, Fort, Mumbai on January 02, 2026 (Friday). Up to 5% of the notified amount of the sale of the security will be allotted to eligible individuals and institutions as per the Scheme for Non-Competitive Bidding Facility in the Auction of Government Securities.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rabi acreage sees marginal rise of 1% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rabi-acreage-sees-marginal-rise-of-1-on-year/1662375</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662375</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total area sown to all rabi crops stood at 61.4 million hectares as of December 26 in the 2024-25 rabi season, up 1.08% from 60.74 million hectares a year ago, said latest data from the Ministry of Agriculture.

The total area sown to all rabi crops stood at 61.4 million hectares as of December 26 in the 2024-25 rabi season, up 1.08% from 60.74 million hectares a year ago, said latest data from the Ministry of Agriculture. Wheat, the primary rabi crop, area remained flat at 32.26 million hectares. Last year 32.24 million hectares were sown.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/agriculture-1551091__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Banks GNPA ratio declines to a multi-decadal low of 2.1% at end-September 2025: RBI data ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/banks-gnpa-ratio-declines-to-a-multi-decadal-low-of-21-at-end-september-2025-rbi-data/1662373</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662373</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian commercial banking sector remained resilient during 2024-25, supported by double-digit balance sheet expansion, the Reserve Bank of India said in its Report on Trend and Progress of Banking in India 2024-25.

The Indian commercial banking sector remained resilient during 2024-25, supported by double-digit balance sheet expansion, the Reserve Bank of India said in its Report on Trend and Progress of Banking in India 2024-25. Deposits and credit of scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) grew in double digits, albeit with a moderation from the previous year. The capital to risk weighted assets ratio of SCBs was 17.4 per cent at end-March 2025 and 17.2 per cent at end-September 2025. RBI stated. Asset quality strengthened further, with the gross non-performing assets (GNPA) ratio declining to a multi-decadal low of 2.2 per cent at end-March 2025 and 2.1 per cent at end-September 2025. Profitability of the SCBs remained robust with the return on assets (RoA) at 1.4 per cent and return on equity (RoE) at 13.5 per cent in 2024-25. During H1: 2025-26, RoA and RoE of the SCBs stood at 1.3 per cent and 12.5 per cent, respectively. The consolidated balance sheet of urban co-operative banks recorded higher growth in 2024-25 than that in the previous year. Their asset quality improved for the fourth consecutive year, alongside strengthening of their capital buffers and profitability. The non-banking financial companies continued to record double digit credit growth along with robust capital buffers. Their asset quality also improved during the year, RBI further noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Electronics bags additional orders worth Rs 569-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-electronics-bags-additional-orders-worth-rs-569-cr/1662374</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662374</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the defence public sector undertaking said that the major orders include a wide range of products and services such as radars, tank overhaul systems, communication equipment, fire control systems, simulators, antenna stabilisation systems, security software, components, upgrades, spares, and related services.

In an exchange filing, the defence public sector undertaking said that the major orders include a wide range of products and services such as radars, tank overhaul systems, communication equipment, fire control systems, simulators, antenna stabilisation systems, security software, components, upgrades, spares, and related services. Bharat Electronics (BEL) is a Navratna PSU under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. It manufactures electronic products and systems for the army, navy, and air force. As of September 2025, the Government of India held a 51.14% stake in the company. Its consolidated net profit jumped 17.87% to Rs 1,287.77 crore on 25.78% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 5,792.09 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.17% to Rs 392.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatElectron_81586952923_2298.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India sees highest-ever renewable energy expansion in 2025]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-sees-highest-ever-renewable-energy-expansion-in-2025/1662372</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662372</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of New and Renewable Energy has stated in a latest update that the year 2025 has marked highest-ever renewable energy expansion in India.

Ministry of New and Renewable Energy has stated in a latest update that the year 2025 has marked highest-ever renewable energy expansion in India. The country has added a record 44.5 GW renewable energy capacity in 2025 (till November 2025), nearly doubling annual additions. It also noted that Solar installed capacity has touched 132.85 GW as India added nearly 35 GW this year so far.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/wind-turbine-1804055__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,950 mark; metal shares climb]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25950-mark-metal-shares-climb/1662364</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662364</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers recovered from early losses and edged into positive territory in morning trade.

The key equity barometers recovered from early losses and edged into positive territory in morning trade. Trading activity remained rangebound due to absence of strong domestic triggers and the year-end holiday period. The Nifty traded above the 25,950 mark while volatility may persist owing to the Nifty F&O expiry. Metal shares rebounded sharply after declining in the previous trading session. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 80.69 points or 0.09% to 84,776.42. The Nifty 50 index rose 20.05 points or 0.08% to 25,962.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.02% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.11%. The market breadth was almost even. On the BSE, 1,778 shares rose and 1,773 shares fell. A total of 237 shares were unchanged. New Listing: Shares of Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality were currently trading at Rs 115.25 at 10:20 IST on the BSE, representing a premium of 1.10% as compared with the issue price of Rs 114. The stock debuted at Rs 120.75, marking a premium of 5.92% to the issue price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 123.25 and a low of 114. On the BSE, over 11.13 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index jumped 0.77% to 10,872.15. The index shed 0.16% in the past trading session. Hindustan Copper (up 6.43%), Jindal Stainless (up 1.88%), National Aluminium Company (up 1.6%), NMDC (up 1.04%), Hindalco Industries (up 1.02%), Steel Authority of India (up 0.64%), Hindustan Zinc (up 0.56%), Jindal Steel (up 0.5%), JSW Steel (up 0.42%) and Vedanta (up 0.4%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) rose 0.04%. The company said it has emerged as the lowest bidder (L1) for a contract worth Rs 201.23 crore from East Coast Railway. Niraj Cement Structurals added 2.07% after the company has secured a Rs 34.86-crore contract from Mumbai Metropolitan Region Development Authority (MMRDA) for building linkway foot overbridges (FOBs) at the Metro Line-7 Goregaon (East) station.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aditya-birla-sun-life-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1662383</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662383</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has announced 01 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme: Aditya Birla Sun Life Dynamic Bond Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Quarterly Option: Rs 0.1483 per unit.

Aditya Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund has announced 01 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme: Aditya Birla Sun Life Dynamic Bond Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Quarterly Option: Rs 0.1483 per unit. Direct Plan – IDCW Quarterly Option: Rs 0.1520 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waaree Energies slides as CEO Amit Paithankar resigns]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waaree-energies-slides-as-ceo-amit-paithankar-resigns/1662345</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662345</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[His resignation will be effective from 15 May 2026, or an earlier date as may be mutually agreed, the company said.

His resignation will be effective from 15 May 2026, or an earlier date as may be mutually agreed, the company said. Following Paithankar’s resignation, the board has appointed Jignesh Rathod as chief executive officer-designate with effect from 29 December 2025. Rathod will hold the position until Paithankar’s date of relieving. Rathod is a seasoned leader with over 18 years of experience and has been associated with Waaree Energies since 28 November 2007. He currently oversees end-to-end operations across the company’s manufacturing facilities and has played a key role in scaling production capacity, driving operational efficiencies, strengthening quality systems and supporting expansion and modernisation initiatives. He holds a Bachelor’s degree in Engineering from Gujarat University, an MBA for Working Executives from NMIMS, Mumbai, and a Doctorate in Business Administration from XIBMS. The company said Rathod’s leadership and deep institutional knowledge have been instrumental in building resilient operations aligned with Waaree Energies’ long-term strategic vision. Mumbai-based Waaree Energies is a renewable energy company. It offers innovative solar solutions, including panel manufacturing, EPC services, project development, and rooftop systems. Waaree Energies reported a 132.97% year-on-year (YoY) surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 842.55 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 361.65 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Revenue from operations jumped 69.69% YoY to Rs 6,065.64 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WaareeEnergiesLtd_42747859_39763.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lemon Tree Hotels gains after arm signs HOA for Andhra Pradesh property]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lemon-tree-hotels-gains-after-arm-signs-hoa-for-andhra-pradesh-property/1662346</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662346</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agreement has been signed by Carnation Hotels, a wholly owned subsidiary of Lemon Tree Hotels.

The agreement has been signed by Carnation Hotels, a wholly owned subsidiary of Lemon Tree Hotels. Under the arrangement, Carnation Hotels will operate the property under the brand name Lemon Tree Suites, subject to the execution of a licence agreement by Lemon Tree Hotels. The upcoming Lemon Tree Suites, Tirupati will be located in one of India’s most prominent pilgrimage destinations, known for the Sri Venkateswara Temple, which attracts millions of devotees annually. Tirupati, situated in the Eastern Ghats of Andhra Pradesh. The hotel will feature 228 rooms and suites, a restaurant, banquet and meeting facilities, and recreational amenities including a swimming pool and a spa. In terms of connectivity, Tirupati International Airport is approximately 10 km from the property, while Tirupati Railway Station is around 6.3 km away, ensuring easy access through public and private transport. Vilas Pawar, CEO - Managed & Franchise Business, Lemon Tree Hotels, commented, “With this signing, we are pleased to extend our pilgrimage portfolio in a place that holds deep spiritual resonance. Moreover, the vibrant tourism, rich cuisine, and growing hotel infrastructure make Andhra Pradesh a magnet for tourism travellers seeking unforgettable experiences. The state has six operational and three upcoming hotels." Lemon Tree Hotels (LTHL) is one of the largest hotel chains in India and owns/leases/operates/franchises hotels across the upscale, upper-midscale, midscale, and economy segments. The group offers seven brands to meet guests’ needs across all levels, viz., Aurika Hotels & Resorts, Lemon Tree Premier, Lemon Tree Hotels, Red Fox Hotels by Lemon Tree Hotels, Keys Prima by Lemon Tree Hotels, Keys Select by Lemon Tree Hotels, and Keys Lite by Lemon Tree Hotels. The company reported a 16.73% advance in consolidated net profit to Rs 34.60 crore, while revenue from operations rose 7.7% to Rs 306.28 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LemonTreeHotelsLtd_62193476144_40619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>