<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Comm Q3 PAT jumps 55% YoY to Rs 365 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-comm-q3-pat-jumps-55-yoy-to-rs-365-cr/1666333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666333</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Income from operations rose 6.74% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,188.97 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Income from operations rose 6.74% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,188.97 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) gained 23.51% to Rs 457.91 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 370.72 crore in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, EBITDA stood at Rs 1,228 crore, registering the growth of 4% compared with Rs 1,181 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin reduced 52 bps to 19.8% in Q3 FY26 as against 20.4% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, data revenue increased by 9.3% to Rs 5,359 crore as against Rs 4,903 crore reported in Q3 FY25. A.S. Lakshminarayanan, MD and CEO, Tata Communications, said: “This quarter’s performance reflects our disciplined focus on driving data-led growth with expanding margins and a healthy order book. We are gaining momentum across the business, and the capability shift we have invested in is now clearly translating into stronger products and sharper execution for customers. With multiple launches ahead, we are well positioned to build sustainably and accelerate the next phase of growth.” Kabir Ahmed Shakir, chief financial officer (CFO), Tata Communications, said: “Q3 has been a strong quarter with robust revenue growth and steadily improving margins, reflecting disciplined execution across the business. Our continued focus on capital efficiency has strengthened the balance sheet and is funding our growth priorities. We are confident of our direction and our “Fit to Grow” strategy allows us to build on the momentum we are seeing across.” Tata Communications is a global digital ecosystem enabler powering today's fast-growing digital economy in more than 190 countries and territories. Leading with trust, it enables the digital transformation of enterprises globally with collaboration and connected solutions, core and next-gen connectivity, cloud hosting and security solutions, and media services. Shares of Tata Communications shed 0.31% to Rs 1,708.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataComm_9163241039_2295.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Consumer price inflation for agricultural labourers flat in Jul-25, food prices stay slippery]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/consumer-price-inflation-for-agricultural-labourers-flat-in-jul-25-food-prices-stay-slippery/1666329</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666329</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Labour Bureau, Ministry of Labour & Employment, has released the Consumer Price Index Numbers for Agricultural Labourers and Rural Labourers (CPI – AL & RL) with the base year 2019=100 for the month of December 2025.

Labour Bureau, Ministry of Labour & Employment, has released the Consumer Price Index Numbers for Agricultural Labourers and Rural Labourers (CPI – AL & RL) with the base year 2019=100 for the month of December 2025. For the month of December 2025, the All-India Consumer Price Index for Agricultural Labourers (Base: 2019=100) decreased by 0.28 points to 137.12, while the index for Rural Labourers decreased by 0.27 points, reaching 137.03. The Food Index decreased by 0.70 points each for Agricultural Labourers (AL) and Rural Labourers (RL) in December 2025. The year-on-year inflation rate for Agricultural Labourers and Rural Labourers stood at 0.04% and 0.11%, respectively, in December 2025. The food inflation in December 2025 stood at -1.80% for AL and -1.73% for RL.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/agriculture-1551086__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME INDO SMC makes a calm debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-indo-smc-makes-a-calm-debut/1666327</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666327</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 149, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 149, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently up 2.85% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 156 and a low of Rs 141.55. About 30.81 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Indo SMC's IPO was subscribed 102.83 times. The issue opened for bidding on 13 January 2026 and it closed on 16 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 141 to Rs 149 per share. The IPO comprised a fresh issue of 44,15,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter group shareholding diluted to 69.49% from 100% pre-issue. The company will utilize the net proceeds for funding capital expenditure to purchase plant and machinery and working capital requirements. Ahead of the IPO, Indo SMC on 12 January 2026, the company raised Rs 26.16 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 17.56 lakh shares at Rs 149 each to 17 anchor investors. Indo SMC is engaged in diversified manufacturing activities comprising the Sheet Moulding Compound (SMC) Division for energy meter enclosure boxes, SMC sheets, and SMC chequered plates; the Fiberglass Reinforced Plastic (FRP) division for grating plates; and the Electrical Components division for HTCTs, HTPTs, LTCTs, feeder pillars, and related power distribution and protection switchgear. The company employed 332 personnel as of 30 November 2025. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 112.54 crore and net profit of Rs 11.45 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/INDOSMCLIMITED_20080393_96000.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Allcargo Terminals Ltd Partly Paidup leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/allcargo-terminals-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-losers-in-b-group/1666326</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666326</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Umiya Buildcon Ltd, Race Eco Chain Ltd, ICDS Ltd and N K Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 21 January 2026.

Umiya Buildcon Ltd, Race Eco Chain Ltd, ICDS Ltd and N K Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 21 January 2026. Allcargo Terminals Ltd Partly Paidup tumbled 14.83% to Rs 9.42 at 14:28 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 421 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3345 shares in the past one month. Umiya Buildcon Ltd lost 11.63% to Rs 70.62. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4312 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1439 shares in the past one month. Race Eco Chain Ltd crashed 10.77% to Rs 102.35. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 452 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 609 shares in the past one month. ICDS Ltd corrected 10.00% to Rs 36.9. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 60 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd slipped 9.98% to Rs 58.15. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 10 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 70 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops over 299 pts; realty shares slide]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-over-299-pts-realty-shares-slide/1666322</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666322</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade as persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings, and lingering concerns over global trade and geopolitics weighed on investor sentiment.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade as persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings, and lingering concerns over global trade and geopolitics weighed on investor sentiment. A sharp rise in the India VIX signaled heightened volatility expectations as investors stayed on the sidelines ahead of key Q3 earnings outcomes and cues from the World Economic Forum. The Nifty traded below the 25,150 mark. Realty shares extended losses for the third consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 299.07 points or 0.36% to 81,881.40. The Nifty 50 index lost 102.80 points or 0.41% to 25,140.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tumbled 1.42% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.17%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,221 shares rose and 2,979 shares fell. A total of 138 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 9.74% to 13.97. The Indian rupee fell to a record low of 91.19 against the US dollar on Wednesday, pressured by a stronger greenback as fresh tariff threats from US President Donald Trump over Greenland fueled global risk aversion. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 1.23% to 784.15. The index dropped 8.07% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Godrej Properties (down 3.86%), Phoenix Mills (down 2.59%), Brigade Enterprises (down 2.36%), Sobha (down 1.94%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.66%), Lodha Developers (down 1.4%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 0.95%), DLF (down 0.47%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.1%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.16% to 6.662 as compared with the previous close of 6.684. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6700 compared with its close of 90.9700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 4.54% to Rs 1,57,452. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 98.60. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.54% to 4.272. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 94 cents or 1.45% to $63.98 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Rallis India rose 1.11%. The company’s standalone net profit tanked 81.81% to Rs 2 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 11 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 19.34% year on year (YoY) to Rs 623 crore in Q3 FY26, driven primarily by strong volume growth across businesses. K.P. Energy shed 0.27%. The company reported a 56.68% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 41.35 crore on a 62.83% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 344.96 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at CreditAccess Grameen Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-creditaccess-grameen-ltd-counter/1666321</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666321</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Carborundum Universal Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd, SRF Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 21 January 2026.

Carborundum Universal Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd, SRF Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 21 January 2026. CreditAccess Grameen Ltd notched up volume of 144.44 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 53.72 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.69 lakh shares. The stock rose 12.83% to Rs.1,402.00. Volumes stood at 2.89 lakh shares in the last session. Carborundum Universal Ltd saw volume of 10.43 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.51 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.10 lakh shares. The stock increased 2.49% to Rs.799.10. Volumes stood at 2.39 lakh shares in the last session. Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd clocked volume of 318.49 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.54 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 48.67 lakh shares. The stock lost 11.91% to Rs.397.70. Volumes stood at 54.44 lakh shares in the last session. Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd registered volume of 527.97 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.66 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 93.25 lakh shares. The stock rose 8.10% to Rs.150.70. Volumes stood at 55.72 lakh shares in the last session. SRF Ltd registered volume of 17.11 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.53 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.09 lakh shares. The stock slipped 7.09% to Rs.2,678.80. Volumes stood at 6.69 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CreditAccessGrameenLtd_17343154102_37419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Narmadesh Brass Industries bends under listing pressure ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-narmadesh-brass-industries-bends-under-listing-pressure/1666324</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666324</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 495, a discount of 3.88% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 495, a discount of 3.88% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its lower limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 495 and a low of Rs 470.25. About 2,400 shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Narmadesh Brass Industries' IPO was subscribed 1.23 times. The issue opened for bidding on 12 January 2026 and it closed on 16 January 2026. The price of the IPO was fixed at Rs 515 per share. The IPO comprised a fresh issue of 700,800 equity shares and an offer for sale of 1,70,400 equity shares. The company will utilize the net proceeds for repayment/ prepayment, in full or in part, of certain outstanding borrowings, Purchase of machinery and equipment, funding Working capital requirements and general corporate purpose. Narmadesh Brass Industries is engaged in manufacturing diverse range of brass products catering to both domestic and international market. It also offers casting and forging services related to brass components at its manufacturing facility. As on 30 September 2025, the company has 81 labour. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 34.17 crore and net profit of Rs 4.01 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NarmadeshBrassIndustriesLtd_44179091_93340.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Supreme Inds slides as Q3 PAT drops 18% YoY to Rs 153 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/supreme-inds-slides-as-q3-pat-drops-18-yoy-to-rs-153-cr/1666307</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666307</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 7.05% year on year (YoY) to Rs 2,686.94 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

However, revenue from operations rose 7.05% year on year (YoY) to Rs 2,686.94 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 206.07 crore in the third quarter of FY26, registering a de-growth of 16.03%. Operating profit declined 2.29% YoY to Rs 323.21 crore during the period under review. Operating profit margin reduced to 12.01% in Q3 FY26, compared to 13.13% in Q3 FY25. The overall turnover of value-added products stood at Rs 1,118 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16% from Rs 961 crore in the same quarter last year. M. P. Taparia, Managing Director, The Supreme Industries Limited, said, “The global economy faced slower growth in 2025 due to geopolitical tensions in multiple regions, resulting in extreme volatility in commodity prices. These factors negatively impacted global economic growth. However, we believe the downward trend has now reversed, and polymer prices have started an upward trajectory. Polymer producers faced a challenging period, leading to closures of several petrochemical plants or operation at low capacity, which has helped stabilize prices. Starting 2026, polymer prices have shown upward movement. The Company operates across multiple business segments. In the first nine months of the current year, overall volumes grew 10%, with the Plastic Piping business rising 13%. For the full year, the Company expects overall volume growth of 12–14% and 15–17% in the Plastic Piping business. Growth in the Plastic Piping business is returning to normalcy as the continuous downward price trend has been arrested. A good monsoon and favorable economic conditions across housing, agriculture, and infrastructure in Q4 FY26 are expected to support strong demand. The Company is well equipped to meet the increased demand for its piping products. The newly launched PP Silent Pipe System, developed in technical collaboration with M/s. Poloplast GmbH of Austria, has been well received in the market. The Company is also expanding its range of Electrofusion (EF) fittings and bathware products. Supreme Industries continues to invest in enlarging its product portfolio and increasing the share of value-added products. Capacity expansions for Plastic Piping and Protective Packaging products are nearing completion and will be fully operational in FY27. New greenfield plants and capacities are planned for execution in the next financial year. The three units acquired through the Wavin Business acquisition are fully integrated and realigned, with full potential expected from February 2026. Total installed capacity for the Plastic Piping business is projected to reach one million MT per annum by March 31, 2026. Production trials for the Profile Window project are nearing completion, with commercial production expected to commence in February 2026. During the first nine months, the Company incurred capital expenditure of Rs 1,031 crore, including the Wavin Business acquisition. Total capex for the year is expected to be around Rs 1,200 crore, funded entirely from internal accruals. All other product divisions are performing well, with moderate growth expected. The Protective Packaging division is driving growth by expanding its product range, capacities, and customized solutions. The Company has fully executed an LOI to supply 2 lakh 10-kg composite LPG cylinders to Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited (BPCL) and has received an additional LOI to supply another 2 lakh cylinders this quarter. Efforts are ongoing to expand export geographies and participate in national and international energy and gas exhibitions.” Supreme Industries is engaged mainly in production of plastic products and operate in various product categories like Plastic piping system, cross laminated films & products, protective packaging products, industrial molded components, molded furniture, storage & material handling products, performance packaging films and composite LPG cylinders.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SupremeInds_28660861665_541.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-bank-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1666291</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666291</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

ICICI Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1349.4, down 1.92% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25214.4. The Sensex is at 82152.2, down 0.03%.ICICI Bank Ltd has lost around 1.4% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which ICICI Bank Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.53% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59404.2, down 0.7% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 151.82 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 115.4 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1351, down 1.86% on the day. ICICI Bank Ltd jumped 12.41% in last one year as compared to a 8.89% rally in NIFTY and a 21.06% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 20.05 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIBank_93786457618_5418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bosch Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bosch-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1666292</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666292</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bosch Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Bosch Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 34955, down 1.74% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25214.4. The Sensex is at 82152.2, down 0.03%.Bosch Ltd has lost around 3.33% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bosch Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 3.41% in last one month and is currently quoting at 26948.1, down 0.05% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 20766 shares today, compared to the daily average of 36132 shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 35145, down 1.5% on the day. Bosch Ltd jumped 14.3% in last one year as compared to a 8.89% rally in NIFTY and a 20.92% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 46.1 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Bosch_19930465954_378.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siemens-energy-india-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1666293</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666293</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Siemens Energy India Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2262.9, down 0.29% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25214.4. The Sensex is at 82152.2, down 0.03%.Siemens Energy India Ltd has eased around 13.51% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Siemens Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.22% in last one month and is currently quoting at 33360, up 0.56% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.16 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 73.1 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiemensEnergyIndiaLtd_11731431_93274.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jaiprakash-power-ventures-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1666294</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666294</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 15.34, down 0.32% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25214.4. The Sensex is at 82152.2, down 0.03%.Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd has lost around 13.77% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.22% in last one month and is currently quoting at 33360, up 0.56% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 414.45 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 308.53 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 14.27 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JPPowerVen_30572663793_14266.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Inox Wind Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inox-wind-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1666295</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666295</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Inox Wind Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Inox Wind Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 106.65, down 1.32% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25214.4. The Sensex is at 82152.2, down 0.03%.Inox Wind Ltd has lost around 15.74% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Inox Wind Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.22% in last one month and is currently quoting at 33360, up 0.56% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 71.36 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 98.96 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 106.2, down 1.61% on the day. Inox Wind Ltd tumbled 30.76% in last one year as compared to a 8.89% rally in NIFTY and a 0.77% fall in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 31.78 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InoxWind_85471052866_43989.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Cards & Payment Services Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-cards-payment-services-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1666296</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666296</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBI Cards & Payment Services Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

SBI Cards & Payment Services Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 795.75, down 1.98% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25214.4. The Sensex is at 82152.2, down 0.03%.SBI Cards & Payment Services Ltd has lost around 8.77% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which SBI Cards & Payment Services Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.49% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27200.6, down 0.48% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 8.99 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 11.92 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 796.7, down 1.99% on the day. SBI Cards & Payment Services Ltd jumped 5.18% in last one year as compared to a 8.89% rally in NIFTY and a 19.51% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 40.24 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SBICardsPaymentServicesLtd_48121040_20149.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Piramal Pharma Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/piramal-pharma-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1666297</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666297</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Piramal Pharma Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Piramal Pharma Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 157.07, down 0.47% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.07% on the day, quoting at 25214.4. The Sensex is at 82152.2, down 0.03%.Piramal Pharma Ltd has eased around 11.61% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Piramal Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 5.58% in last one month and is currently quoting at 21714.3, down 0.31% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 23.5 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 30.73 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 156.7, down 0.88% on the day. Piramal Pharma Ltd tumbled 35.18% in last one year as compared to a 8.89% rally in NIFTY and a 1.76% fall in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 29.71 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PiramalPharmaLtd_79555676_76066.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with minor cuts; consumer durables shares tumble; VIX zooms 7.93%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-minor-cuts-consumer-durables-shares-tumble-vix-zooms-793/1666290</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666290</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded near the flatline with some negative points in the afternoon trade as global uncertainties and patchy earnings weighed on risk appetite.

The key equity benchmarks traded near the flatline with some negative points in the afternoon trade as global uncertainties and patchy earnings weighed on risk appetite. The Nifty traded below the 25,250 mark. Oil & gas, metal and media shares advanced while consumer durables, IT and private bank shares declined. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex shed 65.95 points or 0.08% to 82,116.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 24.15 points or 0.09% to 25,212.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.65% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.58%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,424 shares rose and 2,715 shares fell. A total of 155 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 7.93% to 13.74. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 5,01,76,200 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:20 IST on Wednesday (21 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.56 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Gainers & Losers: Eternal (up 5.73%), Interglobe Aviation (up 2.18%), Power Grid Corporation of India (up 1.65%), Ultratech Cement (up 1.60%) and Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (up 1.55%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. ICICI Bank (down 1.69%), Trent (down 1.05%), Apollo Hospitals Enterprise (down 0.93%), Tata Consumer Products (down 0.93%) and Eicher Motors (down 0.89%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Supreme Petrochem added 3.78%. The company’s standalone net profit fell 57.74% to Rs 30.15 crore on 10% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,264.69 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Persistent Systems declined 2.31% after the company reported a 6.79% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 439.4 crore despite of 5.52% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3778.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. IndiaMart InterMESH jumped 4.43% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 55.62% to Rs 188.3 crore on 13.35% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 401.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. AU Small Finance Bank (SFB) rose 0.63%. The company reported a 26.34% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 667.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 528.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25. SRF declined 5.66%. The company reported a 59.60% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 432.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 271.08 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations rose 6.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 3,712.53 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: European markets opened lower on Wednesday as investors awaited U.S. President Donald Trump’s address at the World Economic Forum later in the day. Most Asian market traded higher, while gold jumped to a record high level after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on countries resisting the transfer of Greenland to the United States. Spot gold prices rose over 1% to an all-time high of $4,813 per ounce as investors rushed into safe haven assets. On Saturday, Trump said that exports from eight European countries would face tariffs of 10% from Feb. 1, rising to 25% by June 1 if talks fail to deliver U.S. control of mineral-rich Greenland. He also threatened to slap 200% tariffs on French wine and champagne, following reports that President Emmanuel Macron was unwilling to join his proposed “Board of Peace.” Trump further criticized the U.K., calling its plan to transfer sovereignty of the Chagos Islands, which is home to a joint U.K.-U.S. military base, to Mauritius an “act of great stupidity,” citing the move as further justification for acquiring Greenland on national security grounds. European leaders have labeled President Donald Trump’s latest tariff threats “unacceptable” and are reportedly weighing retaliatory measures. France is said to be urging the European Union to deploy its strongest economic response tool, the so-called Anti-Coercion Instrument. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 870.74 points, or 1.76%, to end the session at 48,488.59. The S&P 500 dipped 2.06% to settle at 6,796.86. The Nasdaq Composite slid 2.39%, closing at 22,954.32. It was the worst session since October for all three major averages. U.S. Treasury yields spiked and the U.S. dollar declined as Trump’s threat caused a flight from U.S. assets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rallis India Q3 PAT slumps 82% YoY to Rs 2 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rallis-india-q3-pat-slumps-82-yoy-to-rs-2-cr/1666289</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666289</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 19.34% year on year (YoY) to Rs 623 crore in Q3 FY26, driven primarily by strong volume growth across businesses.

However, revenue from operations rose 19.34% year on year (YoY) to Rs 623 crore in Q3 FY26, driven primarily by strong volume growth across businesses. Profit before tax stood at Rs 1 crore in Q3 FY26, slumped 94.73% as against Rs 19 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported exceptional loss of Rs 35 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA were at Rs 58 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 44 crore in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, business performance was driven by strong volume traction across segments. Crop Care business registered healthy growth supported by improved field activity, customer engagement, and traction in key products. The Seeds business delivered strong growth during the quarter, aided by better volume performance and seasonal demand. The B2B business also recorded robust volume growth, driven by persistent customer engagement and traction in key accounts. During the quarter, the company successfully launched a new herbicide, Fateh Nxt™ and continued to strengthen its innovation pipeline. A three-way herbicide combination for wheat received an Indian patent, and the Mesotrione process patent was granted in the US, reinforcing Rallis’ focus on innovation and intellectual property. The business continued to leverage digital channels to drive customer and retailer engagement through digital vans, farmer database creation, and online engagement initiatives. Multiple farmer- and retailer-level schemes were rolled out to enhance market reach and engagement. For the nine months ended 31 December 2025, Rallis reported revenue of Rs 2,441 crore, up 9% year-on-year. EBITDA rose 18% to Rs 362 crore, supported by improved gross contribution and operational efficiencies. Profit before tax (PBT), after exceptional items, stood at Rs 267 crore, compared with Rs 227 crore in the same period last year, while profit after tax (PAT) grew 26% to Rs 199 crore, reflecting sustained profitability improvement. For the nine-month period, Crop Care business recorded steady growth, supported by volume expansion and product mix improvement. The B2B business continued to grow on the back of volume-led expansion and selective price improvements. Dr. Gyanendra Shukla, MD & CEO, Rallis India, said: “Q3 saw volume-led growth across businesses, supported by focused execution, strong customer engagement, and disciplined cost management. While demand remained moderate with seasonal fluctuations, we continued to strengthen our product portfolio, digital engagement, and innovation pipeline. Our focus remains on improving quality of sales, driving volume expansion, and preparing strongly for the upcoming seasons through product launches and market activation initiatives.” Rallis India, a Tata Group company Group Co., has a history of over 150 years. The company is into manufacturing of Agrochemicals and is present across the value chain of agriculture inputs - from seeds to organic plant growth nutrients. Rallis is also in the business of contract manufacturing for global corporations. Shares of Rallis India rose 2.15% to Rs 235.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RallisIndia_35352177968_465.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[D B Corp Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/d-b-corp-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1666286</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666286</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[D B Corp Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

D B Corp Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 258.85, up 3.05% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.19% on the day, quoting at 25279.3. The Sensex is at 82284.25, up 0.13%. D B Corp Ltd has slipped around 0.02% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which D B Corp Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 3.03% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1360.4, down 0.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.19 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 71455 shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 13.91 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DBCorp_72647549474_28589.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd spurts 1.93%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-ltd-spurts-193-gains-for-third-straight-session/1666287</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666287</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 693.9, up 1.93% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.19% on the day, quoting at 25279.3. The Sensex is at 82284.25, up 0.13%. Hindustan Zinc Ltd has risen around 14.41% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Hindustan Zinc Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 7.3% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11374.45, up 0.64% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 196.44 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 144.69 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 691.7, up 1.71% on the day. Hindustan Zinc Ltd is up 47.84% in last one year as compared to a 9.17% spurt in NIFTY and a 35.15% spurt in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 24.64 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee tanks to new low near 91.50 per US dollar, NIFTY tests and half month low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-tanks-to-new-low-near-9150-per-us-dollar-nifty-tests-and-half-month-low/1666288</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666288</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee tanked to a new low on Wednesday, witnessing sustained losses and breaking beyond 91 per US dollar mark.

Indian Rupee tanked to a new low on Wednesday, witnessing sustained losses and breaking beyond 91 per US dollar mark. INR has lost 50 paise to reach 91.47 per US dollar as local equities extended downward trajectory. Meanwhile, Local stocks stayed slippery as headline index NIFTY tested lowest in three and half months, adding to recent losses. NSE Nifty 50 index broke under 25000 mark. The index has lost more than 3% this month so far.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/general-business-1241245_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>