<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:00:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Asian Paints Ltd Spikes 0.87%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/asian-paints-ltd-spikes-087/1663280</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663280</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Asian Paints Ltd rose 0.87% today to trade at Rs 2839.

Asian Paints Ltd rose 0.87% today to trade at Rs 2839. The BSE Consumer Durables index is up 0.4% to quote at 61485.6. The index is up 1.08 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Titan Company Ltd increased 0.39% and Voltas Ltd added 0.19% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went down 5.65 % over last one year compared to the 9.45% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Asian Paints Ltd has lost 4.32% over last one month compared to 1.08% gain in BSE Consumer Durables index and 0.44% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1648 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 32813 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2985.5 on 04 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 2125 on 04 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AsianPaints_3886867460_34.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SJVN Ltd Slips 1.62%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sjvn-ltd-slips-162/1663281</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663281</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SJVN Ltd fell 1.62% today to trade at Rs 86.21.

SJVN Ltd fell 1.62% today to trade at Rs 86.21. The BSE Utilities index is down 0.45% to quote at 5313.26. The index is up 4.07 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Denta Water & Infra Solutions Ltd decreased 1.57% and Ion Exchange (India) Ltd lost 1.06% on the day. The BSE Utilities index went up 1.16 % over last one year compared to the 9.45% surge in benchmark SENSEX. SJVN Ltd has added 16.42% over last one month compared to 4.07% gain in BSE Utilities index and 0.44% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1.08 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 9.96 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 109.65 on 06 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 69.82 on 19 Dec 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SJVN_64650197956_12076.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR stays pressured as dollar regains momentum ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-stays-pressured-as-dollar-regains-momentum/1663278</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663278</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee continues to stay pressured beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark in opening trades o Tuesday.

The Indian rupee continues to stay pressured beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark in opening trades o Tuesday. INR opened at Rs 90.22 per dollar but recovered slightly to a high of 90.10 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee stayed weak for the fourth straight session and closed 10 paise lower at 90.30 against the US dollar as a surge in geopolitical uncertainty has bolstered the greenback's appeal. Renewed geopolitical uncertainties after the US military intervention in Venezuela fuelled dollar demand worldwide, while a sluggish domestic stock market, triggered sell off in foreign capital and dented investor sentiments further. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty ended down around 0.4 percent and 0.3 percent.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NBCC bags Rs 134-cr work orders in Odisha]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nbcc-bags-rs-134-cr-work-orders-in-odisha/1663274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663274</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders, received in the ordinary course of business, include a Rs 45.87-crore contract from Maharaja Sriram Chandra Bhanja Deo University, Odisha, for construction, repair, and renovation works at its campus in Baripada, Mayurbhanj district, under the PM-USHA scheme.

The orders, received in the ordinary course of business, include a Rs 45.87-crore contract from Maharaja Sriram Chandra Bhanja Deo University, Odisha, for construction, repair, and renovation works at its campus in Baripada, Mayurbhanj district, under the PM-USHA scheme. The company has also bagged an Rs 88.18-crore order from the Odisha School Programme Authority, Bhubaneswar, for execution of civil works under the Godabarisha Mishra Adarsha Prathamika Vidyalaya Scheme. Both contracts have been awarded by domestic entities and involve project management consultancy services. The projects will be executed as per the terms and conditions specified by the respective clients, NBCC said. NBCC (India) is in business and operates in three major segments, namely project management consultancy, real estate, and engineering procurement & construction. The company's consolidated net profit advanced 25.21% to Rs 156.68 crore on an 18.99% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,910.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of NBCC (India) rose 0.71% to Rs 120.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NBCC_1807915630_13166.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IndusInd Bank total deposits drop 4% YoY in Q3 FY26.]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indusind-bank-total-deposits-drop-4-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663272</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Retail deposits and deposits from small business customers amounted to Rs 1,84,550 crore as of 31 December 2025, registering de-growth of 2.22% compared with Rs 1,88,731 crore as of 31st December 2024.

Retail deposits and deposits from small business customers amounted to Rs 1,84,550 crore as of 31 December 2025, registering de-growth of 2.22% compared with Rs 1,88,731 crore as of 31st December 2024. Net advances declined 13.1% YoY to Rs 3,18,844 crore as of 31st December 2025. CASA Ratio fell to 30.3% as of 31st December 2025 from 34.9% as of 31st December 2024. Indusind Bank offers a wide range of products and services for individuals and corporates, including microfinance, personal loans, personal and commercial vehicle loans, credit cards and SME loans. The bank reported standalone net loss of Rs 444.79 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with net profit of Rs 1,325.45 crore in Q2 FY25. Total income fell 10.9% to Rs 13,256.59 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 14,870.18 crore in Q2 FY25. The counter rose 0.28% to Rs 902.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndusIndBankLtd_64968625_5531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at negative opening for key indices]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-negative-opening-for-key-indices/1663266</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663266</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 30.00 points, indicating a negative opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 30.00 points, indicating a negative opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 36.25 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,764.07 crore in the Indian equity market on 05 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 3,015.05 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets opened mixed Tuesday, building on a record-breaking rally in global stocks as investors continued to assess ongoing geopolitical tensions following the U.S.′ attack on Venezuela and capture of ousted leader Nicolas Maduro. U.S. big oil got a boost from the country's military raid at the weekend that captured Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Crude oil eased back after rising $1 a barrel overnight as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Overall, however, the events had a limited effect on risk sentiment, with equities driven more by momentum and currencies focused on macroeconomic data. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. Trump plans to meet with executives from U.S. oil companies later this week to discuss boosting Venezuelan oil production, media reports stated. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose even after the U.S.′ attack on Venezuela, as crude oil prices advanced and investors bet the action would not lead to broader geopolitical conflict. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 594.79 points, or 1.23%, to close at 48,977.18. The 30-stock index also hit a new all-time high in the session. The S&P 500 advanced 0.64% and ended at 6,902.05. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.69%, settling at 23,395.82. Domestic Market: Domestic equity market ended marginally lower on Monday after a choppy session. Early optimism from strong corporate updates faded as investors turned cautious amid rising geopolitical tensions linked to U.S. military action in Venezuela. The Sensex and Nifty moved between small gains and losses through the day. The Nifty finally settled near the 26,250 mark as profit booking emerged in select heavyweight stocks. Sectoral cues were mixed. IT and oil and gas shares remained under pressure, while FMCG and consumer durables showed resilience. Overall sentiment stayed guarded yet constructive, suggesting consolidation rather than a broad based shift in market direction. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 322.39 points or 0.38% to 85,439.62. The Nifty 50 index dropped 78.25 points or 0.30% to 26,250.30.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: IndusInd Bank, Axis Bank, Kotak Mahindra Bank, Tata Motors PV]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-indusind-bank-axis-bank-kotak-mahindra-bank-tata-motors-pv/1663264</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663264</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 6 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 6 January 2026. Stocks in Spotlight: IndusInd Bank's deposits fell 3.8% YoY to Rs 3,94,022 crore as of 31st December 2025. On a sequential basis however, deposits rose 1.1% from Rs 3,89,600 crore as of 30 September 2025. Net advances tumbled 13.1% YoY to Rs 3,66,889 crore as of 31st December 2025. Axis Bank’s total deposits jumped 15% to Rs 12,60,800 crore as on 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 10,95,900 crore as on 31st December 2024. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicle's wholly owned subsidiary Jaguar land rover (JLR) wholesale volumes for the third quarter were 59,200 units (excluding the Chery Jaguar Land Rover China JV (‘CJLR’) ), down 43.3% YoY and down 10 .6% QoQ. Retail sales for the third quarter of 79,600 units (including CJLR ) were down 25.1 % YoY and down 6.7% QoQ. Production returned to normal levels only by mid -November post the cyber incident. Utkarsh Small Finance Bank (SFB) total deposits jumped 4.5% to Rs 21,087 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 20,172 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross loan portfolio fell 3.9% YoY to Rs 18,306 crore in Q3 FY26. Dabur India said that it expects consolidated revenue to grow in the mid-single digits with operating profit and Profit after Tax to grow ahead of revenuein Q3 FY26. During the quarter, early signs of demand recovery were witnessed, aided by GST rate revisions. Post trade stabilisation, consumer sentiment improved in urban and rural areas. Rural demand continued to outperform urban demand this quarter as well. Kotak Mahindra Bank’s average total deposits climbed 14.7% to Rs 5,26,025 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 5,10,138 crore as of 31st December 2024. Average advances jumped 16.2% YoY to Rs 465,879 crore as of 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Highway Infrastructure bags Rs 32-crore LOA from NHAI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/highway-infrastructure-bags-rs-32-crore-loa-from-nhai/1663263</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663263</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the engagement of a user fee agency at the Jawar Fee Plaza located at Km 37.100 on the Mathura–Devinagar Bypass, covering the stretch from design kilometre 0.000 to design kilometre 66.000 of National Highway-530B in Uttar Pradesh.

According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the engagement of a user fee agency at the Jawar Fee Plaza located at Km 37.100 on the Mathura–Devinagar Bypass, covering the stretch from design kilometre 0.000 to design kilometre 66.000 of National Highway-530B in Uttar Pradesh. The scope of work also includes the upkeep and maintenance of adjacent toilet blocks, along with recouping consumable items. The total value of the order stands at Rs 32,00,77,777 and the contract is to be executed within a period of one year. The company clarified that neither its promoters nor members of the promoter group have any interest in the entity awarding the contract. It further stated that the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions under applicable regulatory norms. Highway Infrastructure (HIL) is a Madhya Pradesh-based infrastructure development and management company. Its core operations span tollway collection, EPC infra projects, and real estate development. The firm has completed 27 tollway projects and currently operates 4, deploying advanced ETC and ANPR technologies. The EPC arm has delivered over 66 projects across roads, bridges, and irrigation works under schemes such as PMAY and PMGSY. In real estate, HIL is expanding its footprint in Indore with residential and integrated township projects. For FY25, toll collection contributed over 77% of revenue, followed by EPC and real estate. As of 31 May 2025, the company’s order book stood at Rs 666.31 crore. For the twelve months ended 31 March 2025, HIL reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 22.40 crore on revenue of Rs 495.72 crore. The counter slipped 2% to Rs 58.66 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HighwayInfrastructureLtd_53703943_66257.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>