<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:38:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee posts marginal gain]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-posts-marginal-gain/1664428</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664428</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed slightly higher at 90.2400 per Dollar on Monday (12 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.2600 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper soars more than 2% as Dow and S&P 500 hit new record closing highs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-soars-more-than-2-as-dow-and-sp-500-hit-new-record-closing-highs/1664427</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664427</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Copper zoomed impressively as positive cues from equities and a stellar run in metals boosted the counter.

Copper zoomed impressively as positive cues from equities and a stellar run in metals boosted the counter. COMEX Copper broke above $6 per pound and currently trades at $6.03 per pound, up 2.20% on the day. The metal has recorded good gains in last week. Meanwhile, Asian markets moved up with China's Shanghai Composite Index rallying 1.1% and the Hang Seng Index of the Hong Kong Stock Exchange gaining 1.44%. European markets are also supported in cautious trades. The US stocks moved mostly higher over the course of the trading day. The major averages all climbed firmly into positive territory, with the Dow and the S&P 500 reaching new record closing highs. For the first full trading week of the new year, the Dow added 2.3%, while the Nasdaq and the S&P 500 jumped by 1.9% and 1.6%, respectively. MCX Copper futures are trading at Rs 1316.10 per kg, up 2.72% on the day after hitting a high around Rs 1319 per kg.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-city-stock-market-data-and-charts-on-skyscrapers-b_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1664411</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664411</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2025 futures closed at 25,880, a premium of 89.75 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,790.25 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2025 futures closed at 25,880, a premium of 89.75 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,790.25 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index jumped 106.95 points or 0.42% to 25,790.25. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 4.05% to 11.37. HDFC Bank, Tata Consultancy Services and Reliance Industries were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/investor-watching-the-change-of-stock-market-on-laptop-pict_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Coking Coal subscribed 33.60 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-coking-coal-subscribed-3360-times/1664412</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664412</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 11,65,79,29,200 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (12 January 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 11,65,79,29,200 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (12 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 33.60 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The offer is a pure offer-for-sale (OFS) of up to 46.57 crore equity shares of face value Rs 10 each by Coal India. At the upper price band of Rs 23 per equity share, Coal India will raise Rs 1,071 crore. The IPO includes a reservation of up to 2.32 crore equity shares for eligible employees and up to 4.66 crore shares for eligible shareholders of Coal India under the shareholder reservation portion. Ahead of the IPO of Bharat Coking Coal on 8 January 2026, the company raised Rs 273.13 crore from anchor investors by allotting 11.87 crore shares at Rs 23 each to 15 anchor investors. Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) produces coking coal, non-coking coal, and washed coal. BCCL is India's largest producer of coking coal and operates primarily in the Jharia coalfields of Jharkhand and the Raniganj coalfields of West Bengal. It is the wholly owned subsidiary of Coal India and was conferred with Mini Ratna status in 2014. The primary product is coking coal, catering to the steel and power industries. BCCL had an estimated coking coal reserve of approximately 7,910 million tonnes (mt) as of 01 April 2024. It accounted for 58.50% of the total domestic coking coal production in India in FY 2025. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 123.88 crore and sales of Rs 5,659 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JPY/INR futures end lower ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jpyinr-futures-end-lower/1664408</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664408</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures ended mildly lower at 90.25.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures ended mildly lower at 90.25. EUR/INR and GBP/INR added 0.31% and 0.43% to end at 105.51 and 121.56 respectively. Meanwhile, JPY/INR ended lower by 0.17% to end at 57.30.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TCS Q3 PAT drops 12% QoQ; board declares special dividend of Rs 46/ share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tcs-q3-pat-drops-12-qoq-board-declares-special-dividend-of-rs-46-share/1664391</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664391</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The decline in profitability was impacted due to one-time exceptional charges including Rs 2,120 crore related to the statutory impact of new labour codes and it also made a provision towards a legal claim of of Rs 1,010 crore during the December quarter.

The decline in profitability was impacted due to one-time exceptional charges including Rs 2,120 crore related to the statutory impact of new labour codes and it also made a provision towards a legal claim of of Rs 1,010 crore during the December quarter. On year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 13.92%, while revenue from operations increased 4.87% in Q3 FY26. The company’s YoY performance was supported by growth in key verticals, led by Life Sciences & Healthcare (+2.2%), along with steady gains in Energy, Resources and Utilities (ERU) (+2.2%) and Technology & Services (+1.7%) in Q3 FY26. The company’s order book total contract value (TCV) stood at $9.3 billion in Q3 December 2025, lower than $10 billion in Q2 September 2025 and $9.4 billion in Q1 June 2025. In constant currency terms, revenue growth stood at 0.8% QoQ in the Q3 FY26. Revenue from annualized AI Services stood at $1.8 billion, registering a 17.3% QoQ growth in constant currency. Operating and net margins stood at 25.2% and 20% during the quarter. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared a third interim dividend of Rs 11 per share and special dividend of Rs 46 per equity share of Rs 1 each of the company. The record date has been fixed as on Saturday, 17 January 2026 and payout will be made on Tuesday, 3 February 2026. K Krithivasan, chief executive officer (CEO) and managing director (MD), said “The growth momentum we witnessed in Q2FY26 continued in Q3FY26. We remain steadfast in our ambition to become the world’s largest AI-led technology services company, guided by a comprehensive five-pillar strategy. Our AI services now generate $1.8 billion in annualized revenue, reflecting the significant value we provide to clients through targeted investments across the entire AI stack, from Infrastructure to Intelligence.” Sudeep Kunnumal, chief HR officer, said “Our associates are at the heart of our transformation into an AIfirst enterprise. As of this quarter, there are over 217,000 associates with advanced AI skills, directly powering client success at scale. We doubled our intake of fresh graduates with higher order skills, rapidly expanding our next-generation talent pool. The passion and commitment our associates show in mastering next-gen capabilities gives us the confidence to innovate responsibly and deliver sustainable value as AI reshapes the services landscape.” TCS is a digital transformation and technology partner of choice for industry-leading organizations worldwide. The counter rose 0.86% to end at Rs 3235.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TCS_30661368_5400.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty snap five-day losing streak on trade optimism]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-snap-five-day-losing-streak-on-trade-optimism/1664405</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664405</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks snapped a five-day losing streak on Monday after a sharp intraday rebound.

Domestic equity benchmarks snapped a five-day losing streak on Monday after a sharp intraday rebound. The move was driven by positive global cues, value buying and reassuring comments on India-US trade ties from newly appointed US Ambassador to India Sergio Gor. The Sensex, which was down over 700 points in early trade, recovered more than 1,000 points from the day’s low by the close. The Nifty also climbed back above the 25,790 level as sentiment improved, with metals, PSU banks and energy stocks leading the recovery. The market reacted after Gor said India and the US remain actively engaged on trade and that talks are continuing despite differences. He also conveyed greetings from President Donald Trump to Prime Minister Narendra Modi. Sentiment received an added boost after Gor announced that India would be invited next month to join PaxSilica. The recovery was broad-based. Bank Nifty rebounded sharply, while midcap and smallcap indices erased a large part of their early losses. Export-oriented stocks also gained as fears of an immediate tariff escalation eased after weeks of sustained selling and foreign fund outflows. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 301.93 points or 0.36% to 83,878.17. The Nifty 50 index gained 106.95 points or 0.42% to 25,790.25. In the past five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%. State Bank of India (up 1.40%), ICICI Bank (up 1.12%) and Reliance Industries (up 0.59%) were major drags on the Nifty today. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.41% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.68%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,569 shares rose and 2,724 shares fell. A total of 192 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 4.05% to 11.37. Economy: India’s consumer inflation rose to 1.33% in December, accelerating from 0.71% in the prior month. The rise in consumer inflation was mainly driven by food prices, while fuel and light inflation rate eased in December. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.48% to 6.604 as compared with the previous close of 6.636. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1700 compared with its close of 90.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement added 1.91% to Rs 141,470. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.29% to 98.84. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.72% to 4.202. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement declined 32 cents or 0.51% to $63.02 a barrel. Global Markets: The Dow Jones Futures were down 375 points, indicating a weak opening in the US market today. European were mixed on Monday as investors weighed geopolitical developments in Iran and renewed pressure on Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Most Asian markets ended higher, tracking gains on Wall Street from last week after a US jobs report showed that the unemployment rate fell, signaling resilience in the labor market. South Korea’s Kospi closed at an all-time high today as Asia-Pacific markets advanced. Japanese markets were closed for a holiday. Investors will be keeping an eye on oil prices as Iran entered a third week of protests, which have reportedly seen more than 500 people killed. President Donald Trump is weighing options for intervention in Iran, media reports said. On Sunday, Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s coalition partner, Hirofumi Yoshimura, said that she may call an early general election. His comments come after domestic media reported that Takaichi was considering a snap election in February, citing government sources. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 rose to new highs on Friday, notching a weekly gain, following the release of the latest jobs report. The broad market index closed up 0.65% to 6,966.28, a fresh record close. It also notched a new all-time intraday high in the session. The Nasdaq Composite gained 0.81% to 23,671.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 237.96 points, or 0.48%, to end at 49,504.07, scoring a new closing record as well. The December jobs report showed nonfarm payrolls increasing by 50,000 last month, less than the 73,000 estimate that was widely reported in the media. That data, though slightly weaker than expected, showed a U.S. economy that’s still trudging along, with investors anticipating that growth will ramp up. The unemployment rate inched down to 4.4%, while widely circulated media reports had provided a forecast of 4.5%. Traders took that as a sign that improvement in the economy would happen soon. Stocks in Spotlight: TCS rose 0.86%. The IT major reported a 14% year-on-year (YoY) decline in consolidated net profit for the December quarter at Rs 10,657 crore, compared with Rs 12,380 crore in the year-ago period. The profit after tax (PAT) is attributable to the company’s shareholders. Revenue from operations in Q3 rose 5% YoY to Rs 67,087 crore, up from Rs 63,973 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous financial year. The company announced an interim dividend of Rs 57 per equity share for FY26, comprising a third interim dividend of Rs 11 per share and a special dividend of Rs 46 per equity share. The company has fixed 17 January 2026, as the record date. The company's order book total contract value (TCV) stood at $9.3 billion in Q3 December 2025, lower than $10 billion in Q2 September 2025 and $9.4 billion in Q1 June 2025. Avenue Supermarts (Dmart) rose 0.75%. The company consolidated net profit rallied 18.26% to Rs 855.92 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 723.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 13.32% to Rs 18,100.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15,972.55 crore in Q3 FY26. Tejas Networks tumbled 9.40% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 196.55 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 165.67 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Manappuram Finance rose 3.17% after the company denied a media report claiming regulatory concerns had delayed its proposed transaction with Bain Capital-linked entities. The company termed the report factually incorrect and speculative. KP Green Engineering rose 3.28% after the company announced its largest-ever order win, securing advance work orders worth Rs 819 crore from BSNL under the 4G Saturation Project. Hindustan Zinc rose 3.40%, as silver prices surged to fresh record highs. Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) gained 3.55% after the company’s consolidated net profit rallied 15.42% to Rs 1,381.36 crore on 26.80% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 6,135.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Globus Spirits slipped 3.33%. The company’s standalone net profit skyrocketed over fifteen times to Rs 31.42 crore on a 19.1% increase in revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) to Rs 716.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shakti Pumps India jumped 5.19% after the company received letter of award (LoA) for setting up 16,780 stand‐alone off‐grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems (SPWPS) pumps in Karnataka. The contract is valued at Rs 654.03 crore and is expected to be executed on or before 31st March 2026. Signatureglobal (India) dropped 6.47% after the company flagged a slowdown in demand and said it will miss its earlier pre-sales guidance for FY26. In a regulatory filing on 11 January 2026, the real estate developer reported a 27% decline in pre-sales to Rs 20,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with 27,700 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Maruti Suzuki India added 0.65%. The company said that its board approved the acquisition of land at the Khoraj Industrial Estate from Gujarat Industrial Development Corporation (GIDC) to expand production capacity, driven by growing market demand, including exports. Cupid advanced 2.30% after the company announced that a meeting of the board of directors will be held on Thursday, 29 January 2026, to consider the declaration of bonus shares and the Q3 results. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) rose 0.34%. The company reported a 25.41% increase in production to 68,992 units in December 2025, compared with 55,015 units in December 2024. Embassy Developments hit an upper circuit of 5% after the company reported pre-sales of approximately Rs 1,392 crore in Q3 FY26, up 240% QoQ from Rs 409 crore in Q2 FY26. Alembic Pharmaceuticals shed 0.49%. The company announced that it has received tentative approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) for its supplemental Abbreviated New Drug Application (sANDA) for Bosutinib Tablets, 400 mg. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 11,65,18,17,600 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:57 IST on Monday (12 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 33.58 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concepts-picture-id519261614_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mild recovery in INR led by rebound in domestic equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mild-recovery-in-inr-led-by-rebound-in-domestic-equities/1664370</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664370</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee recovered from low levels and settled 2 paise higher at 90.16 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday on weak American currency and sliding crude oil prices.

The Indian rupee recovered from low levels and settled 2 paise higher at 90.16 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday on weak American currency and sliding crude oil prices. Equity market sentiment also improved after the new US envoy to India, Sergio Gor, said that both sides are actively engaged in firming up a trade deal. After opening weak and languishing in negative territory till about an hour past noon, Indian shares recovered and moved above the flat line on Monday, lifting the benchmark indexes Sensex and the Nifty50 to a positive close. The benchmark BSE Sensex settled with a gain of 301.93 points or 0.36% at 83,878.17, more than 1,000 points off the day's low of 82,861.07. The National Stock Exchange's Nifty50, which dropped to a low of 25,473.40, settled at 25,790.25, gaining 106.95 points or 0.42%. However, a volatile geopolitical situation kept the domestic currency under pressure.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 302 pts higher; metal index outperforms; VIX rallied 4.05% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-302-pts-higher-metal-index-outperforms-vix-rallied-405/1664344</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664344</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with decent gains today, snapping a five-day losing streak, aided by positive global cues and encouraging remarks by US Ambassador to India Sergio Gor.

The key equity barometers ended with decent gains today, snapping a five-day losing streak, aided by positive global cues and encouraging remarks by US Ambassador to India Sergio Gor. The market rebounded from oversold levels, with buying momentum picking up in the afternoon session. Investors are expected to continue tracking developments on the India–US trade deal, Q3 earnings announcements, and geopolitical developments. The Nifty settled above the 25,750 mark after touching an intraday low of 25,473.40 in early afternoon trade. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 301.93 points or 0.36% to 83,878.17. The Nifty 50 index gained 106.95 points or 0.42% to 25,790.25. In the past five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.41% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.68%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 4.05% to 11.37. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Metal index (up 1.99%), the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 0.65%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 0.54%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Media index (down 1.55%), the Nifty Realty index (down 1.22%) and the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.41%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: India's foreign exchange reserves fell by $9.809 billion to $686.801 billion in the week ended January 02, 2026, showed data shared by the Reserve Bank of India on Friday. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, fell by $7.622 billion, standing at $551.99 billion, the data showed. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund dropped by $25 million to $18.778 billion, while the country’s reserve position in the IMF decreased by $105 million to $4.771 billion as of December 26. Gold reserves, too, decreased by $2.058 billion during the week to $111.262 billion. India’s consumer inflation rose to 1.33% in December, accelerating from 0.71% in the prior month. Inflation has remained below the lower tolerance band of the Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI) 2–6% target range for five of the past six months but is now expected to move closer to the central bank’s 4% target as base effects turn unfavourable. India-US trade deal updates Sergio Gor took charge as US Ambassador to India on Monday and said India and the United States remain actively engaged on trade issues. He said the next round of talks could take place as early as tomorrow. Gor stressed that dialogue continues despite tariff and market-access differences. He described the relationship as resilient and said disagreements do not derail broader cooperation. Gor added that President Donald Trump has sent his best wishes to Prime Minister Narendra Modi. He also announced that India will be invited next month to join Pax Silica as a full member, expanding cooperation in semiconductors, AI and critical supply chains alongside partners such as Japan, South Korea, the UK and Israel. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.48% to 6.604 as compared with the previous close of 6.636. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1700 compared with its close of 90.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement added 1.91% to Rs 141,470. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.29% to 98.84. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.72% to 4.202. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement declined 32 cents or 0.51% to $63.02 a barrel. Global Markets: European traded lower on Monday as investors weighed geopolitical developments in Iran and renewed pressure on Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Most Asian markets ended higher, tracking gains on Wall Street from last week after a US jobs report showed that the unemployment rate fell, signaling resilience in the labor market. South Korea’s Kospi closed at an all-time high today as Asia-Pacific markets advanced. Japanese markets were closed for a holiday. Investors will be keeping an eye on oil prices as Iran entered a third week of protests, which have reportedly seen more than 500 people killed. President Donald Trump is weighing options for intervention in Iran, media reports said. On Sunday, Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s coalition partner, Hirofumi Yoshimura, said that she may call an early general election. His comments come after domestic media reported that Takaichi was considering a snap election in February, citing government sources. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 rose to new highs on Friday, notching a weekly gain, following the release of the latest jobs report. The broad market index closed up 0.65% to 6,966.28, a fresh record close. It also notched a new all-time intraday high in the session. The Nasdaq Composite gained 0.81% to 23,671.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 237.96 points, or 0.48%, to end at 49,504.07, scoring a new closing record as well. The December jobs report showed nonfarm payrolls increasing by 50,000 last month, less than the 73,000 estimate that was widely reported in the media. That data, though slightly weaker than expected, showed a U.S. economy that’s still trudging along, with investors anticipating that growth will ramp up. The unemployment rate inched down to 4.4%, while widely circulated media reports had provided a forecast of 4.5%. Traders took that as a sign that improvement in the economy would happen soon.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts fall further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-fall-further/1664343</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664343</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

Large currency speculators reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 30538 contracts in the data reported through January 06, 2025. This was a weekly drop of 2669 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index rises 1.99%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-rises-199/1664340</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664340</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index closed up 1.99% at 11315.75 today.

Nifty Metal index closed up 1.99% at 11315.75 today. The index is up 7.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Hindustan Copper Ltd gained 4.78%, Hindustan Zinc Ltd rose 3.59% and Vedanta Ltd jumped 2.87%. The Nifty Metal index is up 37.00% over last one year compared to the 10.07% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Media index is down 1.55% and Nifty Commodities index gained 1.32% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.42% to close at 25790.25 while the SENSEX added 0.36% to close at 83878.17 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/arrows-399970__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends higher, snapping five-day losses; Nifty settles above 25,750 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-higher-snapping-five-day-losses-nifty-settles-above-25750-mark/1664339</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664339</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices ended with modest gains on Monday, snapping a five-day losing streak, amid positive global cues supported by encouraging comments from the US Ambassador to India, Sergio Gor.

The domestic equity indices ended with modest gains on Monday, snapping a five-day losing streak, amid positive global cues supported by encouraging comments from the US Ambassador to India, Sergio Gor. The market recovered from oversold levels and rebounded during the afternoon session. Investors will continue to monitor developments related to the India–US trade deal, Q3 earnings, and other geopolitical news. The Nifty settled above the 25,750 mark after touching an intraday low of 25,473.40 in early afternoon trade. Metal, PSU bank and oil & gas shares advanced, while media, realty and pharma shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 301.93 points or 0.36% to 83,878.17. The Nifty 50 index gained 106.95 points or 0.42% to 25,790.25. In the past five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.41% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.68%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,569 shares rose and 2,721 shares fell. A total of 200 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 4.05% to 11.37. Economy: India's foreign exchange reserves fell by $9.809 billion to $686.801 billion in the week ended January 02, 2026, showed data shared by the Reserve Bank of India on Friday. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, fell by $7.622 billion, standing at $551.99 billion, the data showed. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund dropped by $25 million to $18.778 billion, while the country’s reserve position in the IMF decreased by $105 million to $4.771 billion as of December 26. Gold reserves, too, decreased by $2.058 billion during the week to $111.262 billion. India’s consumer inflation rose to 1.33% in December, accelerating from 0.71% in the prior month. Inflation has remained below the lower tolerance band of the Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI) 2–6% target range for five of the past six months but is now expected to move closer to the central bank’s 4% target as base effects turn unfavourable. India-US trade deal updates Sergio Gor took charge as US Ambassador to India on Monday and said India and the United States remain actively engaged on trade issues. He said the next round of talks could take place as early as tomorrow. Gor stressed that dialogue continues despite tariff and market-access differences. He described the relationship as resilient and said disagreements do not derail broader cooperation. Gor added that President Donald Trump has sent his best wishes to Prime Minister Narendra Modi. He also announced that India will be invited next month to join Pax Silica as a full member, expanding cooperation in semiconductors, AI and critical supply chains alongside partners such as Japan, South Korea, the UK and Israel. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 10,27,36,22,400 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Monday (12 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 29.61 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index climbed 1.99% to 11,315.75. The index tumbled 3.72% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Copper (up 4.59%), Hindustan Zinc (up 3.64%), Vedanta (up 2.94%), Tata Steel (up 2.64%), Steel Authority of India (up 2.24%), Hindalco Industries (up 2.11%), JSW Steel (up 2%), NMDC (up 1.50%), Jindal Steel (up 1.22%) and APL Apollo Tubes (up 0.86%) advanced. On the other hand, Welspun Corp (down 1.70%) and Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 0.96%), edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: Avenue Supermarts (Dmart) rose 0.49%. The company consolidated net profit rallied 18.26% to Rs 855.92 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 723.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 13.32% to Rs 18,100.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15,972.55 crore in Q3 FY26. Tejas Networks tumbled 8.45% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 196.55 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 165.67 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company’s total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) gained 3.84% after the company’s consolidated net profit rallied 15.42% to Rs 1,381.36 crore on 26.80% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 6,135.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Globus Spirits slipped 3.98%. The company’s standalone net profit skyrocketed over fifteen times to Rs 31.42 crore on a 19.1% increase in revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) to Rs 716.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shakti Pumps India jumped 5.19% after the company received letter of award (LoA) for setting up 16,780 stand‐alone off‐grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems (SPWPS) pumps in Karnataka. The contract is valued at Rs 654.03 crore and is expected to be executed on or before 31st March 2026. Signatureglobal (India) dropped 6.54% after the company flagged a slowdown in demand and said it will miss its earlier pre-sales guidance for FY26. In a regulatory filing on 11 January 2026, the real estate developer reported a 27% decline in pre-sales to Rs 20,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with 27,700 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Maruti Suzuki India added 0.65%. The company said that its board approved the acquisition of land at the Khoraj Industrial Estate from Gujarat Industrial Development Corporation (GIDC) to expand production capacity, driven by growing market demand, including exports. Cupid advanced 2.30% after the company announced that a meeting of the board of directors will be held on Thursday, 29 January 2026, to consider the declaration of bonus shares and the Q3 results. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) rose 0.34%. The company reported a 25.41% increase in production to 68,992 units in December 2025, compared with 55,015 units in December 2024. Embassy Developments hit an upper circuit of 5% after the company reported pre-sales of approximately Rs 1,392 crore in Q3 FY26, up 240% QoQ from Rs 409 crore in Q2 FY26. Alembic Pharmaceuticals shed 0.23%. The company announced that it has received tentative approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) for its supplemental Abbreviated New Drug Application (sANDA) for Bosutinib Tablets, 400 mg. Global Markets: Most European markets declined on Monday as investors weighed geopolitical developments in Iran and renewed pressure on Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Most Asian markets ended higher, tracking gains on Wall Street from last week after a US jobs report showed that the unemployment rate fell, signaling resilience in the labor market. South Korea’s Kospi closed at an all-time high today as Asia-Pacific markets advanced. Japanese markets were closed for a holiday. Investors will be keeping an eye on oil prices as Iran entered a third week of protests, which have reportedly seen more than 500 people killed. President Donald Trump is weighing options for intervention in Iran, media reports said. On Sunday, Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s coalition partner, Hirofumi Yoshimura, said that she may call an early general election. His comments come after domestic media reported that Takaichi was considering a snap election in February, citing government sources. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 rose to new highs on Friday, notching a weekly gain, following the release of the latest jobs report. The broad market index closed up 0.65% to 6,966.28, a fresh record close. It also notched a new all-time intraday high in the session. The Nasdaq Composite gained 0.81% to 23,671.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 237.96 points, or 0.48%, to end at 49,504.07, scoring a new closing record as well. The December jobs report showed nonfarm payrolls increasing by 50,000 last month, less than the 73,000 estimate that was widely reported in the media. That data, though slightly weaker than expected, showed a U.S. economy that’s still trudging along, with investors anticipating that growth will ramp up. The unemployment rate inched down to 4.4%, while widely circulated media reports had provided a forecast of 4.5%. Traders took that as a sign that improvement in the economy would happen soon.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finance-background-picture-id625756386_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SPARC gains as board to mull fund raising on 14 Jan’26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sparc-gains-as-board-to-mull-fund-raising-on-14-jan26/1664338</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664338</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The board will evaluate a proposal to raise funds through a preferential issue, including convertible warrants, to an identified member of the promoter group, subject to receipt of all requisite approvals, consents and permissions, including from the company’s shareholders as well as the National Stock Exchange of India (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE).

The board will evaluate a proposal to raise funds through a preferential issue, including convertible warrants, to an identified member of the promoter group, subject to receipt of all requisite approvals, consents and permissions, including from the company’s shareholders as well as the National Stock Exchange of India (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE). Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company is a clinical stage bio-pharmaceutical company focused on continuously improving standards of care for patients globally, through innovation in therapeutics and delivery. The company had reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 75.85 crore in the quarter ended September 2025 as against net loss of Rs 107.33 crore during the previous quarter ended September 2024. Sales declined 38.88% to Rs 7.86 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SPARC_86853852407_27675.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI crude futures hover around $59 per barrel on Monday]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-futures-hover-around-59-per-barrel-on-monday/1664337</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664337</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude futures hovered around $59 per barrel on Monday, extending last week’s gains as geopolitical tensions continued to underpin prices.

WTI crude futures hovered around $59 per barrel on Monday, extending last week’s gains as geopolitical tensions continued to underpin prices. Escalating protests in Iran, now in their third week, have heightened concerns over potential supply disruptions, with authorities signaling a tougher response and sharp rhetoric exchanged between Tehran and Washington. Uncertainty also lingered over Venezuela’s crude exports as shifting US policy and sanctions clouded the outlook, while President Donald Trump warned Cuba of possible cuts to Venezuelan oil and financial support. Adding support, a softer US dollar lifted dollar-denominated assets, with the dollar index easing to around 98.5.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/relics-1441253_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc rallies as silver scales fresh lifetime highs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-rallies-as-silver-scales-fresh-lifetime-highs/1664336</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664336</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The move was driven by strong safe-haven demand amid rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran and broader global uncertainty, which pushed silver sharply higher on international and domestic markets.

The move was driven by strong safe-haven demand amid rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran and broader global uncertainty, which pushed silver sharply higher on international and domestic markets. Hindustan Zinc, one of the world’s top five silver producers, stands to benefit as silver contributes majorly to its EBIT. Brokerages remain constructive, with technical indicators pointing to a positive trend. Last month, a foreign broker maintained a 'Buy' rating with a target of Rs 660. It expects strong earnings growth over the next few years, supported by rising silver prices, improved cost efficiency, stable zinc production costs and robust cash generation, even as valuations trade above long-term averages. Hindustan Zinc, a Vedanta Group company, is an integrated producer of zinc, lead and silver. As of December 2025, Vedanta held 61.84% stake in the company. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Hindustan Zinc rose 13.84% to Rs 2649 crore while net sales rose 3.47% to Rs 8282 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siyaram Recycling Inds secures Rs 4-cr order from Saanvi Metal Craft]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siyaram-recycling-inds-secures-rs-4-cr-order-from-saanvi-metal-craft/1664335</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664335</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to a regulatory filing, the order is scheduled to be executed over a period of six months.

According to a regulatory filing, the order is scheduled to be executed over a period of six months. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity and that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Siyaram Recycling Industries is primarily engaged in the recycling of brass scrap. On a full-year basis, the company's net profit jumped 93.8% to Rs 14.57 crore on a 23.9% rise in net sales to Rs 511.56 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiyaramRecyclingIndustriesLtd_80297349_92151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1664334</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664334</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GE Vernova T&D India Ltd, Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd, City Union Bank Ltd and Balaji Amines Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 January 2026.

GE Vernova T&D India Ltd, Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd, City Union Bank Ltd and Balaji Amines Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 January 2026. Tejas Networks Ltd lost 8.03% to Rs 383.25 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 13.69 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 56184 shares in the past one month. GE Vernova T&D India Ltd tumbled 6.03% to Rs 2725.35. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22913 shares in the past one month. Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd crashed 5.82% to Rs 284.9. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 13732 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7129 shares in the past one month. City Union Bank Ltd pared 5.51% to Rs 265.65. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.4 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.06 lakh shares in the past one month. Balaji Amines Ltd shed 5.06% to Rs 1105. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 46118 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 86142 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concor throughputs climb 11% to 14.23 lakh TEUs in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concor-throughputs-climb-11-to-1423-lakh-teus-in-q3-fy26/1664333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664333</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Export import (EXIM) throughput increased 9.94% to Rs 10,72,145 TEUs during the quarter from 9,75,243 TEUs posted in Q3 FY25.

Export import (EXIM) throughput increased 9.94% to Rs 10,72,145 TEUs during the quarter from 9,75,243 TEUs posted in Q3 FY25. Domestic (DOM) throughputs jumped 13.43% to Rs 3,51,121 TEUs in Q3 FY26, compared with 3,09,551 TEUs in Q3 FY25. Container Corporation of India (CONCOR) is engaged in the business of providing inland transportation of containers by rail. It also covers the management of ports and air cargo complexes and establishes cold chains. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 3.6% to Rs 378.70 crore on 2.9% increase in net sales to Rs 2,354.53 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter declined 0.35% to Rs 510.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ContainerCorpn_89474429441_12607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jash Engineering bags orders worth Rs 74 crore in December; orderbook rises to Rs 912 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jash-engineering-bags-orders-worth-rs-74-crore-in-december-orderbook-rises-to-rs-912-crore/1664332</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664332</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Out of the total orders, contracts worth Rs 28 crore are for Indian market while the remaining ones, which are worth Rs 46 crore, are for markets outside India.

Out of the total orders, contracts worth Rs 28 crore are for Indian market while the remaining ones, which are worth Rs 46 crore, are for markets outside India. The significant contributors to the monthly order booking of December 2025 are Enviro Infra Engineers (Delhi), Reliance Industries (Mumbai) & Vindhya Telelinks (Rewa) from India and REC Engineering (Hong Kong) & Cartersville WPCP Expansion (USA) from international market. As on 01 January 2026, the total consolidated order book position of the company is Rs. 912 crore. Out of this, orders worth Rs 284 crore are for Indian market and orders worth Rs 628 crore are for markets outside India. The company further said that as on 01 January 2026, consolidated orders worth Rs 31 crore have been negotiated with clients and formal purchase orders for the same are awaited. Jash Engineering manufactures engineering products for wastewater treatment. The company offers products for use in water and wastewater pumping stations and treatment plants, storm water pumping stations, water transmission lines, desalination, power, steel, cement, paper & pulp, petrochemicals, chemicals, fertilisers and other process plants. The company's consolidated net profit declined 30.29% to Rs 11.16 crore despite a 12.87% increase in revenue to Rs 157.54 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip fell 1.44% to currently trade at Rs 404 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JashEngineeringLtd_71537208307_39683.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Worth Peripherals Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/worth-peripherals-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1664330</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664330</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and Palm Jewels Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 January 2026.

California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and Palm Jewels Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 January 2026. Worth Peripherals Ltd lost 12.17% to Rs 134.9 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 697 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 482 shares in the past one month. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup tumbled 10.20% to Rs 4.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1849 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2259 shares in the past one month. Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd crashed 9.53% to Rs 1090. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 81509 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13390 shares in the past one month. Rollatainers Ltd pared 9.50% to Rs 1.62. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 12286 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.23 lakh shares in the past one month. Palm Jewels Ltd dropped 9.44% to Rs 20.53. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 26655 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22440 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WorthPeripheralsLtd_81529932771_71405.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>