<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:40:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Puravankara launches premium residential project ‘Purva Silversky’ in Bengaluru’s electronic city]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/puravankara-launches-premium-residential-project-purva-silversky-in-bengalurus-electronic-city/1678747</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678747</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Spread across approximately 6.99 acres, the project comprises 356 exclusive residences across three 32-storey towers, with nearly 88% open-to-sky spaces.

Spread across approximately 6.99 acres, the project comprises 356 exclusive residences across three 32-storey towers, with nearly 88% open-to-sky spaces. Positioned as a low-density development with just four units per floor, Purva Silversky promises enhanced privacy, openness, and elevated living experiences. Strategically located in one of Bengaluru’s established technology corridors, the project offers seamless connectivity to major IT hubs, corporate parks, educational institutions, healthcare facilities, and retail destinations. It is situated about 900 metres from Huskur Metro Station and within a 10-minute radius of over 15 IT parks. The development features expansive 3, 4, and 5 BHK residences, along with select larger-format homes, with sizes ranging from 1,864 sq ft to over 5,300 sq ft. Each unit is designed to maximise natural light, ventilation, and spatial efficiency, complemented by premium finishes and private decks. The residences offer 270-degree open views, providing a sense of space and visual openness rarely seen in urban projects. Purva Silversky focuses on holistic wellbeing and community living, featuring a 17,700 sq ft clubhouse and more than 45 lifestyle amenities across a 1.7-acre elevated podium. The project also includes landscaped open spaces and a forest walkway with over 200 trees, catering to the wellness, leisure, and recreational needs of modern urban families. Puravankara is engaged in the business of real estate development. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 59.34 crore in Q3 FY26 as net loss of Rs 93.16 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations zoomed 236.1% year on year to Rs 1,069.31 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of Puravankara fell 1.04% to Rs 232.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Puravankara_83213463793_25459.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lloyds-metals-energy-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678746</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678746</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lloyds Enterprises Ltd, Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd and Easy Trip Planners Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026.

Lloyds Enterprises Ltd, Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd and Easy Trip Planners Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026. Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd tumbled 6.69% to Rs 1130.8 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 6.7 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.04 lakh shares in the past one month. Lloyds Enterprises Ltd lost 4.62% to Rs 55.97. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 66398 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.76 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd crashed 4.34% to Rs 437.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 82436 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.69 lakh shares in the past one month. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd dropped 4.29% to Rs 245.45. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 63223 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.03 lakh shares in the past one month. Easy Trip Planners Ltd plummeted 4.25% to Rs 9.23. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 95.62 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 47.1 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsMetals_76757705405_2629.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hemant Surgical Industries rallies after bagging Rs 264-cr order from CMSS ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hemant-surgical-industries-rallies-after-bagging-rs-264-cr-order-from-cmss/1678745</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678745</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the supply of flat panel detectors with two batteries and a router, hard travel cases along with other utilities, and X-ray generators.

According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the supply of flat panel detectors with two batteries and a router, hard travel cases along with other utilities, and X-ray generators. The final commercial terms, including the delivery schedule of the purchase orders, are currently under discussion and subject to finalisation. The company stated that the order will be executed in tranches by 30 September 2026, subject to negotiations and terms, including any extension requested by Hemant Surgical Industries to CMSS. Hemant Surgical Industries clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It further stated that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Hemant Surgical Industries is in the business of medical equipment & supplies. The company's standalone net profit fell 17% to Rs 8.13 crore on a 0.9% rise in revenue to Rs 106.53 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HemantSurgicalIndustriesLtd_35472315_40414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pine Labs gains after joining hands with OpenAI for agentic commerce]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pine-labs-gains-after-joining-hands-with-openai-for-agentic-commerce/1678743</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678743</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company will embed OpenAI APIs models into the core of a global merchant ecosystem.

The company will embed OpenAI APIs models into the core of a global merchant ecosystem. This transition shift represents a fundamental evolution from the deterministic "if/then" logic that has defined fintech for years. By embedding OpenAI’s intelligence into the core of its stack, Pine Labs is engineering a Reasoning Layer for commerce, transforming its infrastructure into a dynamic system capable of understanding context and weighing probabilities, all while operating within a secure, compliant framework designed for high-stakes financial environments. Users will no longer just "search" for products; they will delegate entire financial lifecycles to intelligent agents within a single dialogue. In this architecture, an agent can autonomously navigate complex tasks—such as negotiating supplier terms, optimizing cross-border settlement cycles, or managing recurring payments— within pre-defined user guardrails. OpenAI provides the critical decision-making intelligence, while while Pine Labs’ payment rails will function as the regulated execution layer. This intelligence is deployed within the company’s enterprise-grade security and compliance architecture. The company also plans to open this agentic stack to its developer ecosystem, providing the tools for third-party innovators to build next-generation, AI-native fintech applications on a trusted foundation. B Amrish Rau, CEO, Pine Labs, said, “For decades, commerce has been built on passive systems that simply follow instructions, At Pine Labs, we are moving beyond that era to build an active, intelligent layer for business. Our work with OpenAI ensures that our infrastructure is no longer just a participant in a trade, but a driver of efficiency and growth. We are building the first agentic stack for the next generation of the global economy.” Oliver Jay, managing director, International, OpenAI, said, “The next phase of AI is about moving from information to action, by combining our advanced reasoning capabilities with Pine Labs’ deep merchant infrastructure, we are helping to create a powerful engine for innovation that turns complex financial workflows into seamless, agentic experiences at scale.” Pine Labs is a technology company focused on digitizing commerce through digital payments and issuing solutions for merchants, consumer brands and enterprises, and financial institutions. The company reported net profit of Rs 42.39 crore in Q3 FY26 comapred with net loss of Rs 56.67 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales jumped 23.7% YoY to Rs 744.27 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PineLabsLtd_41545070_77096.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/veer-global-infraconstruction-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678742</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678742</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hilton Metal Forging Ltd, Sharika Enterprises Ltd, JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd and Primo Chemicals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026.

Hilton Metal Forging Ltd, Sharika Enterprises Ltd, JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd and Primo Chemicals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026. Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd crashed 10.96% to Rs 84.8 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2266 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 922 shares in the past one month. Hilton Metal Forging Ltd tumbled 10.49% to Rs 21.24. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 78114 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 24860 shares in the past one month. Sharika Enterprises Ltd lost 8.94% to Rs 11.2. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.82 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53589 shares in the past one month. JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd fell 7.19% to Rs 24.52. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 38 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 827 shares in the past one month. Primo Chemicals Ltd shed 7.10% to Rs 20.81. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5420 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 20123 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VeerGlobalInfraconstructionLtd.._40400431_75110.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold rebounds sharply amid Fed split and Dollar pullback]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-rebounds-sharply-amid-fed-split-and-dollar-pullback/1678741</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678741</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures climbed above $5,000 per ounce on Thursday, extending a strong rebound of over $100 from the previous session as investors focused on upcoming US PCE inflation and GDP data for cues on Federal Reserve policy.

Gold futures climbed above $5,000 per ounce on Thursday, extending a strong rebound of over $100 from the previous session as investors focused on upcoming US PCE inflation and GDP data for cues on Federal Reserve policy. The dollar index eased slightly to 97.5 after a prior-session surge, while Fed minutes from January revealed a split among officials—some favored pausing rate cuts for now, others supported maintaining a two-sided outlook that could allow future hikes or easing. In domestic markets, MCX April 2026 gold futures gained over ₹1,000 to ₹156,935 per 10 grams, recovering sharply from this year’s low of ₹137,000.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex sinks 901 pts; media shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-sinks-901-pts-media-shares-tumble/1678739</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678739</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major cuts in mid-afternoon trade, pressured by broad-based selling across sectors.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major cuts in mid-afternoon trade, pressured by broad-based selling across sectors. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. Media shares witnessed profit booking after rising in the previous two consecutive trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 901.29 points or 1.08% to 82,832.96. The Nifty 50 index fell 254.65 points or 0.99% to 25,558.70. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.92% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.66%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,449 shares rose and 2,610 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced the MANAV Vision for AI, where MANAV stands for M – Moral and Ethical System, A – Accountable Governance, N – National Sovereignty (right to data), A – Accessible and Inclusive, and V – Valid and Legitimate. Apart from PM Modi, key business and technology leaders such as Mukesh Ambani, Sam Altman and Sundar Pichai also delivered keynote addresses. French President Emmanuel Macron also spoke at the Delhi AI Summit. Tata Sons Chairman N. Chandrasekaran said, “I would like to thank the vision of our Prime Minister, which has enabled us to make a serious foray into chips and semiconductors. Our next step is to build chips that are highly domain-centric and fully AI-optimized for every industry. We will initially focus on developing and launching them for the automotive sector.” Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 1.99% to 1,434.35. The index advanced 0.92% over the previous two trading sessions. PVR Inox (down 3.71%), D B Corp (down 2.87%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 2.65%), Prime Focus (down 1.94%), Tips Music (down 1.89%), Saregama India (down 1.83%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 1.77%), Sun TV Network (down 1.37%), Nazara Technologies (down 0.87%) and Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 0.44%) rose. Numbers to Track: In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6850 compared with its close of 90.7200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.76% to Rs 156,940. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.11% to 97.63. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.44% to 4.098. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose $1.03 cents or 1.46% to $71.38 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: SpiceJet shed 0.53%. The company said it has received a memorandum of understanding (MoU) for the induction of 10 aircraft, marking a fresh step in its capacity expansion and network rebuilding plans. R P P Infra Projects rose 1.93% after the company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 52.17 crore from the Water Resources Department, Tamil Nadu.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Tata Investment Corporation Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-tata-investment-corporation-ltd-counter/1678738</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678738</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Godrej Industries Ltd, NCC Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, India Cements Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 19 February 2026.

Godrej Industries Ltd, NCC Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, India Cements Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 19 February 2026. Tata Investment Corporation Ltd notched up volume of 192.65 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 38.75 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4.97 lakh shares. The stock rose 9.42% to Rs.704.65. Volumes stood at 8.16 lakh shares in the last session. Godrej Industries Ltd notched up volume of 9.64 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.83 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 60913 shares. The stock rose 5.16% to Rs.1,035.90. Volumes stood at 27086 shares in the last session. NCC Ltd clocked volume of 215.76 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.67 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 28.14 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.41% to Rs.149.14. Volumes stood at 23.48 lakh shares in the last session. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd recorded volume of 545.12 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.22 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 87.58 lakh shares. The stock gained 18.30% to Rs.628.85. Volumes stood at 212.78 lakh shares in the last session. India Cements Ltd recorded volume of 11.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.87 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.89 lakh shares. The stock lost 1.63% to Rs.423.20. Volumes stood at 1.62 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataInvCorpn_86313365626_298.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude holds around $65 per barrel after massive spike in last session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-holds-around-65-per-barrel-after-massive-spike-in-last-session/1678737</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678737</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures traded above $65 per barrel on Thursday, holding onto the strongest rally since late October after surging more than 4% in the previous session.

WTI crude oil futures traded above $65 per barrel on Thursday, holding onto the strongest rally since late October after surging more than 4% in the previous session. Support came from signs of tightening US supply, with industry data showing crude inventories fell by 0.61 million barrels last week, partially reversing the sharp build seen earlier. Geopolitical risk also remained firmly in focus as negotiations between the US and Iran continued without a clear breakthrough, despite Tehran citing a “general agreement” on the framework of a potential nuclear deal. Meanwhile, the dollar index hovered near 97.5 after a sharp rise in the prior session, underpinned by strong US economic data and hawkish signals from the Federal Reserve. Minutes from the Fed’s latest meeting highlighted divisions among policymakers and kept the option of further rate hikes on the table should inflation remain elevated, adding to broader market uncertainty.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Holidays launches Club Mahindra Nadiya Parao resort in Jim Corbett]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-holidays-launches-club-mahindra-nadiya-parao-resort-in-jim-corbett/1678735</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678735</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The new resort launch aligns with the company’s accelerated expansion strategy and its ambition to become India’s leading leisure hospitality player, driven by robust resort additions, portfolio premiumisation, and disciplined capital allocation.

The new resort launch aligns with the company’s accelerated expansion strategy and its ambition to become India’s leading leisure hospitality player, driven by robust resort additions, portfolio premiumisation, and disciplined capital allocation. This marks MHRIL’s second resort in Jim Corbett, one of India’s most preferred destinations for nature-led travel. The addition supports the company’s near-term target of 1,000 room additions by FY26 and its longer-term goal of scaling to 10,000 keys under Club Mahindra and 12,000 keys overall by FY30. Spanning around 10 acres, the 57-room resort combines premium leisure stays with extensive event infrastructure, including large landscaped lawns, a banquet hall, and riverfront access. The property is designed to cater to diverse segments, including holidaying families, destination weddings, and corporate offsites, unlocking multiple revenue streams from a single asset. Manoj Bhat, managing director & chief executive officer, Mahindra Holidays & Resorts India, said, “Our ambition is to lead leisure hospitality in India, with families at the heart of everything we do. The launch of Nadiya Parao is another step forward in our expansion journey, in a destination where demand is strong and growing. As we expand, we’re not just adding resorts; we’re delivering superior experience, sharpening execution, and building for the future”. Mahindra Holidays & Resorts India (MHRIL), part of the diversified Mahindra Group, is India’s leading leisure hospitality company. Established in 1996, the company pioneered the vacation ownership model in India and has since redefined family holidays through thoughtfully designed resorts, curated experiences, and a commitment to sustainable tourism. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 93.6% to Rs 2.23 crore on 10.9% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 752.70 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahindraHoliday_70394943904_18268.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/muthoot-finance-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1678721</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678721</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Muthoot Finance Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3448.8, down 0.23% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.82% on the day, quoting at 25607. The Sensex is at 82979.58, down 0.9%.Muthoot Finance Ltd has lost around 12.25% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Muthoot Finance Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 3.71% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28463.25, down 0.89% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.03 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.89 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3454.8, down 0.23% on the day. Muthoot Finance Ltd jumped 51.51% in last one year as compared to a 11.76% rally in NIFTY and a 21.16% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 16.22 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MuthootFinance_48499437395_24769.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex plunges 693 pts; pharma shares decline; VIX rallies 7.40%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-plunges-693-pts-pharma-shares-decline-vix-rallies-740/1678723</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678723</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,650 mark. Barring pharma indices all other sectoral indices traded in the red on the BSE. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 693.11 points or 0.88% to 82,995.55. The Nifty 50 index fell 196.30 points or 0.76% to 25,626.05. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.71% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.50%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,457 shares rose and 2,528 shares fell. A total of 198 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, zoomed 7.40% to 13.13. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced the MANAV Vision for AI, where MANAV stands for: M – Moral and Ethical System, A – Accountable Governance, N – National Sovereignty (right to data), A – Accessible and Inclusive, and V – Valid and Legitimate. Apart from PM Modi, key business and tech leaders such as Mukesh Ambani, Sam Altman, and Sundar Pichai also delivered keynote addresses. French President Emmanuel Macron also spoke at the Delhi AI Summit. Tata Sons Chairperson N. Chandrasekaran stated, “I want to thank the vision of our Prime Minister, which has made it possible for us to make a serious foray into chips and semiconductors. Our next step is to build chips that are highly domain-centric and fully AI-optimized for every industry. We will first focus on developing and launching them for the automotive sector.” Gainers & Losers: Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (India) (up 2.80%), Hindalco Industries (up 1.63%), Infosys (up 0.98%), Dr. Reddy's Laboratories (up 0.72%) and Tata Consultancy Services (up 0.37%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Kwality Wall's (down 3.24%), Trent (down 2.91%), Mahindra & Mahindra (down 2.56%), InterGlobe Aviation (down 2.02%) and Adani Enterprises (down 1.92%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories rose 0.72%. The company said that it has entered into a definitive agreement with Mercury Pharma Group (MPGL) to acquire its trademarks, Progynova and Cyclo Progynova and related assets for India. Tata Consultancy Services rose 0.37%. The company announced a multi-dimensional strategic partnership with OpenAI to drive AI-powered innovation across enterprise, consumer, and social sectors. Stocks in Spotlight: Multi Commodity Exchange of India (MCX) gained 2.80% after the exchange announced withdrawal of additional margins imposed on gold and silver futures contracts with effect from 19 February 2026. B. L. Kashyap and Sons jumped 3.25% after it secured a contract worth Rs 300 crore from CRC Greens for a group housing project in Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) rose 0.16%. The company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from Northern Railway for a project worth Rs 1,201.35 crore. Dhabriya Polywood zoomed 3.30% after it has announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Dynasty Modular Furnitures, has received letters of intent (LOIs) from the Godrej Group aggregating to Rs 25.30 crore. Atishay rose 1.49% after it has secured a domestic work order from the State Health Assurance Society (SHAS), Government of Maharashtra. Global Markets: European markets traded in mixed on Thursday as investors weighed earnings from major companies including Airbus, Nestle, and Rio Tinto. Asian stocks traded higher, supported by gains in technology giants on Wall Street, while lingering U.S.-Iran tensions kept oil prices elevated. In Malaysia, headline inflation rose 1.6% year-on-year in January 2026, with the consumer price index (CPI) increasing to 135.7 from 133.6 in the same month last year, according to the Department of Statistics Malaysia (DOSM). Hong Kong and mainland China markets remained closed for the Lunar New Year break. Meanwhile, Indonesian and U.S. companies signed deals worth $38.4 billion ahead of Indonesian President Prabowo Subianto’s meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump, covering mining, energy, agribusiness, textiles, furniture, and technology sectors. In Australia, the unemployment rate steadied at 4.1% in January, as per data from the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS). Oil prices edged higher as investors digested the latest developments between the U.S. and Iran. Vice President JD Vance reportedly said Tuesday that Iran failed to address U.S. red lines in this week’s nuclear talks and that military action is still a possibility. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 moved higher, supported by gains in key technology names, as traders weighed the release of the minutes from the Federal Reserve’s most recent policy meeting. The broad-based index climbed 0.56% to end at 6,881.31, while the Nasdaq Composite added 0.78% to settle at 22,753.63. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.26% to close at 49,662.66. Investors mulled over the minutes from the Fed’s January meeting, which revealed that participants largely approved of the central bank’s decision to leave its key interest rate unchanged at a range of 3.5% to 3.75%. However, officials were divided on the direction of monetary policy thereafter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen holds near 155 as Fed hawkishness boosts Dollar]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-holds-near-155-as-fed-hawkishness-boosts-dollar/1678719</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678719</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen hovered near 155.15 per dollar on Thursday after logging its sharpest one-day drop of the month, pressured by a stronger US dollar following solid economic data and hawkish signals from the Federal Reserve.

The Japanese yen hovered near 155.15 per dollar on Thursday after logging its sharpest one-day drop of the month, pressured by a stronger US dollar following solid economic data and hawkish signals from the Federal Reserve. Fed minutes showed several officials favored keeping the option of further rate hikes on the table if inflation remains elevated. Domestically, Japan’s December machinery orders rebounded strongly, offering limited support to the currency. Markets are also increasingly pricing in a potential April rate hike by the Bank of Japan, contingent on upcoming data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ajanta Pharma Ltd soars 0.41%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ajanta-pharma-ltd-soars-041-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1678717</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678717</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ajanta Pharma Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Ajanta Pharma Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2974, up 0.41% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.92% on the day, quoting at 25582.55. The Sensex is at 82908.57, down 0.99%. Ajanta Pharma Ltd has risen around 10.8% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Ajanta Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 3.89% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22541.95, up 0.07% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 32363 shares today, compared to the daily average of 94652 shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 39.24 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AjantaPharma_12686194738_13504.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SpiceJet gains after inking MoU to induct 10 aircraft for fleet expansion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/spicejet-gains-after-inking-mou-to-induct-10-aircraft-for-fleet-expansion/1678716</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678716</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The move comes close on the heels of the Board’s approval for a calibrated fleet ramp-up to 60 aircraft through a mix of wet and damp leases, along with the phased return of grounded planes.

The move comes close on the heels of the Board’s approval for a calibrated fleet ramp-up to 60 aircraft through a mix of wet and damp leases, along with the phased return of grounded planes. The airline said it has doubled its capacity in the last quarter, with Available Seat Kilometres (ASKMs) rising from about 55 crores to 105 crores. Riding on the momentum, SpiceJet plans to scale up capacity to 220 crore ASKMs by Winter 2026 and operate over 300 daily flights, aiming to strengthen connectivity, enhance operational reliability and meet rising passenger demand through disciplined growth. Debojo Maharshi, chief business officer (CBO), SpiceJet, said, “Doubling our capacity in the last quarter has been a significant milestone, and the plans we have in place to more than double it further this year reflect growing confidence in the business and strong demand across the network. The receipt of this MoU is an encouraging development as we continue to rebuild and expand our operations in a measured manner. Our focus remains on restoring capacity, strengthening connectivity and improving reliability for our passengers.” SpiceJet is engaged in the business of providing air transport services for the carriage of passengers and cargo and other allied activities. The company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 241.57 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net profit of Rs 20.44 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 14.1% year on year to Rs 1,345.47 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SpiceJet_3698663034_3367.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty drops below 25,650 mark; auto shares snap 2-day gains]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-drops-below-25650-mark-auto-shares-snap-2-day-gains/1678714</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678714</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with sharply lower in early afternoon deals, as profit booking intensified amid rising geopolitical tensions and uncertainty over global growth prospects.

The key equity indices traded with sharply lower in early afternoon deals, as profit booking intensified amid rising geopolitical tensions and uncertainty over global growth prospects. Traders adopted a risk-off stance, leading to broad-based selling across sectors. Investors are also closely monitoring developments at the AI Summit 2026 in Delhi. Auto shares tumbled after advancing in the past two trading sessions. At 12:25 PM ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex fell 666.46 points or 0.80% to 83,050.26. The Nifty 50 index declined 200.20 points or 0.76% to 25,621.35. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.68% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index dropped 0.46%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,471 shares rose and 2,413 shares fell. A total of 217 shares were unchanged. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced the MANAV Vision for AI. He denotes MANAV as M: moral and ethical system, A: accountable of governance, N: national sovereignity (right to data), A: accessible and inclusive, V: valied and legitimate. Apart from PM Modi, key business and tech stalwarts like Mukesh Ambani, Sam Altman, and Sundar Pichai also addressed keynote sessions. French President Emmanuel Macron also addressed in the Delhi AI Summit. Tata Sons Chairperson N Chandrasekaran stated that he wanted to thank the vision of our Prime minister, which made it possible for us to make a serious foray into chips and semiconductors. What we will do next is to build chips that are very domain centric, which will be totally AI optimised. for every industry, and we will first launch or work towards getting it ready for the automotive sector. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 9.18% to 13.35. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures were trading at 25,627, at a premium of 5.65 points as compared with the spot at 25,621.35. The Nifty option chain for the 24 February 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 1.75 crore contracts at the 25,800 strike price. Maximum put OI of 86.5 lakh contracts was seen at the 25,000 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index declined 1.11% to 28,013.50. The index jumped 1.07% in the past two consecutive trading sessions. Mahindra & Mahindra (down 1.93%), Hero MotoCorp (down 1.69%), Samvardhana Motherson International (down 1.52%), Bajaj Auto (down 1.02%) and Exide Industries (down 0.95%), Ashok Leyland (down 0.65%), Bharat Forge (down 0.47%), Bosch (down 0.38%), Eicher Motors (down 0.37%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 0.3%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Multi Commodity Exchange of India (MCX) gained 3.15% after the exchange announced withdrawal of additional margins imposed on gold and silver futures contracts with effect from 19 February 2026. Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories rose 0.41%. The company said that it has entered into a definitive agreement with Mercury Pharma Group (MPGL) to acquire its trademarks, Progynova and Cyclo Progynova and related assets for India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[R P P Infra gains after bagging Rs 52-cr order from water resources department ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/r-p-p-infra-gains-after-bagging-rs-52-cr-order-from-water-resources-department/1678713</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678713</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract has been awarded by the Superintending Engineer, Palar Basin Circle, Chepauk, Chennai.

The contract has been awarded by the Superintending Engineer, Palar Basin Circle, Chepauk, Chennai. According to the company’s exchange filing, the scope of work includes the formation of new tanks, construction of peripheral earthen drains, cut-and-cover channels, and capacity enhancement of surrounding tanks. The project also involves flood mitigation works for the proposed Global Sports City at Semmancheri, Chennai. The total value of the work order stands at Rs 52,17,05,486 and the project is scheduled to be completed within 12 months. The company clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It further stated that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. R P P Infra Projects is engaged in construction across multiple infrastructure verticals like roads, buildings, industrial structures, power, irrigation, and water management and has executed many projects. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 96.4% to Rs 0.67 crore on a 6.9% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 379.73 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RPPInfraProj_96516484906_36162.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahalaxmi Rubtech Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahalaxmi-rubtech-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678710</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678710</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TIL Ltd, Datamatics Global Services Ltd, Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd and Pavna Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026.

TIL Ltd, Datamatics Global Services Ltd, Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd and Pavna Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026. Mahalaxmi Rubtech Ltd spiked 19.17% to Rs 230 at 09:05 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 910 shares in the past one month. TIL Ltd soared 17.40% to Rs 269.25. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 87729 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2730 shares in the past one month. Datamatics Global Services Ltd surged 13.21% to Rs 839. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6899 shares in the past one month. Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd advanced 12.54% to Rs 3.23. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 112 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5685 shares in the past one month. Pavna Industries Ltd rose 11.58% to Rs 26.49. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 57480 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21458 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahalaxmiRubtec_32623583074_4319.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Newgen Software Technologies Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/newgen-software-technologies-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1678708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678708</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Godrej Industries Ltd, Netweb Technologies India Ltd and Safari Industries (India) Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026.

Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Godrej Industries Ltd, Netweb Technologies India Ltd and Safari Industries (India) Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd soared 13.90% to Rs 604.5 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 46.45 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.95 lakh shares in the past one month. Tata Investment Corporation Ltd spiked 9.03% to Rs 702.2. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 12.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 52576 shares in the past one month. Godrej Industries Ltd surged 5.63% to Rs 1040.1. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 31663 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3930 shares in the past one month. Netweb Technologies India Ltd jumped 5.58% to Rs 3561. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.47 lakh shares in the past one month. Safari Industries (India) Ltd added 4.31% to Rs 1881. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3540 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3394 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewgenSoftwareTechnologiesLtd_46602882106_13722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund Has Announced a Change in the Face Value of Certain ETFs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-mutual-fund-has-announced-a-change-in-the-face-value-of-certain-etfs/1678709</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678709</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced a change in the face value of units and creation unit size for certain of its Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) with effect from February 27, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Name of the Scheme Existing Provisions Revised Provisions Kotak Nifty Bank ETF Kotak Nifty India Consumption ETF Kotak Nifty Midcap 50 ETF Kotak Silver ETF Kotak Nifty 50 Value 20 ETF The face value of each unit offered under the Scheme shall be Rs.

Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced a change in the face value of units and creation unit size for certain of its Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) with effect from February 27, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Name of the Scheme Existing Provisions Revised Provisions Kotak Nifty Bank ETF Kotak Nifty India Consumption ETF Kotak Nifty Midcap 50 ETF Kotak Silver ETF Kotak Nifty 50 Value 20 ETF The face value of each unit offered under the Scheme shall be Rs. 10 The face value of each unit offered under the Scheme shall be Rs. 1

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>