<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:32:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold extends historic rally on geopolitics and currency erosion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-extends-historic-rally-on-geopolitics-and-currency-erosion/1668097</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668097</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures vaulted above $5,300 per ounce in electronic trade on Wednesday, carving out fresh record highs as investors intensified their flight to safety amid escalating geopolitical tensions, a Trump-led tariff confrontation, and a pronounced deterioration in the US dollar.

Gold futures vaulted above $5,300 per ounce in electronic trade on Wednesday, carving out fresh record highs as investors intensified their flight to safety amid escalating geopolitical tensions, a Trump-led tariff confrontation, and a pronounced deterioration in the US dollar. Markets also turned cautious ahead of the Federal Reserve’s policy decision, with investors parsing guidance for clues on the timing of the next rate cut. President Trump’s remarks signaling comfort with a weaker greenback — now at a four-year low — reinforced expectations of currency depreciation, amplifying bullion’s allure as a store of value. Policy uncertainty in Washington, including renewed tariff threats and pressure on Federal Reserve independence, further underpinned demand for precious metals. Robust central bank purchases and persistent ETF inflows added structural support to prices. On the domestic front, MCX February gold futures surged over 4%, scaling a record high of ₹1,64,900 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alphalogic Techsys Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alphalogic-techsys-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1668095</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668095</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tokyo Plast International Ltd, Damodar Industries Ltd, N K Industries Ltd and Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 28 January 2026.

Tokyo Plast International Ltd, Damodar Industries Ltd, N K Industries Ltd and Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 28 January 2026. Alphalogic Techsys Ltd lost 12.89% to Rs 38.6 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 69687 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14749 shares in the past one month. Tokyo Plast International Ltd crashed 10.58% to Rs 101.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 390 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 201 shares in the past one month. Damodar Industries Ltd tumbled 9.79% to Rs 25.25. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 333 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5081 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd pared 9.70% to Rs 70. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 27 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 54 shares in the past one month. Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd fell 9.47% to Rs 846.9. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 46025 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22621 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlphalogicTechsys_32674832_74495.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade marginally higher; realty shares jump]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-marginally-higher-realty-shares-jump/1668094</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668094</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices pared most of their gains and traded with minor gains in the mid-afternoon trade amid profit booking and FII selling.

The key domestic indices pared most of their gains and traded with minor gains in the mid-afternoon trade amid profit booking and FII selling. The market sentiment turned cautious, overshadowing the optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA). Investors are closely tracking rupee movements, crude oil, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements, and geopolitical developments, while also tracking upcoming Q3 results from Larsen & Toubro and BHEL. The Nifty slipped below the 25,250 level. Realty shares climbed for second consecutive trading session. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 70.28 points or 0.09% to 81,927.48. The Nifty 50 index added 43.15 points or 0.18% to 25,217.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 0.41% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.41%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,736 shares rose and 1,408 shares fell. A total of 155 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 5.43% to 13.67. Indian Politics: Ajit Pawar, NCP chief and Maharashtra’s Deputy Chief Minister, died in a plane crash near Baramati on Wednesday while travelling from Mumbai. Four others, including the pilots and his security personnel, were also killed. The small aircraft, a Learjet 45 operated by VSR, reportedly crashed during a landing attempt near Baramati airport about 45 minutes after take-off, as Pawar was on his way to attend public meetings ahead of the local body polls. Television visuals showed fire and wreckage at the site, while media reports said all five people on board died. The 66-year-old leader was the nephew of Sharad Pawar and the cousin of Supriya Sule, both of whom were in Delhi and were expected to travel to Pune. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 0.86% to 765.90. The index gained 1.26% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Sobha (up 3.12%), DLF (up 2.04%), Godrej Properties (up 1.5%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 1.49%), Lodha Developers (up 1.14%), Oberoi Realty (up 0.4%) and Phoenix Mills (up 0.08%) surged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was declined 0.16% to 6.708 as compared with the previous close of 6.719. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.8000 compared with its close of 91.6850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rallied 4% to Rs 1,64,000. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.51% to 96.24. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.45% to 4.242. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement was unchanged at $67.57 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Bikaji Foods International added 2.58% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 116.32% to Rs 62.17 crore on 11.45% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 775.78 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Vodafone Idea shed 0.20% after the company’s consolidated net loss narrowed to Rs 5,286 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6,609 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue for the quarter stood at Rs 11,323 crore, up 1.9% YoY. Siyaram Silk Mills declined 5.66% to Rs 526 after the company reported a 7.98% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 41.77 crore on a 9.35% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 624.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-international-gemmological-institute-india-ltd-counter/1668090</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668090</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd, Oil India Ltd, Bikaji Foods International Ltd, Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 28 January 2026.

Tejas Networks Ltd, Oil India Ltd, Bikaji Foods International Ltd, Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 28 January 2026. International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd clocked volume of 79.67 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 19.58 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4.07 lakh shares. The stock gained 9.42% to Rs.318.40. Volumes stood at 5.13 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd witnessed volume of 233.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.59 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 22.01 lakh shares. The stock increased 13.17% to Rs.335.15. Volumes stood at 24.87 lakh shares in the last session. Oil India Ltd witnessed volume of 239.03 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.05 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 23.79 lakh shares. The stock increased 9.81% to Rs.492.55. Volumes stood at 30.43 lakh shares in the last session. Bikaji Foods International Ltd witnessed volume of 9.74 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.54 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.49 lakh shares. The stock increased 2.56% to Rs.664.05. Volumes stood at 1.41 lakh shares in the last session. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd recorded volume of 631.47 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.35 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 99.42 lakh shares. The stock gained 7.34% to Rs.266.15. Volumes stood at 159.16 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InternationalGemologicalInstituteIndiaLtd_19768130_79071.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SKM Egg Products jumps as Q3 profit rises sharply]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/skm-egg-products-jumps-as-q3-profit-rises-sharply/1668088</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668088</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit rose to Rs 30.01 crore in Q3 FY26, up sharply from Rs 7.53 crore in Q3 FY25, reflecting a YoY growth of about 299%.

On a consolidated basis, net profit rose to Rs 30.01 crore in Q3 FY26, up sharply from Rs 7.53 crore in Q3 FY25, reflecting a YoY growth of about 299%. Sequentially, profit after tax increased 21% from Rs 24.80 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 50.8% YoY to Rs 203.71 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 135.09 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a sequential basis, revenue was up 0.9% QoQ from Rs 201.93 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 40.00 crore in Q3 FY26, up 290% vs Q3 FY25 and 20.8% vs Q2 FY26. Total expenditure rose 32.4% YoY to Rs 168.56 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 127.33 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed jumped 63.6% YoY to Rs 128.97 crore. Employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 8.01 crore, down 5.1% YoY. Power and fuel costs increased 24.2% YoY to Rs 4.78 crore, while transport and forwarding expenses edged up 5.1% YoY to Rs 3.74 crore. SKM Egg Products Export (India) is an Export Oriented Undertaking engaged in the production and sale of eggs and manufacture and sale of egg products. The company's revenue is mainly on account of export of egg products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SKMEggProd_35096001675_17399.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Motor gains as Q3 PAT climbs 52% YoY to Rs 940 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-motor-gains-as-q3-pat-climbs-52-yoy-to-rs-940-cr/1668080</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668080</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) rose 36.67% year-on-year to Rs 1,226.30 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) rose 36.67% year-on-year to Rs 1,226.30 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. The company’s profit before tax (PBT) before exceptional items rose 57.12% year on year to Rs 1,314.65 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 836.68 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. The company reported exceptional items of Rs 41.37 crore during the quarter. The company’s operating EBITDA surged 51% year on year to Rs 1,634 crore in the third quarter of FY26, compared with Rs 1,081 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Operating EBITDA margin for the quarter stood at a record 13.1%, higher than the normalised operating EBITDA margin of 12.4% in Q3 FY25. Overall two-wheeler and three-wheeler sales, including international operations, rose 27% year on year to a record 15.44 lakh units in the quarter ended December 2025, compared with 12.12 lakh units in the year-ago period. Motorcycle sales increased 31% to 7.26 lakh units from 5.56 lakh units, while scooter sales grew 25% to 6.14 lakh units from 4.93 lakh units in the corresponding quarter last year. Two-wheeler sales in the international business jumped 35% to 3.66 lakh units, up from 2.72 lakh units in the quarter ended December 2024. Total three-wheeler sales more than doubled, rising 106% year on year to 0.60 lakh units compared with 0.29 lakh units in Q3 FY25. During the quarter under review, the company’s electric vehicle (EV) sales rose 40% year on year to a record 1.06 lakh units in the quarter ended December 2025, compared with 0.76 lakh units in the corresponding period last year. TVS Motor Company is a reputed two-wheeler and three-wheeler manufacturer globally. It has four manufacturing facilities located in India and Indonesia.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSMotorCo_68147319859_8029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc edges lower after promoter Vedanta launches OFS for 6.7 crore shares]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-edges-lower-after-promoter-vedanta-launches-ofs-for-67-crore-shares/1668086</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668086</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Promoter Vedanta Limited is offering a base lot of 3.35 crore shares, representing 0.79% of the company’s equity.

Promoter Vedanta Limited is offering a base lot of 3.35 crore shares, representing 0.79% of the company’s equity. The offer includes an oversubscription option for an additional 0.79%, taking the total potential divestment to 6.70 crore shares, or 1.59%. The floor price has been set at Rs 685 per share, a discount of 5.73% to the stock’s previous close of Rs 726.60 on January 27, 2026. The OFS opened on January 28 for non-retail investors. Retail investors can participate on January 29, along with non-retail bidders carrying forward unallotted bids. The offer is being conducted through a special window on the BSE and NSE during market hours. By 2:00 p.m. on T Day, the non-retail portion was subscribed 22.88% of the base offer size. Bids were received for 68.97 lakh shares against 3.01 crore shares on base non-retail offer. As of September 2025, Vedanta Limited held a 61.84% stake in Hindustan Zinc. Shares of Vedanta rose 3.99% to Rs 733.80 on the BSE. Hindustan Zinc, a Vedanta Group company, is the world's largest integrated zinc producer and is amongst the top 5 silver producers globally. The company supplies to more than 40 countries and holds a market share of about 77% of the primary zinc market in India. The company had reported 46.23% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,916 crore on a 27.81% increase in revenue to Rs 10,627 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Metro Brands Q3 PAT jumps 36% YoY to Rs 128 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/metro-brands-q3-pat-jumps-36-yoy-to-rs-128-crore/1668079</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668079</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 15.38% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 811.27 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, driven by strong festive and wedding season demand and supported by a reduction in GST on footwear priced below Rs 2,500.

Revenue from operations rose 15.38% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 811.27 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, driven by strong festive and wedding season demand and supported by a reduction in GST on footwear priced below Rs 2,500. Total expenditure increased 15.53% YoY to Rs 655.09 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 567.02 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses rose 21.62% YoY to Rs 77.10 crore, while finance costs increased 22.75% YoY to Rs 28.81 crore during the quarter. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 172.71 crore, up 7.97% from Rs 159.96 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA improved 17.6% YoY to Rs 265 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 226 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 32.7% in Q3 FY26 from 32.1% in Q3 FY25. E-commerce and omni-channel sales grew 24% during the quarter, contributing 12% of revenue, compared with 11% in Q3 FY25. During Q3 FY26, the company opened 35 new stores and closed 11. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 15.12% YoY to Rs 294.56 crore, while revenue increased 12.12% YoY to Rs 2,090.65 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Over the nine-month period, 100 new stores were added, offset by 18 closures, reflecting a calibrated approach to network expansion. Nissan Joseph, CEO, Metro Brands, said, “I’m pleased to see our growth momentum continue with a 15% increase in revenue. Q3 reinforces our view that long-term retail success is built through scale, portfolio depth, and rigorous execution. We are shaping a diversified platform that spans fashion, comfort, and performance, with strong omni-channel capability at its core. Our investments in brand, digital, and international partnerships are deliberate and long-term, and they are designed to strengthen resilience and compound growth over time.” Metro Brands is one of the largest Indian footwear speciality retailers. Metro Brands retails footwear under its own brands of Metro, Mochi, Walkway, Da Vinchi and J. Fontini, as well as certain third‐party brands such as Crocs, Fitflop, Fila, Clarks, Skechers, Puma and Adidas, which complement its in‐house brands. As of 31 December 2025, the company operated 990 stores across 212 cities spread across 31 states and union territories in India. The counter slipped 1.64% to Rs 1,042.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Metro-Brands-Ltd_59361533_17628.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CarTrade Tech drops after Q3 PAT slides 4% QoQ to Rs 62 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cartrade-tech-drops-after-q3-pat-slides-4-qoq-to-rs-62-cr/1668071</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668071</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit and revenue jumped 35.12%, and total income rose 18.36% in Q3 FY26.

On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit and revenue jumped 35.12%, and total income rose 18.36% in Q3 FY26. EBITDA rose 56% YoY to Rs 78.25 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 50.08 crore in Q3 FY25, with margins expanding to 37% in Q3 FY26 from 28% in Q3 FY25. The company reported profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 84.50 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 53.39 crore in the year-ago period. The quarter included exceptional items of Rs 6.51 crore, mainly on account of incremental provisions towards gratuity and compensated absences following the implementation of the labour codes. The Consumer Group business continued to scale profitably, delivering 27% YoY growth in revenue and 17% YoY growth in PAT. The Remarketing Business also posted solid numbers with 12% YoY growth in revenue and 68% YoY growth in PAT. Meanwhile, OLX India maintained strong momentum, posting 18% YoY growth in revenue and a remarkable 37% YoY rise in PAT. During the quarter, CarTrade Tech attracted approximately 85 million average monthly unique visitors, with 95% of the traffic being organic, highlighting its strong brand equity and content leadership. The company now has a presence across 500+ physical locations through Shriram Automall, CarWale abSure and Signature dealerships, and OLX India franchise outlets, further enhancing its nationwide presence and enabling effective last-mile connectivity. Its flagship digital platforms—CarWale, BikeWale, and OLX India—each cater to more than 150 million annual unique visitors, underscoring the scale and depth of engagement across the ecosystem. The remarketing business achieved an annualized run rate of 1.9 million auction listings, reaffirming its leadership position in the vehicle remarketing space. Vinay Sanghi, chairman and founder of CarTrade Tech, said, "We are pleased to deliver a record quarter, marked by strong operating leverage and our highest-ever revenues at 228 crores across each of our businesses. This translated into significant margin expansion, with EBITDA at 78.25 crores and margins reaching an all-time high of 37%. The consistent performance across quarters underscores the strength of our diversified digital ecosystem. We will continue to invest in future technologies and platform capabilities to deepen engagement." CarTrade Tech is India's largest digital marketplace ecosystem, operating multiple platforms including CarWale, BikeWale, CarTrade, OLX India, Shriram Automall, CarTrade Exchange, and Adroit Auto. These platforms empower millions of users, including consumers, dealers, OEMs, and enterprises, to buy and sell vehicles, real estate, electronics, mobile phones, furniture, and more with ease and efficiency.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cartrade--Tech-Ltd_25528484_65036.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Digilogic Systems’ debut flight loses altitude ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-digilogic-systems-debut-flight-loses-altitude/1668069</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668069</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 83.20, a discount of 20% to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 83.20, a discount of 20% to the issue price. It later hit its lower circuit of 5% from the listing level. The stock touched a high of Rs 83.20 and a low of Rs 79.05, with around 3.32 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Digilogic Systems' IPO was subscribed 1.09 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 January 2026 and it closed on 22 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 98 to Rs 104 per share. The IPO comprised 70,69,200 equity shares, including a fresh issue of 59,79,600 equity shares and offer for sale (OFS) of 10,89,600 equity shares. The company intends to utilise the net proceeds for capital expenditure towards setting up a proposed new facility, pre-payment/ re-payment, in part or full, of certain outstanding borrowings availed by the company and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Digilogic Systems on 19 January 2025, raised Rs 23.08 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 22.18 lakh shares at Rs 104 each to 11 anchor investors. Digilogic Systems is engaged in the design, development, integration, manufacturing, supply, and support of Automated Test Equipment (ATE) systems, radar and electronic warfare environmental simulators, application software, and embedded signal processing solutions for the defence and aerospace engineering sector. As of 31 December 2025, the company had 102 permanent employees on its payroll. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 18.18 crore and net profit of Rs 1.61 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DIGILOGICSYSTEMSLIMITED_65127176_96056.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market trades marginally higher; European markets decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-trades-marginally-higher-european-markets-decline/1668040</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668040</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The frontline equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the afternoon trade, buoyed by optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and FII inflows.

The frontline equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the afternoon trade, buoyed by optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and FII inflows. Investors are closely tracking rupee movements, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements, and geopolitical developments, with attention also on upcoming Q3 results from Larsen & Toubro, Maruti Suzuki India, and BHEL. The Nifty traded above the 25,200 level. Oil & gas, metal and media shares advanced, while FMCG, pharma and healthcare shares corrected. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 136.37 points or 0.17% to 81,993.85. The Nifty 50 index rose 61.65 points or 0.25% to 25,237.05. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.39% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.11%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,761 shares rose and 1,316 shares fell. A total of 171 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 4.35% to 13.82. Gainers & Losers: Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (up 7.58%), Hindalco Industries (up 4.30%), Coal India (up 3.80%), Bharat Electronics (up 3.26%) and Eternal (up 2.68%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Tata Consumer Products (down 5.10%), Asian Paints (down 4.16%), Eicher Motors (down 1.89%), Infosys (down 1.74%) and Hindustan Unilever (down 1.73%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Indian Politics: Ajit Pawar, NCP chief and Maharashtra’s Deputy Chief Minister, died in a plane crash near Baramati on Wednesday while travelling from Mumbai. Four others, including the pilots and his security personnel, were also killed. The small aircraft, a Learjet 45 operated by VSR, reportedly crashed during a landing attempt near Baramati airport about 45 minutes after take-off, as Pawar was on his way to attend public meetings ahead of the local body polls. Television visuals showed fire and wreckage at the site, while media reports said all five people on board died. The 66-year-old leader was the nephew of Sharad Pawar and the cousin of Supriya Sule, both of whom were in Delhi and were expected to travel to Pune. Stocks in Spotlight: Sunteck Realty rose 0.84%. The company reported a 33.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 56.84 crore on a 112.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 344.12 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Vishal Mega Mart tanked 5.72%. The company reported a 19.10% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 312.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 262.72 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 17.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 3,670.41 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Mahindra Logistics surged 15.51% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25 Mahindra Logistics surged 14.65% to Rs 337 after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25.. Motilal Oswal Financial Services surged 8.80% after the company reported a strong set of earnings for the quarter ended December 2025. The company’s profit after tax (PAT), including treasury income and other comprehensive income (OCI), jumped 58% year on year to Rs 721 crore in Q3 FY26, aided by healthy traction in its asset and private wealth management businesses. Total revenue improved 11% to Rs 1,497 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,345 crore in Q3 FY25. Bondada Engineering declined 4.10%. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 119.12% to Rs 54.19 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 24.73 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 89.40% year on year (YoY) to Rs 712.27 crore in Q3 FY26. Nesco shed 0.67%. The company reported a 4.82% YoY decline in net profit to Rs 104.64 crore in Q3 FY26, on a 20.03% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 247.92 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets declined on Wednesday as investors digested a wave of corporate earnings while cautiously awaiting the latest interest rate decision from the U.S. Federal Reserve. Most Asian markets traded higher, with strong gains in technology and AI-related shares ahead of key U.S. megacap earnings outweighing caution in some markets ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision later in the day. Meanwhile, Australia saw its headline inflation come in at 3.6% for the last quarter of 2025, its highest level of inflation in six quarters. Overnight in the U.S., the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.91% to settle at 23,817.10, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average broke ranks, losing 408.99 points, or 0.83%, and settling at 49,003.4 while S&P 500 added 0.41% to end at 6,978.60. The S&P 500 futures edged higher ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision and earnings reports from major tech companies. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bikaji Foods Intl gains as Q3 PAT more than doubles to Rs 62 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bikaji-foods-intl-gains-as-q3-pat-more-than-doubles-to-rs-62-cr/1668014</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668014</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) soared 111.79% to Rs 81.56 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) soared 111.79% to Rs 81.56 crore during the quarter. EBITDA grew 77.1% YoY to Rs 98.4 crore with a margin of 12.5% (up by 466 bps YoY) due to favorable raw material prices as compared to base quarter. Revenue from ethnic snacks grew 13.3% YoY and accounted for around 67.4% of overall revenue. Western snacks recorded strong growth of 22.6% YoY to Rs 58 crore, contributing approximately 8.0% of total revenue. Revenue from papad increased 14.6% YoY to Rs 47.5 crore. Packaged sweets revenue stood at Rs 89.7 crore, declining 17.1% YoY, and accounted for around 12.3% of overall revenue, primarily due to a seasonal shift with Q2 in the current year compared to Q3 last year. The retail business witnessed significant traction, with revenue nearly doubling to Rs 47.1 crore during the quarter, registering an 86.6% YoY growth compared with Rs 25.2 crore in Q3 FY25. Volume grew 8.4% YoY to 39,218 million tonnes in Q3 FY26 as against 36,173 million tonnes in Q3 FY25. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the additional investment of up to Rs 50 crore in Bikaji Foods Retail, a wholly-owned subsidiary, by way of additional subscription to its share capital. Additionally, the company’s board approved the execution of the joint venture cum shareholders agreement entered into by and amongst the Bikaji Foods International, Deepak Agarwal, managing director and Thayekunni Khaleel (founder of Brand ‘Bakemart’), to synergize the combined experience and expertise efforts of the parties to the agreement to undertake the frozen and bakery business in India, on a joint venture basis, through Bikaji Bakes. Further, the company’s board approved the execution of a loan agreement of up to Rs 5 crore with Petunt Food Processors, subsidiary of the company and loan agreement of up to Rs 8 crore with Dadiji Snacks, contract manufacturing unit. Additionally, the board approved an investment of up to Rs 25 crore in Jai Barbareek Dev Snacks, through issuance of 2,50,00,000 optionally convertible debentures. Deepak Agarwal, managing director(MD), Bikaji Foods International, said, “The company delivered a resilient performance during Q3 and 9M FY26, with revenues growing by 10.7% and 13.3% respectively. This growth was primarily driven by the strong momentum in our Ethnic Snacks portfolio, which recorded growth of 13.3% in Q3 and 9.6% over the nine-month period. Demand remained robust across all product categories, underscoring the strength of our brands and their sustained consumer appeal. All categories delivered healthy double-digit growth, except packaged sweets, which were impacted by seasonality due to early Diwali in current year. Exports continued to be a key growth driver, registering a significant increase of 39.1% in Q3 and 58.7% during 9M FY26, supported by wider distribution and increased penetration across international markets. To address inflationary pressures and enhance margin resilience, the Company implemented a series of strategic initiatives, including selective price increases and focused cost efficiency programs. These measures helped sustain growth momentum, particularly within our core categories Our retail business has also begun contributing meaningfully to overall performance, with revenues growing over 150% year-on-year, reflecting improved store productivity and expanding consumer engagement.” Bikaji Foods International is the third largest ethnic snacks company in India with an international footprint, selling Indian snacks and sweets, and is the second fastest growing company in the Indian organised snacks market. As of December 31, 2025, the company has operations in more than 25 states and 4 union territories in India. The company also exports its products to over 25 international countries, including North America, Europe, the Middle East, Africa, and Asia Pacific.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BikajiFoodsInternationalLtd_26794362_25811.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Idea edges higher after net loss narrows to Rs 5,286 crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vodafone-idea-edges-higher-after-net-loss-narrows-to-rs-5286-crore-in-q3/1668012</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668012</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue for the quarter stood at Rs 11,323 crore, up 1.9% YoY.

Revenue for the quarter stood at Rs 11,323 crore, up 1.9% YoY. While reported EBITDA improved by 2.21% YoY to Rs 4,816 crore, reported EBITDA margin expanded to 42.5% in Q3 FY26 from 42.4% in Q3 FY25. Customer ARPU (ex M2M) was Rs 186 in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 173 in Q3 FY25, up 7.3% YoY. The company’s 4G/5G subscriber base rose to 128.5 million in Q3 FY26 from 126.0 million in Q3 FY25. Average data usage by 4G/5G subscribers was 19.2 GB/day for Q3 FY26, up 26.7% YoY. The company said that it had raised Rs 3,300 crore via NCD issue through its subsidiary and the proceeds from this issue would be utilised towards capex. The Department of Telecommunications has confirmed that Vodafone Idea’s AGR liability has been frozen at Rs 87,695 crore as of 31 December 2025, subject to reassessment. The revised payment structure significantly eases near-term cash outgo, with annual payments capped at Rs 124 crore over the next six years, followed by Rs 100 crore annually for four years, and the balance payable later without additional interest. Abhijit Kishore, CEO, Vodafone Idea, said “This quarter marked an important inflection point for the company with positive resolution of key legacy issues. We are thankful to the Government for offering a definitive, long-term and conclusive solution on the AGR matter. We also concluded the settlement of CLAM receivable of Rs 6,394 crore with the Vodafone Group. One of the key milestones for the quarter was the successful NCD raise of Rs. 3,300 Crore, despite an AGR overhang; a clear reflection of lender confidence on our ability to improve the business performance. Collectively, these developments have strengthened the trajectory of our debt discussions which will enable us to execute our larger capex plan to strengthen the network and further elevate the customer experience. On the operational side, our market initiatives translated into deeper customer engagement with ARPU and data consumption improving sequentially.” Vodafone Idea is an Aditya Birla Group and Vodafone Group partnership. It is amongst India’s leading telecom service providers. The company holds a large spectrum portfolio including mid band 5G spectrum in 17 circles and mmWave spectrum in 16 circles. The company provides Voice and Data services across 2G, 4G and 5G platforms and is expanding 5G services across 17 circles.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VodafoneIdea_33393045864_23040.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siyaram Silk slips as Q3 PAT falls 8% YoY to Rs 42 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siyaram-silk-slips-as-q3-pat-falls-8-yoy-to-rs-42-crore/1668010</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668010</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Siyaram Silk Mills declined 5.66% to Rs 526 after the company reported a 7.98% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 41.77 crore on a 9.35% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 624.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiyaramSilk_78390441628_516.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd soars 12.15%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-copper-ltd-soars-1215/1668008</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668008</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Hindustan Copper Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 630.45, up 12.15% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25265.1. The Sensex is at 82129.59, up 0.33%. Hindustan Copper Ltd has added around 29.34% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Hindustan Copper Ltd is a constituent, has added around 12.39% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11829.65, up 2.51% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 734.4 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 521.29 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 94.81 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindCopper_52829551966_3898.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd soars 7.74%, gains for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-natural-gas-corpn-ltd-soars-774-gains-for-fifth-straight-session/1668003</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668003</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 267.15, up 7.74% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.4% on the day, quoting at 25275.35. The Sensex is at 82136.46, up 0.34%. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd has gained around 13.77% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.17% in last one month and is currently quoting at 33293.1, up 3.51% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 532.61 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 119.69 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 266, up 7.31% on the day. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd is up 6.26% in last one year as compared to a 9.12% jump in NIFTY and a 5.69% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 9.58 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ONGC_65712746772_6068.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd spurts 0.25%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tech-mahindra-ltd-spurts-025-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1668004</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668004</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Tech Mahindra Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1749.5, up 0.25% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.4% on the day, quoting at 25275.35. The Sensex is at 82136.46, up 0.34%. Tech Mahindra Ltd has gained around 8.5% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Tech Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.52% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38566.1, down 0.22% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 13.17 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 20.64 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1753.9, down 0.01% on the day. Tech Mahindra Ltd is up 4.07% in last one year as compared to a 9.12% jump in NIFTY and a 10.33% jump in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 40.67 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TechMahindra_28047796713_17215.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd spurts 5.38%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/national-aluminium-company-ltd-spurts-538-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1668005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668005</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

National Aluminium Company Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 405.3, up 5.38% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.4% on the day, quoting at 25275.35. The Sensex is at 82136.46, up 0.34%. National Aluminium Company Ltd has gained around 34.7% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which National Aluminium Company Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 12.64% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11829.65, up 2.73% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 149.3 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 200.5 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 401.05, up 4.97% on the day. National Aluminium Company Ltd is up 109.14% in last one year as compared to a 9.12% jump in NIFTY and a 46.27% jump in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 11.47 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NatlAluminium_39819539035_2304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd soars 4.9%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-ltd-soars-49-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1668006</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668006</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Vedanta Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 740.05, up 4.9% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.4% on the day, quoting at 25275.35. The Sensex is at 82136.46, up 0.34%. Vedanta Ltd has risen around 24.78% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Vedanta Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 12.64% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11829.65, up 2.73% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 195.21 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 167.96 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 738.8, up 4.37% on the day. Vedanta Ltd is up 71.86% in last one year as compared to a 9.12% spurt in NIFTY and a 46.27% spurt in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 29.33 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd gains for fifth session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindalco-industries-ltd-gains-for-fifth-session/1668007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668007</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd is quoting at Rs 1006.45, up 4.64% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The stock is up 72.31% in last one year as compared to a 9.12% gain in NIFTY and a 46.27% gain in the Nifty Metal.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindalcoInds_40254437488_252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>