<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of India Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-india-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1676449</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676449</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bank of India Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Bank of India Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Arun Thukral has been appointed as an Independent Director with effect from February 11, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Mr. Arun Thukral Age: 62 years Designation: Independent Director Qualification: • M.Com • LLB • MBA (Finance) • IICA registered as Independent Director

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ONGC Q3 PAT rises 2% YoY to Rs 8,372 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ongc-q3-pat-rises-2-yoy-to-rs-8372-cr/1676433</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676433</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations declined 6.43% YoY to Rs 31,546.51 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

However, revenue from operations declined 6.43% YoY to Rs 31,546.51 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 10,602.36 crore during the quarter, down 3.61% from Rs 1,1000.26 crore posted in same quarter last year. The company’s net crude oil realization was $61.63 per barrel (down 15.08% YoY) while gas price realization was $6.59 per mmtbu (up 1.38% YoY) during the period under review. During the quarter, crude oil production declined 1.31% YoY to 4.592 million metric tonnes (MMT) and gas production was 4.988 billion cubic metre (BCM), (up 0.20% YoY). On consolidated basis, the company’s net profit jumped 16.67% YoY to Rs 10,015.78 crore on 0.12%marginal rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,67,422.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The board has approved a 2nd interim dividend of 125%, i.e.,Rs 6.25 per equity share of Rs 5, amounting to a total payout of Rs 7,863 crore. The record date for the dividend distribution is 18th February 2026, as intimated to the stock exchanges. Maharatna ONGC is the largest crude oil and natural gas company in India, contributing around 71% to Indian domestic production. It has in-house service capabilities in all areas of exploration and production of oil & gas and related oil-field services. The Government of India held a 58.89% stake in ONGC as of December 2025. Shares of Oil and Natural Gas Corporation declined 2.90% to currently trade at Rs 268.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ONGC_65712746772_6068.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries declines after Q3 PAT falls over 45% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindalco-industries-declines-after-q3-pat-falls-over-45-yoy/1676431</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676431</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the segmental front, Novelis revenue was Rs 36,663 crore (up 9% YoY), Aluminium Upstream revenue was Rs 10,620 crore (up 6% YoY), Aluminium Downstream revenue was Rs 3,909 crore (up 22% YoY) and Copper revenue was Rs 18,233 crore (up 33% YoY).

On the segmental front, Novelis revenue was Rs 36,663 crore (up 9% YoY), Aluminium Upstream revenue was Rs 10,620 crore (up 6% YoY), Aluminium Downstream revenue was Rs 3,909 crore (up 22% YoY) and Copper revenue was Rs 18,233 crore (up 33% YoY). EBITDA rose by 5% to Rs 8,543 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 8,108 crore in Q3 FY25. The company recorded an exceptional charge of Rs 2,610 crore in Q3 FY26. Hindalco said that on 20 November 2025, Novelis' plant located in Oswego, New York, was impacted by another major fire apart from an earlier reported fire that occurred on 16 September 2025. The fire was contained to the hot mill and did not impact the rest of the plant. Novelis expects to incur costs related to repairs, clean-up and other costs related to this event until the operations are fully-restored at the facility. The plant is insured for property damage and business interruption losses related to such events, subject to deductibles and policy limits. The costs associated with both the events have been recorded as exceptional expenses (net of insurance proceeds) amounting to Rs 2,610 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 2,829 crore, down by 47% from Rs 5,296 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Hindalco stated that the impacts of Oswego disruption were partly offset by cost efficiency benefits at Novelis, and record profits by the India business. The India business continued to outperform on the back of favourable macros coupled with the company’s focus on resource security, value enhancement through new product development, and operational efficiencies. Novelis registered an improvement of 6% in EBITDA per tonne despite lower volumes due to the Oswego disruption, reflecting its focus on cost-optimisation and operational excellence. Satish Pai, managing director, Hindalco Industries, said: “We made strong progress across our downstream portfolio with the commissioning and ramping up of key projects including Aditya FRP, battery foil, AC fin-coating, and Copper tubes, positioning us well for emerging growth opportunities. We have entered the next phase of growth with a clear roadmap to expand upstream capacities across alumina, aluminium and copper with aluminium capacity planned to scale up from 1.3 million tonnes to 1.7 million tonnes, and copper smelting capacity from 400 KT to 700 KT. Novelis’ underlying performance remains strong despite short-term capacity constraints from the Oswego disruption. The 600 KT Bay Minette project, on track for commissioning in the second half of FY27, will be a key growth driver.” Hindalco Industries is the metals flagship company of the Aditya Birla Group. A $28 billion metals powerhouse, Hindalco is the world’s largest aluminium company by revenues, and the world’s second largest copper rods manufacturer (outside China).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindalcoInds_40254437488_252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coal India Q3 PAT tanks 16% YoY to Rs 7,166 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coal-india-q3-pat-tanks-16-yoy-to-rs-7166-cr/1676427</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676427</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The growth was led by lower coal offtake as power demand moderated amidst a prolonged spell of monsoon and an increased share of renewables in power generation.

The growth was led by lower coal offtake as power demand moderated amidst a prolonged spell of monsoon and an increased share of renewables in power generation. Profit before tax tanked 19.67% to Rs 9,472.61 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 11,792.42 crore in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, total expenses stood at Rs 28,132 crore in Q3 FY26, up 3.12% from Rs 27,280.39 crore posted in Q3 FY25. The cost of material consumed was at Rs 2,805.34 crore in Q3 FY26, down 2.42% from Rs 2,874.79 crore posted in Q3 FY25. While employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 13,719.77 crore (up 26.4% YoY), finance costs stood at Rs 320.73 crore (up 42.21% YoY) during the quarter. The company reported production of 200.05 million tonnes (MT) in Q3 FY26, down 1% YoY from 202.02 MT in Q3 FY25. Coal offtake also declined 3% YoY to 188.66 MT, compared with 194.53 MT in the corresponding quarter last year. The miner's average realisation from e-auction sales stood at Rs 2,434.56 per tonne, lower than the Rs 2,684.79 per tonne in the year-ago period, while the overall average price realization of coal supplied during the quarter fell by Rs 29 from a year ago to Rs 1,638 per tonne, its earnings' filing showed. Meanwhile, the state-owned producer announced their third interim dividend in the ongoing financial year of Rs 5.50 per equity share. The company has also set Wednesday, February 18, as the record date to determine the eligibility of shareholders for the dividend payout. The dividend will be paid on or before Friday, March 13. Coal India is mainly engaged in mining and production of coal and also operates coal washeries. The major consumers of the company are the power and steel sectors. Consumers from other sectors include cement, fertilizers, and brick kilns. Shares of Coal India shed 0.97% to Rs 415.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoalIndia_84226386779_12019.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drift lower in early trade; breadth weak]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drift-lower-in-early-trade-breadth-weak/1676426</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676426</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in early trade, tracking continued weakness in global equities following a sharp sell-off in technology stocks.

The key equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in early trade, tracking continued weakness in global equities following a sharp sell-off in technology stocks. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. All other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the red, with IT, metal and realty stocks declining the most. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 694.80 points or 0.83% to 82,980.12. The Nifty 50 index fell 210.70 points or 0.82% to 25,592.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index dropped 1.48% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.57%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 829 shares rose and 2,243 shares fell. A total of 163 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 108.42 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 276.85 crore in the Indian equity market on 12 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Honasa Consumer rose 3.34% after the company reported a 93.1% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 50.2 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operation increased 16.2% year-on-year to Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. Indian Hotels Company shed 0.24%. The company reported a 55.1% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 903 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 582 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 12.2% year-on-year to Rs 2,842 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,533 crore in Q3 FY25. Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation added 1.29% after the company reported a 15.5% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 394 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 341 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 18.3% year-on-year to Rs 1,449 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,225 crore in Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.36% to 6.686 compared with previous session close of 6.710. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6650 compared with its close of 90.6100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 1.08% to Rs 154,492. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 96.96. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.113. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement shed 10 cents or 0.15% to $67.42 a barrel. Global Markets: The Asia-Pacific market traded mostly lower Friday, tracking Wall Street declines, as fears over artificial intelligence disruption drove the S&P 500 to a third straight day of losses. Certain pockets of the U.S. stock market have been hit this year by the release of AI tools that threaten to automate tasks performed by some companies—or at least risk eating into their profit margins. Overnight on Wall Street, US stocks fell sharply Thursday as the market punished companies seen as potential losers from artificial-intelligence technology. The S&P 500 fell 108.71 points to 6,832.76. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 669.42 to 49,451.98, and the Nasdaq Composite sank 469.32 to 22,597.15.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Transrail Lighting gains on bagging Rs 2,350-cr orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/transrail-lighting-gains-on-bagging-rs-2350-cr-orders/1676424</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676424</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders are primarily in the domestic T&D segment, along with a Civil order and select wins in Poles & Lighting.

The orders are primarily in the domestic T&D segment, along with a Civil order and select wins in Poles & Lighting. With these additions, the company’s cumulative order inflows for FY26 have crossed Rs 7,980 crore, reflecting strong momentum across its core business segments. Transrail Lighting also holds an L1 position of over Rs 800 crore and maintains a healthy bidding pipeline across domestic and international markets, bolstering its growth outlook. Randeep Narang, MD & CEO stated, “The Rs 2,350 crore order wins in the domestic T&D segment, which includes mainly construction of 765 kV Transmission Lines, along with contributions from Civil and Poles & Lighting underscore the strong demand potential and our competitive positioning in the market. These orders take our FY26 inflows beyond Rs 7,980 crore. With L1 position exceeding Rs 800 crore and a strong bidding pipeline, we are well positioned to sustain the growth momentum while maintaining execution discipline and delivering strong margins.” Transrail Lighting is a leading turnkey engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) company with a primary focus on the power transmission and distribution business, with 4 decades of experience in construction and manufacturing. The company’s consolidated net profit increased 17.7% to Rs 109.74 crore on a 32.6% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,777.19 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TransrailLightingLtd_72945274_67061.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR loses momentum amid AI led sharp sell-off in equities globally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-loses-momentum-amid-ai-led-sharp-sell-off-in-equities-globally/1676421</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676421</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee lost slight momentum in opening trades on Friday tracking modest rebound din dollar index from two-week low and sharp slide in equities globally.

The Indian rupee lost slight momentum in opening trades on Friday tracking modest rebound din dollar index from two-week low and sharp slide in equities globally. INR opened at Rs 90.69 per dollar and edged up to 90.65 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee appreciated 17 paise to settle for the day at 90.61 against the US dollar, as foreign fund investments lifted investor sentiments. However, domestic shares ended the session lower as IT stocks extended their slide from the previous session on renewed concerns about the disruption AI start-ups will have on established companies. The benchmark BSE Sensex dropped 558.72 points, or 0.66 percent, to 83,674.92 on its weekly derivatives expiry day. The broader NSE Nifty index fell 146.65 points, or 0.57 percent, to 25,807.20.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests positive opening for key indices]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-positive-opening-for-key-indices/1676406</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676406</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 30.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 30.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 108.42 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 276.85 crore in the Indian equity market on 12 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 6,021.85 crore so far in February (till 12 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific market traded mostly lower Friday, tracking Wall Street declines, as fears over artificial intelligence disruption drove the S&P 500 to a third straight day of losses. Certain pockets of the U.S. stock market have been hit this year by the release of AI tools that threaten automating tasks performed by some companies — or at least risk eating into their profit margins. Overnight on Wall Street, US stocks fell sharply Thursday as the market punished companies seen as potential losers from artificial-intelligence technology. The S&P 500 fell 108.71 points to 6,832.76. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 669.42 to 49,451.98, and the Nasdaq composite sank 469.32 to 22,597.15. Domestic Market: Benchmark indices closed sharply lower on Thursday, weighed down by intense selling in IT stocks amid rising concerns over AI-led disruption and an uncertain global environment. Weekly expiry-related volatility in BSE derivatives reinforced the risk-off mood. Sentiment deteriorated further after stronger-than-expected US jobs data tempered hopes of near-term rate cuts. The Nifty regained the 25,800 mark after hitting an intraday low of 25,752.40 in late trade, with technology stocks at the forefront of the decline. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 558.72 points or 0.66% to 83,674.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 146.65 points or 0.57% to 25,807.20.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ACS Technologies secures order worth Rs 1 crore from RVNL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acs-technologies-secures-order-worth-rs-1-crore-from-rvnl/1676140</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676140</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract is to be executed as per the terms outlined in the purchase order.

The contract is to be executed as per the terms outlined in the purchase order. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not involve any interest from the promoter, promoter group, or group companies. This transaction does not qualify as a related party transaction. ACS Technologies is primarily engaged in the business of system integration, security and surveillance, IoT solutions, and software products and services in the area of information technology. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 46% to Rs 2.19 crore on a 45.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 48.25 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of ACS Technologies rose 0.32% to close at Rs 40.97 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LNIndustries_79964971756_5092.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Honasa Consumer, Indian Hotels Company, IRCTC, HCC, Coal India]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-honasa-consumer-indian-hotels-company-irctc-hcc-coal-india/1676139</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676139</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&O trading on 13 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&O trading on 13 February 2026. Result Today: Ipca Laboratories, IRB Infrastructure Developers, Brainbees Solutions Firstcry, Alkem Laboratories, Akums Drugs and Pharmaceuticals, Ola Electric Mobility, Azad Engineering, Siemens Energy India, Fortis Healthcare, GMR Airports, Inox Wind, KFin Technologies, Info Edge (India), Narayana Hrudayalaya, Tenneco Clean Air India, Torrent Pharmaceuticals, Vijaya Diagnostic Centre, and Western Carriers (India) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Key events to watch: Narendra Modi, Nitin Gadkari, and Tuhin Kanta Pandey are scheduled to speak at the Global Business Summit in New Delhi. Society of Indian Automobile Manufacturers to release January auto sales data. Stocks to Watch: Honasa Consumer reported a 93.1% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 50.2 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operation increased 16.2% year-on-year to Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. Indian Hotels Company reported a 55.1% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 903 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 582 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 12.2% year-on-year to Rs 2,842 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,533 crore in Q3 FY25. Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation reported a 15.5% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 394 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 341 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 18.3% year-on-year to Rs 1,449 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,225 crore in Q3 FY25. HCC reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 8.1 crore in Q3 FY26 versus a loss of Rs 38.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 8.1% year-on-year to Rs 925 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,007 crore in Q3 FY25. Coal India reported a 15.9% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 7,157 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 8,506 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 5.3% year-on-year to Rs 34,924 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 36,859 crore in Q3 FY25. Inox India reported a 4.0% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 60.7 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 58.4 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 28.4% year-on-year to Rs 429 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 334 crore in Q3 FY25. Mishra Dhatu Nigam reported an 8.2% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 27.6 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 25.5 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 16.0% year-on-year to Rs 276 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 238 crore in Q3 FY25. Hindalco Industries reported a 56.8% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 2,049 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,741 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations rose 0.7% quarter-on-quarter to Rs 66,521 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 66,058 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>