<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:21:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Privi Speciality Chemicals Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/privi-speciality-chemicals-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662672</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662672</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd, Pil Italica Lifestyle Ltd, Bonlon Industries Ltd and Creative Eye Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 31 December 2025.

Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd, Pil Italica Lifestyle Ltd, Bonlon Industries Ltd and Creative Eye Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 31 December 2025. Privi Speciality Chemicals Ltd crashed 11.58% to Rs 2804.9 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 5.09 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4437 shares in the past one month. Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd tumbled 9.40% to Rs 53. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 541 shares in the past one month. Pil Italica Lifestyle Ltd lost 9.17% to Rs 9.11. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.38 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17054 shares in the past one month. Bonlon Industries Ltd shed 8.88% to Rs 54.15. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.4 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 64591 shares in the past one month. Creative Eye Ltd slipped 6.58% to Rs 6.82. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 8 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8610 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FairchemSpeci_81335984825_4846.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade with strong gains; oil & gas shares surge]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-with-strong-gains-oil-gas-shares-surge/1662670</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662670</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with significant gains in mid-afternoon trade on the last trading day of the year.

The key equity benchmarks traded with significant gains in mid-afternoon trade on the last trading day of the year. Nifty climbed above 26,150 mark. Trading activity remained strong on positive expectations for the coming year. The Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark. Oil & gas shares jumped after declining in the four consecutive trading sessions. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 654.29 points or 0.77% to 85,327.39. The Nifty 50 index jumped 220.65 points or 0.85% to 26,161.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.97% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.05%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,759 shares rose and 1,376 shares fell. A total of 175 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index jumped 2.58% to 12,222.15. The index fell 1.13% in the past four trading sessions. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (up 5.92%), Gujarat Gas (up 5.74%), Gujarat State Petronet (up 4.33%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (up 4.13%), Oil India (up 3.35%), Indian Oil Corporation (up 3.19%), Mahanagar Gas (up 2.33%), Reliance Industries (up 2.28%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (up 1.85%) and Aegis Logistics (up 1.8%) advanced. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.06% to 6.572 as compared with the previous close of 6.576. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8650 compared with its close of 89.7500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement fell 0.98% to Rs 135,331. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.15% to 98.39. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.44% to 4.111. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement declined 22 cents or 0.36% to $61.11 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Sumit Woods surged 11.96% after the company said its subsidiary, Sumit Hills, has signed a development agreement for the redevelopment of Nav Vidya Laxmi CHSL at Mahim, Mumbai, as part of a composite project with Brothers CHSL. Mazda surged 4.45% after it has secured a Rs 28.75 crore order from a domestic waste management company for the manufacture and supply of Multi Effect Evaporator (MEE) systems & Agitated Thin Film Dryers (ATFD). Solar Industries India advanced 1.78% after the company announced that it has secured an additional order worth Rs 1,746 crore from Coal India, for and on behalf of its subsidiaries, for the supply of bulk explosives.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-deepak-fertilisers-petrochemicals-corp-ltd-counter/1662669</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662669</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd, Graphite India Ltd, HEG Ltd, Gujarat Gas Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 31 December 2025.

Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd, Graphite India Ltd, HEG Ltd, Gujarat Gas Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 31 December 2025. Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd registered volume of 28.01 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 16.1 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.74 lakh shares. The stock rose 6.54% to Rs.1,288.10. Volumes stood at 4.04 lakh shares in the last session. Mangalore Refinery And Petrochemicals Ltd registered volume of 312.16 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.91 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 19.62 lakh shares. The stock rose 11.21% to Rs.157.65. Volumes stood at 15.44 lakh shares in the last session. Graphite India Ltd saw volume of 109.26 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.56 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 12.76 lakh shares. The stock increased 9.25% to Rs.642.05. Volumes stood at 13.14 lakh shares in the last session. HEG Ltd notched up volume of 221.07 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.03 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 27.53 lakh shares. The stock rose 5.61% to Rs.634.40. Volumes stood at 47.15 lakh shares in the last session. Gujarat Gas Ltd notched up volume of 22.77 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.31 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.12 lakh shares. The stock rose 5.15% to Rs.411.60. Volumes stood at 3.23 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DeepakFert_23363290328_135.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude softens as focus stays on US inventories]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-softens-as-focus-stays-on-us-inventories/1662668</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662668</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures eased on last session of the year.

WTI Crude oil futures eased on last session of the year. The counter has come off a three-week high and is currently trading around $57.74 per barrel, down 0.36% on the day. The commodity is headed for its steepest annual decline since 2020 and some surprising measures could be in store from leading oil producers following sustained weakness in the commodity in last few months. Meanwhile, data out from American Petroleum Institute (API) showed yesterday that the US crude oil inventories saw a build of 1.7 million barrels in the week ending December 26. Crude oil inventories rose by 2.4 million barrels in the previous week. MCX Crude oil is trading at Rs 5208 per barrel, down 0.52% on the day after testing a low of Rs 5204 per barrel.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-on-the-north-sea-picture-id48328_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sumit Woods jumps on Mahim redevelopment project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sumit-woods-jumps-on-mahim-redevelopment-project/1662665</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662665</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The proposed project is a super-premium residential redevelopment comprising 2 BHK and 3 BHK apartments.

The proposed project is a super-premium residential redevelopment comprising 2 BHK and 3 BHK apartments. The project entails an approximate free-sale FSI area of 1.70 lakh sq ft and carries an estimated project value of about Rs 737 crore. Sumit Woods is in the business of real estate development. The company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 87.1% to Rs 0.29 crore on a 72% decrease in revenue from operations to Rs 12.82 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SumitWoodsLtd_73887458_73121.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 26,150 mark; broader mrkt outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-26150-mark-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1662664</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662664</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major gains in the afternoon trade, ending a four-session losing streak on the final trading day of the year, as bargain hunting lifted indices despite ongoing concerns over sustained foreign fund outflows.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major gains in the afternoon trade, ending a four-session losing streak on the final trading day of the year, as bargain hunting lifted indices despite ongoing concerns over sustained foreign fund outflows. The Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark. Barring the Nifty IT index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the green, with the Oil & Gas, Metal and PSU Bank indices gaining the most. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex rallied 643.50 points or 0.76% to 85,318.58. The Nifty 50 index climbed 215.50 points or 0.84% to 26,154.70. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 1.03% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index surged 1.08%. The market breadth was advanced. On the BSE, 2,810 shares rose and 1,252 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: JSW Steel (up 4.66%), Tata Steel (up 2.74%), SBI Life Insurance Company (up 2.22%), Reliance Industries (up 1.99%) and Titan Company (up 1.92%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.83%), Wipro (down 0.64%), Bajaj Finance (down 0.32%), Tech Mahindra (down 0.21%) and Infosys (down 0.07%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Waaree Energies rose 0.33%. The company announced that it has secured an order to supply 1,500 MW of solar modules (1,000 MW DCR and 500 MW non-DCR) from a renowned power sector customer. Shakti Pumps India rallied 3.57% after the company announced that it has secured a new work order worth Rs 170.25 crore from Madhya Pradesh Urja Vikas Nigam. ZF Steering Gear India surged 8.42% after the company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Drivesys Systems, has secured a significant order worth Rs 151 crore for its renewable energy business. Power Grid Corporation of India rose 1.44% after the company said that it has declared a successful bidder for the 2,000 MWh battery energy storage project. Premier Energies added 0.21%. The company has secured new orders worth Rs 2,307.30 crore during the third quarter of FY26, with execution scheduled across FY27 and FY28. Ahasolar Technologies shed 0.21%. The company has received a contract from CIL Rajasthan Akshay Urja for providing owner’s engineering and project management consultancy (OEPMC) services for an 875 MW solar photovoltaic power project. Apollo Micro Systems jumped 4.70% after the company’s step- down subsidiary IDL Explosives bagged supply contracts worth approximately Rs 421 crore. RITES gained 4.66% after the company has received a Letter of Award for the supply of in-service Cape gauge diesel-electric locomotives from Berhard Development Corporation, Zimbabwe. The order is valued at $3.6 million. Global Markets: Most European shares advanced on Wednesday. Markets will operate for a half-day on Wednesday and will remain closed on Thursday for the New Year’s Day holiday, before reopening on Friday. In Asia, markets traded mixed on the holiday-shortened final trading day of the year. Hong Kong and Australia will close early for the holidays, while Japan and South Korea remained closed for the day. China’s economy ended the year on a slightly less gloomy note, as factory activity expanded in December for the first time since March, beating expectations, according to official data released Wednesday. The official manufacturing purchasing managers index rose to 50.1 in December, higher than 49.2 reading that was recorded in November. A reading above 50 indicates expansion. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 fell modestly, notching a third consecutive losing session. The broad market index lost 0.14% and closed at 6,896.24, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.24% and settled at 23,419.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.20% and ended at 48,367.06. The three major averages have slumped to start the week, dragged down by losses in tech. Nvidia posted back-to-back losing sessions, as did another AI stock Palantir Technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mazda jumps after securing Rs 29-cr MEE & ATFD order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mazda-jumps-after-securing-rs-29-cr-mee-atfd-order/1662663</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662663</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract is slated for completion within eight months from the date of approval of technical drawings and documents.

The contract is slated for completion within eight months from the date of approval of technical drawings and documents. The deal does not involve any related-party transaction, and neither the promoters nor promoter group companies hold any interest in the awarding entity. The order highlights Mazda’s expanding presence in the waste management equipment segment and its ability to deliver critical industrial systems on schedule. Mazda is engaged in the business of manufacturing engineering goods like vacuum products, evaporators, pollution control equipment and manufacturing of food products like food colour, various fruit jams & fruit mix powders, etc. The company reported a standalone net profit of Rs 7.58 crore in Q2 FY26, down 15.6% from Rs 8.98 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations fell 10.5% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 50.84 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Mazda_56183286306_2838.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank soars 1.57%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/punjab-national-bank-soars-157-up-for-third-straight-session/1662647</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662647</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank rose for a third straight session today.

Punjab National Bank rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 124.3, up 1.57% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Punjab National Bank has dropped around 0.8% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Punjab National Bank is a constituent, has dropped around 0.01% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59171.25, up 0.85% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 122.62 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 167.82 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 125.16, up 1.82% on the day. Punjab National Bank is up 21.08% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% gain in NIFTY and a 16.87% gain in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 8.99 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd up for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-forge-ltd-up-for-third-consecutive-session/1662648</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662648</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Bharat Forge Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1472.2, up 1.21% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Bharat Forge Ltd has gained around 2.74% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bharat Forge Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.56% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27889.65, up 0.93% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 13.3 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.62 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1479, up 0.93% on the day. Bharat Forge Ltd is up 13.25% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% jump in NIFTY and a 21.65% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 51.1 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatForge_36016338711_69.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Auto Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-auto-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662649</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662649</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bajaj Auto Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Bajaj Auto Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 9377, up 1.02% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Bajaj Auto Ltd has gained around 3.09% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bajaj Auto Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.56% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27889.65, up 0.93% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.85 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.05 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 9447, up 1.16% on the day. Bajaj Auto Ltd is up 7.28% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% jump in NIFTY and a 21.65% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 29.72 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajAuto_20897586_28074.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil India Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-india-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1662650</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662650</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil India Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Oil India Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 427.95, up 4.01% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Oil India Ltd has risen around 3.32% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Oil India Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 0.55% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34813.9, up 1.52% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 19.74 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 14.36 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 431.15, up 3.94% on the day. Oil India Ltd is down 2.09% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% spurt in NIFTY and a 0.25% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 14.34 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OilIndia_41919311821_5452.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd spurts 2.05%, rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-life-insurance-company-ltd-spurts-205-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662651</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662651</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 668.25, up 2.05% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd has added around 7.51% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd is a constituent, has added around 0.75% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27382.8, up 0.81% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 8.66 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 11.61 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 670.5, up 1.79% on the day. ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd is up 1.28% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% gain in NIFTY and a 16.87% gain in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 72.19 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIPrudentialLifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_18603840404_22005.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dabur India Ltd spurts 2.11%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dabur-india-ltd-spurts-211-gains-for-third-straight-session/1662652</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662652</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Dabur India Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Dabur India Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 506.1, up 2.11% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Dabur India Ltd has dropped around 1.78% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Dabur India Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 0.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 55033.15, up 0.92% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 14.42 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 12.4 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 509.05, up 2.12% on the day. Dabur India Ltd is down 0.95% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% gain in NIFTY and a 2.59% gain in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 61.72 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DaburIndia_45461479947_3392.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd soars 2.93%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nazara-technologies-ltd-soars-293-up-for-third-straight-session/1662653</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662653</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Nazara Technologies Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 272.25, up 2.93% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Nazara Technologies Ltd has added around 11.67% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Nazara Technologies Ltd is a constituent, has added around 1.51% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1423.4, up 1.35% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 24.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 31.07 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 367.15 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NazaraTechnologies_39505358.8300902_33311.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Steel Ltd spurts 3.62%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-steel-ltd-spurts-362-up-for-third-straight-session/1662654</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662654</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jindal Steel Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Jindal Steel Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1058.3, up 3.62% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Jindal Steel Ltd has added around 0.98% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Jindal Steel Ltd is a constituent, has added around 8.01% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11007.65, up 1.59% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 32.4 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 11.63 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1062.5, up 3.39% on the day. Jindal Steel Ltd is up 12.81% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% gain in NIFTY and a 29.43% gain in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 21.45 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalSteelLtd_73073935_20287.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Steel Ltd soars 2.56%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-steel-ltd-soars-256-gains-for-third-straight-session/1662655</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662655</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Steel Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Tata Steel Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 180.3, up 2.56% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Tata Steel Ltd has added around 6.92% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Tata Steel Ltd is a constituent, has added around 8.01% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11007.65, up 1.59% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 363.15 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 231.11 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 181.35, up 2.67% on the day. Tata Steel Ltd is up 31.86% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% gain in NIFTY and a 29.43% gain in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 14.07 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataSteel_98454158604_566.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Stainless Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-stainless-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1662656</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662656</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jindal Stainless Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Jindal Stainless Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 846.6, up 1.27% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Jindal Stainless Ltd has gained around 12.13% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Jindal Stainless Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 8.01% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11007.65, up 1.59% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 16.89 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.11 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 25.51 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalStain_15230115440_24610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ajanta Pharma Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ajanta-pharma-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1662657</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662657</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ajanta Pharma Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Ajanta Pharma Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2771, up 1.62% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Ajanta Pharma Ltd has gained around 8.13% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Ajanta Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.91% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22540.05, up 0.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 28897 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.25 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 35.82 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AjantaPharma_12686194738_13504.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of Maharashtra spurts 2.81%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-maharashtra-spurts-281-up-for-third-straight-session/1662658</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662658</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bank of Maharashtra rose for a third straight session today.

Bank of Maharashtra rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 62.21, up 2.81% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Bank of Maharashtra has added around 7.91% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty PSU Bank index of which Bank of Maharashtra is a constituent, has added around 0.4% in last one month and is currently quoting at 8431.5, up 1.64% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 324.66 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 235.19 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 7.6 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofMaha_49685557243_5607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of India soars 1.38%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-india-soars-138-gains-for-third-straight-session/1662659</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662659</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bank of India is up for a third straight session in a row.

Bank of India is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 143.97, up 1.38% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.76% on the day, quoting at 26136.25. The Sensex is at 85259.33, up 0.69%. Bank of India has dropped around 2.22% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty PSU Bank index of which Bank of India is a constituent, has dropped around 0.4% in last one month and is currently quoting at 8431.5, up 1.64% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 55.26 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 67.55 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 144.88, up 1.56% on the day. Bank of India is up 40.27% in last one year as compared to a 10.08% gain in NIFTY and a 30.91% gain in the Nifty PSU Bank index. The PE of the stock is 6.5 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofIndia_12067469065_5654.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>