<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee continues to fall]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-continues-to-fall/1663251</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663251</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.4025 per Dollar on Monday (05 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.3400 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper sees excellent upmove amid supportive equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-sees-excellent-upmove-amid-supportive-equities/1663250</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663250</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper extended its winning spree on Monday, edging higher despite firm US dollar index as tight inventories and new age demand drivers boosted the metal.

COMEX Copper extended its winning spree on Monday, edging higher despite firm US dollar index as tight inventories and new age demand drivers boosted the metal. The counter has zoomed near record highs and currently trades up 3% at $5.86 per pound. On MCX, Copper futures are trading at Rs 1299 per kg, up 0.92% on the day, coming off highs of Rs 1320 per kg. Asian stocks rose on Monday as markets shrugged off US-Venezuela tension and China's Shanghai Composite index surged 1.38%. European markets are off to good start too. On Friday, the US stocks fluctuated over the course of the first trading day of 2026 on Friday before eventually ending the day little changed. However, US equities recorded smashing gains in last year. DOW rose 13% and S&P 500 added 16%. NASDAQ led the up move with a 20% spike

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/colorful-infographic-chart-of-businessrelated-elements-pict_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T Finance records 49% YoY rise in disbursements; loan book rises to Rs 1.11 lakh crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-finance-records-49-yoy-rise-in-disbursements-loan-book-rises-to-rs-111-lakh-crore/1663248</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663248</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The retail disbursements for Q3 FY2024-25 were Rs 15,210 crore.

The retail disbursements for Q3 FY2024-25 were Rs 15,210 crore. Urban Finance disbursements amounted to Rs 9,670 crore (up 48% YoY), Rural Business Finance disbursements were Rs 6,740 crore (up 47% YoY), Farmer Finance disbursements aggregated to Rs 2,780 crore (up 11% YoY) and SME Finance disbursements added up to Rs 1,550 crore (up 24% YoY). Gold Finance disbursements for December’25 quarter were Rs 1,400 crore. The value of the acquired portfolio was Rs 550 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 336 crore in Q3 FY25. The retail loan book as on 31 December 2025 was Rs 1,11,900 crore as against Rs 92,224 crore as on 31 December 2024, up 21% YoY. The realisations improved to 98% in Q3 FY26 from 97% in Q3 FY25. L&T Finance offers financing for two-wheelers, consumer goods, homes, farm equipment, women entrepreneurs, rural groups, real estate, and infrastructure. It provides financing for small and medium enterprises through term loans and overdraft facilities. The company had reported a 5.64% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 734.84 crore on a 7.74% increase in total income to Rs 4,335.79 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip had advanced 0.19% to end at Rs 320.40 on the BSE today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LTFinanceLtd_36546723_41147.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR weakens as slide beyond 90 per US dollar extends]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-weakens-as-slide-beyond-90-per-us-dollar-extends/1663247</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663247</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee stayed under stress after breaking above 90 per US dollar mark.

Indian Rupee stayed under stress after breaking above 90 per US dollar mark. The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today as investors booked profits in select heavyweights amid heightened geopolitical tensions following U.S. military action in Venezuela and the capture of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife. The Nifty settled near the 26,250 mark. Safe haven demand propped up precious metals impressively following this and the US dollar index also edged up to one-month high. This weighed on Indian Rupee and INR lost 8 paise to 90.28 per US dollar. Meanwhile, India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-currency-trading-concept-picture-id504246822_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shukra Pharma inks MoU with US-based Borns Medical Robotics for surgical robotic systems]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shukra-pharma-inks-mou-with-us-based-borns-medical-robotics-for-surgical-robotic-systems/1663246</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663246</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The MOU sets out the framework for collaboration between the parties to introduce, promote and commercialize next-generation Al-enabled soft-tissue surgical robotic systems across lndia and select South Asian markets, including Nepal, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Maldives and Bhutan, subject to applicable regulatory approvals.

The MOU sets out the framework for collaboration between the parties to introduce, promote and commercialize next-generation Al-enabled soft-tissue surgical robotic systems across lndia and select South Asian markets, including Nepal, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Maldives and Bhutan, subject to applicable regulatory approvals. Shukra Pharmaceuticals stated that this collaboration will focus on expanding access to robot-assisted minimally invasive surgeries, integrating AI-driven digital surgery workflows to improve standardization and efficiency, and strengthening regional healthcare infrastructure through technology transfer and clinician training. Borns Medical Robotics will contribute its surgical robotics and AI expertise, while the company will leverage its regulatory capabilities and healthcare market reach across India and South Asia. The collaboration supports the company’s long-term strategy of expanding into high-value, technology-led healthcare segments. It is expected to strengthen its medical technology portfolio and market positioning, unlock new revenue opportunities through commercialization and hospital partnerships, enhance brand visibility and competitiveness in digital healthcare, and contribute to sustainable long-term shareholder value by gaining exposure to the fast-growing global surgical robotics market. "The MOU is non-binding in nature and outlines the intent of the parties to explore definitive agreements in due course, subject to detailed commercial terms, regulatory approvals, and mutual consent,” the company said in a statement. Shukra Pharmaceuticals manufactures and markets pharmaceutical products and does laboratory testing. The company's consolidated net profit surged to Rs 2.38 crore in the quarter ended September 2025 as against Rs 0.54 crore during the previous quarter ended September 2024. Sales rose 5.76% to Rs 5.88 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip had declined 4.98% to end at Rs 54.15 on the BSE today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShukraPharma_17853739038_4083.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end lower amid geopolitical tensions ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-lower-amid-geopolitical-tensions/1663245</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663245</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity market ended marginally lower on Monday after a choppy session.

Domestic equity market ended marginally lower on Monday after a choppy session. Early optimism from strong corporate updates faded as investors turned cautious amid rising geopolitical tensions linked to U.S. military action in Venezuela. The Sensex and Nifty moved between small gains and losses through the day. The Nifty finally settled near the 26,250 mark as profit booking emerged in select heavyweight stocks. Sectoral cues were mixed. IT and oil and gas shares remained under pressure, while FMCG and consumer durables showed resilience. Overall sentiment stayed guarded yet constructive, suggesting consolidation rather than a broad based shift in market direction. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 322.39 points or 0.38% to 85,439.62. The Nifty 50 index dropped 78.25 points or 0.30% to 26,250.30. HDFC Bank (down 2.35%), Infosys (down 2.09%) and Reliance Industries (down 0.94%) were major drags today. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.05% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.07%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,723 shares rose and 2,544 shares fell. A total of 203 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.05% to 10.02. US and Venezuela Situation: The U.S. launched a military operation in Venezuela over the weekend, resulting in the arrest of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores. The couple is set to appear before a New York court on drug-related charges. President Donald Trump stated that the U.S. is now in control of Venezuela and warned of potential further military action. The UN Security Council is scheduled to meet today to discuss the U.S. intervention, which UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres called a dangerous precedent. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper advanced 0.38% to 6.634 compared with the previous session close of 6.609. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2750 compared with its close of 90.2050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 1.50% to Rs 137,839. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.18% to 98.60. The United States 10-year bond yield slipped 0.60% to 4.166. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement advanced 7 cents or 0.12% to $60.82 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares advanced on Monday as traders digested the U.S.-led overthrow of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Asian market began the first full trading week of 2026 on a stronger note after the U.S. said it had attacked Venezuela and captured President Nicolas Maduro over the weekend. Oil prices edged lower as markets weighed the potential impact of geopolitical tensions. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. On Friday stateside, the first trading day of 2026, the S&P 500 closed slightly higher as gains in semiconductor names kept the index afloat. The benchmark closed up 0.19% at 6,858.47, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.03% to finish at 23,235.63. The two had been solidly positive earlier in the day, with the S&P 500 and the tech-heavy Nasdaq trading higher by 0.7% and 1.5% at their peaks, respectively. Stocks in Spotlight: Corona Remedies added 1.44% after it reported a 21.75% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 52.32 crore on 15.05% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 361.13 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. AVG Logistics rose 4.55% after the company announced a strategic partnership with Nestlé India and Ashok Leyland to develop a green supply chain corridor. Under the partnership, AVG Logistics will deploy 50 CNG powered trucks to service Nestlé India, creating a dedicated green corridor aimed at improving efficiency while lowering environmental impact. The company said the fleet is expected to cover around 2.75 lakh kilometres per month and reduce carbon emissions by about 1.1 lakh kg of CO₂ annually. CSB Bank surged 16.23% after the bank’s total deposits climbed 21% to Rs 40,460 crore as on 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 33,407 crore as on 31st December 2024. Of the total deposits, CASA increased 3% YoY to Rs 8,316 crore, while term deposits jumped 27% YoY to Rs 32,144 crore as of 31 December 2025. Gross advance stood at Rs 37,208 crore as of 31st December 2025, registering the growth of 29% compared with Rs 28,915 crore as of 31st December 2024. Advances against gold & gold jewellery (excluding receivables secured against gold) jumped 46% YoY to Rs 19,023 crore as of 31st December 2025. Amber Enterprises India jumped 3.62% after its step down subsidiaries received approval under the Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme. PC Jeweller surged 7.32% after the company reported a strong business update for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The jewellery retailer said standalone revenue rose around 37% year on year in Q3 FY26, driven by robust demand during the ongoing festival and wedding season. NIBE surged 4.17% after it secured a domestic defence contract worth Rs 292.69 crore from the Indian Army under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. Jammu & Kashmir Bank added 1.07%. The bank's gross advances jumped 17.26% to Rs 1,16,247.92 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 99,133.35 crore as of 31 December 2024. V-Mart Retail jumped 5.35% after the company’s revenue from operations for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 stood at Rs 1,126 crore, recording the growth of 10%, compared with Rs 1,027 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1663243</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663243</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,329, a premium of 78.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,250.30 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,329, a premium of 78.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,250.30 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index fell 78.25 points or 0.30% to 26,250.30. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.05% to 10.02. HDFC Bank, ITC and Reliance Industries were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro speculative net longs climb to two and half year high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-speculative-net-longs-climb-to-two-and-half-year-high/1663239</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663239</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market climbs to a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market climbs to a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of Euro futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net long position of 159891 contracts in the data reported through December 23, 2025. This was a weekly addition of 14988 net long contracts

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices end with modest losses; IT shares tumble ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-end-with-modest-losses-it-shares-tumble/1663238</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663238</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today as investors booked profits in select heavyweights amid heightened geopolitical tensions following U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today as investors booked profits in select heavyweights amid heightened geopolitical tensions following U.S. military action in Venezuela and the capture of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife. The Nifty settled near the 26,250 mark. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 322.39 points or 0.38% to 85,439.62. The Nifty 50 index dropped 78.25 points or 0.30% to 26,250.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.05% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.07%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.05% to 10.02. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Realty index (up 2.07%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 1.12%) and the Nifty FMCG index (up 0.68%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 1.43%), the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 1.02%) and the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.32%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. US and Venezuela Situation: The U.S. launched a military operation in Venezuela over the weekend, resulting in the arrest of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores. The couple is set to appear before a New York court on drug-related charges. President Donald Trump stated that the U.S. is now in control of Venezuela and warned of potential further military action. The UN Security Council is scheduled to meet today to discuss the U.S. intervention, which UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres called a dangerous precedent. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper advanced 0.38% to 6.634 compared with the previous session close of 6.609. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2750 compared with its close of 90.2050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement advanced 1.50% to Rs 137,839. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.18% to 98.60. The United States 10-year bond yield slipped 0.60% to 4.166. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement advanced 7 cents or 0.12% to $60.82 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares traded advanced on Monday as traders digested the U.S.-led overthrow of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Asian market began the first full trading week of 2026 on a stronger note after the U.S. said it had attacked Venezuela and captured President Nicolas Maduro over the weekend. Oil prices edged lower as markets weighed the potential impact of geopolitical tensions. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. Oil prices fell after the escalation involving the oil-rich nation. Brent crude prices slipped more than 1% earlier before paring losses and were last trading 0.25% lower, while the West Texas Intermediate crude prices fell 0.4%. On Friday stateside, the first trading day of 2026, the S&P 500 closed slightly higher as gains in semiconductor names kept the index afloat. The benchmark closed up 0.19% at 6,858.47, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.03% to finish at 23,235.63. The two had been solidly positive earlier in the day, with the S&P 500 and the tech-heavy Nasdaq trading higher by 0.7% and 1.5% at their peaks, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index rises 2.07%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-rises-207/1663237</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663237</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index closed up 2.07% at 917.4 today.

Nifty Realty index closed up 2.07% at 917.4 today. The index is up 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Sobha Ltd gained 5.79%, Lodha Developers Ltd rose 3.16% and Prestige Estates Projects Ltd added 2.98%. The Nifty Realty index is down 12.00% over last one year compared to the 9.35% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty IT index is down 1.43% and Nifty FMCG index increased 0.68% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has slid 0.30% to close at 26250.3 while the SENSEX is down 0.38% to close at 85439.62 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude slippery near $56 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-slippery-near-56-per-barrel/1663236</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663236</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude Oil futures slipped below $57 per barrel as markets assessed the fallout from the capture of Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro by US forces and its potential impact on global crude supply.

WTI Crude Oil futures slipped below $57 per barrel as markets assessed the fallout from the capture of Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro by US forces and its potential impact on global crude supply. Despite Venezuela holding the world’s largest proven oil reserves, investors remained cautious, noting that the OPEC producer accounts for only a small share of global output and the market is already dealing with a growing supply glut. Brent traded near $60 a barrel after volatile moves, while West Texas Intermediate hovered around $56.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concept-with-oil-rig-in-the-gulf-picture-id597_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 322 pts lower; Nifty ends near 26,250 mark; VIX rallies 6.05%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-322-pts-lower-nifty-ends-near-26250-mark-vix-rallies-605/1663234</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663234</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today as investors booked profits in select heavyweights amid heightened geopolitical tensions following U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today as investors booked profits in select heavyweights amid heightened geopolitical tensions following U.S. military action in Venezuela and the capture of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife. The Nifty settled near the 26,250 mark. Realty, consumer durables and FMCG shares advanced while IT, oil & gas and pharma shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 322.39 points or 0.38% to 85,439.62. The Nifty 50 index dropped 78.25 points or 0.30% to 26,250.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.05% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.07%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,607 shares rose and 2,568 shares fell. A total of 222 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.05% to 10.02. US–Venezuela situation: The U.S. launched a military operation in Venezuela over the weekend, resulting in the arrest of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores. The couple is set to appear before a New York court on drug-related charges. President Donald Trump stated that the U.S. is now in control of Venezuela and warned of potential further military action. The UN Security Council is scheduled to meet today to discuss the U.S. intervention, which UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres called a dangerous precedent. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 1.43% to 37,771.15. The index rallied 1.15% in the past two consecutive trading sessions. Wipro (down 2.08%), HCL Technologies (down 2.08%), Infosys (down 2.08%), Persistent Systems (down 1.37%) and Tata Consultancy Services (down 1.11%), Tech Mahindra (down 0.96%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 0.74%), Coforge (down 0.57%), Mphasis (down 0.22%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Corona Remedies added 1.44% after it reported a 21.75% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 52.32 crore on 15.05% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 361.13 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. NIBE surged 4.17% after it secured a domestic defence contract worth Rs 292.69 crore from the Indian Army under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. Jammu & Kashmir Bank added 0.98%. The bank's gross advances jumped 17.26% to Rs 1,16,247.92 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 99,133.35 crore as of 31 December 2024. Bank of Maharashtra rose 0.03%. The bank reported a 15.30% year-on-year (YoY) increase in total deposits to Rs 3,21,695 crore as of 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 2,79,007 crore as of 31st December 2024. V-Mart Retail jumped 5.35% after the company’s revenue from operations for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 stood at Rs 1,126 crore, recording the growth of 10%, compared with Rs 1,027 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. CSB Bank surged 13.77% after the bank’s total deposits climbed 21% to Rs 40,460 crore as on 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 33,407 crore as on 31st December 2024. Global Markets: European shares traded higher on Monday as global markets reacted to the U.S.-led overthrow of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Asian market began the first full trading week of 2026 on a stronger note after the U.S. said it had attacked Venezuela and captured President Nicolas Maduro over the weekend. Oil prices edged lower as markets weighed the potential impact of geopolitical tensions. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. Oil prices fell after the escalation involving the oil-rich nation. Brent crude prices slipped more than 1% earlier before paring losses and were last trading 0.25% lower, while the West Texas Intermediate crude prices fell 0.4%. On Friday stateside, the first trading day of 2026, the S&P 500 closed slightly higher as gains in semiconductor names kept the index afloat. The benchmark closed up 0.19% at 6,858.47, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.03% to finish at 23,235.63. The two had been solidly positive earlier in the day, with the S&P 500 and the tech-heavy Nasdaq trading higher by 0.7% and 1.5% at their peaks, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baazar Style Retail posts 13% YoY rise in Q3 standalone revenue]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baazar-style-retail-posts-13-yoy-rise-in-q3-standalone-revenue/1663233</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663233</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sales per square feet, however, declined by 15% YoY to Rs 70.4 crore in Q3 FY26.

Sales per square feet, however, declined by 15% YoY to Rs 70.4 crore in Q3 FY26. As on 31 December 2025, total store count stood at 252 stores (up 27% YoY) and total rental area aggregated to 23.35 lakh square feet (up 30% YoY). The 90 stores in West Bengal, Assam & Tripura recorded 22% drop in same store sales growth (SSSG) in Q3 FY26. The remaining 63 stores in Other States registered 1% SSSG during the period under review. The company stated that the preponement of festive sales (Durga Puja in Sep-25 as against Oct-24) impacted the SSSG in Q3 FY26. The CY25 SSSG neutralizes the effects of festive shifts between different quarters. Baazar Style Retail further said that its approach of cluster-based store expansion influenced SSSG performance, as incremental stores were added within established clusters. However, the rapid ramp-up of new stores significantly enhanced overall cluster productivity, enabling higher throughput and improved operating leverage. During 9M FY26, the company opened 25 new stores within existing clusters, resulting in a decline of 8% in SSSG of mature stores in these clusters. However, recorded a strong revenue growth of 52% at the cluster level. Heavy rainfall in West Bengal and unrest in parts of Assam and Tripura during peak festive sales impacted SSSG in 9MFY26. States other than West Bengal, Assam, and Tripura continued to deliver healthy growth, with SSSG remaining resilient at 8% in 9MFY26. For the nine months ended in December 2025, the company’s standalone revenue from operations for has grown by an impressive 38% YoY, reaching Rs 1.376 crore, surpassing the company’s earlier guidance of 30% growth. Baazar Style Retail is a value fashion retailer with a leadership position in the states of West Bengal and Odisha in the organized value retail market. The company offers quality and affordable products under the apparel and general merchandise segments, through a chain of 'value retail' stores. Within the apparel vertical, it offers garments for men, women, boys, girls, and infants, whereas the general merchandise offerings include both non-apparels and home furnishing products. The company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 2.05 crore in Q1 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 0.42 crore in Q1 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 37.01% YoY to Rs 377.85 crore in Q1 June 2025. The scrip had declined 7.79% to end at Rs 263.35 on the BSE today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BaazarStyleRetailLtd_39054535_76733.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IDBI Bank Q3 total business grows 12% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/idbi-bank-q3-total-business-grows-12-yoy/1663232</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663232</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a sequential basis, the bank’s total business rose 2.41%.

On a sequential basis, the bank’s total business rose 2.41%. The bank's total deposits stood at Rs 3,07,828 crore in Q3 FY26, recording a 9% YoY growth and a 1.42% quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) increase. During the quarter, net advances stood at Rs 2,38,806 crore, registering a growth of 15% YoY and 3.72% QoQ. CASA deposits were at Rs 1,35,630 crore, up 4% YoY but down 2.44% QoQ. IDBI Bank is engaged in the business of monetary intermediation of commercial banks, saving banks, postal savings banks, and discount houses. The bank’s standalone net profit jumped 97.5% to Rs 3,627.36 crore on a 9.6% rise in total income to Rs 9,593.64 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter slipped 3.61% to Rs 110.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDBIBank_81101517927_5433.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ESAF SFB’s total deposits rise 7% YoY to Rs 24,006 cr in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/esaf-sfbs-total-deposits-rise-7-yoy-to-rs-24006-cr-in-q3/1663244</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663244</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CASA deposits increased 7.83% YoY to Rs 6,030 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 5,592 crore a year ago.

CASA deposits increased 7.83% YoY to Rs 6,030 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 5,592 crore a year ago. The CASA ratio stood at 25.12% as of 31 December 2025, marginally higher than 24.95% as of 31 December 2024. The bank’s gross advances rose 13.06% YoY to Rs 20,680 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 18,291 crore as of 31 December 2024. Micro loans declined 24.16% YoY to Rs 7,583 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 9,999 crore a year earlier. In contrast, retail and other loans surged 57.95% YoY to Rs 13,097 crore as of 31 December 2025, up from Rs 8,292 crore as of 31 December 2024. The bank’s customer base stood at 99.85 lakh as of 31 December 2025, with 5.71 lakh new customers added during the year. During the quarter, the bank completed transactions involving the sale of non-performing assets (NPAs), including technically written-off assets amounting to Rs 1,693.65 crore, to asset reconstruction companies for an aggregate consideration of Rs 183.18 crore. Kerala-based ESAF Small Finance Bank commenced its banking operations in March 2017. As of 31 December 2025, the bank’s distribution network comprised 788 branches, 720 ATMs and 1045 customer service centers spanning across 24 states and 2 union territories. The company reported a standalone net loss of Rs 115.81 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with a net loss of Rs 190.07 crore in Q2 FY25. Total income declined 11.7% YoY to Rs 964.98 crore in Q2 FY26. The counter rose 0.71% to settle at Rs 26.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ESAFSmallFinanceBankLtd_55474849_71846.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nykaa gains on upper mid-twenties revenue growth guidance in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nykaa-gains-on-upper-mid-twenties-revenue-growth-guidance-in-q3-fy26/1663230</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663230</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s consolidated gross merchandise value (GMV) and net sales value (NSV) growth expected to be in late twenties in Q3 FY2026.

The company’s consolidated gross merchandise value (GMV) and net sales value (NSV) growth expected to be in late twenties in Q3 FY2026. Nykaa’s beauty vertical is expected to deliver accelerated NSV growth of late twenties, highest in the past 6 quarters. This stellar growth comes in a seasonally strong quarter, making it the largest quarter till date in terms of absolute scale. The outperformance of House of Nykaa brands, the success of Pink Friday sale as well as robust new customer acquisition contributed to the superior performance. As a result, beauty vertical’s net revenue growth is expected to be in the upper end of mid-twenties. The fashion vertical is expected to continue its revived growth trajectory with NSV growth of mid-twenties in Q3 FY2026. Net revenue growth for the fashion vertical is expected to be in late teens in Q3 FY2026, lower than NSV growth primarily due to subdued content and marketing income and ongoing channel optimization of fashion owned brands. FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) journey began in 2012 as a digital-first, consumer tech beauty company. It has expanded its offerings to include fashion and B2B, launching platforms such as Nykaa Fashion, Nykaa Man, and Nykaa Superstore. The company’s consolidated net profit soared 242.9% to Rs 34.43 crore on 25.1% increase in net sales to Rs 2,345.98 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FSNE-CommerceVenturesLtd_51987676_75803.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trishakti Industries secures domestic contract from Reliance Industries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trishakti-industries-secures-domestic-contract-from-reliance-industries/1663228</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663228</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves the immediate deployment of advanced machines with manpower and carries an initial tenure of one year.

The contract involves the immediate deployment of advanced machines with manpower and carries an initial tenure of one year. The company said the fresh capex deployment for the project is estimated at around Rs 5 crore, while the contract value is expected to be upwards of Rs 14 million, inclusive of taxes. Trishakti Industries is an infrastructure solutions provider specializing in the hiring of heavy earth-moving equipment. With a strong fleet of advanced machinery, it serves major sectors such as steel, cement, railways, and construction. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 89.3% YoY to Rs 1.59 crore posted in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 0.84 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations climbed 133.3% YoY to Rs 6.65 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Trishakti Industries shed 0.58% to Rs 145.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TrishaktiElectronicsIndustries_12352452_6237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AVG Logistics climbs on green supply chain partnership with Nestlé India, Ashok Leyland]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avg-logistics-climbs-on-green-supply-chain-partnership-with-nestl-india-ashok-leyland/1663226</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663226</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the partnership, AVG Logistics will deploy 50 CNG powered trucks to service Nestlé India, creating a dedicated green corridor aimed at improving efficiency while lowering environmental impact.

Under the partnership, AVG Logistics will deploy 50 CNG powered trucks to service Nestlé India, creating a dedicated green corridor aimed at improving efficiency while lowering environmental impact. The company said the fleet is expected to cover around 2.75 lakh kilometres per month and reduce carbon emissions by about 1.1 lakh kg of CO₂ annually. AVG Logistics said the initiative will help lower dependency on conventional fuel, improve cost efficiency, and strengthen supply chain resilience. The company added that the collaboration aligns operational efficiency with sustainability goals and supports long term environmental responsibility. The company said the partnership is expected to aid financial performance through improved utilisation and stable demand, while reinforcing its focus on green logistics and technology led transportation solutions. AVG Logistics is a multimodal logistics provider offering technology driven solutions across transportation, warehousing, distribution, supply chain management, and 3PL services. Founded in 2010, the company operates road and rail transport, cold chain, and warehousing businesses through 50 plus automated branches nationwide, supported by a workforce of over 600 professionals, a fleet of more than 3,000 vehicles, and about 7.32 lakh sq ft of warehousing space, serving marquee clients such as Nestlé, HUL, ITC, Godrej, Apollo Tyres, UltraTech Cement, and Coca Cola. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 5.6% to Rs 5.08 crore on a 3.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 143.03 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AVGLogisticsLtd_65603643022_72285.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sapphire Foods India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sapphire-foods-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1663225</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663225</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Premier Energies Ltd, Epigral Ltd, Devyani International Ltd and Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 January 2026.

Premier Energies Ltd, Epigral Ltd, Devyani International Ltd and Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 January 2026. Sapphire Foods India Ltd lost 7.48% to Rs 233.8 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 76634 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 58694 shares in the past one month. Premier Energies Ltd crashed 6.63% to Rs 790.3. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.92 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.49 lakh shares in the past one month. Epigral Ltd tumbled 5.71% to Rs 1173.2. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8807 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3478 shares in the past one month. Devyani International Ltd corrected 5.37% to Rs 140.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.45 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.03 lakh shares in the past one month. Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services Ltd dropped 4.46% to Rs 384.8. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.74 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.12 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SapphireFoodsIndiaLtd_23447132_72573.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sai-silks-kalamandir-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663221</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663221</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cupid Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, DCM Financial Services Ltd and SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 January 2026.

Cupid Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, DCM Financial Services Ltd and SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 January 2026. Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd tumbled 11.59% to Rs 134.65 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.29 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 23961 shares in the past one month. Cupid Ltd crashed 10.12% to Rs 377.45. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 60.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7.56 lakh shares in the past one month. Vivimed Labs Ltd lost 9.95% to Rs 13.58. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15545 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9530 shares in the past one month. DCM Financial Services Ltd plummeted 9.14% to Rs 5.07. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 229 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3884 shares in the past one month. SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd slipped 7.80% to Rs 377.1. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 19791 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8088 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SaiSilksKalamandirLtd_62265977_34768.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>