<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:26:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Handson Global Management (HGM) Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/handson-global-management-hgm-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1664908</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664908</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mangalam Organics Ltd, Modis Navnirman Ltd, Next Mediaworks Ltd and Redtape Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 14 January 2026.

Mangalam Organics Ltd, Modis Navnirman Ltd, Next Mediaworks Ltd and Redtape Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 14 January 2026. Handson Global Management (HGM) Ltd lost 7.84% to Rs 61.15 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 806 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1615 shares in the past one month. Mangalam Organics Ltd tumbled 7.37% to Rs 468.8. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1222 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 579 shares in the past one month. Modis Navnirman Ltd crashed 6.98% to Rs 305.1. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 312 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2915 shares in the past one month. Next Mediaworks Ltd pared 6.33% to Rs 5.62. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1800 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1028 shares in the past one month. Redtape Ltd fell 6.19% to Rs 121.9. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 93471 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19270 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HOVServicesLtd_67214910628_27340.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops 377 pts; IT shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-377-pts-it-shares-tumble/1664907</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664907</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity indices traded with modest losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE.

Domestic equity indices traded with modest losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE. Investors stayed cautious as they tracked developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical developments. The Nifty traded below the 25,650 mark. IT shares declined after advancing in the past trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex fell 377.34 points or 0.45% to 83,250.35. The Nifty 50 index slipped 96.70 points or 0.37% to 25,637.10. In the broader market, The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.17%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,930 shares rose and 2,137 shares fell. A total of 195 shares were unchanged. Economy: The annual rate of inflation based on the all-India Wholesale Price Index (WPI) increased 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, compared with a decline of 0.32% in November 2025. Inflation turned positive after three months and marked the fastest pace since April, mainly driven by higher prices of manufactured products. Inflation in manufactured products accelerated to 1.82% in December 2025 from 1.33% in November 2025, led by an increase in prices of food products, pharmaceuticals, medicinal chemical and botanical products, and cement, lime & plaster. Inflation in food products rose to 0.90% from 0.62%, while prices of pharmaceuticals increased to 1.60% from 1.39% a month earlier. Inflation in cement, lime & plaster stood at 0.30% compared with 0.08% in November. Food prices remained unchanged in December after declining 2.27% in November, supported by higher prices of milk, fruits, eggs, meat & fish. Meanwhile, inflation in fuel and power remained negative at 2.31% in December 2025 compared with a contraction of 2.27% in November, weighed down by lower prices of LPG, petrol, and high-speed diesel. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index dropped 1.48% to 37,668.85. The index rose 0.65% in the past trading session. Mphasis (down 3.3%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 2.39%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 2.11%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.73%), Wipro (down 1.59%), Coforge (down 1.50%), Persistent Systems (down 1.31%), LTIMindtree (down 0.96%) and Infosys (down 0.81%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.23% to 6.642 compared with previous session close of 6.627. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2100 compared with its close of 90.2300 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.76% to Rs 143,311. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.01% to 98.91. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.05% to 4.173. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement lost 53 cents or 0.81% to $64.94 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Ajmera Realty jumped 5.32% after the company reported quarterly sales of Rs 630 crore for Q3 FY26, marking a sharp increase of 123% compared with sales of Rs 270 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Just Dial fell 1.54% after the company reported 10.2% decline in net profit to Rs 118 crore despite a 6.4% rise in operating revenue to Rs 305.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chinese-stock-market-down-picture-id486499876_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kolte-Patil Developers inks deal to jointly develop land parcel in Pune]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kolte-patil-developers-inks-deal-to-jointly-develop-land-parcel-in-pune/1664906</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664906</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bhugaon, is an emerging residential destination in Pune, blending natural flora and fauna with excellent urban connectivity.

Bhugaon, is an emerging residential destination in Pune, blending natural flora and fauna with excellent urban connectivity. This land parcel is surrounded by established premium markets like Bavdhan and Kothrud and is adjacent to the Mumbai-Pune Expressway as well as Shivaji Nagar railway station. The project is set to benefit from being in close proximity to large employment hubs as well as the access to advanced social infrastructure comprising schools, hospitals, shopping malls and entertainment hubs making this a very unique and attractive proposition. Rajesh Patil, managing director, Kolte-Patil Developers, said: “This transaction aligns with our strategy to systematically strengthen our presence in high-potential micro-markets benefitting from evolving demand trends. This project in Bhugaon marks the next step in expanding our portfolio through capital-efficient partnerships." The Kolte-Patil Developers group is one of the largest residential real estate developers in Pune. The company has a healthy project portfolio of affordable, mid-income, and luxury residential segments through its brands, Kolte-Patil and 24K, respectively, and is expanding its presence in Bengaluru and Mumbai. The company had recorded a consolidated net loss of Rs 10.43 crore in the quarter ended September 2025 as against net profit of Rs 9.74 crore during the previous quarter ended September 2024. Sales declined 55.02% to Rs 138.66 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip shed 0.74% to currently trade at Rs 368.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KoltePatilDev_27715195099_26184.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at AAVAS Financiers Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-aavas-financiers-ltd-counter/1664903</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664903</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[MMTC Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Jupiter Wagons Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 14 January 2026.

MMTC Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Jupiter Wagons Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 14 January 2026. AAVAS Financiers Ltd notched up volume of 24.65 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 17.73 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.39 lakh shares. The stock slipped 0.28% to Rs.1,443.00. Volumes stood at 56656 shares in the last session. MMTC Ltd notched up volume of 862.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.52 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 55.54 lakh shares. The stock rose 11.71% to Rs.70.99. Volumes stood at 27.05 lakh shares in the last session. Go Digit General Insurance Ltd recorded volume of 21.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.21 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.76 lakh shares. The stock lost 3.26% to Rs.327.90. Volumes stood at 73307 shares in the last session. Jupiter Wagons Ltd notched up volume of 298.14 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.4 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 28.67 lakh shares. The stock rose 12.47% to Rs.330.90. Volumes stood at 22.59 lakh shares in the last session. BLS International Services Ltd saw volume of 54.68 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.26 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.62 lakh shares. The stock increased 4.89% to Rs.311.90. Volumes stood at 6.94 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AAVASFinanciersLtd_99454046263_45828.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ Quadrant Future Tek jumps on bagging Rs 288-cr KAVACH order from CLW]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quadrant-future-tek-jumps-on-bagging-rs-288-cr-kavach-order-from-clw/1664902</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664902</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order, including warranty and long-term annual maintenance, is valued at Rs 287.83 crore.

The order, including warranty and long-term annual maintenance, is valued at Rs 287.83 crore. The company said the order has been awarded by a domestic entity and is to be executed within 12 months from the date of the purchase order. The company added that the transaction is at arm’s length, with no interest from the promoter, promoter group or group companies, and does not fall under related-party transactions. Quadrant Future Tek is a technology- and innovation-driven company engaged in the development of next-generation train control and signalling systems, specialty cables and interconnect products, offering high levels of safety and reliability to rail passengers. The company serves customers in India. The company reported a standalone net loss of Rs 15.89 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 3.56 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 13.2% year-on-year to Rs 34.40 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Quadrant-Future-Tek-Ltd_73067085_93245.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pace Digitek bags Rs 376-cr order from Bondada Engineering]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pace-digitek-bags-rs-376-cr-order-from-bondada-engineering/1664900</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664900</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves design, engineering, site development, manufacture, inspection at supplier’s works, supply, insurance, transportation, storage, erection, installation, testing and commissioning of a 300 MW solar power project.

The project involves design, engineering, site development, manufacture, inspection at supplier’s works, supply, insurance, transportation, storage, erection, installation, testing and commissioning of a 300 MW solar power project. The scope also includes balance-of-system (BOS) works under the EPC framework, along with operations and maintenance (O&M) for a period of three years. The order is to be executed within 15 months from the receipt of the letter of award (LoA). Pace Digitek is a telecom infrastructure solutions provider with a significant focus on the telecom industry, including telecom tower infrastructure and optical fiber cables. The company’s consolidated net profit slipped 32.7% to Rs 64.08 crore on a 37% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 533.45 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Pace Digitek shed 0.73% to Rs 176 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PACEDIGITEKLIMITED_26475505_94643.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India WPI inflation rebounds to 0.83% in December]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-wpi-inflation-rebounds-to-083-in-december/1664894</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664894</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s wholesale price inflation rebounded to 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, reversing a contraction in November.

India’s wholesale price inflation rebounded to 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, reversing a contraction in November. This marked the first increase in three months and the strongest pace since April, driven primarily by firmer manufacturing costs. Manufacturing inflation accelerated to 1.82%, led by higher prices of food products, pharmaceuticals, and cement-related items. Food prices stabilized after a sharp decline in November, supported by gains in milk, fruits, and protein items. In contrast, fuel prices remained in deflation, weighed down by lower LPG, petrol, and diesel prices, limiting broader inflationary pressures.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/valentine-sms-1312776_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ajmera Realty surges after quarterly sales rise 123% to Rs 630 crore in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ajmera-realty-surges-after-quarterly-sales-rise-123-to-rs-630-crore-in-q3-fy26/1664892</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664892</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total sales volume for Q3 FY26 added up to 2,62,975 square feet, up by 59% from the volume of 1,65,116 square feet registered in for Q3 FY25.

The total sales volume for Q3 FY26 added up to 2,62,975 square feet, up by 59% from the volume of 1,65,116 square feet registered in for Q3 FY25. Collections during the quarter aggregated to Rs 333 crore, registering a 99% year-on-year growth. On a nine-month basis, the company delivered a sales volume of 5,55,991 square feet, up 36% YoY, while sales value rose 72% YoY to Rs 1,431 crore. Collections for 9M FY26 stood at Rs 787 crore, reflecting a 70% YoY increase. The company stated that Ajmera Realty delivered a strong performance in Q3 FY26, primarily driven by the blockbuster launch of Ajmera Solis at Vikhroli. Phase 1 of the project witnessed an encouraging response, with 84% of inventory absorbed post launch. Dhaval Ajmera, Director - Corporate Affairs, said, “We have achieved strong performance in this quarter, achieving 2x growth in both sales and collections for Q3. This performance has strengthened our overall trajectory, resulting in approximately 70% growth across both metrics for the nine-month period. The launch of Ajmera Solis at Vikhroli was a key driver, with its well-configured 1, 2, and 3 BHK homes and prime connectivity instantly resonated strongly with buyers seeking value, reinforced by the reliability of the Ajmera brand. This success validates our asset-light strategy and our capability to expand into new micro-markets. Having already secured Rs 1,431 crore in sales, we have exceeded our required run-rate and remain confident of outperforming our yearly guidance of Rs 1,600 crore. Looking ahead, this robust sales velocity and high cash flow visibility, we are set to aggressively fast-track upcoming launches and capitalize on strategic business development opportunities, while ensuring faster project execution and continued deleveraging of our balance sheet.” Ajmera Realty & Infra India has a PAN India presence along with an international presence. The company is focused on premium developments in luxury and mid-luxury projects in the residential segment. The company has a huge development potential available on its balance land parcel at Ajmera I-Land, Bhakti Park, Wadala, and Central Mumbai. Meanwhile, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 14.1% to Rs 30.37 crore, even as revenue rose 9.6% to Rs 219.04 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AjmeraRealty_44715430837_2404.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks pare all gains; European mrkt advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-pare-all-gains-european-mrkt-advance/1664884</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664884</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices pared all initial gains and traded with marginal losses in afternoon trade, weighed down by mild profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE.

The key equity indices pared all initial gains and traded with marginal losses in afternoon trade, weighed down by mild profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the BSE. Investors stayed cautious as they tracked developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical developments. The Nifty traded near the 25,700 level. Metal, PSU Bank and Oil & Gas shares advanced while realty, IT and auto shares declined. At 13:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 101.66 points or 0.12% to 83,523.12. The Nifty 50 index fell 27.65 points or 0.10% to 25,705.20. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.13% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.24%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,045 shares rose and 1,949 shares fell. A total of 206 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: NTPC (up 3.57%), Tata Steel (up 3.57%), Axis Bank (up 2.95%), Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC)(up 2.81%) and Ultratech Cement (up 2.04%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) (down 1.92%), Asian Paints (down 1.76%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (down 1.64%), Hindustan Unilever (down 1.61%) and Tech Mahindra (down 1.36%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Economy: The annual rate of inflation based on the all-India Wholesale Price Index (WPI) increased 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, compared with a decline of 0.32% in November 2025. Inflation turned positive after three months and marked the fastest pace since April, mainly driven by higher prices of manufactured products. Inflation in manufactured products accelerated to 1.82% in December 2025 from 1.33% in November 2025, led by an increase in prices of food products, pharmaceuticals, medicinal chemical and botanical products, and cement, lime & plaster. Inflation in food products rose to 0.90% from 0.62%, while prices of pharmaceuticals increased to 1.60% from 1.39% a month earlier. Inflation in cement, lime & plaster stood at 0.30% compared with 0.08% in November. Food prices remained unchanged in December after declining 2.27% in November, supported by higher prices of milk, fruits, eggs, meat & fish. Meanwhile, inflation in fuel and power remained negative at 2.31% in December 2025 compared with a contraction of 2.27% in November, weighed down by lower prices of LPG, petrol, and high-speed diesel. Stocks in Spotlight: Just Dial fell 1.73% the company reported 10.2% decline in net profit to Rs 118 crore despite a 6.4% rise in operating revenue to Rs 305.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Elxsi fell 4.47% after the company reported 45.28% decline in net profit to Rs 108.89 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 199 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 1.52% to Rs 953.47 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 939.17 crore posted in Q3 FY25. 5paisa Capital added 1.21% the company reported a 23.98% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 12.30 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 16.18 crore in the same quarter last year. Total revenue from operations fell 7.02% YoY to Rs 79.28 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Puravankara surged 12.23% after the real estate developer reported a 17% increase in sales value to Rs 1,414 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,209 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s collections climbed 22% YoY to Rs 1,140 crore in Q3 FY26. Mini Diamonds India surged 2.82% after the company said it has received an order worth Rs 14 crore from Aura Diamond, a Mumbai-based domestic entity, for the supply of lab-grown polished diamonds. Global Markets: European market advanced as investors in the region focus on a meeting between U.S., Greenlandic and Danish officials to discuss the Arctic island’s future. Most Asian markets advanced as Japanese indexes hit record highs on Wednesday. The rally in Japanese stocks was fuelled by expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi could call for a snap election, likely in February. If called, it will be Takaichi’s first time facing Japan’s voters in an election. Overnight in the U.S., all three major indexes fell as investors grappled with volatility from a flurry of proposals from U.S. President Donald Trump floated in the past few days. The S&P 500 dipped 0.19% as investors sold JPMorgan despite better-than-expected numbers, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.8%. The Nasdaq Composite fell 0.1%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Federal Bank Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/federal-bank-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664875</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664875</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Federal Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Federal Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 246.6, down 1.08% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Federal Bank Ltd has eased around 7.03% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Federal Bank Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.47% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59578.8, up 0.27% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 79.84 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 79.93 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 246.45, down 1.5% on the day. Federal Bank Ltd jumped 27.02% in last one year as compared to a 10.9% rally in NIFTY and a 22.54% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 16.14 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FederalBank_48888244722_3709.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eicher-motors-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664876</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664876</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Eicher Motors Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 7317.5, down 1.17% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Eicher Motors Ltd has added around 2.75% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Eicher Motors Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.86% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27915.1, down 0.39% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.15 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.19 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 7305, down 1.46% on the day. Eicher Motors Ltd jumped 43.99% in last one year as compared to a 10.9% rally in NIFTY and a 22.42% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 43.23 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EicherMotors_60312767308_151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aegis-logistics-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664877</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664877</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Aegis Logistics Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 720, down 0.59% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Aegis Logistics Ltd has eased around 4.13% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Aegis Logistics Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.83% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34416.7, up 0.93% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 83432 shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.55 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 48.2 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisLogistics_61348536029_9.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CESC Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cesc-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1664878</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664878</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CESC Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

CESC Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 158.8, down 0.81% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.CESC Ltd has eased around 7.11% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which CESC Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.83% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34416.7, up 0.93% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 20.56 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 11.57 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 25.15 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CESC_38062435381_99.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1664879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664879</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Hitachi Energy India Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 16864, down 1.41% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Hitachi Energy India Ltd has eased around 13.67% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Hitachi Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.83% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34416.7, up 0.93% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.23 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.5 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 16901, down 1.62% on the day. Hitachi Energy India Ltd jumped 33.08% in last one year as compared to a 10.9% rally in NIFTY and a 2.71% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 106.29 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HitachiEnergyIndiaLimited_51485438_74646.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Britannia Industries Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/britannia-industries-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1664880</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664880</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Britannia Industries Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Britannia Industries Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5909, down 0.15% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Britannia Industries Ltd has lost around 2.14% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Britannia Industries Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.63% in last one month and is currently quoting at 52577.15, down 0.48% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.94 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.49 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5915, down 0.42% on the day. Britannia Industries Ltd jumped 21.16% in last one year as compared to a 10.9% rally in NIFTY and a 5.8% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 61.93 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BritanniaInds_60979410361_93.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Saregama India Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/saregama-india-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664881</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664881</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Saregama India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Saregama India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 347.25, down 1.34% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Saregama India Ltd has lost around 7.71% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Saregama India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.39% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1413.85, up 0.1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.57 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 8.45 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 33.17 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SaregamaIndia_37590946820_204.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welspun Corp Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/welspun-corp-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664882</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664882</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Welspun Corp Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Welspun Corp Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 740, down 0.09% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Welspun Corp Ltd has lost around 7.02% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Welspun Corp Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 10.45% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11355.2, up 2.65% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.81 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.88 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 25.98 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WelspunCorp_23409759814_7947.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lloyds-metals-energy-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1664883</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664883</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1232.2, down 0.28% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25743.05. The Sensex is at 83591.37, down 0.04%.Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd has lost around 4.33% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 10.45% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11355.2, up 2.65% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.43 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.17 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 36.7 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsMetals_76757705405_2629.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Victory Electric Vehicles International loses charge on debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-victory-electric-vehicles-international-loses-charge-on-debut/1664871</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664871</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 34.45, a discount of 15.98% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 34.45, a discount of 15.98% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its lower limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 34.45 and a low of Rs 32.75. About 48,000 shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Victory Electric Vehicles International's was subscribed 0.96 times. The issue opened for bidding on 7 January 2026 and it closed on 9 January 2026, with the IPO priced at Rs 41 per share. The IPO consisted entirely of a fresh issue of 84.3 lakh equity shares. Post issue, promoter and promoter group shareholding declined to 63.33% from 97.41% earlier. The company plans to utilise the net proceeds towards capital expenditure, working capital requirements, and general corporate purposes. Victory Electric Vehicles is engaged in the manufacture of electric vehicles such as electric rickshaws, passenger rickshaws, e-loaders, cargo rickshaws and electric scooters. Its product portfolio also includes customised e-three-wheelers, catering to niche applications such as food vending and ice cream distribution. As of 30 September 2025, the company had 110 permanent employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 16.81 crore and net profit of Rs 1.62 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VICTORYELECTRICVEHICLESINTERNATIONALLIMITED_13154367_94189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IndusInd Bank Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indusind-bank-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1664861</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664861</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IndusInd Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

IndusInd Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 946, up 3.89% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25754.85. The Sensex is at 83636.15, up 0.01%. IndusInd Bank Ltd has gained around 11.13% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which IndusInd Bank Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.31% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59578.8, up 0.12% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 57.39 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 35.56 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 943.4, up 3.51% on the day. IndusInd Bank Ltd is down 1.71% in last one year as compared to a 10.95% jump in NIFTY and a 22.35% jump in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndusIndBankLtd_64968625_5531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>