<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zaggle Prepaid inks pact with Rebel Foods]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zaggle-prepaid-inks-pact-with-rebel-foods/1675710</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675710</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the agreement, Zaggle will provide its Zaggle Zoyer platform to Rebel Foods for a period of one year.

Under the agreement, Zaggle will provide its Zaggle Zoyer platform to Rebel Foods for a period of one year. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and is in the nature of an agreement. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services (Zaggle) is a leading player in spend management, with a differentiated value proposition and diversified user base. The company operates in the business-to-business-to-customer segment. It is one of the largest numbers of issued prepaid cards in India in partnership with its banking partners. Additionally, the company has a diversified portfolio of software as a service (SaaS) products, including tax and payroll software, and a wide touchpoint reach. The company’s standalone net profit surged 79.1% to Rs 33.24 crore on a 42.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 430.98 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services fell 1.16% to Rs 293.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZagglePrepaidOceanServicesLtd_95613182_78337.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ceigall India rises after subsidiary secures Rs 2,160 crore NHAI project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ceigall-india-rises-after-subsidiary-secures-rs-2160-crore-nhai-project/1675709</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675709</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company's wholly owned subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects, has received a Letter of Award from the National Highways Authority of India for a highway project in Bihar.

The company's wholly owned subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects, has received a Letter of Award from the National Highways Authority of India for a highway project in Bihar. The project involves four-laning of the Sahebganj-Areraj-Bettiah section of NH-139W in Bihar, with a total length of 78.942 km. The stretch comprises Section 1 from Sahebganj to Areraj covering 38.362 km and Section 2 from Areraj to Bettiah covering 40.580 km. The bid project cost is approximately Rs 2,160 crore, and the project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). The construction period is 730 days, followed by a 15-year operation and maintenance period. The company said the corridor is expected to improve regional connectivity in Bihar and support economic activity in the region. Ceigall India is an infrastructure engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) company engaged in the development of highways, expressways, bridges, flyovers, railway overbridges, tunnels, and runways. The company executes projects under EPC as well as Hybrid Annuity Model (HAM) formats and has a strong track record of timely execution across multiple states in India. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Ceigall India rose 1.24% to Rs 74.11 crore while net sales rose 19.34% to Rs 991.14 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CeigallIndiaLtd_68678209_85110.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IRCON Intl Q3 PAT jumps 16% YoY to Rs 100 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ircon-intl-q3-pat-jumps-16-yoy-to-rs-100-cr/1675708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675708</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations declined 18.89% to Rs 2,119.04 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 2,612.86 crore in the same quarter last year.

However, revenue from operations declined 18.89% to Rs 2,119.04 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 2,612.86 crore in the same quarter last year. Profit from operations before tax stood at Rs 134.69 crore in Q3 FY26, up 2.17%, compared with Rs 131.82 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. EBITDA were at Rs 269.3 crore in Q3 FY26, up 23.36% as compared with Rs 218.3 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s EBITDA margin stood at 12.2% in Q3 FY26. The company's revenue from international customers fell 38.47% YoY to Rs 49.52 crore in Q3 FY26, while revenue from domestic customers decreased 18.27% YoY to Rs 2,069.52 crore. As of 31 December 2025, the total order book stands at Rs 23,801 crore, with the Railways segment accounting for Rs 17,781 crore, Highways contributing Rs 4,297 crore, and other segments making up Rs 1,723 crore. The board of directors has approved an interim dividend of Rs 1.20 per equity share of Rs 2 each for the financial year 2025-26. On its outlook, the company is well-positioned to capitalize on India’s rapidly evolving infrastructure landscape. With robust government support through initiatives like PM Gati Shakti, Bharatmala, Sagarmala, and the Smart Cities Mission, alongside increased CAPEX of Rs 12.20 lakh crore and new high-speed rail and freight corridors proposed in Budget 2026, the company expects strong growth opportunities across railways, roadways, and urban infrastructure projects. Leveraging its existing order book and strategic capabilities, the company is poised to benefit from these developments and strengthen its market presence. Ircon International is a public sector construction company with an emphasis on infrastructure projects, with a specialization in the execution of railway projects on a turnkey basis and otherwise. After commencing business as a railway construction company, it diversified progressively to roads, buildings, electrical substations and distribution, airport construction, commercial complexes, as well as metro rail works. Shares of Ircon International shed 0.93% to Rs 154.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IrconIntl_4733182919_5497.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Power spurts on reporting turnaround Q3 numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-power-spurts-on-reporting-turnaround-q3-numbers/1675707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675707</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income rose by 16.5% year on year (YoY) to Rs 401.25 crore in the third quarter of FY26.

Total income rose by 16.5% year on year (YoY) to Rs 401.25 crore in the third quarter of FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 131.57 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 24.48 crore a year ago. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 27.57 crore during the quarter relating to the impact of newly notified labour codes. The EBITDA margin for the quarter ended (QE) 31 December 2025 is 35%, compared to 9.0% for the quarter ended (QE) 31 December 2024. The order backlog stood at Rs 1,670.6 crore as of 31 December 2025, down 38.3% compared with Rs 2,706.0 crore as of 31 December 2024 for continuing operations, primarily due to the termination of two FGD EP contracts—Jaypee Bina and Nigrie—aggregating Rs 775 crore. Puneet Bhatla, MD, GE Power India, said, “Execution discipline and operational excellence have continued to drive meaningful margin expansion across our core services and upgrade businesses. With a focused portfolio, improving margins, and a healthy order book, we are well positioned for building momentum.” GE Power India is one of the leading players in the Indian power generation equipment market. Hydro and gas businesses are also housed in the company in addition to steam power. The company offers a comprehensive portfolio of power generation solutions with a focus on emissions control and a services portfolio providing sustainable, affordable, and reliable electricity.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GEPower_62970729410_20944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lenskart Solutions zooms after Q3 PAT rises over 3x YoY to Rs 132.7 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lenskart-solutions-zooms-after-q3-pat-rises-over-3x-yoy-to-rs-1327-crore/1675705</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675705</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While EBITDA improved by 90.6% to Rs 462.4 crore, EBITDA margin expanded by 550 basis points YoY to 20.0% in Q3 FY26.

While EBITDA improved by 90.6% to Rs 462.4 crore, EBITDA margin expanded by 550 basis points YoY to 20.0% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 178.4 crore, up by _ % from Rs 19.2 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company has performed 6.3 million eye tests (up 53.8% YoY) and the total number of eyewear units sold added up to 8.9 million (up 29.7% YoY) in Q3 FY26, It has added 195 net new stores in Q3 FY26 as against 81 stores in Q3 FY25. This includes 169 stores in India and 26 stores in International domain, taking FY26 YTD net additions to 420 stores. Net store additions in the same period last year were 193 stores. Lenskart Solutions is a technology-led eyewear company involved in designing, manufacturing, branding and retailing prescription glasses, sunglasses, contact lenses and related accessories.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LENSKARTSOLUTIONSLIMITED_69247877_68840.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR rebounds well in opening trades; Sustained dollar weakness supports]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-rebounds-well-in-opening-trades-sustained-dollar-weakness-supports/1675700</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675700</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee rebounded well in opening trades on Thursday, as dollar index stayed well below 97 mark.

The Indian rupee rebounded well in opening trades on Thursday, as dollar index stayed well below 97 mark. US Dollar Index holds losses below 97.00 despite stronger-than-expected NFP report. INR opened at Rs 90.55 per dollar and hit a high of 90.40 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee depreciated 14 paise to close at 90.70 against the US dollar, on dollar demand from importers and geopolitical tensions. Local shares also ended on a muted note tracking mixed cues from global markets and amid profit taking after three days of gains on optimism surrounding an interim trade agreement with the United States. Higher oil prices also kept investors on edge ahead of a meeting between Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and U.S. President Donald Trump that would halt Iran's uranium enrichment. The benchmark BSE Sensex slipped 40.28 points to end at 84,233.64, while the broader NSE Nifty index closed up 18.70 points at 25,953.85. However, FPI inflows may support the local unit at lower levels. Foreign institutional investors net bought shares to the extent of Rs 944 crore on Wednesday while domestic institutional investors offloaded shares worth Rs 125 crore, according to provisional exchange data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Capital markets key to empowering SMEs for Viksit Bharat; says SEBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/capital-markets-key-to-empowering-smes-for-viksit-bharat-says-sebi/1675698</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675698</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[At the India SME Finance & Investment Summit, SEBI highlighted the critical role of capital markets in supporting India’s ambition to become a global manufacturing hub and achieve the vision of ‘Viksit Bharat’.

At the India SME Finance & Investment Summit, SEBI highlighted the critical role of capital markets in supporting India’s ambition to become a global manufacturing hub and achieve the vision of ‘Viksit Bharat’. India remains one of the fastest-growing major economies, with GDP projected to grow at 7.4% in FY26. MSMEs, comprising over 70 million enterprises, contribute 35% to manufacturing, 49% to exports, and 31% to GDP, making them central to the country’s growth story. Dedicated SME platforms on NSE and BSE have seen significant progress, with over 1,400 SMEs listed and a combined market capitalization of ₹4.1 trillion. In FY25, 241 SME IPOs raised ₹98 billion, while 232 IPOs raised ₹105 billion in FY26 (till January 31, 2026). Over 350 SMEs have successfully migrated to the Main Board. SEBI has strengthened the SME framework following instances of misuse, enhancing due diligence, disclosure standards, and governance requirements to protect investors and maintain market integrity. Exchanges are leveraging technology, including AI, to streamline approvals. Looking ahead, SEBI is reviewing regulations, developing a dedicated SME portal, expanding regional outreach, and promoting corporate bond markets to widen access. The message is clear: transparency, strong governance, and diversified financing will be key to scaling India’s SMEs sustainably.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drift lower; breadth weak]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drift-lower-breadth-weak/1675684</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675684</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses as investors engaged in profit booking.

The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses as investors engaged in profit booking. Market participants remained cautious due to mixed global cues and FII selling. The Nifty traded below the 25,850 mark. IT, realty and media shares leading the fall while private bank and FMCG stocks advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 376.48 points or 0.44% to 83,862.16. The Nifty 50 index fell 116.65 points or 0.45% to 25,838.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.77% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.86%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,241 shares rose and 1,986 shares fell. A total of 159 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 69.45 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,174.21 crore in the Indian equity market on 10 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Lenskart Solutions surged 11.35% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 131 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 1.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Consolidated revenue from operations rose 38.3% year-on-year to Rs 2,308 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,669 crore in Q3 FY25. Capacite Infraprojects shed 0.85%. The company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, down 3.8% from Rs 52 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 14.4% year-on-year to Rs 675 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 590 crore in Q3 FY25. Jupiter Wagons declined 3.91% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 63 crore in Q3 FY26, down 35.3% from Rs 97.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 13.6% year-on-year to Rs 890 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,030 crore in Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.25% to 6.727 compared with previous session close of 6.710. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.4900 compared with its close of 90.7800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.50% to Rs 157,966. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.09% to 96.83. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.19% to 4.164. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 53 cents or 0.77% to $69.33 a barrel. Global Markets: Most Asian market advanced on Thursday, buoyed by Japan’s post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Japanese stocks have notched several fresh highs in recent days, fueled by the so-called “Takaichi trade,” following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s landslide victory in the Lower House, said market watchers. Media reports noted that Takaichi’s snap-election landslide gives her an unusually strong, multi-year mandate to execute policy, which they view as broadly supportive for Japan’s markets and corporate sector. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day win streak after a better-than-expected January jobs report. The blue-chip index lost 66.74 points, or 0.13%, and closed at 50,121.40. The S&P 500 was nearly flat at 6,941.47. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 0.16% to end at 23,066.47. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000. Strong labor market has reduced the odds for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The jobs report follows weaker-than-expected consumer data released on Tuesday. That report showed that consumer spending in December was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain expected from economists polled by Dow Jones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SJVN rises after Q3 PAT jumps 51% YoY to Rs 224 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sjvn-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-51-yoy-to-rs-224-cr/1675675</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675675</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations surged 61.2% year-on-year to Rs 1,081.97 crore during the quarter under review, up from Rs 670.99 crore in the corresponding period last year.

Revenue from operations surged 61.2% year-on-year to Rs 1,081.97 crore during the quarter under review, up from Rs 670.99 crore in the corresponding period last year. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 356.81 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a robust 88.9% increase from the Rs 188.91 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total expenses rose 24.32% to Rs 705.25 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Q3 FY25. During the quarter, employee benefits expense stood at Rs 67.13 crore, down 15.13% YoY, while other expense was Rs 103.02 crore, up 0.28% YoY. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared an interim dividend of Rs 1.15 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the purpose of payment of interim dividend has been fixed as February 20, 2026. The board of the firm also approved raising funds up to Rs 1,000 crore via the issuance of unsecured, rated, taxable, redeemable, non-convertible, non-cumulative debentures on a private placement basis. SJVN is principally engaged in electricity generation. The company is also engaged in the business of providing consultancy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SJVN_64650197956_12076.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd Spurts 0.84%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-ltd-spurts-084/1675672</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675672</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd gained 0.84% today to trade at Rs 5729.25.

Hero MotoCorp Ltd gained 0.84% today to trade at Rs 5729.25. The BSE Auto index is up 0.28% to quote at 63502.54. The index is up 2.48 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Eicher Motors Ltd increased 0.74% and Balkrishna Industries Ltd added 0.47% on the day. The BSE Auto index went up 26.54 % over last one year compared to the 10.24% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hero MotoCorp Ltd has lost 0.15% over last one month compared to 2.48% gain in BSE Auto index and 0.41% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 177 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 15232 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 6390 on 05 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 3322.6 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at flat opening for equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-flat-opening-for-equities/1675664</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675664</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 1.50 points, suggesting a muted start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 1.50 points, suggesting a muted start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 69.45 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,174.21 crore in the Indian equity market on 10 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 4,969.62 crore so far in February (till 10 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian market advanced on Thursday, led by Japan that extended its post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Japanese stocks have notched several fresh highs in recent days, fueled by the so-called “Takaichi trade,” following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s landslide victory in the Lower House, said market watchers. Media reports noted that Takaichi’s snap-election landslide gives her an unusually strong, multi-year mandate to execute policy, which they view as broadly supportive for Japan’s markets and corporate sector. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day win streak after a better-than-expected January jobs report. The blue-chip index lost 66.74 points, or 0.13%, and closed at 50,121.40. The S&P 500 was nearly flat at 6,941.47. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 0.16% to end at 23,066.47. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000. Strong labor market has reduced the odds for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The jobs report follows weaker-than-expected consumer data released on Tuesday. That report showed that consumer spending in December was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain expected from economists polled by Dow Jones. Domestic Market: The key domestic indices ended almost flat on Wednesday, as gains in select sectors were offset by caution ahead of global triggers. The market opened on a positive note, with the Nifty reclaiming the 26,000 mark in early trade. However, momentum faded as the session progressed, and the index moved in a narrow range for the remainder of the day as investors refrained from aggressive bets ahead of Wednesday’s US jobs report. The Nifty eventually settled above the 25,950 mark. Sectorally, auto, PSU bank and pharma stocks witnessed buying interest, while IT and private bank shares came under pressure. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 40.28 points or 0.05% to 84,233.64. The Nifty 50 index rose 18.70 points or 0.07% to 25,953.85.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel bags Rs 17-cr PMC order from Lucknow Municipal Corporation]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-bags-rs-17-cr-pmc-order-from-lucknow-municipal-corporation/1675514</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675514</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project entails project management consultancy (PMC) for Lucknow Municipal Corporation for five years, with execution scheduled by 15 February 2031.

The project entails project management consultancy (PMC) for Lucknow Municipal Corporation for five years, with execution scheduled by 15 February 2031. RailTel was incorporated in 2000, with the objective of creating nationwide broadband and VPN services, telecom, and multimedia networks to modernize the train control operation and safety system of Indian Railways. The company’s standalone net profit declined 4.07% to Rs 62.40 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.05 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 18.99% YoY to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26. The scrip fell 1.99% to settle at Rs 339.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Lenskart Solutions, Capacite Infra, Patanjali Foods, LG Electronics, Godrej Industries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-lenskart-solutions-capacite-infra-patanjali-foods-lg-electronics-godrej-industries/1675513</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675513</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&O trading on 12 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&O trading on 12 February 2026. Result Today: Hindustan Unilever, Oil and Natural Gas Corporation, Coal India, Lupin, Hindalco Industries, Honasa Consumer, Abbott India, Bajaj Hindusthan Sugar, Bharat Forge, Biocon, CRISIL, Endurance Technologies, Engineers India, Entero Healthcare Solutions, Hindustan Aeronautics, Indraprastha Gas, Indian Hotels Company, Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation, Muthoot Finance, Natco Pharma, Petronet LNG, Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers, SpiceJet, TVS Electronics, Welspun Living, and Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services will release their quarterly earnings today. IPO Data: Fractal Analytics IPO: Subscribed 2.66x overall on Day 3, with QIBs leading at 4.18x subscription, followed by NII at 1.1x and retail at 1x. Aye Finance IPO: Subscribed 97% overall on Day 3, with QIBs leading at 1.5x subscription, while retail stands at 77% and NII at 5%. Stocks to Watch: Lenskart Solutions reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 131 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 1.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Consolidated revenue from operations rose 38.3% year-on-year to Rs 2,308 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,669 crore in Q3 FY25. Capacite Infraprojects reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, down 3.8% from Rs 52 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 14.4% year-on-year to Rs 675 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 590 crore in Q3 FY25. Jupiter Wagons reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 63 crore in Q3 FY26, down 35.3% from Rs 97.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 13.6% year-on-year to Rs 890 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,030 crore in Q3 FY25. Elgi Equipments reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 95.2 crore in Q3 FY26, up 18.1% from Rs 80.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 18.4% year-on-year to Rs 1,003 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 848 crore in Q3 FY25. IRCON International reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 101 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% from Rs 86.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 18.9% year-on-year to Rs 2,119 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,613 crore in Q3 FY25. Godrej Industries reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 205 crore in Q3 FY26, up 8.7% from Rs 188 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 4.7% year-on-year to Rs 5,051 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,825 crore in Q3 FY25. LG Electronics reported a standalone net profit of Rs 89.6 crore in Q3 FY26, down 61.6% from Rs 233 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 6.4% year-on-year to Rs 4,114 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,396 crore in Q3 FY25. Patanjali Foods reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 593 crore in Q3 FY26, up 60.0% from Rs 371 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 16.5% to Rs 10,484 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 8,997 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>