<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:26:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manappuram Finance appoints Buvanesh Tharashankar as Group CFO]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/manappuram-finance-appoints-buvanesh-tharashankar-as-group-cfo/1662250</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662250</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In his role as Group CFO, Buvanesh will provide strategic financial leadership across the Manappuram Group.

In his role as Group CFO, Buvanesh will provide strategic financial leadership across the Manappuram Group. He will work closely with the leadership team to strengthen financial governance, support long-term business strategy, enhance capital efficiency and enable sustainable value creation while ensuring strong regulatory and compliance standards. Buvanesh is a highly accomplished finance professional and a Chartered Accountant with nearly three decades of experience across leading banking and financial services institutions, having held senior roles across RBL Bank (CFO), Jana Small Finance Bank (CFO), and Citibank in India and overseas. His career spans critical areas such as financial strategy, capital and balance sheet management, regulatory interface, governance, investor engagement, and business analytics. He has consistently partnered business leadership in driving disciplined growth, strengthening controls, and enhancing organizational resilience. Meanwhile, the board also approved an investment of Rs 250 crore in Asirvad Micro Finance (AMFL), a subsidiary of the company, in single/ different tranches. The funds will be used to support AMFL’s capital expenditure and working capital requirements. Founded in 1949, Manappuram Finance is a leading non-banking financial institution and the 2nd largest financier in the gold loan segment in India, Over the years, it has evolved into a diversified financial services provider, offering a wide range of products including gold loans, microfinance, housing finance, vehicle loans, and SME financing. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 61.5% to Rs 219.88 crore on 13.3% fall in total income to Rs 2,285.36 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.73% to Rs 311.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManappuramFin_40714085963_6083.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Linde India appoints Milan Sadhukhan as MD]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/linde-india-appoints-milan-sadhukhan-as-md/1662251</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662251</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Abhijit Banerjee will step down as managing director of the company with effect from 31 December 2025.

Abhijit Banerjee will step down as managing director of the company with effect from 31 December 2025. Milan Sadhukhan (50) is a B.Com (Hons.) graduate, Chartered Accountant, and Cost & Management Accountant. He currently serves as Head of Finance—ASEAN & South Asia and has over 25 years of experience across various finance roles in Asia and the UK. He has no inter se relationship with other members of the board. Linde India is primarily engaged in the manufacture of industrial and medical gases and the construction of cryogenic and non-cryogenic air separation plants. The company's consolidated net profit surged 60.7% to Rs 171 crore, while net sales rose 1.5% to Rs 644.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Linde India shed 0.05% to Rs 5,954.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LindeIndia_26168951827_284.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Modi Rubber Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/modi-rubber-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662248</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662248</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nagreeka Exports Ltd, Teamo Productions HQ Ltd, Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd and Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 29 December 2025.

Nagreeka Exports Ltd, Teamo Productions HQ Ltd, Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd and Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 29 December 2025. Modi Rubber Ltd tumbled 9.99% to Rs 150.9 at 14:10 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 21723 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9433 shares in the past one month. Nagreeka Exports Ltd lost 9.30% to Rs 26.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2769 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 596 shares in the past one month. Teamo Productions HQ Ltd crashed 8.97% to Rs 0.71. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.12 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9.79 lakh shares in the past one month. Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd pared 8.65% to Rs 1151.05. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 270 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 206 shares in the past one month. Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd fell 8.62% to Rs 3.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 16416 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3908 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ModiRubber_80848865387_387.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade lower; consumer durables shares climb ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-lower-consumer-durables-shares-climb/1662249</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662249</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with moderate cuts in mid-afternoon trade amid persistent FII selling and a weakening rupee.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with moderate cuts in mid-afternoon trade amid persistent FII selling and a weakening rupee. The Nifty traded below the 26,950 mark. Consumer durables shares declined after jumping in the past trading session. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 288.93 points or 0.34% to 84,764.04. The Nifty 50 index lost 93.40 points or 0.36% to 25,948.90. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.36% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.51%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,515 shares rose and 2,751 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index shed 0.65% to 36,583.30. The index rose 0.34% in the past trading session. Dixon Technologies (India) (down 2.88%), Kajaria Ceramics (down 2.26%), Amber Enterprises India (down 1.67%), Blue Star (down 1.53%), Bata India (down 1.12%), PG Electroplast (down 1.04%), Kalyan Jewellers India (down 0.89%), Cera Sanitaryware (down 0.81%), Century Plyboards (India) (down 0.62%) and Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (down 0.45%). Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.08% to 6.565 as compared with the previous close of 6.560. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9800 compared with its close of 89.9000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement fell 1.21% to Rs 138,162. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 98.06. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.56% to 4.108. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 86 cents or 1.42% to $61.50 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Suzlon Energy shed 0.56%. The company informed that Vivek Srivastava, chief executive officer (CEO) of its WTG Division, has resigned with effect from the close of business hours on 26th December 2025. Arfin India fell 1.32% after the company announced that it has received a fresh order worth Rs 321 crore from Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited for the supply of aluminium sector conductor.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at HFCL Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-hfcl-ltd-counter/1662246</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662246</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[MMTC Ltd, HEG Ltd, Graphite India Ltd, Hindustan Copper Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 29 December 2025.

MMTC Ltd, HEG Ltd, Graphite India Ltd, Hindustan Copper Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 29 December 2025. HFCL Ltd saw volume of 1499.18 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.2 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 182.82 lakh shares. The stock increased 6.77% to Rs.65.63. Volumes stood at 592.47 lakh shares in the last session. MMTC Ltd recorded volume of 732.73 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.96 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 105.34 lakh shares. The stock gained 7.29% to Rs.68.92. Volumes stood at 718.8 lakh shares in the last session. HEG Ltd witnessed volume of 68 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.72 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10.12 lakh shares. The stock increased 6.23% to Rs.594.65. Volumes stood at 17.84 lakh shares in the last session. Graphite India Ltd recorded volume of 38.57 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.44 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5.99 lakh shares. The stock gained 3.84% to Rs.605.20. Volumes stood at 8.9 lakh shares in the last session. Hindustan Copper Ltd clocked volume of 1618.73 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.17 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 313.26 lakh shares. The stock gained 2.05% to Rs.485.35. Volumes stood at 963.53 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HFCL_23392864533_1189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suzlon Energy CEO Vivek Srivastava resigns]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suzlon-energy-ceo-vivek-srivastava-resigns/1662245</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662245</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[He will also cease to be a Senior Managerial Personnel (SMP) of the company from the same date.

He will also cease to be a Senior Managerial Personnel (SMP) of the company from the same date. The company added that Srivastava is not related to any of its directors. As this is a resignation, details regarding terms of appointment or profile are not applicable. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 539.08% to Rs 1,279.44 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 200.20 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 84.68% YoY to Rs 3,865.54 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of Suzlon Energy declined 0.56% to Rs 52.89 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuzlonEnergy_13614358127_13872.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi and US President Donald Trump Discuss India–US Trade Deal, Boost Strategic Partnership and Global Cooperation]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prime-minister-narendra-modi-and-us-president-donald-trump-discuss-indiaus-trade-deal-boost-strategic-partnership-and-global-cooperation/1662239</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662239</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi and US President Donald Trump held discussions on bilateral economic partnership in a phone conversation amid signs of the two sides inching closer to firm up a much-awaited trade deal.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi and US President Donald Trump held discussions on bilateral economic partnership in a phone conversation amid signs of the two sides inching closer to firm up a much-awaited trade deal. India and the US will continue to work together for global peace, stability and prosperity. Both of them reviewed the steady progress in India-US bilateral relations and exchanged views on key regional and global developments, reviewed progress in India-US comprehensive global strategic partnership and exchange views on expanding cooperation in trade, critical technologies, energy, defense and security. Both leaders agreed to work closely to address shared challenges and advance common interests besides expressing satisfaction at the steady strengthening of bilateral cooperation across all domains. They also underlined the importance of sustaining momentum in shared efforts to enhance bilateral trade, the officials said. The leaders also exchanged views on expanding cooperation in critical technologies, energy, defense and security, and other priority areas that are central to the implementation of the India-“US COMPACT (Catalyzing Opportunities for Military Partnership, Accelerated Commerce and Technology) for the 21st century. Further, they discussed various regional and global developments and agreed to work closely to address shared challenges and advance common interests. The US has been putting pressure on India to cut its procurement of Russian crude oil as it believes Moscow is financing its war against Ukraine using the oil revenue. India turned to purchasing Russian oil sold at a discount after Western countries imposed sanctions on Moscow and shunned its supplies over its invasion of Ukraine in February, 2022. Consequently, from a mere 1.7% share in total oil imports in 2019-20, Russia's share increased to 35.1% in 2024-25, and it is now the biggest oil supplier to India. In the last few weeks, India's procurement of Russian crude oil has declined following American sanctions on two leading Russian oil giants.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-19818__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Timex Group slumps as promoter launches OFS]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/timex-group-slumps-as-promoter-launches-ofs/1662240</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662240</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Promoter Timex Group Luxury Watches BV is offering a base lot of 45.09 lakh shares, representing 4.47% of the company’s equity.

Promoter Timex Group Luxury Watches BV is offering a base lot of 45.09 lakh shares, representing 4.47% of the company’s equity. The offer includes an oversubscription option for an additional 4.47%, taking the total potential divestment to 90.18 lakh shares, or 8.93%. The floor price has been set at Rs 275 per share, a discount of 21.82% to the stock’s previous close of Rs 351.75 on December 26, 2025. The discounted pricing and large offer size weighed on investor sentiment. The OFS opened on December 29 for non-retail investors. Retail investors can participate on December 30, along with non-retail bidders carrying forward unallotted bids. The offer is being conducted through a special window on the BSE and NSE during market hours. By 1:42 p.m. on T Day, the non-retail portion was subscribed 113.61% of the base offer size. Bids were received for 46.11 lakh shares against 40.58 lakh shares on base non-retail offer. As of September 2025, the promoter held a 59.93% stake in Timex Group India. Timex Group India designs, manufactures, and markets innovative timepieces and is part of Timex Group, a privately held company headquartered in Middlebury, Connecticut, with multiple operating units and over 2,000 employees worldwide. In India, TGIL manages a portfolio of brands including Timex, Versace, Guess, Gc, Philipp Plein, Plein Sport, Ferragamo, Nautica, Ted Baker, adidas, and UCB. It retails via more than 5,000 offline trade stores and key online marketplaces, along with over 40 exclusive franchise stores under the Just Watches and Timex World banners. On a standalone basis, net profit of Timex Group India rose 69.74% to Rs 30.23 crore while net sales rose 39.98% to Rs 243.67 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimexGroup_79144198960_3143.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Arfin India rises after securing Rs 321-cr repeat order from Diamond Power Infra]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/arfin-india-rises-after-securing-rs-321-cr-repeat-order-from-diamond-power-infra/1662237</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662237</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order entails the supply of 11,000 metric tonnes over an eleven-month period from January to November 2026, implying an average monthly dispatch of around 1,000 MT.

The order entails the supply of 11,000 metric tonnes over an eleven-month period from January to November 2026, implying an average monthly dispatch of around 1,000 MT. The company estimates the monthly order value at approximately Rs 29.2 crore. This is a repeat order from the same customer. Arfin India had earlier secured an order for 1,000 MT valued at about Rs 29.2 crore and said the latest contract strengthens its long-term customer relationship and market presence. Arfin India manufactures and trades in non-ferrous metals. The company reported a 5% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 2.45 crore on a 14.2% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 127.94 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArfinIndia_43866435046_7464.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,950 mark; broader mrkt underperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25950-mark-broader-mrkt-underperforms/1662238</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662238</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest losses in afternoon trade as investors remained cautious amid persistent FII selling.

The domestic equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest losses in afternoon trade as investors remained cautious amid persistent FII selling. The Nifty traded below the 25,950 mark. Barring the Nifty Media index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the red, with the Realty, Consumer Durables and Healthcare indices declining the most. At 13:26 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 339.87 points or 0.40% to 84,702.37. The Nifty 50 index lost 96.60 points or 0.37% to 25,945.70. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.60% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 0.76%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,395 shares rose and 2,811 shares fell. A total of 214 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Tata Steel (up 1.90%), Grasim Industries (up 1.09%), Tata Consumer Products (up 1.09%), Nestle India (up 0.57%) and Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (up 0.51%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Power Grid Corporation of India (down 1.90%), Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (down 1.59%), Trent (down 1.48%), Hindalco Industries (down 1.20%) and HCL Technologies (down 1.07%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) rose 0.02%. The company announced that its transportation infrastructure business vertical has secured a significant order for Hyderabad Greenfield Radial Road. Coforge shed 0.01%. The company said that it has signed definitive agreements to acquire Encora, an AI native firm born in the Silicon Valley with deep strengths across AI driven engineering underlaid by Cloud and Data. Siyaram Recycling Industries added 0.11%. The company has secured a significant order from The Supreme Industries, Jalgaon (F) – MDP, for the supply of 1/2" female insert (new modified) and female insert 1/2" CPVC/aqua topper. Ceigall India gained 0.29%. The company’s subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects has received a LoA from Madhya Pradesh Road Development Corporation for the construction of the Indore–Ujjain access-controlled four-lane greenfield highway. Vikran Engineering surged 6.25% after it has secured letter of awards (LoA) from M.P. Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of power plants with a total capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh. Jindal Steel rose 0.66%. The company announced a significant expansion of its structural steel manufacturing capabilities at its Raigarh facility. This expansion would double the company’s existing structural steel capacity from 1.2 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) to 2.4 MTPA by mid 2028. VA Tech Wabag lost 0.73%. The company has received a letter of award from the Saudi Water Authority for a large repeat EPC order to build a 50 MLD advanced BWRO plant at Aljouf, Saudi Arabia. JD Cables declined 2.32%. The company announced that it has secured orders worth Rs 8.81 crore from reputed EPC contractors for cable supply operations in Bihar and Jharkhand. Solarworld Energy Solutions climbed 9.81% after the company announced that it has received a letter of award for the EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project worth Rs 725.33 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy. Global Markets: European market declined, while most Asian markets advanced on Monday as investors kicked off the final trading week of the year. Prices of spot silver rose to a fresh record high of above $80 per ounce before pulling back sharply to $77. Silver’s recent surge was driven by speculative buying and lingering supply tightness, said experts. Media report further stated silver’s rally this year reflects a depletion of freely traded inventory, amplifying price moves as demand increases. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 reached a new high and posted weekly gains as traders came back from the Christmas holiday. The broad market index closed down 0.03% to end at 6,929.94. At its high, the S&P 500 was up 0.2%, reaching 6,945.77. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.09% and closed at 23,593.10. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 20.19 points, or 0.04%, and settled at 48,710.97.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[State Bank of India slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/state-bank-of-india-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1662228</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662228</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[State Bank of India dropped for a fifth straight session today.

State Bank of India dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 964.1, down 0.23% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.State Bank of India has lost around 0.92% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which State Bank of India is a constituent, has eased around 1.42% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59011.35, down 0.3% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 18.55 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 82.56 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 964.15, down 0.34% on the day. State Bank of India jumped 22.3% in last one year as compared to a 9.74% rally in NIFTY and a 15.47% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 12.5 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StBkofIndia_57185891_1375.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sona-blw-precision-forgings-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1662229</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662229</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 474.4, down 1.6% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd has eased around 6.75% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.18% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27739.85, down 0.28% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 15.63 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 14.09 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 474.9, down 1.54% on the day. Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd tumbled 20.83% in last one year as compared to a 9.74% rally in NIFTY and a 21.5% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 50.51 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SonaBLWPrecisionForgingsLtd_30715559_18341.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cg-power-industrial-solutions-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1662230</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662230</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 648.05, down 1.21% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd has lost around 3.24% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.98% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35058.8, down 0.64% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.53 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 19.76 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 648.4, down 1.43% on the day. CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd tumbled 11.93% in last one year as compared to a 9.74% rally in NIFTY and a 0.01% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 92.75 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CGPowerIndu_42121517029_125.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jaiprakash-power-ventures-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1662231</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662231</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 17.03, down 1.62% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd has eased around 9.27% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.98% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35058.8, down 0.64% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 184.07 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 416.81 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 16.04 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JPPowerVen_30572663793_14266.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dabur India Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dabur-india-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1662232</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662232</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Dabur India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Dabur India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 487.25, down 0.19% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.Dabur India Ltd has lost around 5.43% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Dabur India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 55132.05, down 0.1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.34 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 12.02 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 489.95, up 0.01% on the day. Dabur India Ltd tumbled 3.56% in last one year as compared to a 9.74% rally in NIFTY and a 2.73% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 60.83 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DaburIndia_45461479947_3392.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/colgate-palmolive-india-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1662233</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662233</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2068.1, down 0.92% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd has eased around 3.94% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 55132.05, down 0.1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.22 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.04 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2069.9, down 0.88% on the day. Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd tumbled 25.07% in last one year as compared to a 9.74% rally in NIFTY and a 2.73% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 42.84 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ColgatePalm_37609617182_118.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PVR Inox Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pvr-inox-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1662234</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662234</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PVR Inox Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

PVR Inox Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1000, down 0.09% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.PVR Inox Ltd has lost around 8.79% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which PVR Inox Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 3.52% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1410.95, up 0.16% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.19 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.75 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PVR_11003844262_14622.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aurobindo-pharma-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1662235</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662235</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Aurobindo Pharma Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1198.8, down 0.61% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.Aurobindo Pharma Ltd has eased around 1.43% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.26% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22684.65, down 0.37% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.55 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.38 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1202.3, down 0.37% on the day. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd tumbled 7.66% in last one year as compared to a 9.74% rally in NIFTY and a 2.76% fall in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 34.66 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurobindoPharma_66877283489_4666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of India down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-india-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1662236</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662236</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bank of India is down for a fifth straight session today.

Bank of India is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 139.05, down 0.52% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25948.55. The Sensex is at 84699.55, down 0.4%.Bank of India has lost around 5.56% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty PSU Bank index of which Bank of India is a constituent, has eased around 3.08% in last one month and is currently quoting at 8287.45, down 0.17% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 19.01 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 63.9 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark December futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 138.98, down 0.54% on the day. Bank of India jumped 37.77% in last one year as compared to a 9.74% rally in NIFTY and a 27.41% spurt in the Nifty PSU Bank index. The PE of the stock is 6.4 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofIndia_12067469065_5654.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Arvind Fashions to acquire Flipkart's stake in Arvind Youth Brands for Rs 135 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/arvind-fashions-to-acquire-flipkarts-stake-in-arvind-youth-brands-for-rs-135-crore/1662227</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662227</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Over the last five years Flying machine has re-established as a well-accepted brand on the digital channels.

Over the last five years Flying machine has re-established as a well-accepted brand on the digital channels. The partnership with the Flipkart group helped Flying Machine become one of the top casual wear brand on digital platforms, catering to the fashion-conscious youth of India. Amisha Jain, managing director & chief executive officer of Arvind Fashions, said, “We are thankful to the Flipkart Group for their support in building Flying Machine into a brand of choice on digital channels. Our relationship with the Flipkart group will continue ensuring consumers can still shop Flying Machine on its platforms. The brand will also be available to consumers on other digital channels and portals.” Arvind Fashions is engaged in the wholesale and retailing of owned and licensed branded apparels in India. With a host of renowned brands, both international and indigenous, like U.S. Polo Assn., Arrow, Tommy Hilfiger, Calvin Klein, and Flying Machine, it has presence across lifestyle brands. The scrip fell 1.47% to currently trade at Rs 508.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArvindFashionsLtd_45999851552_72051.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>