<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:27:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Budget will give India’s Reform Express new energy and new momentum: PM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/budget-will-give-indias-reform-express-new-energy-and-new-momentum-pm/1670076</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670076</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi today hailed the Budget 2026-2027 and described it as historic.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi today hailed the Budget 2026-2027 and described it as historic. Modi said, this budget is the foundation for country’s journey towards a Viksit Bharat by 2047. He said, the budget reflects the aspirations of 140 crore Indians and strengthens the reform journey and charts a clear roadmap for Viksit Bharat. He said, this year’s budget will give India’s Reform Express new energy and new momentum.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/budget-planning-and-allocating-money-concept-picture-id5081_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tokyo Plast International Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tokyo-plast-international-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1670075</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670075</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eco Recycling Ltd, TransIndia Real Estate Ltd, B&B Triplewall Containers Ltd and Incredible Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 February 2026.

Eco Recycling Ltd, TransIndia Real Estate Ltd, B&B Triplewall Containers Ltd and Incredible Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 February 2026. Tokyo Plast International Ltd crashed 15.89% to Rs 100.05 at 14:22 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1403 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 131 shares in the past one month. Eco Recycling Ltd tumbled 11.42% to Rs 391.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.6 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 34264 shares in the past one month. TransIndia Real Estate Ltd lost 10.25% to Rs 24.52. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 13090 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5768 shares in the past one month. B&B Triplewall Containers Ltd shed 9.05% to Rs 181. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 382 shares in the past one month. Incredible Industries Ltd slipped 8.72% to Rs 37.14. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 124 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2001 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TokyoPlastInternationalLtd_60698755021_4159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices  trade in negative terrain; realty shares snap 4-day gains ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-in-negative-terrain-realty-shares-snap-4-day-gains/1670073</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670073</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in mid-afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium.

The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in mid-afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium. The move directly hit the most active part of the market, triggering aggressive unwinding in brokerages, exchanges and high beta stocks linked to F&O volumes. Nifty dropped below 25,100 level. Realty shares declined after rallying the past four trading sessions. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 814.83 points or 0.93% to 81,501.15. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 261.15 points or 1.03% to 25,059.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.27% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index slipped 1.11%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,820 shares rose and 2,234 shares fell. A total of 190 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 5.96% to 14.45. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 1.62% to 770.30. The index jumped 3.52% in the past four trading session. Godrej Properties (down 2.98%), DLF (down 2.89%), Sobha (down 2.64%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 2.2%) and Lodha Developers (down 1.91%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.69%), Phoenix Mills (down 1.09%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.75%), Brigade Enterprises (down 0.26%) declined. Numbers to Track : MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.58% to Rs 1,44,400, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement declined 8.67% to Rs 2,66,623.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Anant Raj Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-anant-raj-ltd-counter/1670068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670068</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Intellect Design Arena Ltd, Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd, Angel One Ltd, BSE Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 01 February 2026.

Intellect Design Arena Ltd, Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd, Angel One Ltd, BSE Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 01 February 2026. Anant Raj Ltd witnessed volume of 208.91 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.91 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 26.40 lakh shares. The stock increased 8.70% to Rs.548.15. Volumes stood at 31.61 lakh shares in the last session. Intellect Design Arena Ltd notched up volume of 12.75 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.99 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.13 lakh shares. The stock slipped 3.22% to Rs.884.30. Volumes stood at 2.73 lakh shares in the last session. Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd witnessed volume of 8.75 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.32 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.64 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.34% to Rs.1,007.00. Volumes stood at 2.39 lakh shares in the last session. Angel One Ltd saw volume of 35.94 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.29 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.79 lakh shares. The stock dropped 8.46% to Rs.2,326.00. Volumes stood at 4.87 lakh shares in the last session. BSE Ltd recorded volume of 141.16 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.03 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 35.06 lakh shares. The stock lost 8.00% to Rs.2,573.30. Volumes stood at 38.06 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AnantRaj_28642833798_1538.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade lower; broader mrkt underperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-lower-broader-mrkt-underperforms/1670064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670064</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium.

The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium. Nifty skid below 25,050 mark after hitting day’s high of 25,440 in mid-morning trade. PSU Bank, oil & gas and realty shares declined while IT and consumer durables shares advanced At 13:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 542.62 points or 0.66% to 81,727.16. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 274.20 points or 0.79% to 25,087.30. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.03% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index slipped 0.93%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,711 shares rose and 2,215 shares fell. A total of 217 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 5.02% to 14.32. MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.58% to Rs 1,42,800, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement declined 8.79% to Rs 2,66,269. Gainers & Losers: Titan Company (up 3.45%), Wipro (up 3.14%), Max Healthcare Institute (up 2.74%), Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) (up 2.53%) and Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 1.22%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Hindalco Industries (down 4.70%), Coal India (down 3.99%), State Bank of India (down 3.98%), Bharat Electronics (BEL) (down 3.90%) and Oil & Natural Gas Corporations of India (ONGC) (down 3.62%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries rose 1.22% after it has reported 16.03% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,368.81 crore on a 13.49% increase in revenue to Rs 15,520.54 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Union Budget 2026 Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman used the Union Budget 2026 to underline a reform-heavy path built around fiscal consolidation, job creation and sharper global competitiveness. The Centre reiterated its medium-term debt sustainability goal, with the FRBM roadmap indicating a steady decline in the debt-to-GDP ratio and projecting central government debt at around 55.6% in BE 2026 27 versus 56.1% in RE 2025 26, framing the glide towards a sub 50% target by 2030 as a policy anchor rather than a hard statutory number. On the deficit side, the government stuck to its consolidation track, with the fiscal gap seen at 4.4% of GDP in RE FY26 and budgeted to narrow to 4.3% in BE FY27, a sequence that keeps the post pandemic promises on course while still giving room for capex-driven growth. On the expenditure and borrowing front, the Budget raised capital expenditure to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore for FY27, signalling another year of heavy public investment in infrastructure, especially in emerging tier 2 and tier 3 growth centres that are starting to look more like mini metros than satellite towns. To fund the gap, the Centre plans net market borrowing of Rs 11.54 lakh crore through dated securities, with the balance coming from small savings and other sources, in line with the glide path indicated in the Budget 2025 26 speech. That combination—slower deficit, still high capex and a calibrated borrowing programme—is meant to keep bond yields contained while nudging the baton from public to private capex over the medium term. Markets, however, zeroed in on the tax tweaks. On the indirect side, the Finance Bill, 2026 sharply increased the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives: STT on futures goes up from 0.02% to 0.05% of the traded value, while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium (and from 0.125% to 0.15% when options are exercised). That makes high-churn F&O strategies more expensive at the margin and nudges some speculative volume off the table, even as it modestly boosts revenue. On the direct tax side, the Income-tax Act, 2025 is slated to take full effect from 1 April 2026, with fresh slab structures, harmonised surcharge rules and a cleaned up TDS/TCS and penalty framework, all aimed at reducing litigation and making the law more “plain English” for taxpayers. The Budget also delivered compliance relief via Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rationalisation under the LRS and travel bucket. TCS on overseas tour packages has been pared down to a flat 2%, replacing the earlier structure that included higher 5–20% slabs and thresholds. Similarly, TCS on remittances under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme for education and medical treatment drops to 2% from 5%, with a higher trigger threshold, easing the cash flow pinch on families sending children abroad or paying for medical procedures. Alongside, the Bill tightens the architecture for revised and updated returns—allowing revised returns up to the end of the assessment year (or 12 months in the new Act), with a modest fee if filed late—while keeping the extended “updated return” window of up to four years, albeit at a steep additional tax to discourage strategic under reporting. For cross border and enforcement issues, the Budget has carved out a targeted Foreign Assets of Small Taxpayers Disclosure Scheme, 2026. The scheme ring fences smaller cases—undisclosed foreign assets and income up to defined ceilings—into a one time, time bound window where taxpayers can come clean by paying 30% tax plus a 100% penalty on that tax on previously untaxed foreign assets or income, or a flat Rs 1 lakh fee in benign cases where foreign assets bought out of already taxed income were not reported in the foreign asset schedule. In return, declarants get immunity from further tax, penalty and prosecution under the Black Money Act on the declared items. The exact opening and closing dates will be notified separately, but the policy signal is clear: clean up small legacy foreign asset issues before the information exchange net tightens further. On the business tax side, several structural tweaks stand out. First, supply of manpower is now explicitly included in the statutory definition of “work” for TDS purposes, putting manpower contracts clearly under the contractor TDS net at the familiar 1%–2% slabs depending on the payer’s status. Second, the Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) regime has been recalibrated: the MAT rate in the old corporate tax regime is trimmed to 14% and treated as a final tax, while companies moving into the new lower rate regime are allowed to use their legacy MAT credits under the old law, but with a tight 25% cap on the amount of MAT credit that can be set off against normal tax in any one year and a 15 year sunset for utilisation. That balances taxpayer expectations on MAT credit with the government’s desire to avoid MAT shielded “zero tax” years under the new regime. For non resident and digital economy players, the government has doubled down on India as a data and cloud hub. Through amendments to the exemption schedules, qualifying foreign companies that deliver global cloud or data centre services by procuring capacity from “specified” Indian data centres—which themselves must be owned and operated by Indian companies, notified by the Centre and meet detailed conditions—can enjoy a long duration tax exemption on such income, available up to the tax year ending 31 March 2047. The idea is to attract global cloud majors to build onshore stacks on top of Indian owned infrastructure, without triggering immediate tax friction on the foreign service entity’s income sourced from those data centre services. The Budget also rationalises a few smaller but high friction levies. On the collection side, TCS rates on scrap and alcoholic liquor for human consumption are unified at 2%, down from higher earlier rates, giving a modest relief to cash flow sensitive sectors like metals trade and liquor distribution while keeping traceability intact. On capital markets, the long criticised buyback tax is being redesigned: rather than a blunt corporate level levy, the Bill proposes an additional capital gains tax on promoter level gains arising from buybacks, at differentiated rates for domestic and foreign promoters, while non promoter shareholders simply pay normal capital gains tax. That structure softens the blow for retail holders and aligns with the policy goal of penalising aggressive promoter buyback engineering more than ordinary investors. Beyond taxes, the Budget leans hard into manufacturing, logistics and services as growth engines. Customs schedules have been overhauled to remove rate clutter, cut or eliminate basic customs duty on a basket of critical minerals and components for electronics, clean tech, batteries, telecom and shipping, and amend rates for shipbuilding, airports and select agri linked products, all with an eye on domestic value addition and supply chain resilience. Infrastructure plans—from PPP pipelines, a new asset monetisation plan and multimodal connectivity under PM Gati Shakti to continued support for Jal Jeevan, urban challenge funds and maritime corridors—are meant to keep the public investment cycle humming even as the deficit comes down. On the services and social side, the government has layered in measures such as a fresh Rs 10,000 crore fund of funds for startups, expanded skilling and research allocations, and sector specific pushes in tourism, medical tourism and urban livelihoods, framing the entire package as an attempt to deliver both hard infrastructure growth and more inclusive, employment rich development. Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Auto shed 0.87%. The company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. VST Tillers Tractors advanced 1.27% after the company reported a 53.89% surge in total sales to 5,257 units in January 2026, up from 3,416 units sold in January 2025. Meesho fell 4.97% after the company's consolidated net loss widened to Rs 490.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 37.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) advanced 0.66% after the company reported a net turnover of Rs 480.03 crore for January 2026, marking a 17.32% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 409.16 crore recorded in January 2025. R R Kabel rose 1.10% after the company reported growth in profit and revenue for the December quarter. On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 72.4% YoY to Rs 118.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 68.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Relaxo Footwears fell 2.06% after the company reported a 19.6% decline in net profit to Rs 26.54 crore, despite a 0.2% rise in net sales to Rs 668.03 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Escorts Kubota advanced 2.29% after the company’s Agri Machinery Business in January 2026 sold 9,799 tractors registering a growth of 46.9% as against 6,669 tractors sold in January 2025. Global Markets: On Friday, U.S stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Spot gold and silver dropped around 9% and 28%, respectively. Over the past year, gold and silver futures have soared about 67% and 142%, respectively. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Laurus Labs Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/laurus-labs-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1670060</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670060</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Laurus Labs Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Laurus Labs Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 944.45, down 2.13% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.8% on the day, quoting at 25118.1. The Sensex is at 81829.23, down 0.54%.Laurus Labs Ltd has lost around 14.65% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Laurus Labs Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 5.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 21715.1, down 0.37% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 11.2 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 23.57 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 948.75, down 2.06% on the day. Laurus Labs Ltd jumped 61.07% in last one year as compared to a 7.52% rally in NIFTY and a 1.28% spurt in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 65.08 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LaurusLabsLtd_52621883889_45955.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VST Tillers gains after reporting 54% YoY sales growth in January 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vst-tillers-gains-after-reporting-54-yoy-sales-growth-in-january-2026/1670058</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670058</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s power tiller sales grew by 54.91% to 4,810 units in January 2026, compared to 3,105 units in the same month last year.

The company’s power tiller sales grew by 54.91% to 4,810 units in January 2026, compared to 3,105 units in the same month last year. Tractor sales also grew 43.72% to 447 units in January 2026, up from 311 units sold in January 2025. VST Tillers Tractors is engaged in the manufacturing of power tillers and diesel engines. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 44.24% to Rs 24.98 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 44.80 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 11.19% year-on-year to Rs 315.15 crore for the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VSTTillTract_79364939960_2531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM announces allocation of Rs 10,000 crore over next five years under Biopharma Shakti]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-announces-allocation-of-rs-10000-crore-over-next-five-years-under-biopharma-shakti/1670057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670057</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman in her Budget 2026 speech announced allocation of Rs 10,000 crore over the next five years under the Biopharma Shakti.

Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman in her Budget 2026 speech announced allocation of Rs 10,000 crore over the next five years under the Biopharma Shakti. This will include a biopharma-focused network with three new National Institutes of Pharmaceutical Education and Research, popularly known as NIPERs, and upgrading seven existing ones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/piggy-bank-with-doctors-stethoscope-picture-id490672108_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM proposes to reduce the tariff rate on all dutiable goods imported for personal use from 20% to 10% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-proposes-to-reduce-the-tariff-rate-on-all-dutiable-goods-imported-for-personal-use-from-20-to-10/1670056</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670056</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Union Minister for Finance and Corporate Affairs, Smt.

The Union Minister for Finance and Corporate Affairs, Smt. Nirmala Sitharaman, while presenting the Union Budget 2026-27 today in the Parliament announced that the proposals for Customs and Central Excise aim to further simplify the tariff structure, support domestic manufacturing, promote export competitiveness, and correct inversion in duty. Budget proposes to reduce the tariff rate on all dutiable goods imported for personal use from 20 per cent to 10 per cent to rationalize the customs duty structure. To provide relief to patients, particularly those suffering from cancer, the Budget proposes to exempt basic customs duty on 17 drugs or medicines. The Budget also proposes to add 7 more rare diseases for the purposes of exempting import duties on personal imports of drugs, medicines and Food for Special Medical Purposes (FSMP) used in their treatment. The Union Budget further proposes to revise provisions governing baggage clearance during international travel to address genuine concerns of passengers. The revised rules will enhance duty-free allowances and provide clarity in temporary carriage of goods brought in or taken out. Furthermore, the honest taxpayers will now be able to settle their dues and close cases by paying an additional amount in lieu of penalty, the Budget added.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[STT hike sparks sell-off; Nifty slips below 25,000 level ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stt-hike-sparks-sell-off-nifty-slips-below-25000-level/1670053</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670053</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices tumbled during the ongoing Budget 2026 proceedings.

The key equity indices tumbled during the ongoing Budget 2026 proceedings. Investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05%. Nifty skid below 25,000 level, breaching its 200-day moving average. Oil & gas shares plunged for the second consecutive trading session. At 12:50 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 994.52 points or 1.13% to 81,338.35. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 278.45 points or 1.09% to 24,994. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.54% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index tumbled 1.12%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,711 shares rose and 2,215 shares fell. A total of 217 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 7.11% to 14.60. MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.30% to Rs 1,43,217, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement declined 9% to Rs 2,65,652. Union Budget 2026 Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman is presenting her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to deliver nine budgets in a row. She said Budget 2026–27 was prepared at Kartavya Bhavan and was being presented amid a challenging global environment where trade and multilateralism have become increasingly important. Continuing the Union Budget 2026 announcements, Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled a series of tax measures affecting capital markets, including an increase in the Securities Transaction Tax on futures contracts to 0.05%. She also announced that share buybacks will be taxed as capital gains for all shareholders, bringing their treatment in line with other equity income. On the corporate tax front, the finance minister proposed reducing the Minimum Alternate Tax rate from 15% to 14%, and said MAT will be treated as a final tax from April 1, 2026, with no carry-forward or utilisation of MAT credit, marking a shift in the existing tax framework. The Budget also outlined several customs duty changes to support domestic manufacturing and reduce input costs. These include exemption of basic customs duty on capital goods used for processing critical minerals, duty relief on select parts used in microwave oven manufacturing, and exemption on 17 cancer-related drugs to ease costs in critical healthcare segments. Further measures were announced to support the aviation sector and consumers, including exemption and reduction of basic customs duty on components and raw materials used for manufacturing, maintenance and repair of civilian and defence aircraft, alongside a cut in the tariff rate on dutiable personal imports from 20% to 10%. To strengthen India’s IT services sector and attract global investment, Sitharaman announced faster timelines for concluding Advanced Pricing Agreements, reducing the process to two years with a possible six-month extension, and extending the facility of modified returns to associated entities. She also announced a tax holiday until 2047 for foreign companies providing global cloud services using data centres in India, aimed at positioning the country as a global hub for digital and cloud infrastructure. The Nifty Oil & Gas index declined 1.63% to 11,599.45. The index fell 2.16% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Aegis Logistics (down 3.22%), GAIL (India) (down 2.66%), Gujarat Gas (down 2.14%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 1.99%) and Indian Oil Corporation (down 1.81%), Petronet LNG (down 1.74%), Indraprastha Gas (down 1.62%), Reliance Industries (down 1.15%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 1.14%) and Gujarat State Petronet (down 0.95%) declined.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CCUS stocks in action as FM announces Rs 20,000 crore push in Budget 2026–27]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ccus-stocks-in-action-as-fm-announces-rs-20000-crore-push-in-budget-202627/1670048</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670048</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of companies linked to Carbon Capture, Utilization and Storage (CCUS) technologies were in action after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in Union Budget 2026–27, announced an outlay of Rs 20,000 crore over five years to scale up CCUS projects and enhance technology readiness across sectors.

Shares of companies linked to Carbon Capture, Utilization and Storage (CCUS) technologies were in action after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in Union Budget 2026–27, announced an outlay of Rs 20,000 crore over five years to scale up CCUS projects and enhance technology readiness across sectors. The funding aims to accelerate adoption of carbon capture solutions in industries such as power, steel, cement, and oil refining. Indian companies expected to benefit include Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) (down 0.55%), Larsen & Toubro (L&T) (down 1.68%), Wipro (up 3.30%) and Infosys (up 1.01%), which could see growth opportunities through technology deployment, industrial infrastructure, and clean energy integration. The Finance Minister highlighted that the initiative will not only support green and sustainable industrial practices, but also strengthen India’s readiness for emerging carbon management technologies. Experts say the government’s focus on CCUS is likely to stimulate both engineering and technology sectors, boost R&D in industrial decarbonization, and create new avenues for investment in clean technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Capital market shares slump after FM announces hike in STT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/capital-market-shares-slump-after-fm-announces-hike-in-stt/1670046</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670046</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The hike raised concerns over trading volumes in the F&O segment.

The hike raised concerns over trading volumes in the F&O segment. The announcement marked a significant change for derivatives market participants, as the STT on futures contracts was raised to 0.05% from 0.02%, while the STT on options contracts increased to 0.15% from 0.10%, signaling higher transaction costs for traders and investors. Following the news, broker stocks tumbled, with Billionbrains Garage Ventures (Groww) down 10.11% and Angel One falling 11.12%. The only listed stock exchange, BSE was down 15%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM announces hike in STT for futures and options trading]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-announces-hike-in-stt-for-futures-and-options-trading/1670044</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670044</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman on Sunday, February 1 proposed to raise Securities transaction tax (STT) on both, futures and options.

Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman on Sunday, February 1 proposed to raise Securities transaction tax (STT) on both, futures and options. The Securities Transaction Tax on Futures has been raised to 0.05% from 0.02% earlier and for options has been raised to 0.15% from the previous 0.1%. Securities transaction tax (STT) is a tax imposed on the value of securities transactions on recognised stock exchanges in the country.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM proposes duty-free imports of certain specified inputs for leather exports sector]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-proposes-duty-free-imports-of-certain-specified-inputs-for-leather-exports-sector/1670039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670039</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman proposed duty-free imports of certain specified inputs for promoting the country's exports of leather.

Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman proposed duty-free imports of certain specified inputs for promoting the country's exports of leather. The move will help provide cushion to leather exporters who are reeling under the steep 50 per cent US tariffs. The country's leather and leather products shipments dipped marginally 0.23 per cent to USD 3.3 billion during April-December 2025-26. duty-free imports of certain specified inputs for leather exports sector

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Seafood exporter stocks rise after budget boost; Govt to develop 500 fisheries reservoirs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/seafood-exporter-stocks-rise-after-budget-boost-govt-to-develop-500-fisheries-reservoirs/1670031</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670031</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of seafood exporters advanced after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in the Union Budget 2026, announced initiatives for the integrated development of 500 reservoirs and Amrut Sarovars to strengthen the fisheries value chain across coastal regions.

Shares of seafood exporters advanced after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in the Union Budget 2026, announced initiatives for the integrated development of 500 reservoirs and Amrut Sarovars to strengthen the fisheries value chain across coastal regions. Apex Frozen Foods (up 1.65%), Avanti Feeds (up 1.52%), Coastal Corporation (up 3.49%), Waterbase (up 4.39%), and Zeal Aqua (up 4.76%) edged higher. “We will develop these reservoirs and Amrut Sarovars to enhance the fisheries value chain, enabling market linkages involving start-ups, women-led groups, and fish farmer producer organizations,” Sitharaman said while presenting Budget 2026. The announcements were made during Sitharaman’s ninth consecutive Union Budget presentation in the Lok Sabha.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks slip into red as Budget 2026 unfolds; PSU Bank shares drop]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-slip-into-red-as-budget-2026-unfolds-psu-bank-shares-drop/1670032</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670032</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices erased all gains and slipped into negative territory in early afternoon trade amid the ongoing Budget 2026 proceedings.

The key equity indices erased all gains and slipped into negative territory in early afternoon trade amid the ongoing Budget 2026 proceedings. Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to achieve the milestone. Nifty dropped below 25,050 mark, breaching its 200-day moving average. PSU bank shares declined after advancing in the past trading session. At 12:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 789.90 points or 0.94% to 81,513.27. The Nifty 50 index fell 276.45 points or 1.09% to 25,044.20. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.96% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index tumbled 1.39%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,796 shares rose and 2,083 shares fell. A total of 215 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 2.56% to 13.98. MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.21% to Rs 1,42,880, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement declined 9% to Rs 2,65,665. Union Budget 2026 Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman is presenting her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to deliver nine budgets in a row. She said Budget 2026–27 was prepared at Kartavya Bhavan and was being presented amid a challenging global environment where trade and multilateralism have become increasingly important. Continuing the Union Budget 2026 announcements, Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman said the government has met its fiscal consolidation commitment of bringing the fiscal deficit below 4.5% of GDP by FY26. The revised estimate for FY26 has been pegged at 4.4% of GDP, while the fiscal deficit is projected to further decline to 4.3% of GDP in FY27. To finance the deficit, the government will borrow Rs 11.7 lakh crore through dated securities in FY27. On the tax front, Sitharaman announced that the Income Tax Act, 2025, will come into force from April 1, with rules and return forms to be notified shortly. The Budget also proposed several compliance-friendly measures, including removal of interest liability on penalty amounts during the pendency of appeals before the first appellate authority, simplification of TDS on property purchases from non-residents through PAN-based challans, and immunity from prosecution for non-disclosure of non-immovable foreign assets valued below Rs 20 lakh, effective retrospectively from October 1, 2024. Further easing taxpayer compliance, the finance minister proposed extending the timeline for revising income tax returns from December 31 to March 31 on payment of a nominal fee, along with a staggered filing calendar. Under the proposal, individuals filing ITR-1 and ITR-2 will continue to have a July 31 deadline, while non-audit business cases and trusts will be allowed to file returns up to August 31. Significant relief was also announced for NRIs and overseas travellers through sharp cuts in Tax Collected at Source. The TCS rate on overseas tour packages will be reduced to a flat 2% from the existing 5-20%, with no minimum threshold, while TCS on education and medical remittances under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme will be lowered from 5% to 2%, improving cash flows and easing the tax burden. Tourism was positioned as a major driver of employment and growth, with proposals including the establishment of a National Institute of Hospitality, a pilot programme to upskill 10,000 tourist guides, and the creation of a National Destination Digital Knowledge Grid. The Budget also announced a push for eco-tourism through sustainable trekking trails and wildlife tourism initiatives, alongside the setting up of one girls’ hostel in every district to support higher education. The finance minister also outlined steps to strengthen creative, design and media education through ABGC content creator labs, a new National Institute of Design in eastern India, and five university townships near major industrial and logistics corridors. In the primary sectors, measures were announced to strengthen fisheries, animal husbandry and high-value agriculture through improved infrastructure, market linkages, credit-linked subsidies and support for crops such as coconut and sandalwood. In the healthcare space, Sitharaman announced the establishment of NIMHANS 2.0, a premier mental health institute to be set up in North India, reinforcing the government’s focus on mental healthcare infrastructure. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 1.63% to 13.86. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures were trading at 25,309, at a premium of 264.8 points as compared with the spot at 25,044.20. The Nifty option chain for the 24 February 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 204.2 lakh contracts at the 26,000 strike price. Maximum put OI of 110.3 lakh contracts was seen at 24,000 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index fell 2.71% to 8,774.80. The index rose 0.06% in the past trading session. Bank of Baroda (down 5.33%), Bank of India (down 4.98%), Indian Bank (down 3.07%), Punjab National Bank (down 2.74%) and Bank of Maharashtra (down 2.47%), Indian Overseas Bank (down 2.3%), Union Bank of India (down 2.23%), Punjab & Sind Bank (down 2.12%), State Bank of India (down 2.01%) and Central Bank of India (down 1.55%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: logistics and cargo-related stocks rallied on the bourses. Container Corporation of India rose up to 2.99%, Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone gained 0.87%, JSW Infrastructure climbed 2.69%, Shipping Corporation of India advanced 3.24%, Allcargo Logistics added 1.63% and Delhivery rose 1.37% after Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman proposed a new dedicated freight corridor connecting Surat in Gujarat with Dankuni in West Bengal to strengthen freight movement across the country.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tourism stocks rally after FM announces development of 15 archaeological sites in Budget 2026 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tourism-stocks-rally-after-fm-announces-development-of-15-archaeological-sites-in-budget-2026/1670025</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670025</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initiative aims to shift from traditional sightseeing to experience-led tourism by enhancing visitor infrastructure, offering curated cultural experiences, and improving connectivity.

The initiative aims to shift from traditional sightseeing to experience-led tourism by enhancing visitor infrastructure, offering curated cultural experiences, and improving connectivity. The Finance Minister also proposed the creation of a National Institute of Hospitality to bridge academia, industry, and government, strengthen India’s services economy, and boost foreign exchange earnings. Additionally, she launched a pilot programme to train 10,000 tourist guides across 20 iconic sites through a 12-week hybrid training course developed in collaboration with the Indian Institute of Management. Following the announcements, tourism stocks rallied sharply: Easy Trip Planners surged 11.15%, Lemon Tree Hotels rose 3.13%, Yatra Online gained 3.05%, EIH advanced 2.06%, IRCTC added 0.36%, Mahindra Holidays 1%, TBO Tek 0.64%, and BLS International Services 1.65%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AVGC sector set to grow as FM announces talent, job initiatives]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avgc-sector-set-to-grow-as-fm-announces-talent-job-initiatives/1670021</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670021</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of companies and startups in India’s Animation, Visual Effects, Gaming, and Comics (AVGC) ecosystem are expected to benefit after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in Union Budget 2026–27, announced initiatives to strengthen the sector and boost employment.

Shares of companies and startups in India’s Animation, Visual Effects, Gaming, and Comics (AVGC) ecosystem are expected to benefit after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in Union Budget 2026–27, announced initiatives to strengthen the sector and boost employment. The government plans to support the Indian Institute of Creative Technologies, Mumbai, in setting up AVGC Content Creator Labs across 15,000 secondary schools and 500 colleges to nurture talent. Shares of Zensar Technologies gained 3.60%, Tata Consultancy Services rose 0.82%, Onmobile Global and added 0.13%, The Finance Minister highlighted the sector’s massive job potential, projecting that it will require 2 million professionals by 2030. She said the government aims to position India as a global hub for AVGC under a “Create in India” initiative, shifting from being primarily a consumption market to a content-creation economy. The government has also established a National Centre of Excellence (NCoE) to build a world-class talent pool. In her statement, FM Sitharaman noted that following the Promotion and Regulation of Online Gaming Act, 2025, the government is distinguishing between skill-based recreational gaming and harmful real-money betting games. The measures are designed to optimise growth, employment, and exports in the AVGC sector while assessing the impact of emerging technologies, including artificial intelligence, on jobs and skill requirements.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM announces launch of India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-announces-launch-of-india-semiconductor-mission-ism-20/1670022</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670022</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has announced the launch of India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0 in her Budget for 2026-27, alongside a sharp increase in the outlay for the electronics components manufacturing scheme (ECMS) to Rs 40,000 crore.

Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has announced the launch of India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0 in her Budget for 2026-27, alongside a sharp increase in the outlay for the electronics components manufacturing scheme (ECMS) to Rs 40,000 crore. The move builds on the gains of ISM 1.0, which expanded India’s semiconductor sector capabilities. Building on the success of ISM 1.0, we will launch ISM 2.0 to produce equipment and materials, design full-stack Indian IP, and fortify supply chains, she noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-2785864__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Foodbrands Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-foodbrands-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1670017</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670017</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Ind Bank Housing Ltd, Brightcom Group Ltd and Welspun Specialty Solutions Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 February 2026.

Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Ind Bank Housing Ltd, Brightcom Group Ltd and Welspun Specialty Solutions Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 February 2026. United Foodbrands Ltd surged 20.00% to Rs 216.9 at 01-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 31438 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3339 shares in the past one month. Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd spiked 20.00% to Rs 34.62. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 8422 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17030 shares in the past one month. Ind Bank Housing Ltd soared 18.24% to Rs 44.99. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 4195 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1484 shares in the past one month. Brightcom Group Ltd added 16.85% to Rs 10.75. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 12.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.78 lakh shares in the past one month. Welspun Specialty Solutions Ltd exploded 14.34% to Rs 42.27. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 24.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.03 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Barbeque-Nation-Hospitality-Ltd_78482688_33202.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>