<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:54:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee closes unchanged]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-closes-unchanged/1678604</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678604</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed unchanged from its previous day's close of 90.7100 per Dollar on Wednesday (18 February 2026).

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures linger around 123 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-linger-around-123-mark/1678589</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678589</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures end almost flat at 90.71.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures end almost flat at 90.71. GBP/INR and EUR/INR lose around 0.1% to end at 123.19 and 107.40 respectively. Meanwhile, JPY/INR slumps 0.76% to close at 59.02.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dhabriya Polywood arm bags Rs 25-cr orders from Godrej Group ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dhabriya-polywood-arm-bags-rs-25-cr-orders-from-godrej-group/1678587</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678587</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said Dhabriya Polywood has secured an order worth Rs 16.10 crore for facade glazing, aluminium door and window works.

In a regulatory filing, the company said Dhabriya Polywood has secured an order worth Rs 16.10 crore for facade glazing, aluminium door and window works. The project is scheduled to be completed over 24 months in various tranches, as per the terms of the order. Separately, Dynasty Modular Furnitures has received an order worth Rs 9.20 crore for modular kitchen works. This contract is to be executed over 12 months in multiple tranches. Both orders are domestic in nature. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding entity. The contracts do not fall under related party transactions. Dhabriya Polywood is one of the leading manufacturer & suppliers of Extruded PVC/uPVC Profile Sections and Dstona Sheets & Moldings for various furnishing & furniture applications (i.e. Doors, Partitions, Ceiling, Paneling, fencing, prefabs, interior & furnishing etc.), uPVC Window & Doors and Aluminum Window Systems. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 100.5% to Rs 7.66 crore on 19.6% rise in revenue fro, operations to Rs 65.66 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Dhabriya Polywood rose 0.91% to end at Rs 370.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DhabriyaPoly_79481632112_45947.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Inflow of foreign funds and positive domestic equity markets drives INR higher]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inflow-of-foreign-funds-and-positive-domestic-equity-markets-drives-inr-higher/1678586</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678586</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee rose 5 paise to close at 90.67 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday driven by inflow of foreign funds and positive domestic equity markets.

The Indian rupee rose 5 paise to close at 90.67 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday driven by inflow of foreign funds and positive domestic equity markets. Indian shares ended a choppy session slightly higher on Wednesday after some late-session buying. A cautious undertone prevailed amid fears of Artificial Intelligence led disruption and fading hopes of an early interest rate cut by the U.S. Federal Reserve. Investors are increasingly worried that artificial intelligence could disrupt multiple industries, not just information technology services. The benchmark BSE Sensex swung between gains and losses before closing up 283.29 points, or 0.34 percent, at 83,734.25. The broader NSE Nifty index settled 93.95 points, or 0.37 percent, higher at 25,819.35. However, higher global crude oil prices and a strengthening greenback capped sharp gains in the local unit. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 90.60 against the US dollar and traded in a narrow range of 90.60-90.71 before settling at 90.67 (provisional), higher by 5 paise against its previous close.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks extend gains for third day; Nifty settles above 25,800]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-extend-gains-for-third-day-nifty-settles-above-25800/1678583</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678583</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks closed with decent gains on Wednesday, extending their rally to a third straight session.

The domestic equity benchmarks closed with decent gains on Wednesday, extending their rally to a third straight session. Sentiment, however, remained cautious amid a broader risk-off tone in overseas markets, while investors continued to track upcoming macro data for direction. In the absence of major domestic triggers, trading remained selective and largely stock-specific. The Nifty settled above the 25,800 mark, supported by strength in metal, PSU bank and FMCG counters, while IT shares underperformed amid lingering AI-related uncertainties, limiting the overall upside. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 283.29 points or 0.34% to 83,734.25. The Nifty 50 index rallied 93.95 points or 0.37% to 25,819.35. Over the three consecutive sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.34% and 1.37%, respectively. ITC (up 2.21%), Axis Bank (up 1.41%) and Reliance Industries (up 1.26%) boosted the Nifty higher today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.50% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.39%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,187 shares rose and 2,018 shares fell. A total of 191 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 3.55% to 12.22. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.26% to 6.676 compared with the previous session close of 6.659. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6800 compared with its close of 90.7200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement gained 0.74% to Rs 152,541. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.09% to 97.14. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.44% to 4.070. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 41 cents or 0.61% to $67.83 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently up by 216 points, signaling a strong opening for US stocks today. European indices traded higher on Wednesday as investors weighed the latest U.K. inflation data and monitored global market developments. The U.K. inflation rate fell to 3% in January, according to the latest figures from the Office for National Statistics. Most Asian stocks ended higher despite the renewed artificial intelligence worries gripping international markets, while oil prices were under pressure after Iran touted progress in nuclear negotiations with the United States. Mainland China, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan and South Korea were among the markets closed for Lunar New Year holidays. US equity market saw a lackluster session on Tuesday as investors grappled with the outlook for the AI boom. Concerns that companies are over-investing, along with angst about the extent to which the nascent technology could disrupt labor markets, have fuelled investor jitters in recent weeks. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 0.07% to 49,533.19, the S&P 500 was up 0.10% at 6,843.22, and the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.14% to 22,578.38. Brent and West Texas Intermediate crude oil futures were little changed on Wednesday after both slid to close at more than two-week lows in the previous session. Following talks in Geneva on Tuesday, Iran's foreign minister reportedly said Tehran and Washington reached an understanding on main "guiding principles" towards resolving their longstanding nuclear dispute, easing worries about a military conflict near the Strait of Hormuz that could disrupt global oil supply. Stocks in Spotlight: E2E Networks surged 12.91% after NVIDIA announced that the Indian company is building an NVIDIA Blackwell GPU cluster on its TIR cloud platform. E2E Networks however clarified later stating that the latest media coverage was a reiteration and public acknowledgement of its existing relationship with NVIDIA, and not the result of fresh negotiations, binding agreements or new partnerships. Netweb Technologies India surged 8.84% after the company launched artificial intelligence (AI) supercomputing systems, Tyrone Camarero Spark and Tyrone Supercomputing Systems, powered by NVIDIA Sovereign AI Development. Bharti Airtel rose 0.05%. The company announced that its subsidiary, Airtel Money, has received a Certificate of Registration from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to operate as a Type II Non-Deposit Accepting Non-Banking Financial Company [Type II-NBFC-ND (ICC)]. Power Mech Projects surged 4.39% after securing domestic orders worth Rs 1,005 crore from subsidiaries of Adani Power. The contracts were awarded by Mirzapur Thermal Energy (UP) and Mahan Energen for ultra-supercritical thermal power projects. The Mirzapur order is valued at Rs 515 crore, while the Mahan order is worth Rs 490 crore. Dilip Buildcon rose 3.71% after the company announced that it has emerged as the lowest (L-1) bidder for a major infrastructure project in Gujarat. The tender, floated by the Narmada Water Resources, Water Supply & Kalpasar Department, is valued at Rs 702 crore. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone fell 1%. The company announced that it has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Port of Marseille Fos, France’s leading port, to enhance trade facilitation, port innovation, and energy transition. Aurionpro Solutions jumped 4.83% after the company announced that it has bagged a significant order from a reputed global data center developer and operator. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) shed 0.67%. The company has announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance from Steel Authority of India (SAIL) for executing a Captive Power Plant (CPP) package. Bosch rose 0.97%. The company announced that its board approved the appointment of Tillmann Olsen as the chief financial officer (CFO) with effect from 1 June 2026. Dabur India declined 1.47%. The company announced the appointment of Herjit S. Bhalla as chief executive officer (CEO) India Business, with effect from 15 April 2026, as part of a leadership realignment aimed at sharpening operational focus. Spandana Sphoorty Financial shed 0.47%. The company announced that its board has approved the appointment of Avinash Yadav as chief information officer (CIO), effective 17 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICRA reaffirms ratings of Railtel Corporation at 'AA/A1+' with ‘stable’ outlook]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icra-reaffirms-ratings-of-railtel-corporation-at-aaa1-with-stable-outlook/1678584</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678584</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘ICRA] A1+’.

The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘ICRA] A1+’. ICRA stated that the reaffirmation of ratings considers Railtel’s long track record (over 20 years) of operations in the telecom infrastructure space. In addition, it has executed critical projects of national importance such as BharatNet, National Knowledge Network (NKN) and railway signalling, among others. The ratings continue to factor in Railtel’s strong parentage, with the majority ownership by the Government of India (GoI) under the Ministry of Railways (MoR). This strong parentage enables the company to execute all connectivity-related projects of the Indian Railways and secure business from other public-sector undertakings (PSUs). The ratings factor in the healthy growth in the operating income (OI)and the sustenance of its strong financial risk profile, supported by zero debt and a healthy liquidity position. ICRA expects the company to continue demonstrating significant growth in OI, aided by its robust order book position of Rs. 8,600 crore as of January 2026. ICRA continues to consider Railtel’s strong liquidity position, bolstered by its sizeable cash and liquid investments (including fixed deposits) of Rs 319 crore as on 30 September 2025. Further, Railtel maintains healthy financial flexibility with a conservative capital structure. The ratings, however, are constrained by the expected moderation in the company’s operating profit margins (OPM) due to a growing proportion of the project segment which has lower margins compared to telecom segment. However, its cash flow generation is anticipated to remain healthy, translating into a comfortable credit profile. The ratings also factor in the company’s obligations to pay dividends to the GoI, which might impact its liquidity position. Railtel Corporation of India is a "Mini Ratna (Category-I)” public sector undertaking which owns a pan India optic fibre network to provide broadband and multimedia network in all parts of the country along with modernisation and maintenance of railway network. The scrip had gained 1.14% to end at Rs 333.25 on the BSE today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1678582</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678582</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,827, a premium of 7.65 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,819.35 in the cash market.

The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,827, a premium of 7.65 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,819.35 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index rallied 93.95 points or 0.37% to 25,819.35. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 3.55% to 12.22. Infosys, HDFC Bank and Tata Consultancy Services were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers ends with modest gains; Nifty settles above 25,800 level; VIX drops 3.55%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-ends-with-modest-gains-nifty-settles-above-25800-level-vix-drops-355/1678574</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678574</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices ended with decent gains today, extending their rally for the third consecutive session, led by metal and PSU bank stocks.

The domestic equity indices ended with decent gains today, extending their rally for the third consecutive session, led by metal and PSU bank stocks. Meanwhile, IT shares lagged amid persistent AI-related uncertainties, which capped broader gains. The Nifty ended above the 25,800 level. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 283.29 points or 0.34% to 83,734.25. The Nifty 50 index rallied 93.95 points or 0.37% to 25,819.35. In the three consecutive trading sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.34% and 1.37%, respectively. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.50% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.39%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 3.55% to 12.22. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Metal index (up 1.33%), the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 1.31%) and the Nifty FMCG index (up 1.21%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 1.23%), Nifty Pharma index (up 0.21%) and the Nifty Media index (up 0.24%) and the underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.26% to 6.676 compared with the previous session close of 6.659. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6800 compared with its close of 90.7200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement gained 0.74% to Rs 152,541. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.09% to 97.14. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.44% to 4.070. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 41 cents or 0.61% to $67.83 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets traded higher on Wednesday as investors weighed the latest U.K. inflation data and monitored global market developments. The U.K. inflation rate fell to 3% in January, according to the latest figures from the Office for National Statistics. Asian stocks ended higher despite the renewed artificial intelligence worries gripping international markets, while oil prices were under pressure after Iran touted progress in nuclear negotiations with the United States. Mainland China, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan and South Korea were among the markets closed for Lunar New Year holidays. The positive start in Asia followed a lackluster session on Tuesday on Wall Street as investors grappled with the outlook for the AI boom. Concerns that companies are over-investing, along with angst about the extent to which the nascent technology could disrupt labor markets, have fuelled investor jitters in recent weeks. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 0.07% to 49,533.19, the S&P 500 was up 0.10% at 6,843.22, and the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.14% to 22,578.38. The S&P 500 fell 0.88% initially before making up ground to close in positive territory. Brent and West Texas Intermediate crude oil futures were little changed on Wednesday after both slid to close at more than two-week lows in the previous session. Following talks in Geneva on Tuesday, Iran's foreign minister reportedly said Tehran and Washington reached an understanding on main "guiding principles" towards resolving their longstanding nuclear dispute, easing worries about a military conflict near the Strait of Hormuz that could disrupt global oil supply.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Forge gains after inking MoU with VVDN Technologies ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-forge-gains-after-inking-mou-with-vvdn-technologies/1678573</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678573</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the MoU, the parties intend to jointly pursue opportunities in next-generation technologies across the Automotive, Defence, AI, and Datacentre domains.

Under the MoU, the parties intend to jointly pursue opportunities in next-generation technologies across the Automotive, Defence, AI, and Datacentre domains. The strategic partnership is established to drive innovation and jointly develop the next generation of products for Automotive, Defence, and AI server platforms, leveraging their complementary strengths in engineering, manufacturing, and technology innovation. By combining VVDN’s strengths in electronics design, software, system integration, and manufacturing with Bharat Forge’s expertise in advanced manufacturing and precision engineering, the two companies aim to explore the development of scalable, high-impact solutions aligned with evolving industry requirements and emerging technologies. Bharat Forge vice chairman & Joint MD Amit Kalyani, said: “This partnership enables us to leverage advanced technologies, accelerate innovation, and enhance the quality of solutions we deliver to our clients and stakeholders. By aligning with partners who share our vision for excellence, we create a robust ecosystem that fosters knowledge exchange, operational efficiency, and long-term value creation. Such alliances are integral to our strategy, ensuring that we remain competitive, future-ready, and capable of addressing the evolving needs of the markets we serve.” Puneet Agarwal CEO of VVDN, said: “This partnership with Bharat Forge aligns with our vision of driving innovation through advanced engineering and digital technologies. By combining our product engineering and manufacturing strengths with Bharat Forges domain leadership, we aim to accelerate the development of next-generation solutions across automotive, defense and data center ecosystems, amongst other Next-Gen Technologies.” Bharat Forge manufactures an extensive array of critical and safety components for several sectors, including automobiles (across commercial & passenger vehicles), oil & gas, aerospace, locomotives, marine, energy (across renewable and non-renewable sources), construction, mining, and general engineering. The company’s consolidated net profit rallied 28.21% to Rs 272.80 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 212.78 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations soared 24.96% YoY to Rs 4,342.93 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatForge_36016338711_69.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RVNL bags Rs 1,201-cr bridge contract from Northern Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rvnl-bags-rs-1201-cr-bridge-contract-from-northern-railway/1678571</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678571</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the design and construction of a new rail-cum-road Bridge No.

The project involves the design and construction of a new rail-cum-road Bridge No. 11 over the river Ganga, 50 meters downstream of the existing old Malviya Bridge near Kashi Railway Station in Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh. The scope includes substructure and superstructure works (8 x 108.5 m + 2 x 103.3 m open web steel girder), four railway tracks on the lower deck and a six-lane road on the upper deck, along with railway and road approaches, associated OHE works, and general electrical works. The project is to be executed within 48 months. The total contract value stands at Rs 1,201.35 crore. RVNL will execute the project in a joint venture, with a 60% share, while GPT Infraprojects holds the remaining 40% stake. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related party transactions, the company said. Rail Vikas Nigam is engaged in executing a wide range of railway infrastructure projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, cable-stayed bridges, and institutional buildings. The company reported a 3.65% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 322.83 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 311.44 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 2.56% YoY to Rs 4,684.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of Rail Vikas Nigam rose 0.32% to close at Rs 309.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[B L Kashyap bags Rs 300-cr order from CRC Greens for Greater Noida housing project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/b-l-kashyap-bags-rs-300-cr-order-from-crc-greens-for-greater-noida-housing-project/1678569</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678569</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said the order involves construction and supervision of civil structural works for the residential project.

In a regulatory filing, the company said the order involves construction and supervision of civil structural works for the residential project. The contract is domestic in nature and is to be executed over an approximate period of 42 months. The total contract value stands at Rs 300 crore, excluding GST. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group companies have any interest in the awarding entity. The contract does not fall under related party transactions. BL Kashyap & Sons is one of India’s most respected construction and infrastructure development company with a pan India presence. The company's consolidated net profit zoomed 965.8% to Rs 11.83 crore on a 33.9% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 323.87 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of B. L. Kashyap and Sons rose 0.30% to end at Rs 50.08 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BLKashyap_84180144928_27242.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lloyds Metal and Energy climbs after LGRF incorporates subsidiary in DMCC zone]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lloyds-metal-and-energy-climbs-after-lgrf-incorporates-subsidiary-in-dmcc-zone/1678568</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678568</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The wholly owned subsidiary company incorporated Virtus for expansion of the group’s investment activities in metals and mining sector in United Arab Emirates, Dubai in the DMCC zone.

The wholly owned subsidiary company incorporated Virtus for expansion of the group’s investment activities in metals and mining sector in United Arab Emirates, Dubai in the DMCC zone. The new entity will enter into strategic partnership with metals and minerals developers from United States of America (USA). LGRF will acquire 100% stake in Virtus for total consideration of AED 50,000. Lloyds Metals and Energy (LMEL) is the leading player in the iron and steel-making industry. The company’s consolidated net profit soared 169.05% to Rs 1,047.39 crore on 201.94% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 5,058.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsMetals_76757705405_2629.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index records a surge of 1.33%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-records-a-surge-of-133/1678567</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678567</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index ended up 1.33% at 11985.75 today.

Nifty Metal index ended up 1.33% at 11985.75 today. The index has added 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Hindustan Copper Ltd jumped 3.63%, Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd rose 3.04% and Tata Steel Ltd gained 2.93%. The Nifty Metal index has increased 45.00% over last one year compared to the 12.53% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index increased 1.31% and Nifty IT index has dropped 1.23% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.37% to close at 25819.35 while the SENSEX witnessed a rise of 0.34% to close at 83734.25 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 283 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,800 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-283-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25800-level/1678566</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678566</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended with modest gains today, extending their rally for the third consecutive session, led by metal and PSU bank stocks.

The key domestic indices ended with modest gains today, extending their rally for the third consecutive session, led by metal and PSU bank stocks. Meanwhile, IT shares lagged amid persistent AI-related uncertainties, which capped broader gains. The Nifty ended above the 25,800 level. Barring the IT index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE ended in the green, led by metal, PSU bank, and FMCG stocks. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 283.29 points or 0.34% to 83,734.25. The Nifty 50 index rallied 93.95 points or 0.37% to 25,819.35. In the three consecutive trading sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.34% and 1.37%, respectively. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.50% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.39%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,241 shares rose and 1,957 shares fell. A total of 185 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 3.55% to 12.22. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index rose 1.33% to 11,985.75. The index fell 1.06% in the past trading session. Hindustan Copper (up 3.4%), Tata Steel (up 2.99%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 2.86%), Jindal Stainless (up 2.52%), Vedanta (up 1.44%), Steel Authority of India (up 1.44%), NMDC (up 1.35%), Hindalco Industries (up 1.07%), National Aluminium Company (up 0.95%) and Jindal Steel (up 0.92%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: E2E Networks surged 12.91% after NVIDIA announced that the Indian company is building an NVIDIA Blackwell GPU cluster on its TIR cloud platform. E2E Networks however clarified later stating that the latest media coverage was a reiteration and public acknowledgement of its existing relationship with NVIDIA, and not the result of fresh negotiations, binding agreements or new partnerships. Netweb Technologies India surged 8.84% after the company launched artificial intelligence (AI) supercomputing systems, Tyrone Camarero Spark and Tyrone Supercomputing Systems, powered by NVIDIA Sovereign AI Development. Power Mech Projects surged 4.23% after securing domestic orders worth Rs 1,005 crore from subsidiaries of Adani Power. The contracts were awarded by Mirzapur Thermal Energy (UP) and Mahan Energen for ultra-supercritical thermal power projects. The Mirzapur order is valued at Rs 515 crore, while the Mahan order is worth Rs 490 crore. Dilip Buildcon rose 3.71% after the company announced that it has emerged as the lowest (L-1) bidder for a major infrastructure project in Gujarat. The tender, floated by the Narmada Water Resources, Water Supply & Kalpasar Department, is valued at Rs 702 crore. The project involves the construction of a flood protection embankment on the Narmada River in the Bharuch District. Executed on an engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) basis, the project is scheduled for completion within a 24-month timeframe. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone fell 1.20%. The company announced that it has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Port of Marseille Fos, France’s leading port, to enhance trade facilitation, port innovation, and energy transition. Aurionpro Solutions jumped 4.83% after the company announced that it has bagged a significant order from a reputed global data center developer and operator. Bharti Airtel rose 0.05%. The company announced that its subsidiary, Airtel Money, has received a Certificate of Registration from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to operate as a Type II Non-Deposit Accepting Non-Banking Financial Company [Type II-NBFC-ND (ICC)]. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) shed 0.67%. The company has announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance from Steel Authority of India (SAIL) for executing a Captive Power Plant (CPP) package. Bosch rose 0.97%. The company announced that its board approved the appointment of Tillmann Olsen as the chief financial officer (CFO) with effect from 1 June 2026. Dabur India declined 1.47%. The company announced the appointment of Herjit S. Bhalla as chief executive officer (CEO) India Business, with effect from 15 April 2026, as part of a leadership realignment aimed at sharpening operational focus. Spandana Sphoorty Financial shed 0.47%. The company announced that its board has approved the appointment of Avinash Yadav as chief information officer (CIO), effective 17 February 2026. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently up by 216 points, signaling a strong opening for US stocks today. European indices traded higher on Wednesday as investors weighed the latest U.K. inflation data and monitored global market developments. The U.K. inflation rate fell to 3% in January, according to the latest figures from the Office for National Statistics. Most Asian stocks ended higher despite the renewed artificial intelligence worries gripping international markets, while oil prices were under pressure after Iran touted progress in nuclear negotiations with the United States. Mainland China, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan and South Korea were among the markets closed for Lunar New Year holidays. US equity market saw a lackluster session on Tuesday as investors grappled with the outlook for the AI boom. Concerns that companies are over-investing, along with angst about the extent to which the nascent technology could disrupt labor markets, have fuelled investor jitters in recent weeks. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 0.07% to 49,533.19, the S&P 500 was up 0.10% at 6,843.22, and the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.14% to 22,578.38. Brent and West Texas Intermediate crude oil futures were little changed on Wednesday after both slid to close at more than two-week lows in the previous session. Following talks in Geneva on Tuesday, Iran's foreign minister reportedly said Tehran and Washington reached an understanding on main "guiding principles" towards resolving their longstanding nuclear dispute, easing worries about a military conflict near the Strait of Hormuz that could disrupt global oil supply.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aptech bags Rs 4-cr contract from state government body for computer-based exam]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aptech-bags-rs-4-cr-contract-from-state-government-body-for-computer-based-exam/1678565</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678565</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said the contract has been awarded to Aptech Limited for providing end-to-end computer-based examination services.

In a regulatory filing, the company said the contract has been awarded to Aptech Limited for providing end-to-end computer-based examination services. The exam is expected to commence from February 2026. Under the terms of the agreement, Aptech has been instructed to submit the final list of exam cities and centres — already audited by the state government body — along with the number of seats. The company will conduct the examination in accordance with the request for proposal (RFP) and master service agreement (MSA). The contract outlines specific terms and conditions, including scope of work, deliverables, service level agreements and payment terms. The company clarified that the order has been awarded by a domestic entity and that neither the promoter nor promoter group companies have any interest in the awarding body. The contract does not fall under related party transactions. Aptech is primarily engaged in the business of education training and assessment solution services. It is a global learning solutions company that has commenced its education and training business for the last over three decades. The company's consolidated net profit zoomed 139.1% to Rs 8.56 crore on a 24.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 137.11 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Aptech fell 1.75% to close at Rs 94.92 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Aptech_92953066796_8039.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Airfloa Rail Technology secures Rs 12-cr order from Integral Coach Factory]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/airfloa-rail-technology-secures-rs-12-cr-order-from-integral-coach-factory/1678564</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678564</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order pertains to the supply and installation of 159 sets of roller blinds for LHB AC Amrit Bharat Version 3.0 coaches.

The order pertains to the supply and installation of 159 sets of roller blinds for LHB AC Amrit Bharat Version 3.0 coaches. The total contract value stands at Rs 11.78 crore. The company said the order will be executed within 45 days from the date of the purchase order. Airfloa Rail Technology clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It also stated that the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Airfloa Rail Technology is primarily engaged in the manufacturing of components used in rolling stock for Indian Railways, supplying through railway production units such as the Integral Coach Factory (ICF) and other coach factories. The company also undertakes turnkey interior furnishing projects for Indian Railways. In the aerospace and defence sectors, it manufactures intricate, highly engineered, and critical components. Along with Indian Railways, the company also serves other railway factories and global rolling stock OEMs. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 192.39 crore and net profit of Rs 25.56 crore for the year ended 31 March 2025. The counter rose 0.58% to Rs 286.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AirfloaRailTechnologyLtd_25258252_29288.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Green Energy’s arm incorporates new wholly-owned subsidiary Skyspin Energy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-green-energys-arm-incorporates-new-wholly-owned-subsidiary-skyspin-energy/1678562</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678562</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Skyspin Energy has been incorporated to undertake the generation of power using renewable sources of energy.

Skyspin Energy has been incorporated to undertake the generation of power using renewable sources of energy. Its primary objective is to generate, develop, transform, distribute, transmit, sell and supply power or electrical energy through wind, solar and other renewable energy sources. The newly formed entity has an authorised share capital of Rs 1,00,000 and a paid-up share capital of Rs 1,00,000. The company is yet to commence business operations. AREH11L holds 100% of the share capital of Skyspin Energy, making it a step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of Adani Green Energy. Adani Green Energy is India’s largest and one of the leading renewable energy companies in the world enabling the clean energy transition. It develops, owns, and operates utility scale grid-connected solar, wind, hybrid and hydro pumped storage renewable power plants. The company has set a target of achieving 50 GW by 2030 aligned to India’s decarbonization goals. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 41 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net profit of Rs 492 crore in Q3 FY25. Total sales rose 7.6% year on year to Rs 2,433 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter slipped 1.68% to Rs 999.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniGreenEnergyLtd_74416007001_70666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brainbees Solutions Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brainbees-solutions-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678560</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678560</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IIFL Capital Services Ltd, Hexaware Technologies Ltd, V I P Industries Ltd and Waaree Energies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 18 February 2026.

IIFL Capital Services Ltd, Hexaware Technologies Ltd, V I P Industries Ltd and Waaree Energies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 18 February 2026. Brainbees Solutions Ltd tumbled 5.58% to Rs 217.3 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.37 lakh shares in the past one month. IIFL Capital Services Ltd lost 4.39% to Rs 320.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 36472 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53614 shares in the past one month. Hexaware Technologies Ltd crashed 3.99% to Rs 572.15. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 99049 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.59 lakh shares in the past one month. V I P Industries Ltd pared 3.49% to Rs 369.45. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8412 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9728 shares in the past one month. Waaree Energies Ltd slipped 3.34% to Rs 2952. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.21 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.14 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrainbeesSolutionsLtd_65573979_68149.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[E2E Networks clarifies NVIDIA tie-up; says no new deal beyond earlier disclosure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/e2e-networks-clarifies-nvidia-tie-up-says-no-new-deal-beyond-earlier-disclosure/1678559</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678559</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a filing dated 18 February 2026, the company said it has an existing relationship with NVIDIA that underpins its cloud and AI infrastructure offerings.

In a filing dated 18 February 2026, the company said it has an existing relationship with NVIDIA that underpins its cloud and AI infrastructure offerings. It clarified that the latest media coverage was a reiteration and public acknowledgement of this relationship, and not the result of fresh negotiations, binding agreements or new partnerships. The company pointed out that it had already disclosed the procurement and deployment of NVIDIA B200 GPU clusters in Chennai through a press release dated 9 January 2026. It also referred to statements made by management during analyst and investor conference calls, transcripts of which were filed with the exchange. E2E Networks further stated that there is no undisclosed material information that could explain the recent movement in its share price or trading volumes. It added that the news article does not have any additional material impact on its operations or financial position beyond what has already been communicated to the exchanges. The company reiterated its commitment to regulatory compliance and said it will continue to inform the exchanges of any material developments as required. NVIDIA said that E2E Networks is building a Blackwell GPU cluster on its TIR cloud platform, with the infrastructure being deployed at the L&T Vyoma Data Center in Chennai. The platform will incorporate NVIDIA HGX B200 systems, NVIDIA Enterprise software and NVIDIA Nemotron open models to support sovereign AI development across sectors including healthcare, finance, manufacturing and agriculture. At the AI Impact Summit in New Delhi, NVIDIA also highlighted its broader partnerships in India, aligned with the government’s $1 billion-plus IndiaAI Mission aimed at expanding compute capacity, building sovereign AI models and datasets, and strengthening AI education, startups and responsible AI frameworks. E2E Networks operates as a cloud infrastructure provider in India, offering GPU computing, enterprise cloud solutions and managed services for artificial intelligence and machine learning workloads. On a standalone basis, E2E Networks reported net loss of Rs 5.70 crore in Q3 December 2025 as against net profit of Rs 11.59 crore in Q3 December 2024. Net sales rose 68.32% YoY to Rs 70.02 crore in Q3 December 2025. Shares of E2E Networks were up 10.49% at Rs 2,815.20 on the NSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/E2ENetworksLtd_43382383477_72373.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Netweb Tech sizzles after launching NVIDIA powered-AI supercomputers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/netweb-tech-sizzles-after-launching-nvidia-powered-ai-supercomputers/1678558</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678558</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tyrone Camarero Spark, is the world’s smallest AI supercomputer delivering NVIDIA’s AI stack in a compact desktop form factor.

Tyrone Camarero Spark, is the world’s smallest AI supercomputer delivering NVIDIA’s AI stack in a compact desktop form factor. It combines NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs, NVIDIA Grace CPUs, NVIDIA Networking, NVIDIA CUDA-X libraries and NVIDIA AI software stack, accelerating agentic and physical AI development to address the requirements of millions of AI developers in India. The company has also launched Tyrone AI Supercomputing systems based on NVIDIA Grace Blackwell platforms designed. This product and architecture, built on the NVIDIA GB200 NVL4 platform, delivers revolutionary performance through four NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs connected with an NVLink bridge and two NVIDIA Grace CPUs connected over NVLink-C2C. Compatible with liquid-cooled, NVIDIA MGX™ modular servers, it provides up to 2x performance for scientific computing, AI model training, and inference over the prior generation. Sanjay Lodha, managing director & CEO of Netweb Technologies India, said, “The Tyrone Camarero Spark provides AI developers t 1 Peta Flops of (FP4) performance out of the box in the tiniest form factor of 5.9 in x 5.9 in x 2in inches and with system power supply of just 240 Watts —whereas in 2016 a comparable performance of 170 Tera Flops (FP16) with same memory size of 128GB could be delivered with System Power requirement of 3200 Watts. This milestone revolutionizes AI compute in India by introducing new ways to conduct AI research and development. With this move we have created a whole new customer segment in collaboration with NVIDIA. Our deep collaboration with NVIDIA for the last 15 years has been instrumental in advancing AI infrastructure in India with the nation’s own sovereign-built, latest-generation NVIDIA systems. Make in India Tyrone GB200 systems, coupled with complete sovereign cloud stack and utilities provide a multi-node, liquid-cooled, rack-scale system design for the most compute-intensive workloads. This design will integrate 20 Tyrone GB200 MGX systems within a single liquid-cooled rack, comprising 40 NVIDIA Grace CPUs and 80 NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs, along with NVIDIA BlueField-3 DPUs, high-performance storage, and comprehensive end-to-end security.” Netweb Technologies is India’s leading high-end computing solutions (HCS) provider, with fully integrated design and manufacturing capabilities. The company’s HCS offering comprises HPC, Private cloud and HCI, AI systems and enterprise workstations, High performance storage (HPS) and Data Centre Servers. The company’s standalone net profit soared 146.7% to Rs 73.31 crore on 141% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 804.92 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NetwebTechnologiesIndiaLtd_73333970_78854.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>