<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:05:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HMA Agro Industries Ltd Spikes 2.49%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hma-agro-industries-ltd-spikes-249/1665760</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665760</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HMA Agro Industries Ltd rose 2.49% today to trade at Rs 27.54.

HMA Agro Industries Ltd rose 2.49% today to trade at Rs 27.54. The BSE Fast Moving Consumer Goods index is up 0.17% to quote at 19177.7. The index is down 4.59 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Ugar Sugar Works Ltd increased 2.41% and Godrej Consumer Products Ltd added 1.54% on the day. The BSE Fast Moving Consumer Goods index went down 5.62 % over last one year compared to the 7.96% surge in benchmark SENSEX. HMA Agro Industries Ltd has lost 5.49% over last one month compared to 4.59% fall in BSE Fast Moving Consumer Goods index and 2.03% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 10 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 9213 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 40 on 01 Feb 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 26.5 on 19 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HMA-Agro-Industries-Ltd_63858437_76650.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oberoi Realty Ltd Falls 5.18%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oberoi-realty-ltd-falls-518/1665761</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665761</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oberoi Realty Ltd lost 5.18% today to trade at Rs 1566.3.

Oberoi Realty Ltd lost 5.18% today to trade at Rs 1566.3. The BSE Realty index is down 0.49% to quote at 6487.11. The index is down 5.57 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Sobha Ltd decreased 1.91% and Prestige Estates Projects Ltd lost 1.33% on the day. The BSE Realty index went down 12.8 % over last one year compared to the 7.96% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Oberoi Realty Ltd has lost 6.48% over last one month compared to 5.57% fall in BSE Realty index and 2.03% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 3561 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 32459 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2023.7 on 21 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 1440.05 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OberoiRealty_76593607717_38025.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests red start for key indices; Trump's Greenland takeover bid sours sentiment]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-red-start-for-key-indices-trumps-greenland-takeover-bid-sours-sentiment/1665751</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665751</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 21.00 points, suggesting a red opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 21.00 points, suggesting a red opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,262.82 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 4,234.30 crore in the Indian equity market on 19 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 29,315.22 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asian stocks fell on Tuesday as a resurgence of trade-war concerns hit risk sentiment and sparked selling in U.S. assets. U.S. President Donald Trump's push to take control of Greenland by threatening additional tariffs - a move that risks fuelling trade tensions with Europe - has led to uncertainty in the markets with investors scurrying for safe-haven assets including the Swiss Franc and gold . The tensions have revived talk of the 'Sell America' trade that emerged in the aftermath of his sweeping "Liberation Day" levies last April, where investors sell U.S. stocks, dollar and Treasuries. That trade appeared to be gathering momentum in Asian hours on Tuesday. Trump's threats triggered a sharp pushback in Europe and his remarks have raised questions on the outlook of trade deals struck since then with Europe. All eyes will now be on Davos where Trump is expected to meet global business leaders on Wednesday, as the U.S. president's presence looms large over the annual gathering of the global elite in Switzerland. Meanwhile, Japan's Nikkei saw some selling as investors looked ahead to next month's election. Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi is seeking voter backing for increased spending, tax cuts and a new security strategy that is expected to accelerate a defence build-up. U.S. cash equity markets were closed on Monday for Martin Luther King Jr. Day. Domestic Market: Equity benchmarks closed lower on Monday as investor sentiment turned cautious amid renewed global trade tensions and disappointing earnings from index heavyweights. The Nifty slipping below the 25,600 mark, dragged by energy stocks. Traders were unsettled after US President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on eight European countries over their opposition to his Greenland bid, raising fears of an escalation in global trade wars and triggering volatility across global markets. Sentiment was further dented by uncertainty over the next US Federal Reserve chair after Trump signalled Kevin Hassett may continue in his current role, tempering expectations of aggressive rate cuts in 2026. Back home, persistent foreign institutional selling weighed on sentiment, with FIIs remaining net sellers for a ninth straight session. Market mood was further hit by weak December-quarter earnings. Wipro's subdued outlook for the March quarter added to the caution. ICICI Bank also came under pressure after reporting higher-than-expected provisions for bad loans. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 324.17 points or 0.39% to 83,246.18. The Nifty 50 index declined 108.85 points or 0.42% to 25,585.50.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Info Edge (India) arm Jeevansathi to invest Rs 10-cr in dating platform operator]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/info-edge-india-arm-jeevansathi-to-invest-rs-10-cr-in-dating-platform-operator/1665750</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665750</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company already holds 100% stake in Aisle, through Jeevansathi, which is a wholly owned subsidiary of Info Edge.

The company already holds 100% stake in Aisle, through Jeevansathi, which is a wholly owned subsidiary of Info Edge. Accordingly, Aisle Network is a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of the company. Aisle Network is engaged in the business of running multiple dating platforms on the web via its mobile apps Aisle, Anbe, Arike, Neetho and Jalebi. These platforms allow users to browse through profiles of other users with the intent of finding their suitable partner. Its turnover was Rs 39.62 crore as on 31st March 2025. This investment is being done to meet the working capital requirements of Aisle. The board of directors of Jeevansathi has approved the acquisition of 10,00,000 compulsorily convertible debentures (CCDs) of 0.0001% each, having a face value of Rs 100 per debenture. Post this investment, Aisle remains the step down wholly-owned subsidiary of the company. The said investment will be executed within 30 days from the approval. Info Edge (India) is India's premier online classifieds company in recruitment, matrimony, real estate, education and related services. The company’s consolidaated net profit soared 1,260.81% to Rs 316.39 crore on 14.92% increase in net sales to Rs 805.45 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter fell 0.94% to settle at Rs 1,316.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InfoEdgIndia_32670259917_18844.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: LTIMindtree, Havells, Tata Capital, Oberoi Realty, CEAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-ltimindtree-havells-tata-capital-oberoi-realty-ceat/1665749</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665749</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 20 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 20 January 2026. Result Today: AU Small Finance Bank, Canara Robeco Asset Management Company, CreditAccess Grameen, Cyient DLM, DCM Shriram, Gujarat Gas, IndiaMART InterMESH, ITC Hotels, Jammu & Kashmir Bank, Mastek, Newgen Software Technologies, Persistent Systems, PTC India Financial Services, Rallis India, Shoppers Stop, Supreme Petrochem, SRF, United Spirits, Vardhman Special Steels will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: LTIMindtree has reported 30.7% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 971 crore on 3.7% increase in revenue to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY26. Havells India has reported 8.1% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 301 crore on a 14.3% increase in total revenue to Rs 5,588 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Capital reported 20.4% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,265 crore on a 12.2% increase in total income to Rs 7,979 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Oberoi Realty reported a 0.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 623 crore despite a 5.8% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1,493 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. CEAT reported a 60.4% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 156 crore on 26% increase in revenue to Rs 4,157 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bansal Wire Industries has reported a 3.8% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 43.3 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 41.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased by 11.29% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,029 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>