<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:55:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests red opening for equities; US market rises for fourth consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-red-opening-for-equities-us-market-rises-for-fourth-consecutive-session/1661749</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661749</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 43.00 points, indicating a red opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 43.00 points, indicating a red opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,794.80 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,812.37 crore in the Indian equity market on 23 December 2025, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 22,109.51 crore so far in December. This follows their cash sales of Rs 17,500.31 crore in November and Rs 2,346.89 crore in October. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Wednesday, with several indexes set to close early in lieu of the Christmas Eve holiday. Media reports from Japan said that the country was set to issue about 29.6 trillion yen (about $190 billion) in new government bonds to fund its fiscal 2026 budget. The South Korean won strengthened against the greenback after media reports stated that South Korea’s national pension fund was carrying out strategic foreign exchange hedging activities. Spot gold prices hit another record Wednesday, crossing $4,500 per ounce for the first time, driven by a weaker dollar, geopolitical tensions and U.S. Federal Reserve rate-cut expectations. Gold has notched a series of all-time highs this year, soaring over 70% year to date. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose for a fourth straight session as artificial intelligence names continued to outperform during a holiday-shortened week. The S&P 500 added 0.46%, closing at a record level of 6,909.79. The broad market index is now just below its intraday all-time high of 6,920.34. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.57% to end at 23,561.84. Gains in tech giants such as Nvidia and Broadcom lifted the index. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 79.73 points, or 0.16%, and settled at 48,442.41. Domestic Market: Benchmark equity indices ended Tuesday’s session largely flat as volatility persisted around the weekly expiry of Nifty futures. The market opened lower and hovered around the flat line for most of the session. Mild selling pressure emerged toward the close, though the Nifty still managed to eke out marginal gains. Metal and chemical shares were in demand while IT, PSU banks and healthcare stocks witnessed selling. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. Sentiment found support from a firmer rupee and improving global cues. Expectations of interest-rate cuts by the U.S. Federal Reserve early next year also helped steady investor confidence. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 42.64 points or 0.05% to 85,524.84. The Nifty 50 index rose 4.75 points or 0.02% to 26,177.15.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: GAIL (India), Vikran Engg, Adani Ports, Coal India, RVNL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-gail-india-vikran-engg-adani-ports-coal-india-rvnl/1661747</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661747</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 24 December 2025.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 24 December 2025. Stocks To Watch: GAIL (India) has signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Government of Chhattisgarh for development of a greenfield gas-based fertilizer project in Chhattisgarh. Vikran Engineering received a Rs 2035 crore order from Onix Renewables for EPC works for solar plant development. Adani Ports & Special Economic Zone successfully completed the acquisition of 100% interest in North Queensland Export Terminal (NQXT), Australia pursuant to completion of all condition precedents, with the acquisition of NQXT, APSEZ is on track to achieve 1 Billion tonne of cargo volume by 2030. Emcure Pharmaceuticals has received establishment inspection report (EIR). The US FDA has classified the inspection of the facility as no action indicated (NAI). Inspection was conducted from 6 October to 10 October 2025. Coal India’s board approved for listing of arm Mahanadi Coalfields in the upcoming financial year. Ajanta Pharma has entered into an in-licensing agreement with Biocon for marketing Semaglutide, a GLP-1 receptor agonist. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) board approved the appointment of Saleem Ahmad as chairman & managing director with effect from 23 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITCONS E-Solutions bags Rs 2-cr contract from Directorate of Enforcement]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itcons-e-solutions-bags-rs-2-cr-contract-from-directorate-of-enforcement/1661744</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661744</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the total contract value stands at Rs 1,59,69,854.79 for the deployment of 38 resources under manpower outsourcing services.

In an exchange filing, the company said the total contract value stands at Rs 1,59,69,854.79 for the deployment of 38 resources under manpower outsourcing services. The contract is scheduled to commence on 1 January 2026 and will remain valid until 31 December 2026, unless extended by mutual consent. The company described the order as a significant milestone, highlighting the continued trust placed in it by government agencies. ITCONS E-Solutions also clarified that neither its promoters nor members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding authority. It added that the transaction does not fall under the category of related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. ITCONS E-Solutions is engaged in the business of recruitment and staffing services. On a full-year basis, the company’s net profit surged 70.2% to Rs 3.25 crore on a 96.4% soar in net sales to Rs 55.98 crore in FY25 over FY24. The counter slipped 1.12% to Rs 438.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITCONSESolutionsLtd_70007426_78414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>