<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:39:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EID Parry rises after Q3 PAT jumps 5% YoY to Rs 437 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eid-parry-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-5-yoy-to-rs-437-cr/1676643</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676643</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) rose 1.1% YoY to Rs 587.93 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) rose 1.1% YoY to Rs 587.93 crore during the quarter. Earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 were Rs. 895 Crore, as compared to the Rs. 811 Crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. On the segmental front, the company’s revenue from the sugar business stood at Rs 1,103.22 crore (down 14.98% YoY), distillery came in at Rs 289.05 crore (down 0.17% YoY), consumer products stood at Rs 143.03 crore (down 39.46%), crop protection was at Rs 1,098.29 crore (up 72.78% YoY), and nutrient and allied business was at Rs 7,761.77 crore (up 21.9% YoY) during the period under review. On the other hand, the firm’s income from nutraceuticals was at Rs 61.91 crore (up 44.25% YoY), and revenue from cogeneration stood at Rs 36.59 crore (down 10.36% YoY) in Q3 FY26. Segment-wise, the farm inputs division continued to lead performance, recording a profit before interest and tax (PBIT) of Rs 741 crore for the quarter, up 3.35% from Rs 717 crore a year ago. Consolidated sugar operations, including refinery business, reported a loss before interest and tax of Rs 30 crore for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 as compared to a loss of Rs 59 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. The consolidated nutraceuticals division reported a loss before interest and tax of Rs 2 crore for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 as compared to Rs 5 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. EID Parry (India) is engaged in sugar, nutraceuticals, and ethanol production. It also has a significant presence in the farm inputs business, including biopesticides, through its subsidiary, Coromandel International. Shares of EID Parry (India) rose 0.95% to Rs 990.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EIDParry_79775166468_148.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SpiceJet Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/spicejet-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1676637</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676637</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd and Cohance Lifesciences Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026.

Muthoot Finance Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd and Cohance Lifesciences Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026. SpiceJet Ltd lost 14.85% to Rs 17.38 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 330.6 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 85.37 lakh shares in the past one month. Muthoot Finance Ltd tumbled 11.52% to Rs 3600.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.52 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 27471 shares in the past one month. Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd crashed 10.00% to Rs 397.45. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 40861 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18388 shares in the past one month. Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd corrected 9.74% to Rs 1615.8. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 63045 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21552 shares in the past one month. Cohance Lifesciences Ltd pared 9.16% to Rs 318.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.35 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 30582 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SpiceJet_3698663034_3367.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineers India rallies after Q3 PAT soars 219.30% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/engineers-india-rallies-after-q3-pat-soars-21930-yoy/1676640</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676640</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net sales rose 58.29% YoY to Rs 1,210.24 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 764.59 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net sales rose 58.29% YoY to Rs 1,210.24 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 764.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, revenue increased 31.36% from Rs 921.29 crore in Q2 FY26. Net profit surged 219.30% YoY to Rs 347.17 crore, up from Rs 108.73 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PAT jumped 315.82% from Rs 83.49 crore. Profit before tax climbed 218.37% YoY to Rs 400.60 crore, compared with Rs 125.83 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, PBT rose 174.52% from Rs 145.93 crore. Total expenditure increased 28.70% YoY to Rs 858.02 crore, while rising 7.05% sequentially. Development and construction costs declined 29.30% YoY to Rs 77.87 crore, while employee expenses rose 10.97% YoY to Rs 282.24 crore. Interest costs declined 6.25% YoY to Rs 0.60 crore, and depreciation increased 7.68% YoY to Rs 10.23 crore. Segment-wise, revenue from the consultancy and engineering projects segment stood at Rs 490.14 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 16.36% YoY increase from Rs 421.22 crore in the year-ago period. The turnkey projects segment reported revenue of Rs 720.10 crore, registering a sharp 109.73% YoY jump from Rs 343.37 crore in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, the company secured contracts worth over $350 million from Nigeria’s Dangote Group for the expansion of a mega refinery project, strengthening its international order book and execution pipeline. Engineers India, a Navratna public sector enterprise, is an engineering consultancy and EPC company. As on December 2025, Government of India held 51.32% stake in the company.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EngineersIndia_47008482189_12029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dilip Buildcon bags Rs 124 crore pipeline authorisation from PNGRB]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dilip-buildcon-bags-rs-124-crore-pipeline-authorisation-from-pngrb/1676635</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676635</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves setting up a Petroleum or Petroleum Product (Air Turbine Fuel/ATF) pipeline from Navgam, Gujarat to Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel International Airport, Gujarat.

The project involves setting up a Petroleum or Petroleum Product (Air Turbine Fuel/ATF) pipeline from Navgam, Gujarat to Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel International Airport, Gujarat. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is valued at Rs 124 crore (excluding GST) and will be executed over a period of 25 years. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity and the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Dilip Buildcon is presently in the business of development of infrastructure facilities on an Engineering Procurement and Construction basis (EPC) and undertakes contracts from various government and other parties and special purpose vehicles promoted by the company. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 22.8% to Rs 181.49 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 235.24 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations fell 22.9% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1925.89 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Dilip Buildcon tanked 3.82% to Rs 435.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DilipBuildconLtd_92563827065_36662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Regency Ceramics Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/regency-ceramics-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1676634</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676634</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sharika Enterprises Ltd, Ruchira Papers Ltd, Genesys International Corporation Ltd and Tokyo Plast International Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026.

Sharika Enterprises Ltd, Ruchira Papers Ltd, Genesys International Corporation Ltd and Tokyo Plast International Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026. Regency Ceramics Ltd crashed 13.26% to Rs 41.2 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 817 shares in the past one month. Sharika Enterprises Ltd lost 11.24% to Rs 12. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 45606 shares in the past one month. Ruchira Papers Ltd tumbled 11.08% to Rs 112. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9779 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2959 shares in the past one month. Genesys International Corporation Ltd slipped 10.72% to Rs 302.45. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.62 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62952 shares in the past one month. Tokyo Plast International Ltd shed 10.45% to Rs 98.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 547 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RegencyCeramics_1874361855_831.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks drop over 1%; FMCG shares under pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-drop-over-1-fmcg-shares-under-pressure/1676632</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676632</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with sharp losses in the early afternoon trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with sharp losses in the early afternoon trade. Sentiment remained cautious following the introduction of new AI model by Anthropic, the development intensified concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models. Traders remained cautious, shifting toward a risk-off stance. The Nifty traded near 25,500 level. FMCG shares tumbled for second consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 964.01 points or 1.15% to 82,710.941. The Nifty 50 index tanked 306.45 points or 1.18% to 25,501.60. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 1.32% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 1.20%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,294 shares rose and 2,828 shares fell. A total of 164 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nfity FMCG index fell 1.55% to 51,080.25. The index fell 2.06% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Unilever (down 3.6%), Patanjali Foods (down 1.77%), Radico Khaitan (down 1.67%), Nestle India (down 1.65%), Britannia Industries (down 1.53%), Varun Beverages (down 1.5%), Tata Consumer Products (down 1.16%), Marico (down 1.08%), Godrej Consumer Products (down 0.97%) and United Spirits (down 0.88%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.03% to 6.688 compared with previous session close of 6.686. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7150 compared with its close of 90.6100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.67% to Rs 158,050. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 96.96. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.113. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement shed 10 cents or 0.15% to $67.42 a barrel.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Engineers India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-engineers-india-ltd-counter/1676631</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676631</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Honasa Consumer Ltd, Muthoot Finance Ltd, Birlasoft Ltd, Cohance Lifesciences Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 13 February 2026.

Honasa Consumer Ltd, Muthoot Finance Ltd, Birlasoft Ltd, Cohance Lifesciences Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 13 February 2026. Engineers India Ltd notched up volume of 965.14 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 50.27 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 19.20 lakh shares. The stock rose 14.98% to Rs.207.99. Volumes stood at 16.04 lakh shares in the last session. Honasa Consumer Ltd witnessed volume of 191.32 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 35.22 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5.43 lakh shares. The stock increased 2.59% to Rs.307.00. Volumes stood at 19.79 lakh shares in the last session. Muthoot Finance Ltd clocked volume of 52.96 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.32 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 8.39 lakh shares. The stock lost 11.06% to Rs.3,617.30. Volumes stood at 9.19 lakh shares in the last session. Birlasoft Ltd saw volume of 101.5 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.33 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 19.03 lakh shares. The stock dropped 6.32% to Rs.406.45. Volumes stood at 28.79 lakh shares in the last session. Cohance Lifesciences Ltd witnessed volume of 32.14 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.27 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.10 lakh shares. The stock dropped 8.88% to Rs.319.60. Volumes stood at 7.51 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EngineersIndia_47008482189_12029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty decline; European mrkt advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-decline-european-mrkt-advance/1676607</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676607</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in afternoon trade, mirroring weak global cues amid newly introduced Anthropic AI model, raising concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in afternoon trade, mirroring weak global cues amid newly introduced Anthropic AI model, raising concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models. Sentiment remained cautious and shifting towards risk-off stance. The Nifty traded below the 25,550 mark. Barring media index all the sectoral indices on the NSE were traded in red with metal, IT and realty shares leading the fall. At 13:25 PM ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 813.20 points or 0.97% to 82,850.87. The Nifty 50 index tanked 263.45 points or 1.02% to 25,542.90. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 1.20% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.99%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,293 shares rose and 2,737 shares fell. A total of 178 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Bajaj Finance (up 2.02%), Eicher Motors (up 1.49%), Apollo Hospitals Enterprise(up 0.46%), Tech Mahindra (up 0.46%) and Larsen & Tourbo (up 0.29%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Hindalco Industries (down 5.17%), Hindustan Unilever (down 3.57%), Eternal (down 3.04%), Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) (down 2.62%) and Adani Enterprises (down 2.58%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Honasa Consumer gained 3.64% after reporting a strong operational and financial performance for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a reported basis, consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% YoY from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit after tax stood at Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, up 92.9% YoY from Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY25. Indian Hotels Company declined 1.10%. The company consolidated net profit jumped 55.10% to Rs 903.23 crore on 12.91% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,841.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. NIBE tumbled 5.95% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 18.87 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 1.94 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 60.3% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 59.08 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Lupin shed 0.16%. The company reported 37.46% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,175.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 855.16 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) declined 2.62%. The company reported 1.60% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 8,371.85 crore in Q3 FY2, compared with Rs 8,239.92 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations declined 6.43% YoY to Rs 31,546.51 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: European market advanced as investors awaited U.S. inflation data, due later today. The Asia-Pacific market declined Friday, tracking Wall Street declines, as fears over artificial intelligence disruption drove the S&P 500 to a third straight day of losses. Certain pockets of the U.S. stock market have been hit this year by the release of AI tools that threaten to automate tasks performed by some companies—or at least risk eating into their profit margins. Overnight on Wall Street, US stocks fell sharply Thursday as the market punished companies seen as potential losers from artificial-intelligence technology. The S&P 500 fell 108.71 points to 6,832.76. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 669.42 to 49,451.98, and the Nasdaq Composite sank 469.32 to 22,597.15.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coal India Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coal-india-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1676604</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676604</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Coal India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Coal India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 409.15, down 2.39% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25585.15. The Sensex is at 82937.29, down 0.88%.Coal India Ltd has eased around 5.33% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Coal India Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 3.68% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36452.65, down 1.52% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 49.09 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 89.83 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 404.85, down 2.08% on the day. Coal India Ltd jumped 15.51% in last one year as compared to a 11.58% rally in NIFTY and a 17.42% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 12.15 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoalIndia_84226386779_12019.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITC Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itc-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1676605</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676605</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITC Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

ITC Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 315.4, down 0.65% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25585.15. The Sensex is at 82937.29, down 0.88%.ITC Ltd has eased around 5.78% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which ITC Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.11% in last one month and is currently quoting at 51885.75, down 1.41% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 50.62 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 250.88 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 315.45, down 0.9% on the day. ITC Ltd tumbled 23.12% in last one year as compared to a 11.58% rally in NIFTY and a 3.73% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 19.71 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITC_29088800077_301.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Finance Ltd soars 1.1%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-finance-ltd-soars-11-gains-for-third-straight-session/1676598</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676598</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bajaj Finance Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Bajaj Finance Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 1010.1, up 1.1% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.91% on the day, quoting at 25571.6. The Sensex is at 82902.27, down 0.92%. Bajaj Finance Ltd has added around 6.78% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Bajaj Finance Ltd is a constituent, has added around 2.36% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28385.2, down 0.83% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 95.11 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 85.58 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1012.15, up 1.03% on the day. Bajaj Finance Ltd is up 20.36% in last one year as compared to a 11.52% gain in NIFTY and a 21.4% gain in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 38.71 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajFin_55786316_3722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd spurts 1.96%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-forge-ltd-spurts-196-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1676595</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676595</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Bharat Forge Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1760.6, up 1.96% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25584. The Sensex is at 82991.58, down 0.82%. Bharat Forge Ltd has gained around 21.66% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bharat Forge Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.67% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28504.05, down 0.14% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 34.56 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 13.78 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1767.9, up 1.96% on the day. Bharat Forge Ltd is up 63.27% in last one year as compared to a 11.58% jump in NIFTY and a 28.97% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 60.86 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatForge_36016338711_69.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd soars 1.81%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eicher-motors-ltd-soars-181-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1676596</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676596</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eicher Motors Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Eicher Motors Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 8087, up 1.81% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25584. The Sensex is at 82991.58, down 0.82%. Eicher Motors Ltd has risen around 9.91% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Eicher Motors Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 2.67% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28504.05, down 0.14% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.13 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.46 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 8103, up 2.07% on the day. Eicher Motors Ltd is up 71.94% in last one year as compared to a 11.58% spurt in NIFTY and a 28.97% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 43.82 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EicherMotors_60312767308_151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/samvardhana-motherson-international-ltd-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1676597</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676597</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 133.11, up 0.28% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25584. The Sensex is at 82991.58, down 0.82%. Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd has added around 17.23% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is a constituent, has added around 2.67% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28504.05, down 0.14% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 112.31 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 199.94 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 133.14, up 0.23% on the day. Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is up 58.2% in last one year as compared to a 11.58% gain in NIFTY and a 28.97% gain in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 71.26 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MothersonSumi_60777480057_2966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade in negative terrain; oil & gas shares slide for 2nd day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-in-negative-terrain-oil-gas-shares-slide-for-2nd-day/1676584</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676584</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices continued to trade with major losses in the early afternoon trade.

The domestic equity indices continued to trade with major losses in the early afternoon trade. Sentiment remained cautious following the introduction of new AI model by Anthropic, the development intensified concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models. Traders remained cautious, shifting toward a risk-off stance. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. Oil& gas shares declined for second consecutive trading session. At 12:25 PM ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 684.33 points or 0.83% to 82,984.27. The Nifty 50 index tanked 219 points or 0.86% to 25,587.40. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 1.01% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.88%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,223 shares rose and 2,732 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 6.67% to 12.51. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures were trading at 25,628.30, at a premium of 40.9 points as compared with the spot at 25,587.40. The Nifty option chain for the 24 February 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 68.6 lakh contracts at the 26,000 strike price. Maximum put OI of 58.2 lakh contracts was seen at the 25,500 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil& Gas index fell 1.56% to 12,015. The index rose 2.76% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Mahanagar Gas (down 3.62%), Oil India (down 3.51%), Adani Total Gas (down 3.02%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 2.84%) and Petronet LNG (down 2.24%) were the top losers. Among the other losers were Reliance Industries (down 1.88%), Indraprastha Gas (down 1.38%), Aegis Logistics (down 1.15%), GAIL (India) (down 1.03%) and Indian Oil Corporation (down 0.68%) declined.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Biopol Chemicals enters the market lab, but momentum evaporates]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-biopol-chemicals-enters-the-market-lab-but-momentum-evaporates/1676564</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676564</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 111, a premium of 2.78% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 111, a premium of 2.78% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its lower limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 111 and a low of Rs 105.45. About 18.59 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Biopol Chemicals' IPO was subscribed 21.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 6 February 2026 and it closed on 10 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was set between Rs 102 to Rs 108 per equity share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 28,94,400 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 65.81% from 89.88% pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for acquisition of industrial land, repayment or prepayment, in full or in part, of borrowings availed by company from banks, financial institutions and non-banking financial companies and for general corporate purposes. Biopol Chemicals is a B2B manufacturer and distributor of specialty chemicals with a portfolio of 66 products across silicones, emulsifiers, biochemicals and polyelectrolytes, serving industries such as textiles, home care, agriculture and industrial chemicals. The company operates four establishments across Gujarat and West Bengal, including a manufacturing facility with an installed capacity of 18,25,000 litres per annum. Its product range includes textile auxiliaries, silicone fluids, emulsifiers, agricultural adjuvants and specialty industrial chemicals, designed to meet sector-specific performance and application requirements. As of 31 December 2025, the company had a total of 24 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 48.97 crore and net profit of Rs 6 crore for the period ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BIOPOLCHEMICALSLIMITED_52903502_95994.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Power India Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-power-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1676562</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676562</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kalyani Forge Ltd, Delphi World Money Ltd, Chamanlal Setia Exports Ltd and Anmol India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026.

Kalyani Forge Ltd, Delphi World Money Ltd, Chamanlal Setia Exports Ltd and Anmol India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026. GE Power India Ltd soared 18.26% to Rs 473 at 13-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 19.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18829 shares in the past one month. Kalyani Forge Ltd spiked 14.34% to Rs 698.6. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 491 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 173 shares in the past one month. Delphi World Money Ltd surged 13.26% to Rs 17.25. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11869 shares in the past one month. Chamanlal Setia Exports Ltd gained 12.50% to Rs 309.2. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.96 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2097 shares in the past one month. Anmol India Ltd exploded 11.97% to Rs 13.47. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 46404 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4404 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GEPower_62970729410_20944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME PAN HR Solution makes a quiet debut, treads water at issue price]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-pan-hr-solution-makes-a-quiet-debut-treads-water-at-issue-price/1676561</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676561</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 78.35, a 0.45% premium to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 78.35, a 0.45% premium to the issue price. The stock was currently down 0.45% to the listing price. The stock touched a high of Rs 80 and a low of Rs 78, with around 6.32 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. PAN HR Solutions' IPO was subscribed 9.51 times. The issue opened for bidding on 6 February 2026 and it closed on 10 February 2025. The price band of the IPO was between Rs 74 to Rs 78 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 18,00,000 equity shares and offer for sale (OFS) of 3,84,000 equity shares by existing shareholders. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for funding for working capital requirements and for general corporate purpose. Ahead of the IPO, PAN HR Solutions on 5 February 2026, raised Rs 4.19 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 5.37 lakh shares at Rs 78 per share to 3 anchor investor. PAN HR Solutions is a B2B service provider offering end-to-end human resource and workforce management solutions across industries. The company provides services spanning manpower recruitment, staffing, payroll processing, facility management, compliance audits and e-commerce logistics support, catering to unskilled, semi-skilled and skilled blue-collar workforce requirements. Positioned as a one-stop HR solutions provider, it manages the entire employee lifecycle from hiring and onboarding to payroll administration and statutory compliance, including EPF, ESIC and professional tax regulations, while also delivering housekeeping, office support and delivery staffing services along with independent compliance audits. As of 30 November 2026, the company had 10,374 employees at different client locations. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 153.98 crore and net profit of Rs 5.13 crore for the period ended 30 November 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PANHRSOLUTIONLIMITED_43086913_95963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineers India Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/engineers-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1676548</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676548</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd and Goldiam International Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026.

TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd and Goldiam International Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026. Engineers India Ltd soared 14.49% to Rs 207 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 39.5 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.78 lakh shares in the past one month. TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd spiked 5.73% to Rs 132.71. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 6.81 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.5 lakh shares in the past one month. SignatureGlobal India Ltd surged 5.64% to Rs 1037.5. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 66050 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 51494 shares in the past one month. Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd exploded 3.79% to Rs 1387. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.78 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35887 shares in the past one month. Goldiam International Ltd rose 3.52% to Rs 397.2. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 36094 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 95991 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EngineersIndia_47008482189_12029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Honasa Consumer rises after Q3 PAT climbs 93% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/honasa-consumer-rises-after-q3-pat-climbs-93-yoy/1676549</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676549</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a reported basis, consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% YoY from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a reported basis, consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% YoY from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. On a like-for-like basis, revenue came in at Rs 630 crore, marking the company’s highest-ever quarterly revenue and reflecting 21.7% YoY growth. Gross profit rose 13.9% YoY to Rs 412 crore, although gross margin moderated to 68.5% from 70.0% in the year-ago period. Profit after tax stood at Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, up 92.9% YoY from Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY25. PAT margin improved to 8.3% from 5.0%. Before exceptional items, PAT was reported at Rs 55 crore, nearly doubling year-on-year. Profit before tax increased 128% YoY to Rs 67 crore, while PBT margin expanded to 11.2% from 5.7%. EBITDA surged 150.7% YoY to Rs 66 crore from Rs 26 crore, with EBITDA margin expanding sharply to 10.9% from 5.0% in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses rose to Rs 71 crore, accounting for 11.8% of revenue, compared with 10.0% in the year-ago quarter. Advertisement expenses stood at Rs 186 crore, representing 30.9% of revenue, lower than 34.3% in Q3 FY25. Underlying Volume Growth (UVG) for the quarter stood at 30.2%, indicating steady consumer demand across core categories. Focus categories delivered over 25% growth, while flagship brand Mamaearth returned to double-digit growth, driven by product re-innovation and sharper investments. Younger brands recorded over 25% growth, and The Derma Co. maintained a double-digit EBITDA profile while scaling efficiently. Offline execution improved with direct outlet coverage crossing 1 lakh outlets, and total distribution expanding over 25% YoY to 2.7 lakh outlets, with a strong focus on the top 100 towns. Management highlighted continued investment in product re-innovation, with offerings such as Mamaearth Rice Face Wash and BBlunt Intense Moisture Shampoo performing strongly against leading national and international competitors. The company reiterated its focus on strengthening margins, improving capital efficiency and building a structurally stronger business for sustainable long-term growth. Honasa Consumer is India's largest digital-first beauty and personal care company, with a diverse portfolio of eight brands.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HonasaConsumerLtd_60997811_77264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>