<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T Finance records 18% YoY increase in Q3 PAT; total book size rises to Rs 1.14 lakh crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-finance-records-18-yoy-increase-in-q3-pat-total-book-size-rises-to-rs-114-lakh-crore/1665446</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665446</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income jumped 18% to Rs 2,407 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,041 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net interest income jumped 18% to Rs 2,407 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,041 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating expense for the period under review was Rs 1,135 crore, up 7% YoY. Earnings before credit cost rose by 25% YoY to Rs 1,785 crore in the third quarter of FY26. Credit cost added up to Rs 792 crore in Q3 FY26, up 32% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 at Rs 993 crore, up by 20% from Rs 825 crore in Q3 FY25. For Q3 FY26, retailisation stood at 98% of overall book. Retail book as on 31 December 2025 stood at Rs 1,11,990 crore, up 21% YoY. Total book size was at Rs 1,14,285 crore as on 31 December 2025, up 20% YoY. Gross Stage-3 (GS3) improved sequentially by 10 basis points to 3.19% and Net Stage-3 (NS3) by 8 basis points to 0.92% in Q3 FY26. Return on assets (RoA) stood at 2.31% in Q3 FY26 as against 2.27% in Q3 FY25. RoE after exceptional items was at 11.07% in Q3 FY26 as against 10.21% in Q3 FY25. Consolidated CRAR ratio as on 31 December 2025 stood at 19.10%. Sudipta Roy, managing director & CEO, LTF, said: "Q3 FY26 for the financial services sector has been defined by a powerful convergence of favourable macro-tailwinds. The implementation of GST 2.0, good monsoons, and a series of repo rate cuts have seen a surge in consumption and created an environment for growth. In Q3FY26, LTF’s focus remained on delivering a standout performance across business segments. We registered the highest ever quarterly disbursements of Rs. 22,701 crore, up 49% YoY, and the retail portfolio reaching Rs.1,11,990 crore, reflecting a growth of 21% YoY leading to a PAT of Rs. 760 crore, up 21% YoY (without the impact of a one-time exceptional item). Our proprietary AI driven next-gen digital credit engine ‘Project Cyclops’ is now implemented in Personal Loans in addition to Two-wheeler, Farm Equipment, and SME Finance businesses. It will go live in Home Loans and LAP and Rural Group Loans and MFI businesses in FY27.” L&T Finance is a leading non-banking financial company (NBFC), offering a range of financial products and services. The scrip had added 0.19% to end at Rs 296.30 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LTFinanceLtd_36546723_41147.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quant Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quant-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1665445</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665445</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Quant Mutual Fund has announced that, Mr.

Quant Mutual Fund has announced that, Mr. Mahendra Kumar Jajoo (DIN: 06966229) has been appointed as Whole Time Director on the Board of quant Money Managers Limited (Asset Management Company to the Fund) with effect from January 14, 2026. Details of Mr. Mahendra Kumar Jajoo Age: 57 years Designation: Whole Time Director Qualification: B. Com, ACA, ACS, CFA (USA)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis MF Announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-mf-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1665440</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665440</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the IDCW option of following schemes.

Axis Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the IDCW option of following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Axis Midcap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 3.39 Axis Midcap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.50 Axis Small Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 3.68 Axis Small Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.33 Axis Large & Mid Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.48 Axis Large & Mid Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.88 Axis ELSS Tax Saver Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 2.10 Axis ELSS Tax Saver Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.50 Axis Focused Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.58 Axis Focused Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 2.83 Axis Large Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.38 Axis Large Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.97 Axis Value Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.43 Axis Value Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.52

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Reliance Inds clocks PAT of Rs 22,290 crore in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/reliance-inds-clocks-pat-of-rs-22290-crore-in-q3-fy26/1665438</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665438</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) for the period under review was Rs 29,697 crore, up 3.7% YoY.

Profit before tax (PBT) for the period under review was Rs 29,697 crore, up 3.7% YoY. EBITDA improved by 6.1% to Rs 50,932 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 48,003 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin was 17.3% in Q3 FY26 as against 18% in Q3 FY25, down 70 basis points YoY. Finance costs increased by 7% YoY to Rs 6,613 crore ($ 736 million), largely due to operationalisation of 5G spectrum assets. Mukesh D. Ambani, chairman and managing director, Reliance Industries, said: “FY26 reflects consistent financial delivery and operational resilience across businesses. This quarter, Jio expanded its subscriber base further, through attractive propositions enabled by its comprehensive, indigenous technology stack tailored for Indian markets. The business delivered a robust financial performance with 16.4% growth in EBITDA. Our Retail business also had an eventful quarter, strengthening its portfolio with the onboarding of fresh new brands and product ranges. The demerger of consumer products business came into effect this quarter. Robust growth in O2C business was led by significantly higher fuel margins with favorable demand-supply dynamics, along with operational flexibility. I am happy to highlight the strong growth in our fuel retailing business, with continuing expansion of the Jio-bp network. Upstream segment EBITDA was impacted by lower volumes and prices. Reliance is entering a new phase of value creation with its initiatives in the AI and New Energy domains. I am confident that Reliance will play a pioneering role in the evolution of these epoch-defining technologies, providing sustainable solutions at scale for India and the world.” Jio Platforms Limited (JPL): JPL’s gross revenue increased by 12.7% to Rs 43,683 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 38,750 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 19,303 crore, higher by 16.4% as compared with the value of Rs 16,585 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. ARPU increased by 5.1% YoY to Rs 213.7 per subscriber per month with higher customer engagement, partly offset by promotional offers for unlimited 5G and fixed broadband services. Monthly churn was stable at 1.8%, with net subscriber addition of 8.9 million during the quarter. Reliance Retail Ventures Limited (RRVL): RRVL’s revenue was Rs 97,605 crore (up 8.1% YoY) while EBITDA from operations was Rs 6,770 crore (up 2.1% YoY) in Q3 FY26. The demerger of consumer products division was completed during the quarter. The business expanded its store network with 431 new store openings, taking the total store count to 19,979 with area under operation at 78.1 million square feet. JioMart crossed exit daily orders of 1.6 million and recorded 53% QoQ and over 360% YoY growth in average daily orders, establishing itself as the fastest-growing player in hyper-local commerce. Oil to Chemical (O2C) Segment: Revenue from O2C segment for 3Q FY26 rose by 8.4% YoY to Rs 162,095 crore ($18.0 billion). Production meant for sale increased by 1.7% on a YoY basis. Fuel retailing operations through Jio-bp expanded its network by 14% YoY to 2,125 outlets, driving volume growth of 24.7% for HSD and 20.8% for MS. Segment EBITDA for 3Q FY26 increased by 14.6% YoY to 16,507 crore ($ 1.8 billion) due to sharp increase in transportation fuel cracks and higher Sulphur realisation partially offset by weakness in downstream chemical margins and higher feedstock freight rates. Favorable ethane cracking economics and domestic market placements continued to support profitability. Reliance BP Mobility (RBML) (operating under brand Jio-bp) operated a country-wide network of 2,125 outlets as on 31 December 2025 as against 1,865 outlets as on 31 December 2024. Oil & Gas (Exploration and Production) Segment: Revenue for Q3 FY26 was Rs 5,833 crore, down 8.4% YoY. This was on account of lower volumes and price realisation for KGD6 gas and condensate. The average price realized for KGD6 gas was $9.65 per MMBTU in Q3 FY26 vis-à-vis $9.74 per MMBTU in Q3 FY25. The average price realised for CBM gas was $9.29 per MMBTU in Q3 FY26 vis-à-vis $10.58 MMBTU in Q3 FY25. JioStar Business: JioStar reported strong revenues of Rs 8,010 crore with EBITDA (including other income) of Rs 1,303 crore for 3Q FY26. Television network reached over 830 million viewers, delivering over 60 billion hours of watch time. JioHotstar averaged 450 million monthly active users (MAUs); up 13% QoQ and almost on par with the IPL quarter (Q1 FY26), clearly demonstrating the platform's momentum. The network's TV entertainment viewership share improved by 100 basis points YoY to 34.6%, further solidifying its position as a preferred entertainment destination. Reliance Industries is India's largest private sector company. Its activities span hydrocarbon exploration and production, petroleum refining and marketing, petrochemicals, advanced materials and composites, renewables (solar and hydrogen), retail and digital services. The scrip had shed 0.06% to end at Rs 1457.60 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RelianceInds_29114129325_476.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1665436</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665436</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the regular plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option and direct plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option of HDFC Arbitrage Fund.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the regular plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option and direct plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option of HDFC Arbitrage Fund. The amount of distribution (Rs per unit) will be: HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Regular Plan – Normal IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050 HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Direct Plan – Normal IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050 HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050 HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Seamec says vessel SEAMEC Agastya back on hire after technical redressal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/seamec-says-vessel-seamec-agastya-back-on-hire-after-technical-redressal/1665369</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665369</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said the vessel resumed deployment after completion of technical redressal.

In a regulatory filing, the company said the vessel resumed deployment after completion of technical redressal. SEAMEC Agastya was rehired with effect from 16 January 2026. Seamec provides offshore support services. It undertakes support services through Diving Support Vessels (DSVs). These vessels are owned and operated by Seamec. The company's subsidiary companies owns and operates bulk carriers. On a consolidated basis, Seamec reported net loss of Rs 27.48 crore in Q2 September 2025 as against net profit of Rs 0.11 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales rose 10.87% YoY to Rs 97.42 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SEAMECLtd_17171034074_4760.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>