<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:53:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kothari Products Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kothari-products-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678225</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678225</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd, Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd, Bharat Seats Ltd and Unicommerce eSolutions Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 17 February 2026.

Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd, Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd, Bharat Seats Ltd and Unicommerce eSolutions Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 17 February 2026. Kothari Products Ltd soared 19.99% to Rs 71.55 at 11:52 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 4533 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 760 shares in the past one month. Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd surged 17.16% to Rs 66.9. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 121 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 740 shares in the past one month. Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd spiked 16.71% to Rs 19.91. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 15.31 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.43 lakh shares in the past one month. Bharat Seats Ltd spurt 16.43% to Rs 227.85. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 6.94 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17869 shares in the past one month. Unicommerce eSolutions Ltd advanced 15.02% to Rs 113.7. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.87 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15903 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KothariProducts_4701046090_4936.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Torrent Power rises for fourth day; gains nearly 14% in six months]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/torrent-power-rises-for-fourth-day-gains-nearly-14-in-six-months/1678224</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678224</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip has gained 4.02% in four sessions, from its recent closing low of Rs 1,428.60 recorded on 11 February 2026.

The scrip has gained 4.02% in four sessions, from its recent closing low of Rs 1,428.60 recorded on 11 February 2026. In the last six months, the stock has risen by 13.86% while the S&P BSE MidCap Index has lost 2.60% in the same period. On the technical front, the stock’s RSI (14) was currently at 63.582. An RSI reading of 70 or above indicates an overbought condition. A reading of 30 or below indicates an oversold condition. On the daily chart, the scrip is trading above its 10-day, 20-day and 100-day simple moving averages placed at 1446.26, 1387.68 and 1316.36, respectively. In a regulatory filing made during market hours today, Torrent Power said that it has entered into a definitive agreement with L&T Power Development (L&TPDL) to acquire 100% of equity stake and convertible instruments in Nabha Power (NPL) for an enterprise value of Rs 6,889 crore. NPL is a wholly owned subsidiary of LTPDL, which is a wholly owned subsidiary of Larsen & Toubro (L&T). The transaction is subject to requisite regulatory approvals and customary closing conditions. NPL is a fully contracted thermal power asset with revenue of Rs 4,866 crore and adjusted EBITDA of Rs 1,153 crore in FY 2025. The supercritical plant, built on advanced Japanese technology, maintains sustained availability levels above 90%. Strategically located in a power-deficit region, the plant also supports potential ancillary revenue streams. Furthermore, existing infrastructure allows for seamless expansion of capacity, supporting future growth opportunities. Upon completion of the acquisition, Torrent’s operational capacity will increase from 5 GW to 6.4 GW. Samir Mehta, chairman, said: “The acquisition marks Torrent’s entry into the high-growth power market of northern India. Upon completion, NPL will add a high-quality, best-in-class and well-established operating asset to our portfolio supported by fully contracted cash flows and a strong operational track record. The acquisition will be value accretive from day one, delivering a meaningful uplift in the overall revenues and profitability." Torrent Power is a leading integrated power utility company in India with a presence across the generation, transmission, and distribution of power. The company has reported 35.20% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 643.08 crore on a 4.28% rise in revenue to Rs 6,777.87 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TorrentPower_38030455678_18488.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Easy Trip Planners Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/easy-trip-planners-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1678218</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678218</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, Sterling & Wilson Renewable Energy Ltd, Praj Industries Ltd and Galaxy Surfactants Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 17 February 2026.

Newgen Software Technologies Ltd, Sterling & Wilson Renewable Energy Ltd, Praj Industries Ltd and Galaxy Surfactants Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 17 February 2026. Easy Trip Planners Ltd surged 18.69% to Rs 9.4 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 196.69 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17.8 lakh shares in the past one month. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd soared 10.24% to Rs 510.15. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 16.61 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.27 lakh shares in the past one month. Sterling & Wilson Renewable Energy Ltd spiked 9.35% to Rs 221.05. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.89 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.33 lakh shares in the past one month. Praj Industries Ltd exploded 7.90% to Rs 326.5. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.98 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.42 lakh shares in the past one month. Galaxy Surfactants Ltd gained 7.76% to Rs 2036.85. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1911 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 593 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EasyTripPlanners_83237855.6888425_74649.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Improving access to timely and adequate formal credit for MSMEs remains a key policy priority of the central bank, says RBI Governor]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/improving-access-to-timely-and-adequate-formal-credit-for-msmes-remains-a-key-policy-priority-of-the-central-bank-says-rbi-governor/1678217</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678217</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra on Monday underscored the pivotal role of the MSME sector in India’s economic landscape contributing significantly to GDP, exports and livelihoods.

RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra on Monday underscored the pivotal role of the MSME sector in India’s economic landscape contributing significantly to GDP, exports and livelihoods. The Governor emphasised that improving access to timely and adequate formal credit for MSMEs remains a key policy priority of the Reserve Bank. He also outlined several policy and regulatory measures undertaken for the sector by Government of India and Reserve Bank. He encouraged MSMEs to pursue formalisation, maintain credit discipline and adopt digital payments to build their long-term resilience and competitiveness.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 121 pts; PSU bank shares in demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-121-pts-psu-bank-shares-in-demand/1678216</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678216</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest gains in mid-morning trade after a negative opening, as investors focused on stock-specific moves amid thin trading across Asian markets.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest gains in mid-morning trade after a negative opening, as investors focused on stock-specific moves amid thin trading across Asian markets. The Nifty traded above the 25,650 mark. PSU bank shares extended gains for the second consecutive trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 120.61 points or 0.14% to 83,397.76. The Nifty 50 index rose 7.85 points or 0.03% to 25,690.60. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.11% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index added 0.57%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,327 shares rose and 1,467 shares fell. A total of 195 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s total exports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at US$ 80.45 billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17% vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at US$ 90.83 billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76% vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at US$ 720.76 billion registering a positive growth of 6.15%. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at US$ 823.41 billion registering a growth of 6.54%. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were US$ 36.56 billion as compared to US$ 36.34 billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were US$ 71.24 billion as compared to US$ 59.77 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is US$ 43.90 billion as compared to US$ 34.75 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is US$ 19.60 billion as compared to US$ 16.71 billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy & poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports increased by 10.37% from US$ 9.42 billion in January 2025 to US$ 10.40 billion in January 2026, while petroleum products exports increased by 8.55% from US$ 3.48 billion in January 2025 to US$ 3.77 billion in January 2026. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index rose 1.69% to 9,462. The index jumped 3.22% in the two convictive trading sessions. Punjab National Bank (up 3.43%), Union Bank of India (up 3.01%), UCO Bank (up 2.61%), Central Bank of India (up 2.5%), Indian Overseas Bank (up 2.34%), Bank of Maharashtra (up 2.3%), Punjab & Sind Bank (up 2.25%), Bank of India (up 2.23%), Bank of Baroda (up 2.03%) and Indian Bank (up 1.98%) jumped. Stocks in Spotlight: Cochin Shipyard advanced 4.27% after the state-run shipbuilder said it was declared the lowest bidder at a meeting held at the Ministry of Defence in New Delhi. TVS Supply Chain Solutions (TVS SCS) added 2.81% after the firm signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with ALA Group, to explore opportunities in India’s aerospace and defence supply chain. Lupin added 1.39% after the company announced that it has signed a licence and supply agreement with Spektus Pharma to commercialize the novel antidepressant DeslaFlex in Canada. Global Markets: Asian markets traded cautiously on Tuesday in holiday-thinned volumes, while oil prices edged higher ahead of U.S.–Iran nuclear negotiations scheduled to begin later in the day in Geneva. The Mainland Chinese, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan, and South Korean markets were closed on Tuesday for Lunar New Year holidays. U.S. markets were shut on Monday for Presidents’ Day. Japan’s weakening economy remained in focus on Tuesday, one day after much softer than expected GDP numbers. The country on Monday reported its economy grew an annualized 0.2% in the fourth quarter, far below the widely reported gain forecast of 1.6% as government spending dragged on activity. In today's session, the Japanese yen strengthened 0.15% against the greenback to 153.28 per dollar. The weak figures highlight the challenges ahead for Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and should support her push for more aggressive fiscal stimulus, media reports said. The Bank of Japan next meets on rates in March, with traders forecasting only a slim chance for a hike. Widely reported polls in the media suggest that investors expect the central bank to wait until July before tightening policy again. Meanwhile, oil saw some price gains as investors looked ahead to the U.S. and Iran nuclear negotiations that are scheduled to begin in Geneva later in the day. The higher volatility in crude was triggered by the latest drill that was reportedly held by Iran’s Revolutionary Guards in the Hormuz Strait on Monday. The passage accounts for about 20% of global oil shipments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JSW Infra to consider fund-raising proposal on 20 February]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jsw-infra-to-consider-fund-raising-proposal-on-20-february/1678214</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678214</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company stated that the proposed fundraising could be undertaken through one or more public or private placement offerings, including a qualified institutional placement (QIP), a rights issue, or any other permissible method, or a combination thereof, subject to necessary approvals.

The company stated that the proposed fundraising could be undertaken through one or more public or private placement offerings, including a qualified institutional placement (QIP), a rights issue, or any other permissible method, or a combination thereof, subject to necessary approvals. JSW Infrastructure, a part of JSW Group, is the second largest commercial port operator in India in terms of cargo handling capacity. It develops and operates ports and port terminals pursuant to port concessions. JSW Infrastructure rallied 6.13% to Rs 273.45 after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 8.71% to Rs 364.85 crore on 14.2% revenue from operations to Rs 1,349.66 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter shed 0.63% to Rs 260.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JSWInfrastructureLtd_46143694_42944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GoI announces the sale of three dated securities for a notified amount of &#8377;33,000 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/goi-announces-the-sale-of-three-dated-securities-for-a-notified-amount-of-837733000-crore/1678213</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678213</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.03% Government Security 2029” for a notified amount of ₹9,000 crore, “6.68% Government Security 2033” for a notified amount of ₹11,000 crore and “7.24% Government Security 2025” for a notified amount of ₹13,000 crore.

The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.03% Government Security 2029” for a notified amount of ₹9,000 crore, “6.68% Government Security 2033” for a notified amount of ₹11,000 crore and “7.24% Government Security 2025” for a notified amount of ₹13,000 crore. The auction will be conducted using multiple price method. Both competitive and non-competitive bids for the auction should be submitted in electronic format on the Reserve Bank of India Core Banking Solution (e-Kuber system) on February 20, 2026 (Friday). GoI will have the option to retain additional subscription up to ₹2,000 crore against each security.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Merchandise trade deficit widens to a three-month high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/merchandise-trade-deficit-widens-to-a-three-month-high/1678212</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678212</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s trade numbers for January 2026 reflected excellent performance in exports, with overall exports of merchandise and services hitting USD 80.45 billion, up 13.16 per cent from USD 71.09 billion in January 2025, even as imports rose faster.

India’s trade numbers for January 2026 reflected excellent performance in exports, with overall exports of merchandise and services hitting USD 80.45 billion, up 13.16 per cent from USD 71.09 billion in January 2025, even as imports rose faster. According to Commerce Ministry data, overall imports in January 2026 jumped 18.77 per cent year-on-year to USD 90.83 billion, compared with USD 76.48 billion a year earlier. This pushed the combined merchandise and services trade deficit to USD 10.38 billion from USD 5.39 billion. India’s merchandise trade deficit widened to a three-month high of $34.68 billion in January. The goods trade deficit was widened due to a sharp rise ‌in gold and silver imports, which pushed up total merchandise imports by ‌12% ⁠month-on-month to $71.24 billion, while exports slipped 5% to $36.56 billion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/globe-series-3-1425556_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BLS E-Services gains after board nod to acquire Atyati Tech ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bls-e-services-gains-after-board-nod-to-acquire-atyati-tech/1678208</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678208</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Atyati Technologies, founded in 2006 and headquartered in Bangalore, Karnataka, specializes in providing technology platforms for financial inclusion, focusing on rural banking, last-mile agent banking, and doorstep banking services.

Atyati Technologies, founded in 2006 and headquartered in Bangalore, Karnataka, specializes in providing technology platforms for financial inclusion, focusing on rural banking, last-mile agent banking, and doorstep banking services. Its proprietary platforms—Ganaseva, Swayam, and Aayam—offer comprehensive, mobility-based solutions that extend core banking systems to underserved rural, semi-urban, and urban areas. This enables banking correspondents (BCs / Bank Mitras) to deliver a wide range of financial services. The company will acquire ATPL for a consideration of Rs 154 crore. The acquisition will be an all cash deal and is expected to be completed by 31 March 2026, subject to approvals from the lenders, relevant banks/ financial institutions, statutory/ regulators/ shareholders approval, if any, and completion of other condition precedents as will be agreed in the share purchase agreement/ definitive agreement to be executed by the relevant parties. The acquisition is expected to provide immediate access to Atyati's advanced micro-lending platform, unlocking higher-margin credit distribution opportunities and will position the company as a more comprehensive tech-enabled BC player with enhanced product innovation and reduced third-party dependencies. Atyati's 25,900 Customer Service Points (CSPs) complement the company’s existing 46,000 CSPs, will expand the combined network to over 70,000 touchpoints and amplify transaction volumes, cross-selling potential, and geographic penetration in high growth states. Shikhar Aggarwal, chairman of BLS E-Services, said: "We are delighted to sign the binding term sheet to acquire Atyati Technologies which is in line with our inorganic strategy to grow and enhance our service offerings and play a pivotal role in India’s financial inclusion strategy. The acquisition of Atyati Technologies represents a transformative step in BLSe's journey to redefine rural and semi-urban banking in India. By merging Atyati's extensive network of over 25,900 CSPs with our own, we are creating a powerful combined footprint exceeding 70,000 touchpoints, unlocking unparalleled scale, cost efficiencies through shared infrastructure, and new high-margin avenues in digital lending. This synergy not only diversifies our revenue streams and strengthens geographic penetration in key states but also reinforces our mission to bridge the financial inclusion gap with cuttingedge technology and operational excellence—delivering sustainable value for all stakeholders." BLS E-Services, a subsidiary of BLS International, stands as a leading technology-enabled digital service provider in India, offering a diverse range of services that encompass Business Correspondent (BC / Rural Banking Outlets) services, Business Facilitators, Assisted E-services, and E-Governance Services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BLSE-ServicesLtd_43510775_91812.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI issues Foreign Exchange Management - Borrowing and Lending regulations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-issues-foreign-exchange-management---borrowing-and-lending-regulations/1678206</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678206</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has issued the Foreign Exchange Management (Borrowing and Lending) (First Amendment) Regulations, 2026.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has issued the Foreign Exchange Management (Borrowing and Lending) (First Amendment) Regulations, 2026. The amended regulations have rationalised the ECB framework by expansion of eligible borrower and recognised lender base, rationalisation of borrowing limits and restrictions on average maturity period, removal of restrictions on the cost of borrowing for ECBs, review of end-use restrictions and simplification of reporting requirements. The regulations have been issued after examining and suitably including feedback received from the stakeholders on the draft regulations published on the Bank’s website vide Press Release dated October 03, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/concept-money-tree-on-grass-picture-id462171033_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at IndusInd Bank Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-indusind-bank-ltd-counter/1678205</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678205</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[One 97 Communications Ltd, Cochin Shipyard Ltd, Wipro Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 17 February 2026.

One 97 Communications Ltd, Cochin Shipyard Ltd, Wipro Ltd, Newgen Software Technologies Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 17 February 2026. IndusInd Bank Ltd witnessed volume of 18.83 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 39.18 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 48057 shares. The stock increased 1.73% to Rs.948.00. Volumes stood at 31946 shares in the last session. One 97 Communications Ltd notched up volume of 5.71 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.51 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.04 lakh shares. The stock rose 2.47% to Rs.1,150.65. Volumes stood at 95957 shares in the last session. Cochin Shipyard Ltd registered volume of 2.64 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.15 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 51222 shares. The stock rose 4.28% to Rs.1,531.05. Volumes stood at 59047 shares in the last session. Wipro Ltd notched up volume of 39.59 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.72 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 8.38 lakh shares. The stock rose 1.24% to Rs.215.95. Volumes stood at 7.8 lakh shares in the last session. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd witnessed volume of 4.82 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.64 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.04 lakh shares. The stock increased 10.64% to Rs.512.00. Volumes stood at 1.38 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndusIndBankLtd_64968625_5531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI releases draft norms for reporting OTC Forex Derivative Transactions for Authorised Dealer Category – I Banks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-releases-draft-norms-for-reporting-otc-forex-derivative-transactions-for-authorised-dealer-category-i-banks/1678204</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678204</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released draft guidelines for banks to report foreign exchange derivative transactions involving the rupee by their related parties.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released draft guidelines for banks to report foreign exchange derivative transactions involving the rupee by their related parties. The RBI has been working on increasing transparency in over-the-counter (OTC) markets for foreign exchange, interest rate, and credit derivatives. Currently, all OTC derivative transactions are reported to the trade repository of the Clearing Corporation of India Limited (CCIL) by market-makers. The central bank highlighted a lack of transparency persists due to many offshore rupee derivative transactions not being reported. The RBI stated that this increased transparency would facilitate better pricing decisions for market participants. According to the draft directions, Authorised Dealer Category-I banks will need to report all relevant elements of covered transactions. This includes details like notional value, counterparty name, maturity date, and currency specifications.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hazoor Multi Projects bags Rs 44-cr order from NHAI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hazoor-multi-projects-bags-rs-44-cr-order-from-nhai/1678201</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678201</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves appointment of a user fee agency through competitive bidding via e-tender at the Balenahalli fee plaza (Design Km 397.400) for the four-lane Challakere–Hiriyur stretch of NH-150A.

The order involves appointment of a user fee agency through competitive bidding via e-tender at the Balenahalli fee plaza (Design Km 397.400) for the four-lane Challakere–Hiriyur stretch of NH-150A. The project covers existing chainage from Km 359.120 to Km 411.560 (design chainage Km 358.500 to Km 414.205). The scope includes collection of user fee and upkeep and maintenance of adjacent toilet blocks, including replenishment of consumables. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is to be executed over a period of one year. The company clarified that the contract does not fall under related-party transactions and that neither the promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. Hazoor Multi Projects is engaged in infrastructure and real estate businesses. On the financial front, the company reported a 137.5% year-on-year jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 6.46 crore in Q3 FY26, while revenue from operations declined 15.7% to Rs 139.04 crore. Shares of Hazoor Multi Projects shed 0.20% to Rs 35.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HazMultiProj_28677779210_22849.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's total exports rise around 13% on year in Jan-26, imports spike 19%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-total-exports-rise-around-13-on-year-in-jan-26-imports-spike-19/1678193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678193</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s total exports (Merchandise and Services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at US$ 80.45 Billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17 percent vis-à-vis January 2025.

India’s total exports (Merchandise and Services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at US$ 80.45 Billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17 percent vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (Merchandise and Services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at US$ 90.83 Billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76 percent vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at US$ 720.76 Billion registering a positive growth of 6.15 percent. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at US$ 823.41 Billion registering a growth of 6.54 percent. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were US$ 36.56 Billion as compared to US$ 36.34 Billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were US$ 71.24 Billion as compared to US$ 59.77 Billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is US$ 43.90 Billion as compared to US$ 34.75 Billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is US$ 19.60 Billion as compared to US$ 16.71 Billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include Engineering Goods, Petroleum Products, Meat, Dairy & Poultry Products, Marine Products and Iron Ore. Engineering Goods exports increased by 10.37% from US$ 9.42 Billion in January 2025 to US$ 10.40 Billion in January 2026 while Petroleum Products exports increased by 8.55% from US$ 3.48 Billion in January 2025 to US$ 3.77 Billion in January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty above 25,700 level; IT shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-above-25700-level-it-shares-advance/1678192</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678192</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,700 level. IT shares extended gains for the second consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 202.96 points or 0.24% to 83,480.11. The Nifty 50 index rose 39.95 points or 0.16% to 25,721.45. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.32% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.84%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,435 shares rose and 1,139 shares fell. A total of 208 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s total exports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at US$ 80.45 billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17% vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at US$ 90.83 billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76% vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at US$ 720.76 billion, registering a positive growth of 6.15%. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at US$ 823.41 billion, registering a growth of 6.54%. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were US$ 36.56 billion as compared to US$ 36.34 billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were US$ 71.24 billion as compared to US$ 59.77 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is US$ 43.90 billion as compared to US$ 34.75 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is US$ 19.60 billion as compared to US$ 16.71 billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy & poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports increased by 10.37% from US$ 9.42 billion in January 2025 to US$ 10.40 billion in January 2026, while petroleum products exports increased by 8.55% from US$ 3.48 billion in January 2025 to US$ 3.77 billion in January 2026. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index rose 2.02% to 33,397.85. The index added 2.19% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Persistent Systems (up 2.43%), Coforge (up 2.41%), HCL Technologies (up 1.92%), Oracle Financial Services Software (up 1.73%), Wipro (up 1.47%), Tech Mahindra (up 1.38%), Mphasis (up 1.34%), LTIMindtree (up 1.21%) and Tata Consultancy Services (up 1.2%) rose. Stocks in Spotlight: Highway Infrastructure soared 6.82% after the company said it has secured a contract from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for toll operations on key stretches of the Vadodara–Mumbai Expressway in Gujarat. Infosys advanced 2.83% after the company announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic, an AI safety and research company, to develop and deliver advanced enterprise AI solutions to companies across industries.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin rises on licensing pact with Spektus Pharma for DeslaFlex in Canada]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-rises-on-licensing-pact-with-spektus-pharma-for-deslaflex-in-canada/1678189</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678189</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DeslaFlex is an innovative antidepressant formulation developed by Spektus using its proprietary Flexitab oral drug-delivery platform.

DeslaFlex is an innovative antidepressant formulation developed by Spektus using its proprietary Flexitab oral drug-delivery platform. This strategic partnership combines Lupin’s strong commercial footprint in Canada and Spektus’s capabilities in developing differentiated, novel formulations to successfully introduce DeslaFlex and establish a robust platform for future launches. The collaboration further strengthens Lupin’s CNS portfolio with physician-endorsed, value-added therapies, well aligned with a supportive regulatory environment. Claus Jepsen, President, Global Speciality, Lupin, “This milestone reinforces our long-term commitment to advancing Lupin’s CNS footprint and deepens our commitment to Canadian healthcare. The addition of DeslaFlex™ to our portfolio provides patients and clinicians with much-needed flexibility in the management of Major Depressive Disorder, enabling clinicians to deliver more personalized, patient-focused care.” Zarvaan Merchant, Chief Executive Officer of Spektus Pharma, said, “This partnership with Lupin represents a key milestone as Spektus transitions from development to commercial execution. Lupin’s global brand and established commercial strength in Canada make it an ideal partner to realize the full value of DeslaFlex™ for patients across this important market.” Lupin is a global pharmaceutical leader headquartered in Mumbai, India, with products distributed in over 100 markets. It specializes in pharmaceutical products, including branded and generic formulations, complex generics, biotechnology products, and active pharmaceutical ingredients. Lupin reported a 37.46% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,175.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 855.16 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR stays pressured as dollar rebounds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-stays-pressured-as-dollar-rebounds/1678185</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678185</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee is staying under pressure amid rebound in dollar overseas.

The Indian rupee is staying under pressure amid rebound in dollar overseas. Local equities were muted. The benchmark BSE Sensex was down 68 points at 83,209 in early trade, while the broader NSE Nifty index slipped 49 points to 25,634. INR opened at Rs 90.72 and hit a high of 90.64 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee settled flat at 90.66 against the US dollar in a range-bound trades as positive momentum in domestic equities was offset by a strong US dollar in the overseas market. Lower crude oil prices supported the local unit, while foreign fund outflows limited its movement. Indian shares rose notably on Monday despite lackluster cues from global markets and continued declines in IT stocks on AI disruption fears. Investors shrugged off official data that showed India's wholesale prices increased more-than-expected in January to the highest level in ten months. Recovering from an early slide, the benchmark BSE Sensex ended the session up 650.39 points, or 0.79 percent, at 83,277.15. The broader NSE Nifty index jumped 211.65 points, or 0.83 percent, to 25,682.75.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under three schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-three-schemes/1678187</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678187</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 19 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 19 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of distribution (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: HDFC Large and Mid Cap Fund – Regular Plan - IDCW Option & Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 2.50 each. HDFC Multi-Asset Allocation Fund – Regular Plan - IDCW Option & Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 1.00 each. HDFC Mid Cap Fund – Regular Plan - IDCW Option & Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 5.00 each.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cochin Shipyard jumps on Rs 5,000 crore Navy vessel bid win]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cochin-shipyard-jumps-on-rs-5000-crore-navy-vessel-bid-win/1678181</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678181</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has emerged as the L1 bidder in a key defence tender floated for the construction of five Next Generation Survey Vessels for the Indian Navy.

The company has emerged as the L1 bidder in a key defence tender floated for the construction of five Next Generation Survey Vessels for the Indian Navy. The shipbuilder stated that the estimated total order value is around Rs 5,000 crore. It added that the final award of the contract is subject to completion of necessary formalities, and further updates will be shared in due course. Cochin Shipyard is a leading player in the construction of all kinds of vessels and the repair and refit of all types of vessels, including periodic upgrades and life extensions of ships. The company reported an 18.3% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.67 crore on a 17.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,350.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CochinShipyardLtd_99942576320_5762.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Supply Chains gains after inking MoU with Italy’s ALA Group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-supply-chains-gains-after-inking-mou-with-italys-ala-group/1678182</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678182</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ALA Group brings more than 35 years of experience as a specialised aerospace and defence supply-chain integrator, supporting leading OEMs, MROs, and defence programmes across Europe, North America, and selected international markets.

ALA Group brings more than 35 years of experience as a specialised aerospace and defence supply-chain integrator, supporting leading OEMs, MROs, and defence programmes across Europe, North America, and selected international markets. For the year 2024, it reported revenue of $345 million. As part of the proposed collaboration, TVS SCS and ALA Group will jointly provide integrated supply chain services across both production and aftermarket lifecycles for aerospace and defence programmes. The collaboration will initially focus on India, with potential to evaluate opportunities in other geographies over time. The company said that Aerospace and Defence market in India, estimated at approximately $28 billion, are among the most dynamic and profitable segments within industrial supply chains, driven by sustained demand for complex, regulated, and mission-critical logistics and procurement services. TVS SCS will leverage its long-standing defence and utilities supply chain experience gained through its UK operations, together with its strong domestic presence in India. This includes procurement, market access, government and stakeholder engagement, regulatory and licensing expertise, warehousing and logistics infrastructure, digital platforms, and robust local execution capabilities. ALA Group on the other hand, will contribute its global aerospace and defence domain expertise, technology platforms, and long-standing relationships, especially in the production supply chain with international OEMs and operators across Europe, the US, and the UK, enabling a differentiated, compliant, and scalable value proposition for aerospace and defence stakeholders in India. Currently, TVS SCS’ aerospace, defence and utilities operations generate approximately $140 million in annual revenues, largely anchored in defence and utility programmes in the United Kingdom. R. Dinesh, Executive Chairman, TVS Supply Chain Solutions, said, “This collaboration with ALA Group reflects our long-term strategy of building globally relevant capabilities in complex and regulated sectors. By combining TVS Supply Chain Solutions’ scale, digital platforms, and strong presence in India with ALA’s aerospace and defence domain expertise, we are positioning the company to participate meaningfully in the evolving global aerospace and defence supply chain ecosystem.” He further added, “Importantly, this partnership enables us to build on our established aftermarket and in-service supply chain strengths and extend our support to production programmes, particularly in aerospace where these capabilities are increasingly relevant.” Vittorio Genna, CEO and Co-Founder, ALA Group, added, “From the beginning, ALA has focused on combining technical depth, operational excellence, and long-term partnerships. The collaboration with TVS Supply Chain Solutions reflects this vision and creates a solid platform for sustainable growth across multiple regions, supporting both civil and defence aerospace programs.” TVS Supply Chain Solutions (TVS SCS) is an India-based multinational company, who pioneered the development of the supply chain solutions market in India. The company's customers span across numerous industries such as automotive, industrial, consumer, tech and tech infra, rail and utilities, and healthcare. TVS Supply Chain Solutions reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 10.72 crore in Q3 December 2025 compared with a net loss of Rs 24.65 crore posted in Q3 December 2024. Revenue from operations jumped 11.09% YoY to Rs 2,715.81 crore during the quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSSupplyChainSolutionsLtd_13681781_28638.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>