<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:25:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR stays near record low levels; Weak dollar limits downside]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-stays-near-record-low-levels-weak-dollar-limits-downside/1668311</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668311</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee rebounded in opening trades on Thursday tracking weakness in dollar overseas.

The Indian rupee rebounded in opening trades on Thursday tracking weakness in dollar overseas. Moreover, on the domestic front, industrial production advanced 7.8 percent year-over-year in December, faster than the upwardly revised 7.2 percent gain in November. The expected increase was 5.5 percent. Further, this was the strongest expansion since October 2023. INR opened at Rs 91.95 per dollar but dropped to a low of 92 before recovering slightly. Yesterday rupee ended at 91.99. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty rose by 0.6 percent and 0.7 percent, respectively on Wednesday to extend gains from the previous session amid optimism that the historic free trade agreement between India and the European Union will give an economic boost for India's export sectors. Today, local equities are seen opening a tad lower as the U.S. Federal Reserve kept its policy rate unchanged, as widely expected, after cutting it at three consecutive meetings during the final months of last year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cochin Shipyard Q3 PAT tumbles 18% YoY to Rs 145 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cochin-shipyard-q3-pat-tumbles-18-yoy-to-rs-145-cr/1668309</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668309</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax declined 18.6% YoY to Rs 196.78 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 241.86 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

Profit before tax declined 18.6% YoY to Rs 196.78 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 241.86 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Total expenses jumped 28.52% YoY to Rs 1,224.77 crore during the quarter. The cost of materials consumed was at Rs 596.80 crore (up 16.31% YoY), while employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 123.32 crore (up 19.54% YoY) during the period under review. On the segmental front, revenue from shipbuilding stood at Rs 1,013.12 crore (up 56.49% YoY), while revenue from ship repair stood at Rs 337.29 crore (down 32.57% YoY) during the quarter. Meanwhile, the company declared a second interim dividend of Rs 3.50 per equity share for FY26, with 3 February 2026 set as the record date. The dividend will be paid on or before 26 February 2026. During the quarter, the board approved the formation of a joint venture with HBL Engineering to develop electric mobility technology and energy storage solutions for the marine sector. It also approved the acquisition of a 23% stake in Netherlands-based Conoship International Holding BV to strengthen its European presence by gaining access to advanced ship design capabilities. Cochin Shipyard is a leading player in the construction of all kinds of vessels and the repair and refit of all types of vessels, including periodic upgrades and life extensions of ships. The counter rose 0.53% to Rs 1,631.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CochinShipyardLtd_99942576320_5762.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen recovers as Dollar rally pauses after Fed decision]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-recovers-as-dollar-rally-pauses-after-fed-decision/1668310</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668310</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen hovered near 152.9 per dollar on Thursday after suffering a sharp decline in the previous session, as the US dollar regained strength following Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent’s reaffirmation of Washington’s strong-dollar policy and dismissal of intervention speculation.

The Japanese yen hovered near 152.9 per dollar on Thursday after suffering a sharp decline in the previous session, as the US dollar regained strength following Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent’s reaffirmation of Washington’s strong-dollar policy and dismissal of intervention speculation. The greenback remained supported after the Federal Reserve held interest rates steady, signalling patience amid persistent inflation and resilient growth. Meanwhile, caution prevails in Tokyo over potential unilateral action, with political uncertainty ahead of the February 8 snap election adding further pressure on the yen.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drift lower; breadth positive ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drift-lower-breadth-positive/1668307</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668307</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices opened the session on a subdued note, slipping marginally amid mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment outweighed optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA).

The key equity indices opened the session on a subdued note, slipping marginally amid mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment outweighed optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA). Participants are keeping a close watch on the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments. Attention is also on quarterly results from ITC, Tata Motors, and Vedanta, scheduled to be announced later today. Meanwhile, the Nifty traded below the 25,300 level. IT, auto and FMCG shares witnessed selling pressure while metal, oil & gas and PSU Bank stocks advanced. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 184.81 points or 0.24% to 82,137.24. The Nifty 50 index fell 63.30 points or 0.25% to 25,279.45. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.20% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.02%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,564 shares rose and 1,450 shares fell. A total of 174 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 480.26 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,360.59 crore in the Indian equity market on 28 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Lodha Developers shed 0.20%. The company reported a 1.3% YoY rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 956.9 crore, while revenue from operations increased 14.4% to Rs 4,672.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. LT Foods fell 0.46%. The company reported consolidated net profit rose 9.8% to Rs 157.4 crore on a 23.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2,809.2 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Cochin Shipyard advanced 0.76%. The company reported an 18.3% YoY decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.7 crore, even as revenue from operations rose 17.7% to Rs 1,350.4 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signalling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper advanced 0.30% to 6.723 as compared with previous close of 6.703. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9775 compared with its close of 91.9975 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement jumped 5.78% to Rs 1,75,597. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.24% to 96.12. The United States 10-year bond yield advanced 0.33% to 4.265. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement advanced 75 cents or 1.10% to $69.15 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market mostly traded lower on Thursday after the U.S. Federal Reserve overnight kept its benchmark rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%. Investors will be keeping an eye on developments in Indonesia after the benchmark Jakarta Composite plunged over 8% on Wednesday after index provider MSCI had issued a statement warning of a potential downgrade of the country to frontier-market status. Meanwhile, Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday, while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 reached a milestone level, hitting 7,000 for the first time, before pulling back as the Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged and upped its economic growth assessment. The broad market index ended the day down 0.01% at 6,978.03. Earlier, the S&P 500 was up 0.3% on the day, hitting an all-time intraday high of 7,002.28. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.02% to close at 49,015.60. The Nasdaq Composite outperformed and gained 0.17%, settling at 23,857.45.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Universal Cables Ltd Spikes 11.39%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/universal-cables-ltd-spikes-1139/1668302</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668302</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Universal Cables Ltd rose 11.39% today to trade at Rs 785.

Universal Cables Ltd rose 11.39% today to trade at Rs 785. The BSE Industrials index is up 0.83% to quote at 14258.69. The index is down 2.1 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Zodiac Energy Ltd increased 10% and Ajax Engineering Ltd added 10% on the day. The BSE Industrials index went up 7.11 % over last one year compared to the 7.63% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Universal Cables Ltd has lost 11.69% over last one month compared to 2.1% fall in BSE Industrials index and 2.72% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 3731 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 1007 on 20 Nov 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 29 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UniversalCables_91881013472_587.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Network People Services Technologies Ltd Slides 9%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-slides-9/1668303</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668303</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Network People Services Technologies Ltd fell 9% today to trade at Rs 1133.8.

Network People Services Technologies Ltd fell 9% today to trade at Rs 1133.8. The BSE Information Technology index is down 0.24% to quote at 37158.94. The index is up 0.92 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Digitide Solutions Ltd decreased 2.52% and Subex Ltd lost 2.32% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 11.66 % over last one year compared to the 7.63% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Network People Services Technologies Ltd has lost 19.08% over last one month compared to 0.92% gain in BSE Information Technology index and 2.72% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 543 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2388 on 04 Aug 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 29 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Network-People-Services-Technologies-Ltd_97933685_75371.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests red opening for equities; US Fed votes to keep rates unchanged]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-red-opening-for-equities-us-fed-votes-to-keep-rates-unchanged/1668286</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668286</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 17.50 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 17.50 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today. The Federal Reserve on Wednesday voted to keep its key interest rate in a range between 3.5%-3.75%. The decision put a halt to three consecutive quarter percentage point reductions, billed as maintenance moves to guard against potential downturns in the labor market. In voting to hold the line, the committee raised its assessment of economic growth. It also eased its concerns about the labor market as compared with inflation. Meanwhile, India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signalling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 480.26 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,360.59 crore in the Indian equity market on 28 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 43,292.62 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market mostly traded lower on Thursday after the U.S. Federal Reserve overnight kept its benchmark rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%. Investors will be keeping an eye on developments in Indonesia after the benchmark Jakarta Composite plunged over 8% on Wednesday after index provider MSCI had issued a statement warning of a potential downgrade of the country to frontier-market status. Meanwhile, Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday, while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 reached a milestone level, hitting 7,000 for the first time, before pulling back as the Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged and upped its economic growth assessment. The broad market index ended the day down 0.01% at 6,978.03. Earlier, the S&P 500 was up 0.3% on the day, hitting an all-time intraday high of 7,002.28. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.02% to close at 49,015.60. The Nasdaq Composite outperformed and gained 0.17%, settling at 23,857.45. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks ended higher for a second straight session on Wednesday, as improved risk appetite lifted sentiment. Optimism around the conclusion of the India-EU free trade agreement and supportive global cues underpinned the rally. Meanwhile, a stable rupee and steady crude oil prices added comfort for investors. The Nifty closed above the 25,300 mark led by firmness in energy and metal shares. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 487.20 points, or 0.60%, to 82,344.68, while the Nifty 50 gained 167.35 points, or 0.66%, to settle at 25,342.75. Over the past two sessions, the Sensex has risen 0.99% and the Nifty has climbed 1.17%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Larsen & Toubro, NSDL, Lodha Developers, Cochin Shipyard, Vedanta]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-larsen-toubro-nsdl-lodha-developers-cochin-shipyard-vedanta/1668282</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668282</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Listing In the SME segment, NSE SME KRM Ayurveda is set to list today.

Listing In the SME segment, NSE SME KRM Ayurveda is set to list today. The issue price is set at Rs 135 per share. The issue was subscribed 46.98 times. The issue was open between 21 and 23 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 128 and Rs 135 per equity share. Result Today: ITC, Tata Motors, Swiggy, REC, One 97 Communications (Paytm), Canara Bank, Colgate-Palmolive (India), Adani Power, Aequs, Blue Star, Container Corporation of India, Coromandel International, Dabur India, Dixon Technologies, Indian Energy Exchange, Indegene, Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research, KPIT Technologies, Manappuram Finance, Nippon Life India Asset Management, NTPC Green Energy, Prestige Estates Projects, Vedanta, Voltas, and Websol Energy System will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Larsen & Toubro reported a 4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,215 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,359 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 10% YoY to Rs 71,450 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Lodha Developers reported a 1.3% YoY rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 956.9 crore, while revenue from operations increased 14.4% to Rs 4,672.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. National Securities Depository (NSDL) reported a 4.4% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 89.6 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 85.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 0.8% YoY to Rs 359.6 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. LT Foods reported consolidated net profit rose 9.8% to Rs 157.4 crore on a 23.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2,809.2 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ACC has reported a net profit of Rs 404 crore in Q3 FY26, which is lower by 63% as compared with the PAT of Rs 1,092 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operation rose by 8.6% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,483 crore in Q3 FY26. eClerx Services reported consolidated net profit jumped 39.8% to Rs 191.8 crore on a 25.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,070.3 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. SBI Cards and Payment Services reported consolidated net profit rose 45.2% to Rs 556.6 crore on an 11% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5,127.3 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Cochin Shipyard reported an 18.3% YoY decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.7 crore, even as revenue from operations rose 17.7% to Rs 1,350.4 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Rail Vikas Nigam said that the Rail Vikas Nigam–GPT joint venture has emerged as the lowest bidder (L1) from Northern Railway for a project valued at Rs 1,201.35 crore. The project involves the design and construction of 11 rail-cum-road bridges over the River Ganga, around 50 meters downstream of the existing Malviya Bridge near Kashi Railway Station. The bridges will accommodate four railway tracks on the lower deck and a six-lane road on the upper deck, along with railway and road approaches, associated OHE, and general electrical works in the Lucknow Division at Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh. Vedanta has decided to exercise the oversubscription option in its offer-for-sale (OFS) of Hindustan Zinc to the extent of 1.4 crore shares, in addition to the base offer size of 3.35 crore shares, on January 29. With this, the total offer size will increase to 4.75 crore shares, representing 1.13% of the company’s paid-up equity capital.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RVNL-GPT JV bags Rs 1,201-cr Northern Railway bridge project in Varanasi]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rvnl-gpt-jv-bags-rs-1201-cr-northern-railway-bridge-project-in-varanasi/1668224</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668224</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves construction of Bridge No.

The project involves construction of Bridge No. 11, located around 50 metres downstream of the existing Old Malviya Bridge near Kashi Railway Station. The scope includes substructure and superstructure works for a multi-span bridge comprising eight spans of 108.5 metres and two spans of 103.3 metres using open web steel girders. The bridge will carry four railway lines on the lower deck and a six-lane road on the upper deck. The order also includes construction of railway and road approaches, along with associated overhead electrification (OHE) and general electrical works, to be executed in the Lucknow Division of Northern Railway. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and is to be executed over a period of 48 months. The total project cost is Rs 1,201.36 crore, inclusive of all taxes. Under the joint venture arrangement, RVNL holds a 60% stake, while GPT Infraprojects holds the remaining 40%. The company said that neither the promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority, and the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Rail Vikas Nigam is in the business of executing all types of railway projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, construction of cable-stayed bridges, institution buildings, etc. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 19.73% to Rs 230.29 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 286.88 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5.22% YoY to Rs 5,122.98 crore in Q2 FY26. The scrip rallied 5.73% to end at Rs 342.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>