<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:55:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[XT Global Infotech Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/xt-global-infotech-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1679643</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679643</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tarmat Ltd, Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd, Secmark Consultancy Ltd and STL Global Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 February 2026.

Tarmat Ltd, Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd, Secmark Consultancy Ltd and STL Global Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 February 2026. XT Global Infotech Ltd soared 20.00% to Rs 33.18 at 11:39 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 4844 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2468 shares in the past one month. Tarmat Ltd spiked 20.00% to Rs 64.92. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 39204 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1539 shares in the past one month. Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd surged 19.95% to Rs 21.16. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 2.54 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 32319 shares in the past one month. Secmark Consultancy Ltd gained 16.27% to Rs 140.75. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 27445 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 527 shares in the past one month. STL Global Ltd added 14.25% to Rs 13.79. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 12242 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1092 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FrontierInfo_25254948202_12674.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma gains as arm gets USFDA final nod for Everolimus tablets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aurobindo-pharma-gains-as-arm-gets-usfda-final-nod-for-everolimus-tablets/1679644</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679644</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approval covers Everolimus tablets in strengths of 0.25 mg, 0.5 mg, 0.75 mg and 1 mg.

The approval covers Everolimus tablets in strengths of 0.25 mg, 0.5 mg, 0.75 mg and 1 mg. The product is bioequivalent and therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Zortress Tablets, marketed by Novartis Pharmaceuticals Corp. Everolimus tablets are indicated for the prophylaxis of organ rejection in adult patients undergoing kidney and liver transplants. For kidney transplant patients at low-to-moderate immunologic risk, the drug is used in combination with basiliximab, reduced-dose cyclosporine and corticosteroids. For liver transplant patients, it is administered no earlier than 30 days post-transplant, in combination with reduced-dose tacrolimus and corticosteroids. The approval was granted to Eugia Unit-I, and the product is expected to be launched in the first quarter of FY27. According to IQVIA MAT data for the twelve months ended December 2025, the approved product has an estimated market size of $ 78 million. With this approval, Eugia Pharma Specialities Group has received a total of 184 ANDA approvals, including 10 tentative approvals, across its facilities manufacturing oncology oral and sterile specialty products. Aurobindo Pharma is principally engaged in the manufacturing and marketing of active pharmaceutical ingredients, generic pharmaceuticals, and related services. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 7.6% to Rs 910.29 crore on a 9% increase in net sales to Rs 8,604.51 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurobindoPharma_66877283489_4666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Govt says around 1700 Central Sector infrastructure projects ongoing, puts their revised cost of Rs 39.25 lakh crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/govt-says-around-1700-central-sector-infrastructure-projects-ongoing-puts-their-revised-cost-of-rs-3925-lakh-crore/1679642</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679642</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Ministry of Statistics and Programme Implementation (MoSPI) has operationalised a new web-based portal, PAIMANA (Project Assessment, Infrastructure Monitoring & Analytics for Nation-building), for the mandated monitoring of Central Sector Infrastructure Projects worth Rs 150 crore and above, replacing the erstwhile OCMS-2006 (Online Computerized Monitoring system).

The Ministry of Statistics and Programme Implementation (MoSPI) has operationalised a new web-based portal, PAIMANA (Project Assessment, Infrastructure Monitoring & Analytics for Nation-building), for the mandated monitoring of Central Sector Infrastructure Projects worth Rs 150 crore and above, replacing the erstwhile OCMS-2006 (Online Computerized Monitoring system). It noted that as of January 2026, 1702 ongoing infrastructure projects, with a revised cost of Rs 39.25 lakh crore, are reported on the PAIMANA portal across 17 Central Ministries/Departments. During the month, 3 projects were commissioned and, 203 additional projects were brought under the monitoring of PAIMANA. The cumulative expenditure incurred on these projects up to January 2026 stands at Rs 20.02 lakh crore. Out of 1,702 ongoing infrastructure projects, 645 ( 38%) have achieved over 80% physical progress, while 240 ( 14%) have crossed 80% financial completion, reflecting that a substantial portion of projects are at an advanced stage of implementation. The Transport & Logistics sector accounts for the highest number of ongoing projects (1180 projects), with revised estimates of Rs 20.65 lakh crore underscoring priority to connectivity-driven infrastructure growth.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LTIMIndtree joins hands with NIVDIA to upgrade CBDT”s tax analytics platform]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ltimindtree-joins-hands-with-nivdia-to-upgrade-cbdts-tax-analytics-platform/1679640</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679640</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As part of Insight 2.0 program, the company will deploy a secure cloud environment powered by NVIDIA AI infrastructure to simplify workloads and offer real-time insights for CBDT.

As part of Insight 2.0 program, the company will deploy a secure cloud environment powered by NVIDIA AI infrastructure to simplify workloads and offer real-time insights for CBDT. The company’s BlueVerse serves as the intelligence backbone of the entire program, enabling AI integration across all operational layers of the tax platform, supporting features such as a smart citizen portal, automated campaign management, enhanced case workflows, and AI-driven helpdesk assistance. The BlueVerse platform aims to deliver a seamless citizen interface to enhance governance, reduce leakages, improve compliance and elevate the citizen’s experience. Gururaj Deshpande, Chief Delivery OƯicer, LTM, said, “We are excited to work with NVIDIA and contribute to this critical public service program. This collaboration combines NVIDIA’s deep AI expertise with LTM’s BlueVerse platform and lays the foundation for transparent, resilient, and citizen-friendly tax administration at scale.” Yogesh Agrawal, VP of Data Center GPU Business, NVIDIA, said, “Full-stack AI and accelerated computing are unlocking unprecedented eƯiciencies to modernize tax operations in India, By integrating NVIDIA AI infrastructure with LTM’s BlueVerse platform, this collaboration enables secure, highperformance, and scalable AI-driven digital governance for a program of national importance.” Meanwhile, the company has proposed changing its name from LTIMindtree to LTM, subject to shareholder approval. LTIMindtree is a global technology consulting and digital solutions company that enables enterprises across industries to reimagine business models, accelerate innovation, and maximize growth by harnessing digital technologies. LTIMindtree is a Larsen & Toubro Group company. The company reported a 30.73% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 970.60 crore despite of a 3.72% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q2 September 2025. The counter fell 0.38% to Rs 4,547 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LTIMindtreeLtd_76198734_18105.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1679637</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679637</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd, KSB Ltd, Balu Forge Industries Ltd and SpiceJet Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 February 2026.

Tejas Networks Ltd, KSB Ltd, Balu Forge Industries Ltd and SpiceJet Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 February 2026. Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd soared 15.09% to Rs 4610.15 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 51089 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1121 shares in the past one month. Tejas Networks Ltd spiked 12.13% to Rs 356.45. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 24.86 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.69 lakh shares in the past one month. KSB Ltd surged 10.42% to Rs 793.3. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 6.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3939 shares in the past one month. Balu Forge Industries Ltd exploded 10.00% to Rs 490.75. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.93 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.1 lakh shares in the past one month. SpiceJet Ltd advanced 8.63% to Rs 15.73. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 432.79 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 276.35 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SanofiConsumerHealthcareIndiaLtd_55923168_79141.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Capacite Infraprojects bags Rs 537-cr LOI from TenX Realty for Thane projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/capacite-infraprojects-bags-rs-537-cr-loi-from-tenx-realty-for-thane-projects/1679638</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679638</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order covers the construction of Towers F, G, NTA, and a retail building as part of the Address by GS-3 Project and Invictus-2 Project in Thane (West), Maharashtra.

The order covers the construction of Towers F, G, NTA, and a retail building as part of the Address by GS-3 Project and Invictus-2 Project in Thane (West), Maharashtra. The contract reinforces Capacit’e Infraprojects’ focus on large-scale residential and commercial development projects in urban locations, leveraging its expertise in construction and project management. Rahul Katyal, Managing Director said, “We are thrilled to have beenentrusted by our valued client, Raymond's Realty Division, with repeat orders through TenX Realty (step-down subsidiary of Raymond). We're delighted by the repeat orders, showcasing our strong partnership and dedication to exceptional service. With a strong track record of project delivery, we're confident in our ability to meet timelines and exceed client expectations. At Capacit'e, we're dedicated to expanding our portfolio with quality orders and showcasing our growing expertise in project execution.” Capacit'e Infraprojects is primarily engaged in the EPC business and provides turnkey solutions for housing, high rises, super high rises, speciality buildings and urban infrastructure. The company offers these services to leading real-estate and government bodies in India. The company reported a 3.8% decline in consolidated net profit to ₹50.02 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 14.4% to ₹675.42 crore compared to Q3 FY25. The scrip fell 0.77% to Rs 251.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CapaciteInfraprojectsLtd_26708448592_70490.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India' sugar output seen up around 9% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-sugar-output-seen-up-around-9-on-year/1679639</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679639</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian Sugar & Bio-energy Manufacturers Association (ISMA) has released its third advance estimates of sugar production for the 2025–26 sugar season (SS 2025–26), following a comprehensive review conducted during the meeting of its Executive Committee held on 25th February 2026, media reports noted.

The Indian Sugar & Bio-energy Manufacturers Association (ISMA) has released its third advance estimates of sugar production for the 2025–26 sugar season (SS 2025–26), following a comprehensive review conducted during the meeting of its Executive Committee held on 25th February 2026, media reports noted. The Committee observed that sugarcane yield in Uttar Pradesh is lower than earlier projections. In major sugarcane-growing regions of Maharashtra and Karnataka, it is observed that yields per unit area are lower than initially expected, despite reasonable sugar recovery. India's sugar production has been revised down 5.57% to 32.40 million tonne for the 2025-26 marketing year. The third advance estimate, released after an executive committee meeting, follows a second projection of 34.35 million tonnes. Output last year was 29.62 million tonnes, which means that current projection is still marking a rise of 9.38% on year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-coffee-1-1573107_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Capillary Technologies to acquire Mastercard-subsidiary Session M Inc. for $20 million]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/capillary-technologies-to-acquire-mastercard-subsidiary-session-m-inc-for-20-million/1679635</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679635</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Session M Inc, founded in 2011, is a wholly owned subsidiary of US-based Mastercard Inc.

Session M Inc, founded in 2011, is a wholly owned subsidiary of US-based Mastercard Inc. The company is a leading cloud-based loyalty and engagement platform that empowers brands to have digitalized and seamless engagement through best in-class product suite offerings. It serves customers in industires such as food and beverages, consumer goods / retail, airlines, oil and gas and has presence in North America along with LATAM and APAC markets. The company had recorded turnover of $50.5 million in CY2025. In a regulatory filing made during market hours today, the company said that its board of directors has approved a strategic investment into its wholly owned subsidiary, Capillary Pte. Ltd., to facilitate the purchase of 100% shareholding in in Session M Inc. The transaction also includes the acquisition of Session M Czech Republic s.r.o., further expanding Capillary's European footprint. The deal is being executed through a multi-layered structure involving Capillary Pte. Ltd. and its step-down subsidiary, Capillary Technologies LLC. The proposed acquisition is part of Capillary’s inorganic growth plans to strengthen its presence in the North American, LATAM loyalty markets and adds to its APAC portfolio. Further, the complementary business model, coupled with long-tenured blue-chip clientele, would strengthen Capillary’s ability to unlock post- acquisition efficiencies in the loyalty space. The base consideration to be paid for this acquisition is $20 million, subject to customary closing adjustments towards net debt, working capital and other adjustments as set out in the definitive agreements. The company expects to complete this transaction within 180 days from signing date. Capillary Technologies India, a software product company offering artificial intelligence (AI)-based cloud-native software-as-a-service (SaaS) products and solutions primarily to enterprise customers globally to develop loyalty of its consumer and channel partners. The company had recorded 30% YoY drop in net profit to Rs 7.99 crore despite a 16% increase in operating revenue to Rs 184.04 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.58% to currently trade at Rs 515.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/capillarytechnologiesindiapvtltd_20227085_76330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex gains 230 pts; pharma shares rally for 5th day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-gains-230-pts-pharma-shares-rally-for-5th-day/1679631</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679631</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices maintained moderate gains in mid-morning trade, extending their recovery for the second straight session.

The domestic equity indices maintained moderate gains in mid-morning trade, extending their recovery for the second straight session. The upward momentum was primarily driven by strong buying interest in IT and pharma stocks, keeping the market firmly in positive territory. The Nifty traded above the 25,550 mark. Meanwhile, pharma stocks attracted buying interest for the fifth consecutive trading session. At 11:27 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 230.43 points or 0.28% to 82,506.50. The Nifty 50 index gained 71.50 points or 0.28% to 25,554. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.50% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.30%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,345 shares rose and 1,457 shares fell. A total of 197 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Omnitech Engineering received bids for 18,84,300 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.10 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026 and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 49,72,480 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.87 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty pharma index jumped 0.80% to 23,237.35. The index rallied 3.60% in five consecutive trading sessions. Mankind Pharma (up 4.61%), Zydus Lifesciences (up 1.72%), Lupin (up 1.34%), Gland Pharma (up 1.29%), Aurobindo Pharma (up 1.15%), Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (up 1.01%), Alkem Laboratories (up 1%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 0.74%), Ajanta Pharma (up 0.68%) and Laurus Labs (up 0.62%) advanced. On the other hand, IPCA Laboratories (down 0.28%), Abbott India (down 0.15%) and Biocon (down 0.09%) edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: KP Energy added 1.55% after the company received a letter of award (LoA) from Enerparc Energy for the development of a 40.8 MW wind-solar hybrid power project in Gujarat. Balu Forge Industries surged 9.78% after it entered into a legally binding memorandum of understanding (MoU) for the supply of empty artillery shells from its greenfield manufacturing facility in Belgaum, Karnataka. Coforge rose 0.51%. The company announced a strategic partnership with VHC Health for serving as the latter’s digital and IT services provider. Global Markets: Most Asian markets edged higher with South Korea and Japan stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/blue-stock-chart-growth-picture-id174673054_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alembic Pharma gets USFDA nod for Lamotrigine tablets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alembic-pharma-gets-usfda-nod-for-lamotrigine-tablets/1679629</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679629</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Lamictal ODT Orally Disintegrating Tablets of GlaxoSmithKline LLC.

The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Lamictal ODT Orally Disintegrating Tablets of GlaxoSmithKline LLC. Lamotrigine is indicated as adjunctive therapy for patients aged two years and above for partial-onset seizures, primary generalized tonic-clonic (PGTC) seizures, and generalized seizures of Lennox-Gastaut syndrome. It is also indicated for conversion to monotherapy in certain adult patients with partial-onset seizures and for maintenance treatment of bipolar I disorder. According to IQVIA data, the product has an estimated market size of US$ 27 million for the 12 months ended December 2025. With this approval, Alembic now has a cumulative total of 235 ANDA approvals from the USFDA, comprising 216 final approvals and 19 tentative approvals. Alembic Pharmaceuticals, a vertically integrated research and development company, is engaged in the manufacture and marketing of generic pharmaceutical products across global markets. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 3.9% to Rs 132.97 crore despite a 10.8% jump in net sales to Rs 1,876.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter rose 0.39% to Rs 741.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlembicPharma_46538273359_40294.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KP Energy climbs after bagging LoA for hybrid power project in Gujarat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kp-energy-climbs-after-bagging-loa-for-hybrid-power-project-in-gujarat/1679625</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679625</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order comprises 20.2 MW of wind capacity and 20.6 MWp of solar capacity.

The order comprises 20.2 MW of wind capacity and 20.6 MWp of solar capacity. The project has been awarded on a complete turnkey basis, encompassing supply, installation and commissioning of the project. The scope of work also includes development of evacuation infrastructure, facilitation of grid connectivity, and obtaining requisite statutory and regulatory approvals. K.P. Energy primarily engaged in Wind Farm development, development of Wind power projects and allied services related to it along with generation of electricity through wind power generating assets and operation and maintenance services of wind power projects primarily in India. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 56.7% to Rs 41.35 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 26.39 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales climbed 62.8% YoY to Rs 344.96 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KPEnergy_6501313394_67194.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Balu Forge Inds spurts on inking MoU to supply artillery shells]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/balu-forge-inds-spurts-on-inking-mou-to-supply-artillery-shells/1679623</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679623</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agreement marks the next phase of the company’s expansion into the defence consumables segment following its onboarding into the NATO supply chain and commercialisation of its empty shell production line.

The agreement marks the next phase of the company’s expansion into the defence consumables segment following its onboarding into the NATO supply chain and commercialisation of its empty shell production line. The MoU has been signed with a NATO-affiliated entity, though the end user’s name has not been disclosed due to confidentiality and the sensitive nature of the supplies. Under the agreement, Balu Forge will supply 30,000 units per month of 155 mm M107 shells and 10,000 units per month of 152 mm shells in ‘Ready to Fill’ condition, for a period of five years starting 25 February 2026. Supplies are scheduled to commence from April 2026 and will be ramped up in a phased manner. The contract also covers the broader large-calibre ammunition category, including 155 mm ERFB/BT and 152 mm variants, with potential expansion to 105 mm, 120 mm and 81 mm shells at a later stage, subject to trials and approvals. The agreed price is $315 per unit for both 155 mm M107 and 152 mm shells, indexed to the London Metal Exchange to account for fluctuations in raw material prices. The terms are on an FOB Nhava Sheva basis. Payment terms include 20% advance, with the balance payable through an irrevocable letter of credit within 30 days from invoice issuance. The committed volumes exceed the company’s current installed capacity of 360,000 units per annum. However, Balu Forge said it has plans in place to enhance production capacity through internal accruals to meet the order requirements. The company stated that the agreement aligns with its strategy to build a strong presence in the defence consumables space, beginning with large-calibre ammunition and gradually expanding into medium- and small-calibre segments. Balu Forge Industries is a precision engineering company delivering forged and machined components across multiple global industries. The company offers a comprehensive product portfolio, supporting diverse applications in automotive, industrial vehicles, earthmoving equipment, wind energy, aerospace, defence, oil and gas, railways, marine, and agriculture. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 20.5% to Rs 71.09 crore on 21.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 311.11 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BaluForgeIndustriesLtd.._52578716_5893.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Balkrishna Industries Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-balkrishna-industries-ltd-counter/1679619</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679619</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eternal Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, EID Parry (India) Ltd, Angel One Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 26 February 2026.

Eternal Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, EID Parry (India) Ltd, Angel One Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 26 February 2026. Balkrishna Industries Ltd recorded volume of 3.05 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 43.86 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6964 shares. The stock lost 2.25% to Rs.2,459.00. Volumes stood at 3083 shares in the last session. Eternal Ltd registered volume of 1035.22 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 29.48 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 35.11 lakh shares. The stock rose 1.50% to Rs.254.00. Volumes stood at 18.8 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd recorded volume of 15.01 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 25.83 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 58097 shares. The stock gained 8.41% to Rs.344.65. Volumes stood at 62279 shares in the last session. EID Parry (India) Ltd registered volume of 1.88 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 18.95 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 9897 shares. The stock rose 0.61% to Rs.871.00. Volumes stood at 3062 shares in the last session. Angel One Ltd recorded volume of 3.95 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 12.53 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 31529 shares. The stock lost 1.93% to Rs.244.30. Volumes stood at 34619 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BalkrishnaInds_9898029362_55.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coforge edges higher after signing strategic deal with US-based VHC Health ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coforge-edges-higher-after-signing-strategic-deal-with-us-based-vhc-health/1679621</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679621</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[VHC Health is an independent, not-for-profit, 548-bed health system serving the Washington, DC metropolitan area, anchored by a nationally recognized top teaching hospital.

VHC Health is an independent, not-for-profit, 548-bed health system serving the Washington, DC metropolitan area, anchored by a nationally recognized top teaching hospital. As part of the partnership, Coforge will act as VHC Health’s end-to-end transformation partner across infrastructure, cloud, digital workplace, and cybersecurity services. The scope includes enhancing the caregiver and clinician experience, exiting legacy data centres and migrating to AWS, transforming the network, and enabling hi-trust security to strengthen VHC Health’s overall cyber resilience. These efforts are designed to facilitate long-term, scalable digital transformation in alignment with clinical and operational priorities. "This milestone marks Coforge’s significant expansion in the healthcare provider market and strengthens its Provider Experience Management capabilities,” the company stated. The transformation roadmap will begin with the implementation of IT Service Management processes using ServiceNow, followed by the deployment of Coforge’s AI-driven EvolveOps.AI and SecureOps solutions to enhance service availability, operational resilience, and security, while supporting a proactive, outcomes-driven operating model. Delivery will be facilitated through the creation of a resilient hybrid delivery model tailored for healthcare provider needs. Sudhir Singh, CEO and executive director, Coforge, said: "Healthcare is a key growth engine for Coforge. We are proud to partner with VHC Health on this transformational journey and to support their mission of delivering exceptional patient care through a modern, secure digital foundation." Coforge is a global tech services and solutions provider, that leverages emerging technologies and deep domain expertise to deliver real-world business impact for its clients. The company had reported 33.4% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 250.2 crore despite a 5.1% increase in gross revenues to Rs 4,188.1 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoforgeLtd_47640546_24978.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1679613</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679613</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 02 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 02 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: ICICI Prudential Balanced Advantage Fund: Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW: 0.07 Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW: 0.07 ICICI Prudential Equity & Debt Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.16 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.16

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Canara Robeco MF announces Monthly Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/canara-robeco-mf-announces-monthly-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1679612</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679612</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Canara Robeco Mutual Fund has announced 27 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of quarterly & monthly Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Canara Robeco Mutual Fund has announced 27 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of quarterly & monthly Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The quantum of dividend (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Canara Robeco ELSS Tax Saver Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.22 Canara Robeco ELSS Tax Saver Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.99 Canara Robeco Equity Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.70 Canara Robeco Equity Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option:0.60 Canara Robeco Conservative Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.10 Canara Robeco Conservative Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option:0.10

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions IPO ends with 94% subscription]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/clean-max-enviro-energy-solutions-ipo-ends-with-94-subscription/1679610</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679610</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions 2,05,69,556 received bids for 75,07,654 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer.

The initial public offer (IPO) of Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions 2,05,69,556 received bids for 75,07,654 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.94 times. The Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 2.83 times, the Non-Institutional Investors category was subscribed 0.54 times, and the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 0.06 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it closed on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 14 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue comprised fresh equity shares, aggregating Rs 1,200 crore, and an offer-for-sale (OFS) of equity shares, aggregating Rs 1,900 crore. The OFS by the promoters includes equity shares aggregating Rs 216.799 crore by Kuldeep Jain, Rs 903.898 crore by BGTF One Holdings, and Rs 73 crore by KEMPINC LLP. The OFS by selling shareholders aggregates Rs 541.921 crore, and by DSDG Holdings Rs 164.382 crore. Of the net proceeds, Rs 1122.674 crore will be used for repayment and/or prepayment, in part or full, of all or certain outstanding borrowings and/or certain subsidiaries, and the balance for general corporate purposes. Total borrowings stood at Rs 10,121.46 crore as of 30 September 2025. Ahead of the IPO, Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions, on 20 February 2026, raised Rs 920.99 crore from anchor investors by allotting 87.46 lakh shares at Rs 1,053 each to 41 anchor investors. CleanMax is India's largest commercial and industrial (C&I) renewable energy provider, with a 2799 MW operational capacity portfolio as of 31 October 2025. Additionally, a capacity of 3,044 MW was in an advanced stage, 3,172 MW was contracted, and 1,914 MW was under development. With 15 years of experience since inception, CleanMax specializes in delivering net zero and decarbonization solutions, including supplying renewable power and energy services and carbon credit solutions across data centers, AI and technology industries, and C&I enterprises across a range of sectors, including infrastructure, cement, steel, industrial manufacturing, FMCG, pharmaceuticals, real estate, and global capability centers. The company’s expertise spans across providing energy contracting, engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) services, and operation and maintenance (O&M) services of renewable energy plants, including solar, wind and hybrid plants, within the customer‘s premises (onsite) and within in-house-developed renewable energy (solar, wind, and hybrid) farms (offsite). Renewable energy power sales revenue as a percentage of revenue from operations amounted to 77.09% and 74.03% in H1FY2026 and FY 2025. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 15.44 crore and income from operations of Rs 932.95 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks jumps on inking agreement with NEC to manufacture 5G massive MIMO radios]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-jumps-on-inking-agreement-with-nec-to-manufacture-5g-massive-mimo-radios/1679607</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679607</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Masayuki Kayahara, Corporate Senior Vice President of Global Network Division at NEC Corporation said, “Today’s milestone furthers our collaboration with Tejas Networks for 5G massive MIMO radio and to achieve supply-chain diversification which helps in mitigating risks to our customers by building a resilient, flexible globalized ecosystem.” Arnob Roy, Chief Operating Officer and Executive Director of Tejas Networks said, “Our partnership with NEC will accelerate wireless innovation by leveraging our respective expertise in carrier-class product development for global telcos.

Masayuki Kayahara, Corporate Senior Vice President of Global Network Division at NEC Corporation said, “Today’s milestone furthers our collaboration with Tejas Networks for 5G massive MIMO radio and to achieve supply-chain diversification which helps in mitigating risks to our customers by building a resilient, flexible globalized ecosystem.” Arnob Roy, Chief Operating Officer and Executive Director of Tejas Networks said, “Our partnership with NEC will accelerate wireless innovation by leveraging our respective expertise in carrier-class product development for global telcos. We will continue to work closely with NEC to co-create leading-edge 5G/5G-Advanced solutions that meet the evolving needs of customers worldwide.” Sanjay Malik, Chief Strategy and Business Officer of Tejas Networks said, “We are delighted to win this deal in partnership with NEC as we expand our business internationally. We are looking forward to building on this momentum and replicate this success in other 4G/5G mobile networks across emerging and established markets.” Tejas Networks designs and manufactures wireline and wireless networking products, with a focus on technology, innovation, and R&D. TNL carrier-class products are used by telecom service providers, utilities, governments, and defense networks in 75+ countries. Tejas Networks is a part of the Tata Group, with Panatone Finvest (a subsidiary of Tata Sons) being the majority shareholder. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 196.55 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 165.67 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,500 level; IT shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25500-level-it-shares-rally/1679614</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679614</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains during the morning trade, extending their recovery for the second consecutive day.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains during the morning trade, extending their recovery for the second consecutive day. The upward momentum was largely driven by strong buying interest in IT stocks, which helped keep the market in positive territory. Major IT players such as Tech Mahindra and HCL Tech emerged among the top gainers, supporting the broader rally. The Nifty traded above the 25,500 level. IT shares advanced for the second consecutive trading session. At 10:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 174.51 points or 0.21% to 82,450.58. The Nifty 50 index gained 64.55 points or 0.25% to 25,547.05. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.52% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.35%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,324 shares rose and 1,244 shares fell. A total of 218 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index surged 1.59% to 31,013.05. The index rallied 3.19% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Persistent Systems (up 2.89%), Oracle Financial Services Software (up 2.09%), Tech Mahindra (up 1.98%), Mphasis (up 1.35%), Infosys (up 1.23%), LTIMindtree (up 1.16%), HCL Technologies (up 1.04%), Tata Consultancy Services (up 1.02%), Coforge (up 0.77%) and Wipro (up 0.24%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Websol Energy System added 1.39% after the company secured three purchase orders aggregating 85.5 MW for the supply of solar modules, with a total contract value of Rs 172 crore. Shaily Engineering Plastics advanced 2.66% after the company secured a manufacturing and commercial supply agreement worth approximately Rs 423 crore from a large domestic pharmaceutical company for the supply of pen injectors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baroda-bnp-paribas-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1679608</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679608</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 27 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes.

Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 27 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.12 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.14 per unit Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.39 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.41 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.17 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Balanced Advantage Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.18 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>