<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:29:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concor throughputs climb 11% to 14.23 lakh TEUs in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concor-throughputs-climb-11-to-1423-lakh-teus-in-q3-fy26/1664333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664333</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Export import (EXIM) throughput increased 9.94% to Rs 10,72,145 TEUs during the quarter from 9,75,243 TEUs Domestic (DOM) throughputs jumped 13.43% to Rs 3,51,121 TEUs in Q3 FY26, compared with 3,09,551 TEUs in Q3 FY25.

Export import (EXIM) throughput increased 9.94% to Rs 10,72,145 TEUs during the quarter from 9,75,243 TEUs Domestic (DOM) throughputs jumped 13.43% to Rs 3,51,121 TEUs in Q3 FY26, compared with 3,09,551 TEUs in Q3 FY25. Container Corporation of India (CONCOR) is engaged in the business of providing inland transportation of containers by rail. It also covers the management of ports and air cargo complexes and establishes cold chains. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 3.6% to Rs 378.70 crore on 2.9% increase in net sales to Rs 2,354.53 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter declined 0.35% to Rs 510.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ContainerCorpn_89474429441_12607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jash Engineering bags orders worth Rs 74 crore in December; orderbook rises to Rs 912 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jash-engineering-bags-orders-worth-rs-74-crore-in-december-orderbook-rises-to-rs-912-crore/1664332</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664332</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Out of the total orders, contracts worth Rs 28 crore are for Indian market while the remaining ones, which are worth Rs 46 crore, are for markets outside India.

Out of the total orders, contracts worth Rs 28 crore are for Indian market while the remaining ones, which are worth Rs 46 crore, are for markets outside India. The significant contributors to the monthly order booking of December 2025 are Enviro Infra Engineers (Delhi), Reliance Industries (Mumbai) & Vindhya Telelinks (Rewa) from India and REC Engineering (Hong Kong) & Cartersville WPCP Expansion (USA) from international market. As on 01 January 2026, the total consolidated order book position of the company is Rs. 912 crore. Out of this, orders worth Rs 284 crore are for Indian market and orders worth Rs 628 crore are for markets outside India. As on 01 January 2026, consolidated orders worth Rs 31 crore have been negotiated with clients and formal purchase orders for the same are awaited. Jash Engineering manufactures engineering products for wastewater treatment. The company offers products for use in water and wastewater pumping stations and treatment plants, storm water pumping stations, water transmission lines, desalination, power, steel, cement, paper & pulp, petrochemicals, chemicals, fertilisers and other process plants. The company's consolidated net profit declined 30.29% to Rs 11.16 crore despite a 12.87% increase in revenue to Rs 157.54 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip fell 1.44% to currently trade at Rs 404 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JashEngineeringLtd_71537208307_39683.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Worth Peripherals Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/worth-peripherals-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1664330</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664330</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and Palm Jewels Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 January 2026.

California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and Palm Jewels Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 January 2026. Worth Peripherals Ltd lost 12.17% to Rs 134.9 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 697 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 482 shares in the past one month. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup tumbled 10.20% to Rs 4.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1849 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2259 shares in the past one month. Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd crashed 9.53% to Rs 1090. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 81509 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13390 shares in the past one month. Rollatainers Ltd pared 9.50% to Rs 1.62. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 12286 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.23 lakh shares in the past one month. Palm Jewels Ltd dropped 9.44% to Rs 20.53. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 26655 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22440 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WorthPeripheralsLtd_81529932771_71405.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade with small gains; FMCG shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-with-small-gains-fmcg-shares-advance/1664329</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664329</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in mid-afternoon trade amid positive global cues supported by positive comments from US Ambassador to India, Sergio Gor.

The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in mid-afternoon trade amid positive global cues supported by positive comments from US Ambassador to India, Sergio Gor. The market recovered from oversold levels and moved slightly higher during the session. Investors will monitor India –US trade deal, Q3 earnings and other geopolitical news. The Nifty traded above the 25,700 level after touching day’s low of 25,473.40 in early afternoon trade. FMCG shares advanced after declining in the past three consecutive trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex rose 108.79 points or 0.13% to 83,692.07. The Nifty 50 index added 32.20 points or 0.13% to 25,718.40. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.86% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.89%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,360 shares rose and 2,859 shares fell. A total of 214 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 5.17% to 11.49. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index rose 0.62% to 52,764.85. The index fell 2.09% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Godrej Consumer Products (up 1.63%), Tata Consumer Products (up 1.44%), Hindustan Unilever (up 1.24%), Emami (up 1.24%), Nestle India (up 0.99%), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (up 0.70%), ITC (up 0.5%), Varun Beverages (up 0.34%), Dabur India (up 0.31%) and Marico (up 0.05%) advanced. On the other hand, Radico Khaitan (down 4.04%), United Breweries (down 2.1%) and Britannia Industries (down 0.89%) edged lower. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.38% to 6.611 compared with previous session close of 6.636. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1700 compared with its close of 89.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 2% to Rs 141,590. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.41% to 98.48. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.65% to 4.199. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement lost 19 cents or 0.30% to $63.15 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Embassy Developments hit an upper circuit of 5% after the company reported pre-sales of approximately Rs 1,392 crore in Q3 FY26, up 240% QoQ from Rs 409 crore in Q2 FY26. Alembic Pharmaceuticals shed 0.11%. The company announced that it has received tentative approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) for its supplemental Abbreviated New Drug Application (sANDA) for Bosutinib Tablets, 400 mg.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Tejas Networks Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-tejas-networks-ltd-counter/1664327</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664327</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IFCI Ltd, Linde India Ltd, Aditya Birla Real Estate Ltd, Maharashtra Scooters Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 12 January 2026.

IFCI Ltd, Linde India Ltd, Aditya Birla Real Estate Ltd, Maharashtra Scooters Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 12 January 2026. Tejas Networks Ltd recorded volume of 159.74 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 19.32 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 8.27 lakh shares. The stock lost 10.67% to Rs.372.65. Volumes stood at 34.6 lakh shares in the last session. IFCI Ltd witnessed volume of 1623.07 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 16.17 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 100.35 lakh shares. The stock increased 12.32% to Rs.55.05. Volumes stood at 40.73 lakh shares in the last session. Linde India Ltd saw volume of 2.67 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.68 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 17037 shares. The stock increased 3.45% to Rs.6,111.50. Volumes stood at 21219 shares in the last session. Aditya Birla Real Estate Ltd saw volume of 4 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.96 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 80611 shares. The stock dropped 3.15% to Rs.1,569.90. Volumes stood at 1.14 lakh shares in the last session. Maharashtra Scooters Ltd witnessed volume of 13977 shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 3.96 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3529 shares. The stock dropped 4.48% to Rs.12,935.00. Volumes stood at 2562 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Websol Energy gets Andhra Pradesh govt nod for 4-GW solar cell, module plant]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/websol-energy-gets-andhra-pradesh-govt-nod-for-4-gw-solar-cell-module-plant/1664325</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664325</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approval was granted through a government order issued by the state’s Industries & Commerce Department, following a memorandum of understanding signed with the Andhra Pradesh Economic Development Board (APEDB) on November 15, 2025, the company said in a statement.

The approval was granted through a government order issued by the state’s Industries & Commerce Department, following a memorandum of understanding signed with the Andhra Pradesh Economic Development Board (APEDB) on November 15, 2025, the company said in a statement. Under the approval, the state government has extended an incentive package that includes allotment of land, fixed capital investment subsidy, power tariff reimbursement, electricity duty exemption, subsidy on industrial water charges, and exemption from stamp duty and registration charges. As part of the project, Websol also plans to set up a 100 MW captive solar power plant to support the manufacturing facility. The captive plant is expected to ensure reliable access to renewable energy and help achieve operating cost efficiencies, the company added. Commenting on this Government Order, Sohan Lal Agarwal, MD, Websol Energy System said: “As India advances its renewable energy ambitions alongside the Atmanirbhar Bharat initiative, the approval received from the Government of Andhra Pradesh allows Websol to make a meaningful and exciting contribution with its own expansion plans. The supportive industrial ecosystem in Andhra Pradesh provides a strong manufacturing platform for executing our 4 GW solar cell and 4 GW solar module growth strategy. We look forward to keeping our stakeholders updated on the developments of this expansion plan.” Websol Energy System manufactures solar photovoltaic cells and modules in India. The company supplies solar cells primarily within India, supporting module manufacturers to comply with Domestic Content Requirement norms, while its modules are marketed both in India and internationally. The company reported a standalone net profit of Rs 46.32 crore in Q2 FY26, up 10.3% from Rs 41.98 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 17.2% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 168.22 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Websol Energy System rose 0.77% to Rs 83.79 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WebsolEnergy_85060500051_4320.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold adds $100 in fresh breakout as risk aversion spikes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-adds-100-in-fresh-breakout-as-risk-aversion-spikes/1664324</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664324</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold extended its strong rally on Monday, rising more than 2% to a fresh record high of $4,612 per ounce, as political uncertainty and heightened geopolitical tensions boosted demand for safe-haven assets.

Gold extended its strong rally on Monday, rising more than 2% to a fresh record high of $4,612 per ounce, as political uncertainty and heightened geopolitical tensions boosted demand for safe-haven assets. Concerns over the Federal Reserve’s independence and a softer US dollar, easing toward 98.5, further supported bullion prices. The move was reinforced by expectations of US rate cuts after December jobs data showed a sharper-than-expected slowdown in hiring. Markets are pricing in two rate reductions this year, while attention now turns to this week’s US inflation report for clues on the Fed’s policy outlook. Geopolitical risks remained elevated as protests in Iran entered a third week, keeping risk sentiment fragile. In the domestic market, MCX February gold futures climbed nearly 2% to ₹1,41,500 per 10 grams, mirroring the global surge in prices.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro speculative net longs stay near two and half year high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-speculative-net-longs-stay-near-two-and-half-year-high/1664322</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664322</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market stays at a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market stays at a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of Euro futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net long position of 162812 contracts in the data reported through January 06, 2025. This was a weekly addition of 5351 net long contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Crisil-IBX Gilt Index-April 2026 Index Fund Merger into Tata Short Term Bond Fund]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-crisil-ibx-gilt-index-april-2026-index-fund-merger-into-tata-short-term-bond-fund/1664321</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664321</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Mutual Fund has approved the merger of Tata Crisil-IBX Gilt Index-April 2026 Index Fund Merger into Tata Short Term Bond Fund, with effect from 14 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Embassy Developments rises as Q3 FY26 pre-sales jump 240% QoQ to Rs 1,392 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/embassy-developments-rises-as-q3-fy26-pre-sales-jump-240-qoq-to-rs-1392-cr/1664320</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664320</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Collections during the quarter stood at approximately Rs 415 crore, marking a 15% QoQ increase from Rs 359 crore in Q2 FY26.

Collections during the quarter stood at approximately Rs 415 crore, marking a 15% QoQ increase from Rs 359 crore in Q2 FY26. Cumulative collections for 9M FY26 reached approximately Rs 1,096 crore. During the quarter, the company received RERA approvals for four projects: Embassy Citadel (Worli, Mumbai), Embassy Greenshore (North Bengaluru), Embassy Eden (North Bengaluru), and Embassy Verde Phase II (North Bengaluru), with aggregate GDV exceeding approximately Rs 12,800 crore. The company also secured the Occupancy Certificate (OC) for 239 apartments at Serene Amara, a senior living project being developed in a joint venture with Columbia Pacific Communities in Bengaluru. Based on current momentum and pipeline visibility, Embassy Developments remains on track to achieve its full-year pre-sales guidance of approximately Rs 5,000 crore for FY26. As of 31 December 2025, the company’s net institutional debt stood at approximately Rs 2,939 crore. Embassy Developments is engaged in residential real estate development across affordable, premium, and uber-luxury segments. The company focuses on the construction and development of residential, commercial, and SEZ projects across major Indian metro cities, with a strategic emphasis on the MMR and NCR regions. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 153.32 crore in Q2 FY26, widening from a net loss of Rs 34.34 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 3.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 493.11 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndbullRealEst_49523889882_27800.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TRUSTMF Banking & PSU Fund Merger into TRUSTMF Corporate Bond Fund]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trustmf-banking-psu-fund-merger-into-trustmf-corporate-bond-fund/1664319</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664319</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TRUST Mutual Fund has approved the merger of TRUSTMF Banking & PSU Fund Merger into TRUSTMF Corporate Bond Fund, with effect from 11 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alembic Pharma receives USFDA tentative approval for Bosutinib Tablets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alembic-pharma-receives-usfda-tentative-approval-for-bosutinib-tablets/1664318</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664318</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Bosulif Tablets, 400 mg, of PF Prism C.V.

The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Bosulif Tablets, 400 mg, of PF Prism C.V. Bosutinib is a kinase inhibitor indicated for the treatment of adult patients with chronic-phase Philadelphia chromosome–positive (Ph+) chronic myelogenous leukemia (CML), including newly diagnosed patients as well as those resistant or intolerant to prior therapy. It is also indicated for adult patients with accelerated- or blast-phase Ph+ CML who are resistant or intolerant to earlier treatment. Alembic had earlier received final approvals for Bosutinib Tablets in 100 mg and 500 mg strengths. The 400 mg strength has an estimated market size of about $251 million for the 12 months ended September 2025, according to IQVIA. With this approval, Alembic’s cumulative ANDA approvals from the USFDA stand at 232, comprising 212 final approvals and 20 tentative approvals. Alembic Pharmaceuticals is a vertically integrated research and development pharmaceutical company engaged in the manufacture and marketing of generic pharmaceutical products across global markets. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 20.40% to Rs 184.71 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 153.41 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations grew 15.90% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,910.15 crore in Q2 September 2025. Shares of Alembic Pharmaceuticals shed 0.51% to Rs 795.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlembicPharma_46538273359_40294.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty inch up on positive global cues; European mrkt decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-inch-up-on-positive-global-cues-european-mrkt-decline/1664317</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664317</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with minor gains in afternoon trade amid positive global cues supported by positive comments from US Ambassador to India, Sergio Gor.

The key equity indices traded with minor gains in afternoon trade amid positive global cues supported by positive comments from US Ambassador to India, Sergio Gor. The market recovered from oversold levels and moved slightly higher during the session. Investors will monitor India –US trade deal, Q3 earnings and other geopolitical news. The Nifty traded near 25,700 level after touching day’s low of 25,473.40 in early afternoon trade Realty, Media and pharma shares declined while metal, FMCG and private bank shares advanced. At 13:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex added 21.97 points or 0.03% to 83,598.21. The Nifty 50 index advanced 4.20 points or 0.02% to 25,695.80. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.95% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.12%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,314 shares rose and 2,883 shares fell. A total of 204 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Coal India (up 2.96%), Hindalco Industries (up 2.29%), Tata Steel (up 2.07%), Asian Paints (up 1.67%) and Trent (up 1.67%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Eicher Motors (down 1.55%), Eternal (down 0.90%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (TMPV) (down 0.85%), Bharat Electronics (BEL) (down 0.78%) and Titan Company (down 0.75%) were the major Nifty50 losers. India-US Trade deal: Ambassador of United States (US), Sergio Gor announced that India and U.S. to discuss trade issues tomorrow. Further, he added that he hope President Donald Trump will visit India in next one-two years. Additionally, Gor also announced that India will be a member of the Pax Silica alliance. "I am pleased to announce that India will be invited to join this group of nations as a full member next month," he said. Stocks in Spotlight: Avenue Supermarts (Dmart) rose 0.13%. The company consolidated net profit rallied 18.26% to Rs 855.92 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 723.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 13.32% to Rs 18,100.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15,972.55 crore in Q3 FY26. Tejas Networks tumbled 10.74% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 196.55 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 165.67 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) rallied 3.40% after the company’s consolidated net profit rallied 15.42% to Rs 1,381.36 crore on 26.80% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 6,135.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Globus Spirits declined 2.03%. The company’s standalone net profit skyrocketed over fifteen times to Rs 31.42 crore on a 19.1% increase in revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) to Rs 716.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shakti Pumps India rallied 4.92% after the company received letter of award (LoA) for setting up 16,780 stand‐alone off‐grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems (SPWPS) pumps in Karnataka. The contract is valued at Rs 654.03 crore and is expected to be executed on or before 31st March 2026. Signatureglobal (India) dropped 5.82% after the company flagged a slowdown in demand and said it will miss its earlier pre-sales guidance for FY26. In a regulatory filing on 11 January 2026, the real estate developer reported a 27% decline in pre-sales to Rs 20,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with 27,700 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Maruti Suzuki India rose 0.23%. The company said that its board approved the acquisition of land at the Khoraj Industrial Estate from Gujarat Industrial Development Corporation (GIDC) to expand production capacity, driven by growing market demand, including exports. Cupid advanced 2.97% after the company announced that a meeting of the board of directors will be held on Thursday, 29 January 2026, to consider the declaration of bonus shares and the Q3 results. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) shed 0.46%. The company reported a 25.41% increase in production to 68,992 units in December 2025, compared with 55,015 units in December 2024. Global Markets: European market declined as investors weigh geopolitical developments in Iran, and renewed pressure on Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Asian market advanced on Monday following Wall Street gains from last week after a U.S. job report showed that unemployment rate fell, signaling resilience in the labor market. Japanese markets were closed for a holiday. Investors will be keeping an eye on oil prices as Iran entered a third week of protests, which have reportedly seen more than 500 people killed. President Donald Trump is weighing options for intervention in Iran, media reports said. On Sunday, Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s coalition partner, Hirofumi Yoshimura, said that she may call an early general election. His comments come after domestic media reported that Takaichi was considering a snap election in February, citing government sources. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 rose to new highs on Friday, notching a weekly gain, following the release of the latest jobs report. The broad market index closed up 0.65% to 6,966.28, a fresh record close. It also notched a new all-time intraday high in the session. The Nasdaq Composite gained 0.81% to 23,671.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 237.96 points, or 0.48%, to end at 49,504.07, scoring a new closing record as well. The December jobs report showed nonfarm payrolls increasing by 50,000 last month, less than the 73,000 estimate that was widely reported in the media. That data, though slightly weaker than expected, showed a U.S. economy that’s still trudging along, with investors anticipating that growth will ramp up. The unemployment rate inched down to 4.4%, while widely circulated media reports had provided a forecast of 4.5%. Traders took that as a sign that improvement in the economy would happen soon.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664307</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664307</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 350.3, down 1.09% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25705.2. The Sensex is at 83596.42, up 0.02%.Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd has gained around 0.91% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28087.65, down 0.8% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 62.75 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 134.36 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 350.8, down 1.14% on the day. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd tumbled 22.95% in last one year as compared to a 11.35% rally in NIFTY and a 24.49% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 19.71 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataMotors_19446492084_560.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Uno Minda Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uno-minda-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664308</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664308</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Uno Minda Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Uno Minda Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1214, down 2.86% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25705.2. The Sensex is at 83596.42, up 0.02%.Uno Minda Ltd has eased around 2.05% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Uno Minda Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28087.65, down 0.8% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.86 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.66 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1217.3, down 2.9% on the day. Uno Minda Ltd jumped 17.19% in last one year as compared to a 11.35% rally in NIFTY and a 24.49% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 76.09 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MindaInds_25112038741_12295.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-grid-corporation-of-india-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1664309</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664309</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 257.65, down 0.14% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25705.2. The Sensex is at 83596.42, up 0.02%.Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has lost around 1.74% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.13% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34409.3, down 0.37% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 62.25 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 101.03 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 257.85, down 0.35% on the day. Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd tumbled 10.41% in last one year as compared to a 11.35% rally in NIFTY and a 5.09% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 15.58 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerGridCorpn_89479008350_5455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SJVN Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sjvn-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1664310</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664310</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SJVN Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

SJVN Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 77.94, down 0.24% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25705.2. The Sensex is at 83596.42, up 0.02%.SJVN Ltd has gained around 7.62% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which SJVN Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.13% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34409.3, down 0.37% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 46.49 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 139.72 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 38.29 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SJVN_64650197956_12076.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Castrol India Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/castrol-india-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664311</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664311</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Castrol India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Castrol India Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 186.78, down 0.99% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25705.2. The Sensex is at 83596.42, up 0.02%.Castrol India Ltd has added around 1.72% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Castrol India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.13% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34409.3, down 0.37% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 26.58 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 50.45 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 19.1 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CastrolIndia_44457458795_292.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Gas Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-gas-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1664312</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664312</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Gujarat Gas Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 414.65, down 2.4% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25705.2. The Sensex is at 83596.42, up 0.02%.Gujarat Gas Ltd has added around 5.63% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Gujarat Gas Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.13% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34409.3, down 0.37% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.17 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.11 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 26.15 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujaratGas_6190462003_43934.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-state-petronet-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1664313</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664313</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd is quoting at Rs 303.65, down 2.41% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The stock tumbled 10.41% in last one year as compared to a 11.35% rally in NIFTY and a 5.09% spurt in the Nifty Energy index.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujStPetronet_95223652929_24065.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>