<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:31:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty holds 25,300 level; metal shares shine ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-holds-25300-level-metal-shares-shine/1667962</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667962</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks remained firmly higher in mid-morning trade, buoyed by optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and FII inflows.

The key equity benchmarks remained firmly higher in mid-morning trade, buoyed by optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and FII inflows. Investors are closely tracking rupee movements, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements, and geopolitical developments, with attention also on upcoming Q3 results from Larsen & Toubro, Maruti Suzuki India, and BHEL. Meanwhile, the Nifty traded above the 25,300 level. Metal stocks extend gains for second straight session. At 11:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 511.04 points or 0.62% to 82,368.52. The Nifty 50 index rose 159.50 points or 0.63% to 25,335.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.95% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.89%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,631 shares rose and 1,264 shares fell. A total of 186 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 3.97% to 13.58. Indian Politics: Ajit Pawar, NCP chief and Maharashtra’s Deputy Chief Minister, died in a plane crash near Baramati on Wednesday while travelling from Mumbai. Four others, including the pilots and his security personnel, were also killed. The small aircraft, a Learjet 45 operated by VSR, reportedly crashed during a landing attempt near Baramati airport about 45 minutes after take-off, as Pawar was on his way to attend public meetings ahead of the local body polls. s Television visuals showed fire and wreckage at the site, while media reports said all five people on board died. The 66-year-old leader was the nephew of Sharad Pawar and the cousin of Supriya Sule, both of whom were in Delhi and were expected to travel to Pune. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index surged 2.53% to 12,129.20, logging a cumulative gain of 5.68% over the last two sessions. Hindustan Copper (up 8.5%), National Aluminium Company (up 4.47%), Vedanta (up 4.34%), Hindalco Industries (up 3.05%) and NMDC (up 2.11%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 1.65%), Adani Enterprises (up 1.61%), Welspun Corp (up 1.52%), APL Apollo Tubes (up 1.4%) and Tata Steel (up 1.24%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Mahindra Logistics surged 14.36% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25 Mahindra Logistics surged 14.65% to Rs 337 after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25.. Motilal Oswal Financial Services surged 9.65% after the company reported a strong set of earnings for the quarter ended December 2025. The company’s profit after tax (PAT), including treasury income and other comprehensive income (OCI), jumped 58% year on year to Rs 721 crore in Q3 FY26, aided by healthy traction in its asset and private wealth management businesses. Total revenue improved 11% to Rs 1,497 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,345 crore in Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets were mixed Wednesday, breaking ranks with Wall Street after the S&P 500 closed at a record high. Meanwhile, Australia saw its headline inflation come in at 3.6% for the last quarter of 2025, its highest level of inflation in six quarters. Overnight in the U.S., the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.91% to settle at 23,817.10, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average broke ranks, losing 408.99 points, or 0.83%, and settling at 49,003.4 while S&P 500 added 0.41% to end at 6,978.60. The S&P 500 futures edged higher ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision and earnings reports from major tech companies. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Financial zooms as Q3 PAT jumps 58% YoY to Rs 721 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/motilal-oswal-financial-zooms-as-q3-pat-jumps-58-yoy-to-rs-721-cr/1667960</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667960</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s profit after tax (PAT), including treasury income and other comprehensive income (OCI), jumped 58% year on year to Rs 721 crore in Q3 FY26, aided by healthy traction in its asset and private wealth management businesses.

The company’s profit after tax (PAT), including treasury income and other comprehensive income (OCI), jumped 58% year on year to Rs 721 crore in Q3 FY26, aided by healthy traction in its asset and private wealth management businesses. Total revenue improved 11% to Rs 1,497 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,345 crore in Q3 FY25. The company said it has recorded highest-ever operating profit after tax of Rs 611 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, grew 16% year on year. Motilal Oswal Financial Services’ asset management business posted a robust 65% year-on-year jump in PAT to Rs 227 crore in Q3 FY26. Total assets under management (AUM) grew 33% YoY to Rs 1.89 lakh crore, led by stellar growth in Mutual Fund AUM (up 40%) and Private Alternates AUM (up 62%). The company’s net mutual fund inflows market share remained strong at 7.6%, with systematic investment plan (SIP) inflows surging 55% YoY to Rs 4,515 crore, securing the highest market share at 5%. In the private fund space, the IBEF Fund V, launched in Q2 FY26, has raised a cumulative Rs 8,000 crore so far, with the final close expected in Q4. The company also launched its maiden Private Credit Fund in January 2026, targeting a fund size of Rs 3,000 crore. Motilal Oswal Financial Services’ private wealth management segment reported a PAT of Rs 82 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by net inflows of Rs 4,314 crore. Assets under management (AUM) rose 31% YoY to Rs 1.96 lakh crore, driven by family acquisitions and improved productivity of relationship managers. Annual recurring revenue (ARR) grew 28% YoY. The company’s wealth management segment reported a PAT of Rs 181 crore in Q3 FY26. Brokerage revenue grew 15% sequentially, while cash volume market share remained strong at 6.9% and F&O premium market share rose to 8.4%. Total blended average daily turnover (ADTO) market share stood at 7.8%. The distribution book expanded 34% YoY to Rs 42,775 crore, with the ARR book up 33%. The loan book also grew 25% YoY to Rs 6,630 crore, reflecting strong business traction across key products. Motilal Oswal Financial Services’ capital markets segment reported a PAT of Rs 70 crore in Q3 FY26, up 15% YoY. The company retained its #1 ranking across IPOs and QIPs in CY25 and covers 350 companies through its institutional research, servicing around 903 clients. The housing finance business posted a PAT of Rs 42 crore, up 12% YoY, with AUM rising 24% YoY to Rs 5,379 crore. Adjusted for a one-time change in disbursement recognition, disbursements grew 47% to Rs 578 crore (reported Rs 364 crore). The treasury book expanded 16% YoY to Rs 9,562 crore. Since inception, the book has delivered a healthy XIRR of 18.5% and has grown at a 42% CAGR, supported by reinvestment of operating profits. The board of directors of Motilal Oswal Financial Services, at its meeting held on Tuesday, 27 January 2026, approved an interim dividend of Rs 6 per equity share (face value Re 1 each) for FY26, to be paid out of the company’s profits. The record date for the interim dividend has been fixed as Saturday, 31 January 2026. The dividend will be paid to all equity shareholders whose names appear in the company’s register of members or depositories as of the record date. The interim dividend is scheduled to be paid on or before 25 February 2026. MOFSL is a financial services company. Its offerings include wealth management, capital markets (institutional broking & investment banking), asset & private wealth management (asset management, private equity & private wealth management), housing finance & equity based treasury investments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MotilalOswalFinancialServicesLtd_15371720_28011.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1667961</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667961</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Tata Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Nikunj Kumar Singhal has been designated as Key Personnel – Fund Manager at Tata Asset Management Pvt. Ltd., effective from the above-mentioned date. Details of Mr. Nikunj Kumar Singhal Age: 35 years Designation: Fund Manager Qualification: M.Tech (Industrial Engineering & Management) and B.Tech (Manufacturing Science & Engineering)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen holds near three-month high as BoJ signals further tightening]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-holds-near-three-month-high-as-boj-signals-further-tightening/1667957</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667957</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen hovered near 152.5 per dollar in Asian trade, holding close to a nearly three-month high as Bank of Japan minutes reinforced expectations of further rate hikes.

The Japanese yen hovered near 152.5 per dollar in Asian trade, holding close to a nearly three-month high as Bank of Japan minutes reinforced expectations of further rate hikes. Policymakers signaled growing confidence in a sustained wage-price cycle, widening the policy gap with the US, where rate cuts are still expected in 2026. The BoJ also noted that Japan’s economy is recovering moderately, though pockets of weakness persist. Some board members cautioned that excessive yen weakness could push up underlying inflation, urging careful timing of future rate increases. Meanwhile, Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s pledge to abolish food sales tax for two years ahead of the February 8 election added fiscal uncertainty, keeping markets alert to policy risks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/invesco-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1667958</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667958</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 28 January 2026.

Invesco Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 28 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Name of Existing Fund Manager(s) Name of New Fund Manager(s) Invesco India Large & Mid Cap Fund Mr. Aditya Khemani & Mr. Amit Ganatra Mr. Aditya Khemani Invesco India Contra Fund Mr. Taher Badshah & Mr. Amit Ganatra Mr. Taher Badshah Invesco India MidCap Fund Mr. Aditya Khemani & Mr. Amit Ganatra Mr. Aditya Khemani Invesco India Flexi Cap Fund Mr. Amit Ganatra & Mr. Taher Badshah Mr. Taher Badshah Invesco India Manufacturing Fund Mr. Amit Ganatra & Mr. Nikhil Kale Mr.Nikhil Kale Invesco India Business Cycle Fund Mr. Aditya Khemani & Mr. Amit Ganatra Mr. Aditya Khemani Invesco India Balanced Advantage Fund Mr. Amey Sathe & Mr. Amit Ganatra (Equity Investments) Mr. Manish Kalani (Arbitrage Investments) Mr. Krishna Cheemalapati (Debt Investments) Mr. Amey Sathe (Equity Investments) Mr. Manish Kalani (Arbitrage Investments) Mr. Krishna Cheemalapati (Debt Investments) Invesco India Consumption Fund Mr. Manish Poddar & Mr. Amit Ganatra Mr. Manish Poddar

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-j-b-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-counter/1667945</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667945</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[eClerx Services Ltd, Bajaj Finserv Ltd, Marico Ltd, Force Motors Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 28 January 2026.

eClerx Services Ltd, Bajaj Finserv Ltd, Marico Ltd, Force Motors Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 28 January 2026. J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd recorded volume of 2.11 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 62.37 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3382 shares. The stock lost 1.29% to Rs.1,857.00. Volumes stood at 2097 shares in the last session. eClerx Services Ltd registered volume of 2.11 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 34.71 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6080 shares. The stock slipped 0.07% to Rs.4,401.80. Volumes stood at 2896 shares in the last session. Bajaj Finserv Ltd notched up volume of 20.44 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 22.17 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 92220 shares. The stock rose 0.82% to Rs.1,931.40. Volumes stood at 63797 shares in the last session. Marico Ltd witnessed volume of 4.93 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 15.15 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 32546 shares. The stock dropped 3.03% to Rs.723.30. Volumes stood at 36396 shares in the last session. Force Motors Ltd registered volume of 87933 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 10.69 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 8227 shares. The stock rose 0.25% to Rs.18,845.00. Volumes stood at 14290 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JBChemPharm_56046055785_303.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INDIA-EU FTA unlocks access to $572.3 billion EU Pharmaceuticals & Medical devices market ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-eu-fta-unlocks-access-to-5723-billion-eu-pharmaceuticals-medical-devices-market/1667903</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667903</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India and the European Union (EU) announced the conclusion of negotiations for a Free Trade Agreement (FTA), an important milestone in one of India’s most strategic economic partnerships.

India and the European Union (EU) announced the conclusion of negotiations for a Free Trade Agreement (FTA), an important milestone in one of India’s most strategic economic partnerships. Designed as a modern, rules-based trade partnership, the FTA responds to contemporary global challenges while enabling deeper market integration between the world’s 4th and 2nd largest economies. The FTA unlocks access to the $572.3 billion EU pharmaceuticals & medical devices market giving impetus to the Indian Pharmaceuticals sector. This would enable Pharma industries to scale, generate employment, and reinforce India’s positioning as a reliable partner in the pharmaceuticals sector underlining its growing stature as the pharmacy of the world .It is expected to expand skilled jobs, industrial employment, stronger MSME participation and strengthen global supply chain integration.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/piggy-bank-with-doctors-stethoscope-picture-id490672108_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Logistics spurts on reporting turnaround Q3 numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-logistics-spurts-on-reporting-turnaround-q3-numbers/1667904</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667904</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 19.05% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,898.03 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 19.05% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,898.03 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 19.80 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a pre-tax loss of Rs 1.15 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 7.36 crore during the quarter under review. EBITDA stood at Rs 102.8 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of 39% compared with Rs 73.7 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 17.60% to Rs 1,883.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 1,601.57 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating expenses was at Rs 1,640.32 crore (up 18.75% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 110.20 crore (up 8.80% YoY) and finance cost was at Rs 16.52 crore (down 25.07% YoY) during the period under review. On a nine-month basis, the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 17.90 crore in 9M FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 29.10 crore in 9M FY25, while revenue jumped 14.82% YoY to Rs 5,207.89 crore in 9M FY26. Hemant Sikka, Managing Director and CEO of Mahindra Logistics said, “Q3 FY26 marks a defining inflection point for Mahindra Logistics. After 11 straight quarters of losses, we have returned to profitability, driven by sharper execution, stronger cost discipline, and a more focused growth strategy. Over the past few months, we have stabilized our leadership structure, strengthened alignment across the organization, and rebuilt execution rigor on the ground. Our actions are translating into visible operational improvements — both in margin expansion and revenue growth. We are also making disciplined choices by exiting unviable relationships and selectively investing in high-return opportunities. The transformation underway at Mahindra Logistics is real, systemic, and accelerating. Our priorities remain clear — drive profitable growth, enhance customer satisfaction, and build a high quality, future ready revenue base. Most importantly, our confidence comes from delivery on the ground, not just intent. We are well positioned to build on this momentum in the quarters ahead.” Mahindra Logistics (MLL) is an integrated third-party logistics (3PL) service provider, specializing in supply chain management and enterprise mobility.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahindraLogisticsLtd_50743986006_36025.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ONGC jumps after entering shipbuilding pact with Samsung Heavy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ongc-jumps-after-entering-shipbuilding-pact-with-samsung-heavy/1667900</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667900</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contracts were signed on 27 January 2026 through ONGC's joint venture companies with Japan's Mitsui O.S.K.

The contracts were signed on 27 January 2026 through ONGC's joint venture companies with Japan's Mitsui O.S.K. Lines (MOL). The shipbuilding agreement was executed with Samsung Heavy Industries of South Korea. The two vessels will be owned and operated by Bharat Ethane One IFSC and Bharat Ethane Two IFSC Both entities are incorporated at GIFT City, Gujarat. Each joint venture will own one vessel. The Very Large Ethane Carriers will have a cargo capacity of about one lakh cubic metres each. They will transport ethane from the US to India under long-term time charter agreements signed with ONGC. The vessels are expected to support the transportation of nearly 600 thousand tonnes per annum of ethane for ONGC Petro additions Ltd (OPaL), a subsidiary of ONGC. Delivery is scheduled for FY 2028-29. ONGC said the initiative will help secure specialised marine logistics for critical feedstock. It is also expected to improve supply-chain resilience and ensure continuity of operations for downstream petrochemical units. The project has been undertaken with the support of the Ministry of Petroleum and Natural Gas and the Department of Investment and Public Asset Management. Maharatna ONGC is the largest crude oil and natural gas company in India, contributing around 71% to Indian domestic production. It has in-house service capabilities in all areas of exploration and production of oil & gas and related oil-field services. The Government of India held a 58.89% stake in ONGC as of December 2025. The company reported 5.4% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 10,785 crore on 0.9% fall in gross revenue to Rs 1,57,911 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ONGC_65712746772_6068.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sunteck Realty rises after Q3 PAT climbs 34% YoY to Rs 57 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sunteck-realty-rises-after-q3-pat-climbs-34-yoy-to-rs-57-cr/1667902</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667902</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 77.99 crore, up 57.8% YoY during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 77.99 crore, up 57.8% YoY during the quarter. EBITDA soared 70.83% to Rs 82 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 48 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin moderated to 24% in Q3 FY26 as against 30% in Q3 FY25. Pre-sales jumped 15.59% to Rs 734 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 635 crore posted in the corresponding quarter last year. Collections stood at Rs 319 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 5.06% YoY decline from Rs 336 crore in Q3 FY25. Net operating cash flow surplus improved 12% YoY to Rs 349 crore, according to the exchange filing. During Q3 FY26, Sunteck Realty acquired a 1.75-acre land parcel at Andheri near Mumbai’s international airport, marking its third strategic acquisition in the current financial year. The new project has an estimated gross development value (GDV) of Rs 2,500 crore, according to the company’s exchange filing. Sunteck Realty is a Mumbai-based luxury real estate developer with a development portfolio of 50 million square feet across 32 projects.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SunteckRealty_87854270132_6838.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gopal Snacks surges after PAT rises nearly 3x to Rs 15.5 crore in Q3 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gopal-snacks-surges-after-pat-rises-nearly-3x-to-rs-155-crore-in-q3/1667898</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667898</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operation rose by 1.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 400.8 crore in Q3 FY26.

Total revenue from operation rose by 1.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 400.8 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA almost doubled to Rs 30.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 15.5 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 was 7.6% as against 3.9% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 19.0 crore in Q3 FY26, which is over 1.5 times the pre-tax profit of Rs 7.5 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Bipinbhai Hadvani, chairman and MD said: "As we reflect on Q3 FY2026, it has been marked by steady progress, decisive action and continued operational stability for Gopal Snacks. The quarter saw the successful ramp-up of our Modasa facility and the ongoing recovery from the disruptions caused by the fire incident at our Rajkot I manufacturing facility in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, we focused on scaling production at our Modasa plant, which has now become a pivotal part of our manufacturing base. This facility, with an added installed capacity of 63,085 MT, is focused on Gathiya and Namkeen and its operationalization has significantly strengthened our production capabilities. Additionally, we continued to work with third-party manufacturers to ensure a seamless supply of products to the market, further mitigating any potential disruptions. In terms of operational performance, the Snack Pellets segment saw a 20.8% QoQ growth, driven by strong consumer demand and improved production efficiencies. The Gathiya segment experienced a 10.6% QoQ growth, reflecting higher sales and better utilization of production capacity. During the quarter, our focus on core and focus markets remained strong, supported by 93 micro-distributors under the SSD model to deepen our regional penetration. This initiative has enabled us to strengthen our presence in untapped regions, ensuring better product availability across a wider geography. The growth in Other States has been particularly strong, with an increase of 28.7% YoY, reflecting the success of our regional expansion strategy. Furthermore, the expansion of our distribution network has played a key role in driving sales growth and improving market reach." Gopal Snacks is a leading manufacturer of packaged snacks in India, offering a diverse portfolio that includes gathiya, namkeen, wafers, snack pellets, extruded snacks, and other products such as papad, besan, spices, and bakery items. It has six manufacturing facilities supported by in-house cold storage and a network of ancillary units. Its products reach consumers through an extensive distribution network of over 850 distributors and nearly 300 owned logistics vehicles, supported by advanced distribution management systems.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GopalSnacksLtd_21235410_77239.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade higher; oil & gas shares gain for 2nd day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-higher-oil-gas-shares-gain-for-2nd-day/1667897</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667897</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks extended their gains in morning trade, buoyed by optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA).

The key equity benchmarks extended their gains in morning trade, buoyed by optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA). Investors are closely tracking rupee movements, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements, and geopolitical developments, with attention also on upcoming Q3 results from Larsen & Toubro, Maruti Suzuki India, and BHEL. Meanwhile, the Nifty hovered above the 25,350 mark. Oil & gas shares jumped for two consecutive trading session. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 339.37 points or 0.37% to 82,202.08. The Nifty 50 index rose 139.65 points or 0.55% to 25,315.05. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.60% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.67%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,462 shares rose and 1,213 shares fell. A total of 215 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Larsen & Toubro(up 0.87%), Maruti Suzuki India(down 2.40%), Bharat Electronics(up 0.04%), TVS Motor Company(down 1.25%), SBI Life Insurance Company(up 0.30%), ACC(up 0.20%), Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services(up 2.23%), Aditya Birla Real Estate(up 1.42%), Balkrishna Industries(up 0.49%), CarTrade Tech(up 3.03%), CSB Bank(up 4.59%), Gland Pharma(up 0.58%), ICRA(up 0.43%), Lodha Developers(up 1.37%), National Securities Depository, (up 1.44%) Pine Labs(up 2.88%), SBI Cards and Payment Services(up 2.43%), Star Health and Allied Insurance Company(up 1.37%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. New listing: Shares of Shadowfax Technologies were currently trading at Rs 118.15 at 10:24 IST on the BSE, representing a discount of 4.72% as compared with the issue price of Rs 124. The stock debuted at Rs 113 on the BSE, exhibiting a discount of 8.87% over the issue price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 119.55 and a low of 113. On the BSE, over 15.50 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index advanced 2.57% to 11,669.25. The index jumped 3.21% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Oil India (up 7.88%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (up 6.51%), Aegis Logistics (up 4.18%), Petronet LNG (up 3.93%) and GAIL (India) (up 2.89%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (up 2.35%), Indian Oil Corporation (up 2.01%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (up 1.61%), Gujarat State Petronet (up 1.36%) and Reliance Industries (up 1.25%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Bondada Engineering declined 3.62%. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 119.12% to Rs 54.19 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 24.73 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 89.40% year on year (YoY) to Rs 712.27 crore in Q3 FY26. Nesco shed 0.64%. The company reported a 4.82% YoY decline in net profit to Rs 104.64 crore in Q3 FY26, on a 20.03% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 247.92 crore compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI announces Rs 1 lakh crore OMO, $10 bn USD/INR swap to inject liquidity]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-announces-rs-1-lakh-crore-omo-10-bn-usdinr-swap-to-inject-liquidity/1667855</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667855</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India on Tuesday announced that it would conduct OMO purchase auctions of Government of India securities for an aggregate amount of ₹1,00,000 crore in two tranches of ₹50,000 crore each on January 29 and February 5 as against February 05, 2026, and February 12, 2026 mentioned earlier.

The Reserve Bank of India on Tuesday announced that it would conduct OMO purchase auctions of Government of India securities for an aggregate amount of ₹1,00,000 crore in two tranches of ₹50,000 crore each on January 29 and February 5 as against February 05, 2026, and February 12, 2026 mentioned earlier. The Reserve Bank further stated that it reserves the right to decide on the quantum of purchase of individual securities, accept offers for less than the aggregate amount, purchase marginally higher/lower than the aggregate amount due to rounding-off, accept or reject any or all the offers either wholly or partially without assigning any reasons. RBI also said it will be conducting a USD/INR Buy/Sell swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of three years to inject liquidity into the banking system.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1667854</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667854</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs. per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Bandhan Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.146 Bandhan Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.166 Bandhan Equity Savings Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.055 Bandhan Equity Savings Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.058

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI, ESMA sign a MoU on cooperation and exchange of information related to Central Counterparties]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-esma-sign-a-mou-on-cooperation-and-exchange-of-information-related-to-central-counterparties/1667853</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667853</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) and the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) concerning cooperation and exchange of information in relation to Central Counterparties (CCPs) regulated and supervised by RBI, the RBI said in a statement.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) and the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) concerning cooperation and exchange of information in relation to Central Counterparties (CCPs) regulated and supervised by RBI, the RBI said in a statement. This MoU replaces an earlier MoU between RBI and ESMA which was entered into on February 28, 2017. The MoU enables RBI and ESMA to cooperate regarding CCPs, in line with their respective laws and regulations. The MoU establishes a framework for ESMA to place reliance on RBI’s regulatory and supervisory activities while safeguarding the European Union’s financial stability. The MoU also demonstrates the importance of cross-border cooperation to facilitate international clearing activities.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies lists at discount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shadowfax-technologies-lists-at-discount/1667851</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667851</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock debuted at Rs 113 on the BSE, exhibiting a discount of 8.87% over the issue price.

The stock debuted at Rs 113 on the BSE, exhibiting a discount of 8.87% over the issue price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 119.35 and a low of 113. On the BSE, over 10.44 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 24,23,88,360 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 2.72 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 January 2026 and it closed on 22 January 2026. The Rs 1,907 crore IPO comprised a fresh issue of 80.6 million equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,000 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 73.2 million equity shares worth up to Rs 907.27 crore. Existing investors—Flipkart India, Eight Roads Investments Mauritius II, International Finance Corporation, Qualcomm Asia Pacific, Nokia Growth Partners, NewQuest Asia Fund and Mirae Asset—had offloaded part of their holdings through the OFS. Shadowfax plans to utilize Rs 423.43 crore from the net proceeds of the fresh issue to enhance network infrastructure capacity, Rs 138.64 crore towards lease payments for new first-mile, last-mile, and sort centres, and Rs 88.57 crore for branding, marketing and communication initiatives. The balance had been earmarked for unidentified inorganic acquisitions and general corporate purposes. Shadowfax Technologies is a leading Indian logistics and 3PL player providing e-commerce, D2C, quick commerce and hyperlocal delivery services. It operates a nationwide network covering over 14,700 pin codes and serves major clients such as Flipkart, Meesho, Swiggy, Zomato, Blinkit, and Nykaa. The company is among the fastest-growing large-scale logistics providers, with rising market share and strong order growth. Ahead of the IPO of Shadowfax Technologies on 19 January 2026, the company raised Rs 856.02 crore from anchor investors by allotting 6.90 crore shares at Rs 124 each to 39 anchor investors. For the three months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 21.04 crore and sales of Rs 1,805.64 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SHADOWFAXTECHNOLOGIESLIMITED_24534425_78712.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends rebound; Deep losses in dollar supports]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-rebound-deep-losses-in-dollar-supports/1667831</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667831</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee extends rebound in opening trades on Wednesday tracking deep losses in dollar overseas coupled with positive cues from local equities.

The Indian rupee extends rebound in opening trades on Wednesday tracking deep losses in dollar overseas coupled with positive cues from local equities. INR opened at Rs 91.60 per dollar and hit a high of 91.57 before easing back to 91.64 so far during the day. Domestic shares are seen opening higher on Wednesday amid trade optimism after Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal said the ambitious India-EU free trade agreement is likely to be implemented within the 2026 calendar year. Yesterday, INR rebounded from its all-time low levels and gained 19 paise to close at 91.71 against the US dollar, amid weakness in US dollar index and India-EU FTA announcement. The deal over India-EU FTA boosted domestic market sentiments. Local equities also ended modestly higher after India and the European Union confirmed that they had signed a historic trade pact. The giant free trade deal will cut or eliminate tariffs on almost 97 percent of European exports, saving up to 4 billion euros ($4.75 billion) annually in duties, the 27-nation bloc said. For India, the tariff cuts with the EU will lead to more exports in labor intensive sectors that will help partly offset the impact of U.S. tariffs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bondada Engineering Q3 PAT skyrockets 119% YoY to Rs 54 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bondada-engineering-q3-pat-skyrockets-119-yoy-to-rs-54-cr/1667827</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667827</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 89.40% year on year (YoY) to Rs 712.27 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operations jumped 89.40% year on year (YoY) to Rs 712.27 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 73.27 crore in the December 2025 quarter, registering a growth of 123.52% on a YoY basis. Total expenses increased 85.72% YoY to Rs 643.62 crore during the quarter. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 643.62 crore (up 108.18% YoY), employee benefit expenses were Rs 14.74 crore (up 25.87% YoY) and finance costs jumped 94.27% YoY to Rs 94.27 crore during the period under review. On the segmental front, revenue from the EPC business stood at Rs 627.91 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a year-on-year growth of 109.26%. Revenue from the services business came in at Rs 39.76 crore, up 5.10%, while revenue from the products business rose 16.87% to Rs 44.60 crore. Bondada Engineering provides engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) services and operations and maintenance (O&M) services to companies operating in the telecom and solar energy industry. Shares of Bondada Engineering tanked 2.93% to Rs 314.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BondadaEngineeringLtd_97234508_91662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,350 mark; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25350-mark-breadth-strong/1667821</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667821</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with strong gains in early trade, buoyed by optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA).

The key equity benchmarks traded with strong gains in early trade, buoyed by optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA). Investors are closely tracking rupee movements, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements, and geopolitical developments. Market participants are also awaiting Q3 results from Larsen & Toubro, Maruti Suzuki India, and BHEL. Meanwhile, the Nifty traded above the 25,350 mark. Oil & Gas, media and realty shares advanced while FMCG and PSU Bank shares declined. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 598.24 points or 0.73% to 82,459.68. The Nifty 50 index rose 184.15 points or 0.74% to 25,362.35. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.81% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.80%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,215 shares rose and 778 shares fell. A total of 168 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,068.49 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 8,999.71 crore in the Indian equity market on 27 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Marico shed 0.43%. The company reported a 12.03% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 447 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 399 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 26.59% YoY to Rs 3,537 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Motilal Oswal Financial Services rallied 6.04% after the company reported a marginal 0.25% YoY rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 566 crore, while revenue from operations increased 5.9% to Rs 2,111.7 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Metro Brands surged 8.05% after the company reported consolidated net profit rose 35.7% to Rs 128.4 crore on a 15.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 811.3 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was flat at 6.719 In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6050 compared with its close of 91.6850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement added 2.02% to Rs 160,886. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.37% to 96.10. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.21% to 4.232. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement advanced 37 cents or 0.55% to $67.94 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets were mixed Wednesday, breaking ranks with Wall Street after the S&P 500 closed at a record high. Meanwhile, Australia saw its headline inflation come in at 3.6% for the last quarter of 2025, its highest level of inflation in six quarters. Overnight in the U.S., the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.91% to settle at 23,817.10, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average broke ranks, losing 408.99 points, or 0.83%, and settling at 49,003.4 while S&P 500 added 0.41% to end at 6,978.60. The S&P 500 futures inched up ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision and earnings reports from major tech companies. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd Spikes 4.22%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-ltd-spikes-422/1667817</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667817</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd rose 4.22% today to trade at Rs 308.95.

Tejas Networks Ltd rose 4.22% today to trade at Rs 308.95. The BSE Telecommunication index is up 0.55% to quote at 2875.43. The index is down 8.6 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, ADC India Communications Ltd increased 3.28% and ITI Ltd added 2.13% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 6.52 % over last one year compared to the 7.89% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Tejas Networks Ltd has lost 32.21% over last one month compared to 8.6% fall in BSE Telecommunication index and 3.31% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 7554 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 2 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 973.9 on 27 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 294.1 on 27 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>