<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PPFAS Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ppfas-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1679979</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679979</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PPFAS Mutual Fund has announced that Ms.

PPFAS Mutual Fund has announced that Ms. Sonal Dave has been appointed as an Independent Director with effect from February 17, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Ms. Sonal Dave Age: 61 years Designation: Independent Director Qualification: B. Com, Chartered Accountant .

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vishal Mega Mart promoter Samayat Services sells 14% stake for Rs 7,635 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vishal-mega-mart-promoter-samayat-services-sells-14-stake-for-rs-7635-crore/1679973</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679973</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Samayat Services LLP, a promoter entity of Vishal Mega Mart, has divested nearly a 14% stake in the supermarket chain through open market transactions, raising Rs 7,635.55 crore on Friday, 27 February 2026.

Samayat Services LLP, a promoter entity of Vishal Mega Mart, has divested nearly a 14% stake in the supermarket chain through open market transactions, raising Rs 7,635.55 crore on Friday, 27 February 2026. According to bulk deal data on the NSE, Samayat Services sold 65.25 crore equity shares in two tranches at prices ranging between Rs 117 and Rs 117.03 per share. The sale represents a 13.96% stake in the Gurugram-based retailer. Following the transaction, the promoter’s holding in Vishal Mega Mart declined to 40.13% from 54.09%. On the buy side, a clutch of large institutional investors absorbed a significant portion of the stake. The Government of Singapore acquired 12.69 crore shares, translating into a 2.72% holding, while HDFC Mutual Fund picked up 9.40 crore shares or a 2.01% stake. The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) purchased 7.33 crore shares, representing a 1.57% stake. Collectively, these investors bought over 29.42 crore shares, or 6.3% equity, at an average price of Rs 117 per share, with the aggregate deal value pegged at Rs 3,443.17 crore. Samayat Services LLP has been gradually trimming its holding in the company since Vishal Mega Mart’s listing in December 2024. In June 2025, it had sold around 90 crore shares, representing a 19.6% stake, for about Rs 10,220 crore. Several large institutional investors, including SBI Mutual Fund and HDFC Mutual Fund, had participated in that earlier transaction. Vishal Mega Mart is a leading retail player. It offers products across three major product categories, i.e., apparel, general merchandise and FMCG, through a pan-India network of 771 Vishal Mega Mart stores as of 31 December 2025 and Vishal Mega Mart mobile application and website. It reported a 19.10% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 312.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 262.72 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 17.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 3,670.41 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of Vishal Mega Mart slumped 7.68% to settle at Rs 117.80 on Friday, 27 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VishalMegaMartLtd_95033477_86391.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quality Power Electrical bags orders worth Rs 34-cr for supply of HVDC reactors]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quality-power-electrical-bags-orders-worth-rs-34-cr-for-supply-of-hvdc-reactors/1679972</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679972</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders have been awarded by a domestic entity.

The orders have been awarded by a domestic entity. However, the name of the awarding entity has not been disclosed due to a non-disclosure agreement (NDA), the company clarified. The contracts pertain to the supply of HVDC reactors and are scheduled to be executed over a period of approximately 18 months. The company further stated that the promoter, promoter group, and group companies have no interest in the entity awarding the orders. It also confirmed that the contracts do not fall under related party transactions. Quality Power Electrical Equipment is engaged in the business of energy transition equipment and power technologies. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 220.69% to Rs 62.76 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 19.57 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25. The counter declined 3.99% to end at Rs 868.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/QualityPowerElectricalEquipmentsLtd_48177673_54766.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1679974</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679974</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 March 2026.

SBI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 March 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager New Fund Manager SBI Nifty Index Fund SBI BSE Sensex Index Fund SBI Nifty Next 50 Index Fund SBI BSE SENSEX ETF SBI Nifty Next 50 ETF SBI Nifty Bank ETF SBI Nifty 50 ETF SBI Nifty 200 Quality 30 ETF SBI Gold Fund Mr. Raviprakash Mr. Viral Chhadva SBI Nifty Midcap 150 Index Fund SBI Nifty Smallcap 250 Index Fund SBI Nifty India Consumption Index Fund SBI Nifty Bank Index Fund SBI Nifty IT Index Fund SBI Nifty IT ETF SBI Nifty Private Bank ETF SBI Nifty Consumption ETF SBI Silver ETF Fund of Fund Mr. Harsh Sethi Mr. Viral Chhadva SBI Gold ETF SBI SILVER ETF Ms. Vandna Soni Mr. Viral Chhadva SBI Equity Minimum Variance SBI BSE SENSEX Next 50 ETF Mr. Raviprakash Sharma Mr. Harsh Sethi Ms. Sukanya Ghosh

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[H.G. Infra Engineering bags LOA from NHAI for Odisha road project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hg-infra-engineering-bags-loa-from-nhai-for-odisha-road-project/1679950</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679950</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package III, stretching from Gobindpur on NH-55 to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza on NH-16.

The project involves the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package III, stretching from Gobindpur on NH-55 to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza on NH-16. The total project length stands at 40.33 km. The project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode. While the estimated project cost is Rs 1,827.33 crore, HGINFRA's bid project cost stands at Rs 1,582.11 crore, excluding applicable GST. The construction period for the project is 910 days. HGINFRA is an infrastructure development company. The company specialises in executing end-to-end Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) services and Hybrid Annuity Model (HAM) projects across transport infrastructure, renewable energy, and Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) including Transmission. On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit fell 18.1% to Rs 94.28 crore on a 12.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,421.16 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of H.G. Infra Engineering fell 2.8% to settle at Rs 541.85 on Friday, 27 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HGInfraEngineeringLtd_52714149365_71631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta declared preferred bidder for Karnapodikonda bauxite block in Odisha]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-declared-preferred-bidder-for-karnapodikonda-bauxite-block-in-odisha/1679949</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679949</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said it received a 'Declaration of Preferred Bidder' notification from the Directorate of Mines and Geology, Government of Odisha, on 27 February 2026.

In a regulatory filing, the company said it received a 'Declaration of Preferred Bidder' notification from the Directorate of Mines and Geology, Government of Odisha, on 27 February 2026. The tender process was initiated through a Notice Inviting Tender dated 4 December 2025 for grant of a mining lease for the block. After qualifying at the initial bid stage, Vedanta participated in the live e-auction process and emerged as the preferred bidder. According to the tender document, the Karnapodikonda bauxite block is classified at the G2 level of exploration and spans a total area of 532.747 hectares. The company said the acquisition aligns with its strategic objective of backward integration for its aluminium business, strengthening long-term raw material security. Vedanta is a global producer of critical minerals, energy transition metals, power, and technology, with operations across India, South Africa, Namibia, Liberia, the UAE, Saudi Arabia, Korea, Taiwan, and Japan. It is the world’s largest integrated zinc producer, the fourth-largest silver producer, and among the top aluminium producers globally. Vedanta is also India’s only private oil and gas producer and one of the country’s largest private power generators. On a consolidated basis, Vedanta's net profit surged 60.98% to Rs 5,710 crore while revenue from operations jumped 36.95% YoY to Rs 23,369 crore in Q3 December 2025. Shares of Vedanta fell 2.56% to settle at Rs 718.45 on Friday, 27 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>