<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Home First Finance Company India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679700</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679700</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sagility Ltd, Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd and Tips Music Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 February 2026.

Sagility Ltd, Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd and Tips Music Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 February 2026. Home First Finance Company India Ltd tumbled 5.08% to Rs 1182.75 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.33 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18293 shares in the past one month. Sagility Ltd crashed 4.21% to Rs 40.98. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 17.51 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19.18 lakh shares in the past one month. Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd lost 3.92% to Rs 937.2. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 27279 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 55073 shares in the past one month. Aegis Logistics Ltd slipped 3.79% to Rs 699.7. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.37 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.05 lakh shares in the past one month. Tips Music Ltd corrected 3.36% to Rs 538.45. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3661 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6016 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HomeFirstFinanceCompanyIndiaLtd_56604898_71865.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar continues to dominate global foreign exchange transactions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-continues-to-dominate-global-foreign-exchange-transactions/1679701</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679701</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar is crucial for Americans and global markets alike, and its international standing affects investments, borrowing costs and everyday prices, noted a latest blog post from the St.

The US dollar is crucial for Americans and global markets alike, and its international standing affects investments, borrowing costs and everyday prices, noted a latest blog post from the St. Louis Federal Reserve. The US dollar (USD) is the most widely used, employed in 89% of foreign exchange transactions in 2025, according to data in the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) Triennial Central Bank Survey. The USD has been the dominant reserve currency since 1945, with dollar-denominated securities, mostly US Treasuries and investment-grade corporate bonds, making up approximately 57% of global foreign exchange reserves, for a value of $7.4 trillion, according to another IMF dataset, Currency Composition of Official Foreign Exchange Reserves (COFER), as of the third quarter of 2025. Euro-denominated securities are in second place, making up approximately 20% of global foreign exchange reserves. Governments and central banks hold large quantities of US dollar assets because the US government and corporations issue a large amount of dollar-denominated, liquid assets that are seen as safe. To earn such a reputation for its assets, the US has had solid legal and economic institutions and an open and generally well-regulated financial system. All these factors reduce the perceived risk of investing in such assets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/foreign-currency-exchange-rate-on-digital-led-display-scree_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dynacons Systems gains on bagging Rs 109-cr order from Punjab & Sind Bank]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dynacons-systems-gains-on-bagging-rs-109-cr-order-from-punjab-sind-bank/1679697</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679697</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The five-year domestic contract involves the design and implementation of IT infrastructure, underlying system software and cloud services to support the deployment and hosting of the bank’s applications, including its Data Center and Disaster Recovery (DC–DR) environment.

The five-year domestic contract involves the design and implementation of IT infrastructure, underlying system software and cloud services to support the deployment and hosting of the bank’s applications, including its Data Center and Disaster Recovery (DC–DR) environment. Dynacons will oversee the end-to-end execution of the project, ensuring infrastructure readiness and operational management over the contract tenure. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in Punjab & Sind Bank. It also stated that the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Dynacons Systems & Solutions provides IT infrastructure solutions. The company provides services nation wide. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 28% to Rs 23.48 crore on 9.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 340.59 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Punjab and Sind Bank is a leading public sector bank and a major bank in northern India. The bank provides customer service through innovative products and services for different customer segments. The bank’s standalone net profit jumped 19.3% to Rs 336.42 crore on 8.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3549.27 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip rose 0.62% to Rs 25.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DynaconsSys_66434123216_20947.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679695</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679695</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Usha Martin Education & Solutions Ltd, UR Sugar Industries Ltd, Flexituff Ventures International Ltd and Filatex Fashions Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 February 2026.

Usha Martin Education & Solutions Ltd, UR Sugar Industries Ltd, Flexituff Ventures International Ltd and Filatex Fashions Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 February 2026. R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd crashed 19.96% to Rs 78.4 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 19893 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.12 lakh shares in the past one month. Usha Martin Education & Solutions Ltd lost 12.90% to Rs 4.12. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 58560 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2247 shares in the past one month. UR Sugar Industries Ltd tumbled 10.58% to Rs 2.45. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.08 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.17 lakh shares in the past one month. Flexituff Ventures International Ltd fell 8.82% to Rs 9.82. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 153 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2677 shares in the past one month. Filatex Fashions Ltd pared 8.70% to Rs 0.21. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 170 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 149.74 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RMDripSprinklersSystemsLtd_34584827303_71578.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold trades soft as investors await US jobs and inflation numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-trades-soft-as-investors-await-us-jobs-and-inflation-numbers/1679689</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679689</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures slipped below $5200 per ounce in Asia on Thursday as investors remained cautious ahead of US unemployment data due today and key growth and inflation figures due on Friday.

Gold futures slipped below $5200 per ounce in Asia on Thursday as investors remained cautious ahead of US unemployment data due today and key growth and inflation figures due on Friday. Mild selling pressure was seen at higher levels, though losses were capped as geopolitical tensions in the Middle East, ongoing uncertainty over US trade policies, and a softer dollar index near 97.5 continued to support the metal close to four-week highs. The buildup of US troops ahead of nuclear talks in Geneva and fresh sanctions on Iran kept safe-haven demand intact, while expectations that the Federal Reserve will keep interest rates unchanged helped limit downside. In the domestic market, MCX April gold futures declined over 1% to Rs 159,384 per 10 grams, with immediate support seen around Rs 159,100 and Rs 158,850.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with moderate losses; realty shares extent losses for 4th day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-moderate-losses-realty-shares-extent-losses-for-4th-day/1679683</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679683</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The frontline equity benchmarks trade with limited losses in the mid-afternoon trade amid a shift toward a risk-off sentiment.

The frontline equity benchmarks trade with limited losses in the mid-afternoon trade amid a shift toward a risk-off sentiment. The Nifty traded below the 25,450 mark after hitting a day's high of 25,572.95 in early afternoon trade. Realty shares extended losses for the fourth consecutive trading session. At 14:27 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 155.38 points or 0.19% to 82,120.69. The Nifty 50 index fell 47.10 points or 0.18% to 25,435.90. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.17% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.14%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,921 shares rose and 2,136 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 0.42% to 793.50. The index fell 3.31% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Lodha Developers (down 2.15%), Godrej Properties (down 1.2%), SignatureGlobal India (down 1.1%), Sobha (down 1%), DLF (down 0.44%), Anant Raj (down 0.27%), Phoenix Mills (up 0.54%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.51%) and Brigade Enterprises (up 0.41%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.16% to 6.693 compared with the previous session close of 6.682. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.8800 compared with its close of 90.9100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 1.12% to Rs 159,333. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.02% to 97.64. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.02% to 4.050. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 16 cents or 0.23% to $70.85 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Praveg added 0.72%. The company has received a letter of award (LoA) from the Directorate of Tourism, Government of Meghalaya, for the development, operation and maintenance of luxury cottages at Umiam in Meghalaya. Diamond Power Infrastructure advanced 2.89% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 93.08 crore from KPI Green Energy for the supply of power cables.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at KSB Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-ksb-ltd-counter/1679682</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679682</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, Maharashtra Seamless Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 February 2026.

Tejas Networks Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, Maharashtra Seamless Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 February 2026. KSB Ltd clocked volume of 132.59 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 179.08 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 74039 shares. The stock gained 8.56% to Rs.778.50. Volumes stood at 2.29 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd registered volume of 493.21 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 59.93 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 8.23 lakh shares. The stock rose 13.44% to Rs.360.50. Volumes stood at 6.05 lakh shares in the last session. Home First Finance Company India Ltd witnessed volume of 67.92 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 46.22 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.47 lakh shares. The stock dropped 5.25% to Rs.1,182.30. Volumes stood at 3.89 lakh shares in the last session. Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd registered volume of 85.7 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.42 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 10.18 lakh shares. The stock slipped 1.13% to Rs.1,734.60. Volumes stood at 7.79 lakh shares in the last session. Maharashtra Seamless Ltd witnessed volume of 6.72 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.74 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 86793 shares. The stock increased 4.75% to Rs.570.55. Volumes stood at 1.2 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KSB_11705810441_342.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Praveg gains on secuing 30-year concession for luxury cottage project in Meghalaya]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/praveg-gains-on-secuing-30-year-concession-for-luxury-cottage-project-in-meghalaya/1679679</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679679</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project will be executed under the Design, Build, Finance, Operate and Transfer (DBFOT) model on a public-private partnership (PPP) basis.

The project will be executed under the Design, Build, Finance, Operate and Transfer (DBFOT) model on a public-private partnership (PPP) basis. Praveg has been selected as the bidder for the project, which involves the development of a minimum of 40 luxury cottages on approximately 10 acres of land, along with allied amenities and supporting infrastructure. The company is required to complete the development and make the project operational on a year-round basis within 18 months from the appointed date. The project carries a concession period of 30 years from the appointed date, offering long-term revenue visibility. The company expects strong performance from the upcoming resort, strengthening its presence in the premium eco-tourism segment. Dr. CA Vishnu Patel, Chairman and Managing Director of Praveg Limited, said, “We are pleased to receive the Letter of Award for this prestigious tourism infrastructure project at Umiam, Meghalaya. The project aligns with our strategy to expand ecoresponsible luxury hospitality offerings across emerging and high-potential destinations. We believe this development will deliver a distinctive guest experience while contributing to tourism growth, employment generation, regional economic development, and long-term value creation for all stakeholders.” Praveg is a pioneer in eco-responsible luxury hospitality. The Company’s resorts are located in areas of significance from a cultural and heritage point of view and places of exotic and natural beauty. The company's consolidated net profit rose 2.1% to Rs 9.28 crore on 66.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 90.45 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SwordShieldPharmaLtd_76272121902_6969.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil supported near one-week low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-supported-near-one-week-low/1679678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679678</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures posted marginal gains and held near $65 per barrel during Asian trade on Thursday, snapping a three-day losing streak as markets turned cautious ahead of a third round of US–Iran nuclear talks in Geneva.

WTI crude oil futures posted marginal gains and held near $65 per barrel during Asian trade on Thursday, snapping a three-day losing streak as markets turned cautious ahead of a third round of US–Iran nuclear talks in Geneva. Geopolitical risk lent some support amid concerns over military buildup in the Middle East and fresh US sanctions tied to Iran’s oil and weapons exports, alongside warnings of potential limited strikes if diplomacy fails. However, upside was restrained by a sharp rise in US crude inventories, with EIA data showing a 16-million-barrel build last week—the largest since February 2023. Adding to mixed sentiment, the dollar index slipped toward 97.5 as tariff uncertainty weighed on confidence. Oil had tested around one-week low following the slide in last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id4664857_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,450 mark; European mrkt decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25450-mark-european-mrkt-decline/1679676</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679676</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks trade with modest losses in the afternoon trade amid a shift toward a risk-off sentiment.

The domestic equity benchmarks trade with modest losses in the afternoon trade amid a shift toward a risk-off sentiment. The Nifty traded below the 25,450 mark after hitting day’s high of 25,572.95 in early afternoon trade. Pharma, auto and metal shares advanced while media, FMCG and realty stocks declined. At 13:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 171.97 points or 0.21% to 82,104.10. The Nifty 50 index fell 62.05 points or 0.24% to 25,420.45. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.03% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.20%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,937 shares rose and 2,053 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, advanced 0.07% to 13.50. Gainers & Losers: Tata Motors PV (up 2.21%), Max Healthcare (up 1.56%), Bharat Electronics (BEL) (up 1.46%), Eicher Motors (up 1.23%) and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) (up 0.90%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Power Grid Corporation of India (down 1.56%), Trent (down 1.53%), NTPC (down 1.52%), Coal India (down 1.44%) and Wipro (down 1.22%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Sundaram Clayton jumped 6.84% after the company’s board approved the appointment of R Venkatesh as chief executive officer (CEO) with effect from 1 April 2026. b The development comes after board approved the resignation of Vivek S Joshi as CEO with effect from 31st march 2026, due to personal reasons. Aurobindo Pharma rose 0.64% after the company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Eugia Pharma Specialities, has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) to manufacture and market Everolimus tablets. Capillary Technologies India declined 1.07%. The company has announced the acquisition of Session M Inc., a U.S.-based loyalty and customer engagement platform, from payments giant Mastercard Inc. in an all-cash deal valued at approximately $20 million. Alembic Pharmaceuticals fell 1.04%. The company announced that it has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA), Lamotrigine Orally Disintegrating Tablets USP, 25 mg, 50 mg, 100 mg, and 200 mg. Balu Forge Industries hit an upper circuit of 10% after it has entered into a legally binding memorandum of understanding (MoU) for the supply of empty artillery shells from its greenfield manufacturing facility in Belgaum, Karnataka. Tejas Networks soared 13.38% after the company announced that it has signed an agreement with NEC Corporation to manufacture and supply 5G massive MIMO radios. E2E Networks added 2.71% after the company announced that its board has approved the opening of the issue of qualified institutional placement (QIP) of equity shares. Global Markets: European market declined as investors awaited a raft of corporate earnings from major regional players, including Deutsche Telekom, Schneider Electric, Allianz, Rolls-Royce Holdings, AXA, Munich Re, London Stock Exchange Group, Stellantis and Covestro. Asian markets traded mixed with South Korea and Japan stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Diamond Power rises after bagging Rs 93.08-cr order from KPI Green Energy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/diamond-power-rises-after-bagging-rs-9308-cr-order-from-kpi-green-energy/1679671</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679671</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and will be executed on a "kms rate basis with PV formulae.” The contract is scheduled to be completed by 30 June 2026.

The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and will be executed on a "kms rate basis with PV formulae.” The contract is scheduled to be completed by 30 June 2026. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity. The contract does not fall under related party transactions. Diamond Power Infrastructure is engaged in the business of manufacturing transmission & distribution of power products & services in India. The company's consolidated net profit zoomed 693% to Rs 49.72 crore on a 54.2% surge in net sales to Rs 474.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DiamondPower_44345217117_3225.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd spurts 3.75%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tube-investments-of-india-ltd-spurts-375-up-for-third-straight-session/1679665</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679665</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Tube Investments of India Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2717, up 3.75% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.12% on the day, quoting at 25452.6. The Sensex is at 82117.03, down 0.19%. Tube Investments of India Ltd has added around 24.1% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Tube Investments of India Ltd is a constituent, has added around 7.39% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28466.5, up 0.18% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.57 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.36 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2725, up 3.74% on the day. Tube Investments of India Ltd is up 6.81% in last one year as compared to a 12.9% gain in NIFTY and a 33.66% gain in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 36.63 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TubeInvestmentsofIndiaLtd_81529932771_40963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE Ltd spurts 1.11%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-ltd-spurts-111-up-for-third-straight-session/1679666</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679666</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[BSE Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

BSE Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2803.4, up 1.11% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.12% on the day, quoting at 25452.6. The Sensex is at 82117.03, down 0.19%. BSE Ltd has added around 1.53% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which BSE Ltd is a constituent, has added around 4.42% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28339.65, down 0.3% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 24.58 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 58.74 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2807.4, up 0.71% on the day. BSE Ltd is up 62.91% in last one year as compared to a 12.9% gain in NIFTY and a 21.92% gain in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 58.81 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BSELtd_11315994_21236.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lloyds-metals-energy-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1679667</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679667</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1271.2, up 1.55% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.12% on the day, quoting at 25452.6. The Sensex is at 82117.03, down 0.19%. Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd has risen around 15.49% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 4.83% in last one month and is currently quoting at 12399.4, up 0.01% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.99 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.03 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 29.24 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsMetals_76757705405_2629.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma Ltd spurts 1.16%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aurobindo-pharma-ltd-spurts-116/1679668</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679668</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 1225.5, up 1.16% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.12% on the day, quoting at 25452.6. The Sensex is at 82117.03, down 0.19%. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd has risen around 8.48% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 6.36% in last one month and is currently quoting at 23051.85, up 0.53% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 14.57 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 22.48 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1229.4, up 0.67% on the day. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd is up 13.4% in last one year as compared to a 12.9% spurt in NIFTY and a 14.71% spurt in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 32.89 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurobindoPharma_66877283489_4666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/glenmark-pharmaceuticals-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1679669</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679669</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2107.3, up 1.07% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.12% on the day, quoting at 25452.6. The Sensex is at 82117.03, down 0.19%. Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd has gained around 5.38% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 6.36% in last one month and is currently quoting at 23051.85, up 0.53% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.37 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.7 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2115.8, up 0.94% on the day. Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd is up 60.45% in last one year as compared to a 12.9% jump in NIFTY and a 14.71% jump in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 39.65 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlenmarkPharma_43362397609_20600.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd up for fifth session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-ltd-up-for-fifth-session/1679657</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679657</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 5738, up 0.01% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25459.95. The Sensex is at 82146.86, down 0.16%. Hero MotoCorp Ltd has risen around 6.65% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Hero MotoCorp Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 7.44% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28466.5, up 0.22% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.61 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.81 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5758, down 0.23% on the day. Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up 52.62% in last one year as compared to a 12.93% spurt in NIFTY and a 33.71% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 22.78 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1679658</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679658</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

Hitachi Energy India Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 25397, up 1.64% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25459.95. The Sensex is at 82146.86, down 0.16%. Hitachi Energy India Ltd has added around 52% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Hitachi Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has added around 11.34% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37118.6, down 0.13% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 61593 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.79 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 25535, up 1.66% on the day. Hitachi Energy India Ltd is up 119.6% in last one year as compared to a 12.93% gain in NIFTY and a 20.9% gain in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 126.31 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HitachiEnergyIndiaLimited_51485438_74646.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Vernova T&D India Ltd spurts 1.17%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-vernova-td-india-ltd-spurts-117-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1679659</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679659</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GE Vernova T&D India Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

GE Vernova T&D India Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3860, up 1.17% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25459.95. The Sensex is at 82146.86, down 0.16%. GE Vernova T&D India Ltd has gained around 41.35% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which GE Vernova T&D India Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 11.34% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37118.6, down 0.13% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.49 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.78 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 87.42 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GETDIndia_25039636117_159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahanagar Gas Ltd soars 0.34%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahanagar-gas-ltd-soars-034-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1679660</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679660</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahanagar Gas Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Mahanagar Gas Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1205.1, up 0.34% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.09% on the day, quoting at 25459.95. The Sensex is at 82146.86, down 0.16%. Mahanagar Gas Ltd has risen around 17.16% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Mahanagar Gas Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 11.34% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37118.6, down 0.13% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.52 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 12.26 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahanagarGasLtd_64664984058_13369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>