<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vl-e-governance-it-solutions-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678867</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678867</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Abans Financial Services Ltd, Novartis India Ltd, Centum Electronics Ltd and BLB Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 February 2026.

Abans Financial Services Ltd, Novartis India Ltd, Centum Electronics Ltd and BLB Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 February 2026. VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd surged 19.94% to Rs 17.32 at 20-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 7.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.43 lakh shares in the past one month. Abans Financial Services Ltd soared 15.92% to Rs 233. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14179 shares in the past one month. Novartis India Ltd spiked 14.43% to Rs 950.25. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 8.22 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17776 shares in the past one month. Centum Electronics Ltd jumped 14.22% to Rs 2623.45. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 35572 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5040 shares in the past one month. BLB Ltd added 13.33% to Rs 20.4. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.05 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 26852 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VLEGovernanceITSolutionsLtd_93531239_76164.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AI has the potential to lift global annual GDP growth by up to 0.8 percentage points, says IMF’s Kristalina Georgieva ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ai-has-the-potential-to-lift-global-annual-gdp-growth-by-up-to-08-percentage-points-says-imfs-kristalina-georgieva/1678866</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678866</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[AI has arrived; it is here.

AI has arrived; it is here. Investment is surging into data centers, power plants, and neural networks. It is like when the world was building the railways: the old ways of doing things will be changed forever, and this time it will be much faster, said IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva at the India AI Impact Summit. AI will bring opportunity and challenge—and it is for us to maximize the benefits, she noted. IMF estimates, AI has the potential to lift global annual GDP growth by up to 0.8 percentage points. This is a vast upside potential, she stated but will massively transform the world of work. There will also be dislocation linked to the sheer pace of change—many jobs in the middle that AI will not enhance but rather replace, she noted. I worry about a hollowing out of the middle, for young call-center workers that may be replaced by bots, for IT graduates potentially replaced by algorithms. We must prepare, and the best preparation is to be open-eyed about the risks of AI and invest in people, IMF chief noted. Nevertheless, given the huge challenges of global AI diffusion, India knows the good it can do for others—with its digital interfaces and human ingenuity, it is on the forefront of making things happen, offering a unique focus on democratizing AI. And India has extensive experience in creating practical solutions for rural and urban communities, which can benefit low-income and developing countries across the world, she further noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/welcome-word-written-on-computer-keyboard-picture-id8567109_Analyst-Meet.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/krn-heat-exchanger-and-refrigeration-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1678862</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678862</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ABB India Ltd, Data Patterns (India) Ltd, Brainbees Solutions Ltd and Netweb Technologies India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 20 February 2026.

ABB India Ltd, Data Patterns (India) Ltd, Brainbees Solutions Ltd and Netweb Technologies India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 20 February 2026. KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd spiked 11.91% to Rs 882.3 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.11 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16136 shares in the past one month. ABB India Ltd soared 8.36% to Rs 6193.2. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.46 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17558 shares in the past one month. Data Patterns (India) Ltd surged 6.19% to Rs 3090.15. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.19 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 68487 shares in the past one month. Brainbees Solutions Ltd rose 5.71% to Rs 226. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 30.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.81 lakh shares in the past one month. Netweb Technologies India Ltd gained 5.66% to Rs 3730. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 5.23 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.63 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KRNHeatExchangerandRefrigerationLtd_36100110_92755.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Paras Defence gains after buying 49% stake in Himanshi Thermal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/paras-defence-gains-after-buying-49-stake-in-himanshi-thermal/1678859</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678859</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Himanshi Thermal is engaged in the business of manufacturing fabricated metal products (excluding machinery and equipment).

Himanshi Thermal is engaged in the business of manufacturing fabricated metal products (excluding machinery and equipment). It also specializes in the manufacturing of liquid cold plates for space and airborne applications and provides vacuum heat treatment services. The reported a turnover of Rs 2,15,740 in FY25. The company has acquired 4,900 shares of Himashi Thermal with a face value of Rs 10 each, aggregating to Rs 49,000. Following the acquisition, Himanshi Thermal has become an associate of the company. The said acquisition is expected to open new growth avenues and business opportunities for both organizations at group level, fostering a mutually advantageous partnership. Paras Defence and Space Technologies is primarily engaged in the designing, developing, manufacturing, and testing of a variety of defence and space engineering products and solutions. The company caters to four major segments - defence & space optics, defence electronics, heavy engineering, and electromagnetic pulse protection solutions. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 21.1% to Rs 18.21 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 15.04 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales climbed 24% YoY to Rs 106.35 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ParasDefenceandSpaceTechnologiesLtd_54552381_75439.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CIE Automotive clocks PAT of Rs 204 crore in Q4]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cie-automotive-clocks-pat-of-rs-204-crore-in-q4/1678860</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678860</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PBIDT improve by 7.2% to Rs 362.87 crore in Q4 2025 from Rs 338.61 crore in Q4 2024.

PBIDT improve by 7.2% to Rs 362.87 crore in Q4 2025 from Rs 338.61 crore in Q4 2024. Profit before tax in Q4 2025 stood at Rs 258.70 crore, up by 7.7% from Rs 240.20 crore recorded in Q4 2024. For the full year 2025, the company has recorded consolidated net profit and net sales of Rs 828.17 crore (up 0.1% YoY) and Rs 9,406.47 crore (up 4.9% YoY), respectively. CIE Automotive India is a multi-technology automotive components supplier. It is a subsidiary of the CIE Automotive group of Spain. The scrip shed 0.37% to currently trade at Rs 457.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CIEAutomotiveIndiaLtd_94417373_27486.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Meta Infotech rises after bagging orders worth Rs 4 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/meta-infotech-rises-after-bagging-orders-worth-rs-4-crore/1678858</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678858</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company received a fresh order worth Rs 2.58 crore from one of India’s leading stock exchanges for software subscription services for the period from 31 January 2026 to 31 January 2027.

The company received a fresh order worth Rs 2.58 crore from one of India’s leading stock exchanges for software subscription services for the period from 31 January 2026 to 31 January 2027. The contract entails a three-year commitment with annual renewal and is to be executed within 90 days. Further, the company has obtained a renewal order worth Rs 1.56 crore from a leading private sector bank for Database Activity Monitoring (DAM) licenses for the period from 4 January 2026 to 22 October 2026. The order is to be executed within 15 days. Both contracts are awarded by domestic entities. The promoter/promoter group has no interest in the awarding entities, and the transactions do not fall under related party transactions. Meta Infotech is engaged in trading and providing services related to cybersecurity software products. The company reported a 60.7% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 10.51 crore, while revenue from operations rose 40.3% to Rs 152.13 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MetaInfotechLtd_21921703_94283.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 397 pts; metal shares shine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-397-pts-metal-shares-shine/1678856</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678856</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade, as rising crude on US–Iran tensions weighed on sentiment, offset by bargain buying in selective stocks.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade, as rising crude on US–Iran tensions weighed on sentiment, offset by bargain buying in selective stocks. The Nifty traded above the 25,550 mark. Metal shares advanced after declining in the past trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 397.33 points or 0.48% to 82,895.47. The Nifty 50 index rose 134.35 points or 0.53% to 25,589.75. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.41% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.07%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,964 shares rose and 1,827 shares fell. A total of 211 shares were unchanged. Economy: HSBC India Services PMI eased to 58.4 in February, with exports rising fastest since August 2025, domestic demand easing, modestly faster hiring, and input costs hitting a 2.5-year high. Selling prices and business sentiment rose to a one-year peak. HSBC India Manufacturing PMI climbed to 57.5, led by strong domestic demand, modest export growth, higher employment, inputs, and inventories. Input and output prices rose, while sentiment remained positive. HSBC India Composite PMI hit 59.3, the highest since last November, as factory output, new orders, and foreign sales strengthened. Hiring improved, input costs rose to a 15-month high, selling prices to a six-month peak, and sentiment reached a one-year high on investment optimism. IPO Update: Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 45,93,456 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.31 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it closed on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index rose 1.11% to 11,974.30. The index declined 1.20% in the past trading session. Hindalco Industries (up 2.05%), Steel Authority of India (up 1.42%), Hindustan Copper (up 1.34%), Jindal Steel (up 1.31%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 1.3%), Tata Steel (up 1.16%), JSW Steel (up 1.12%), Jindal Stainless (up 1.06%), Hindustan Zinc (up 0.94%) and APL Apollo Tubes (up 0.77%) jumped. Stocks in Spotlight: ABB India rallied 7.68% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 5.82% to Rs 432.85 crore on 7.44% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3557.01 crore in Q4 CY25 over Q4 CY24. Zydus Lifesciences shed 0.36%. The company said the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) has completed a pre-approval inspection (PAI) at its Injectable Medical Devices facility in Ahmedabad with nil observations. Global Markets: Asian markets traded mixed on Friday, after all three major Wall Street indexes declined overnight, pressured by a drop in private credit stocks and Iran-U.S. tensions. Prospects of a strike on Iran have risen with U.S. President Donald Trump reportedly saying that he would take a call to decide on military action against Tehran in the next 10 days. This pushed Brent Crude higher, gaining 0.26%, to settle at $71.92. In Asia, investors assessed Japan's latest inflation data. The island nation's headline inflation rate fell from 2.1% in December to 1.5% in January, its lowest level since March 2022. The reading ended a run of 45 straight months in which inflation had remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target. The core inflation rate, which excludes fresh food prices, eased to 2%, the lowest level since January 2024. It was down from 2.4% in December. As per reports, despite the slowdown in headline inflation, the Bank of Japan is unlikely to delay rate hikes as fresh-food prices remain volatile, while energy costs fell after Japan scrapped its fuel tax in December. Japan’s manufacturing activity improved in February, with the S&P Global Japan Manufacturing PMI rising to 52.8 from 51.5 in January, marking the strongest expansion since May 2022. Growth was supported by firm domestic and overseas demand, with export orders rising at the fastest pace in eight years. While hiring growth eased from January’s peak, it remained solid. Input costs increased at a slightly faster pace. Manufacturers stayed optimistic about the year-ahead outlook, backed by stronger demand, semiconductor and AI-related orders, and ongoing product launches. Overnight on Wall Street, the US stocks closed lower on Thursday, pulling the S&P 500 close to flat for the year, as investors rotated out of financials and monitored escalating tensions between the US and Iran. Reflecting a surge in imports and a slump in exports, the Commerce Department released a report on Thursday showing the U.S. trade deficit unexpectedly widened in the month of December. The Commerce Department said the trade deficit grew to $70.3 billion in December from a revised $53.0 billion in November. The unexpectedly wider trade deficit partly reflected a continued surge in the value of imports, which shot up by 3.6 percent to $357.6 billion in December after spiking by 4.2 percent to $345.3 billion in November. The report also showed a continued slump in the value of exports, which tumbled by 1.7 percent to $287.3 billion in December after plunging by 3.4 percent to $292.3 billion in November. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 267.50 points, or 0.54%, closing at 49,395.16. The S&P 500 declined 0.28%, ending at 6,861.89, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.31% to 22,682.73. Financial stocks led the decline after Blue Owl Capital said it would tighten investor liquidity following the sale of $1.4 billion in loan assets, raising concerns about potential losses in the private credit market. Shares of Blue Owl dropped about 6%, while Blackstone and Apollo Global Management each fell more than 5%. Software stocks also remained under pressure amid persistent worries about artificial intelligence disruption. The sector has struggled in recent weeks as investors assess how AI could reshape enterprise software demand.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index hovers around one-month high; fast approaching 98 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-hovers-around-one-month-high-fast-approaching-98-mark/1678854</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678854</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index hovered around a one-month high as minutes from the Fed’s latest meeting showed policymakers divided on the rate outlook, suggesting the next chair may face hurdles in delivering cuts.

The dollar index hovered around a one-month high as minutes from the Fed’s latest meeting showed policymakers divided on the rate outlook, suggesting the next chair may face hurdles in delivering cuts. Data released by the US Department of Labor (DOL) on Thursday showed that the Initial Jobless Claims declined to 206,000 for the week ending February 14. This figure came in below the market consensus of 225,000 and down from the previous week’s revised 229,000. Meanwhile, developments surrounding a potential US-Iran conflict will be closely watched. Alongside, investors will also brace for the preliminary reading of US Gross Domestic Product (GDP) for the fourth quarter (Q4), the Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) and the S&P Global Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) data, which are due later on Friday. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 97.93, set for a weekly gain of over 1% and is seen fast approaching the next critical 98 mark.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar has been holding stable share of around 58 to 59% in international reserves since 2020]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-has-been-holding-stable-share-of-around-58-to-59-in-international-reserves-since-2020/1678851</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678851</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Julie Kozack, Director of the Communications Department, IMF has stated that the US dollar remains central to the international monetary system.

Julie Kozack, Director of the Communications Department, IMF has stated that the US dollar remains central to the international monetary system. It continues to dominate trade invoicing, international reserves, international borrowing, and global payments. And in all of these areas, the share of the dollar is larger than the US share in global GDP. She noted that role of the dollar has been broadly stable over time, with only a moderate decline in the share of the dollar in international reserves since the mid-2010s. According to the COFER data, the dollar has been holding onto a stable share of around 58 to 59 percent since 2020. The dollar has depreciated from its peak in 2024. But the current level, when we look in a more historical context, the current level of the dollar against major currencies is close to its historical average over the past decade. She also mentioned that currency markets can be volatile, and it’s important not to read too much into day-to-day movements in currencies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-currency-trading-concept-picture-id504246822_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Novartis India hits the roof as Novartis AG to divest 70.68%; open offer at Rs 860.64/ share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/novartis-india-hits-the-roof-as-novartis-ag-to-divest-7068-open-offer-at-rs-86064-share/1678850</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678850</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Novartis AG has entered into a share purchase agreement to divest 1,74,50,680 equity shares, representing 70.68% of the company’s paid-up equity capital, to a consortium led by WaveRise Investments, ChrysCapital Fund X, and Two Infinity Partners, along with persons acting in concert, ChrysCapital X, LLC, and OceanEdge Investments.

Novartis AG has entered into a share purchase agreement to divest 1,74,50,680 equity shares, representing 70.68% of the company’s paid-up equity capital, to a consortium led by WaveRise Investments, ChrysCapital Fund X, and Two Infinity Partners, along with persons acting in concert, ChrysCapital X, LLC, and OceanEdge Investments. The proposed acquisition has triggered a mandatory open offer to acquire up to 26% of the voting share capital from public shareholders. The open offer price has been fixed at Rs 860.64 per share, representing a premium of 3.64% to the previous closing price of Rs 830.45. The acquirers propose to purchase up to 6,419,608 fully paid-up equity shares of face value Rs 5 each, aggregating to a total consideration of Rs 552.49 crore, payable in cash, assuming full acceptance. The underlying promoter stake transaction is valued at approximately Rs 1,445.89 crore, subject to customary adjustments as per the agreement. Upon completion of the share purchase and assuming full subscription to the open offer, the acquirers’ combined shareholding will increase to 96.68%. In the event of nil tendering, their holding will remain at 70.68%. Post completion, Novartis AG will hold nil stake in the company and cease to be the promoter, with its shareholding reclassified to the public category in accordance with SEBI regulations. The acquirers have stated that they do not intend to delist the company and will ensure compliance with the minimum public shareholding requirement, if necessary. Separately, the company has agreed to change its name to remove all references to the seller group within 120 days from closing and will undertake requisite regulatory filings and other post-closing obligations. The deal marks a change in ownership from a global pharmaceutical major to a private equity-led consortium, while the company continues to remain listed. Novartis India is primarily engaged in the wholesale distribution of pharmaceuticals and medical goods. The company’s standalone net profit declined 36.8% to Rs 16.09 crore on a 7.6% drop in revenue from operations to Rs 85.90 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NovartisIndia_91739713853_243.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Global Health Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-global-health-ltd-counter/1678849</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678849</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CRISIL Ltd, JK Lakshmi Cement Ltd, ABB India Ltd, Shree Cement Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 20 February 2026.

CRISIL Ltd, JK Lakshmi Cement Ltd, ABB India Ltd, Shree Cement Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 20 February 2026. Global Health Ltd recorded volume of 10.22 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 201.84 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5061 shares. The stock lost 1.59% to Rs.1,120.90. Volumes stood at 3624 shares in the last session. CRISIL Ltd registered volume of 48818 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 25.54 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1912 shares. The stock rose 1.29% to Rs.4,582.00. Volumes stood at 954 shares in the last session. JK Lakshmi Cement Ltd witnessed volume of 2.02 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 23.33 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 8668 shares. The stock dropped 0.51% to Rs.714.80. Volumes stood at 2306 shares in the last session. ABB India Ltd recorded volume of 98368 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 15.86 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6204 shares. The stock gained 7.59% to Rs.6,149.45. Volumes stood at 6986 shares in the last session. Shree Cement Ltd notched up volume of 9948 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 11.2 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 888 shares. The stock rose 0.13% to Rs.26,256.65. Volumes stood at 1523 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlobalHealthLtd_90263007_34649.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[5paisa Capital jumps as board to mull fund-raising plan on 24 Feb ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/5paisa-capital-jumps-as-board-to-mull-fund-raising-plan-on-24-feb/1678847</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678847</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company stated that the proposed fund-raising could be carried out through the issuance of equity shares or other eligible securities, in accordance with applicable laws.

The company stated that the proposed fund-raising could be carried out through the issuance of equity shares or other eligible securities, in accordance with applicable laws. The plan will be subject to necessary regulatory and statutory approvals. The official announcement was made on 19 February 2026, after market hours. 5paisa Capital is engaged in providing financial products through its online technology platform and mobile applications. The company provides an online technology platform to clients through internet terminals and mobile applications for trading in securities in NSE and BSE. It is registered with SEBI as a stockbroker, depository participant, and research analyst, and with AMFI as a mutual fund distributor. The company reported a 23.98% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 12.30 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 16.18 crore in the same quarter last year. Total revenue from operations fell 7.02% YoY to Rs 79.28 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/5PaisaCapitalLtd_47826712_68848.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India is a key engine for global growth, says IMF]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-is-a-key-engine-for-global-growth-says-imf/1678846</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678846</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India is a key engine for global growth, noted Julie Kozack, Director of the Communications Department, IMF yesterday.

India is a key engine for global growth, noted Julie Kozack, Director of the Communications Department, IMF yesterday. Indian economy has performed well and the IMF has upgraded our growth projection in the January World Economic Outlook. Real GDP growth for fiscal year 2025-2026 is projected at 7.3 percent, and that's significantly higher than what fund had projected earlier. This was a significant upgrade for India. She noted that IMF welcomes this year’s budget's continued focus on gradual fiscal consolidation while maintaining critical capital expenditure in India, both the central government and states. The fund is encouraging India to continue to focus on a medium-term fiscal consolidation path. This will enable India to rebuild fiscal buffers and ensure that resources, which right now are a bit tied up on debt servicing, that they can then be reallocated for other priority spending over time.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zydus Lifesciences Ahmedabad injectables unit clears USFDA inspection ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zydus-lifesciences-ahmedabad-injectables-unit-clears-usfda-inspection/1678845</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678845</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The inspection was carried out at the company’s Unit 9 facility at Zydus Biotech Park in Changodar, Ahmedabad, from 16 February to 19 February, 2026, the drug maker said in a regulatory filing.

The inspection was carried out at the company’s Unit 9 facility at Zydus Biotech Park in Changodar, Ahmedabad, from 16 February to 19 February, 2026, the drug maker said in a regulatory filing. The company added that the inspection concluded without any observations, indicating compliance with the regulator’s standards. Zydus Lifesciences operates as an integrated pharmaceutical company with business encompassing the entire value chain in the research, development, production, marketing and distribution of pharmaceutical products. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 7.7% to Rs 1,102.64 crore on 32.3% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,780.40 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Zydus Lifesciences rose 0.08% to Rs 903 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CadilaHealth_93490673476_20883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India–France partnership will influence capital formation, offer boost for long-term productivity growth]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indiafrance-partnership-will-influence-capital-formation-offer-boost-for-long-term-productivity-growth/1678843</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678843</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The India–France partnership should not be seen from the realm of just diplomatic engagement but from the perspective of deeper structured economic and industrial collaboration.

The India–France partnership should not be seen from the realm of just diplomatic engagement but from the perspective of deeper structured economic and industrial collaboration. The contours of the pact which include the all-important Double Taxation Avoidance Agreement (DTAA) providing fiscal design for cross-border investment also include well timed economic effects of defence manufacturing, joint ventures (JVs), and industrial capability development on Indian economy, according to Rajeev Juneja, President, PHDCCI. These elements will influence capital formation, sectoral output, employment generation, a much need boost for long-term productivity growth in India, he said. France is a key defence partner of India, particularly through procurement and technology collaboration involving Dassault Aviation (Rafale aircraft programme), Safran (engine and propulsion systems) and Naval Group (submarine construction), he added. In macroeconomic terms, domestic defence manufacturing affects GDP through three key channels. Direct Effect – Manufacturing of aircraft components, engines, missiles, and naval platforms adds to gross value added (GVA) in manufacturing. Backward supply value chain linkages – Through domestic sourcing upstream industries such as metallurgy, electronics, precision machining, and logistics stand to gain. Productivity – Technology transfer improves total factor productivity in high-skill sectors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-markets-currency-trading-concept-picture-id609801990_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel secures Rs 36-cr railway signalling order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-secures-rs-36-cr-railway-signalling-order/1678840</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678840</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order pertains to the provision of MSDAC and other associated works, including suitable indoor alterations in EI/RRI/PI stations in the Prayagraj (Pryj.) Division of NCR.

The order pertains to the provision of MSDAC and other associated works, including suitable indoor alterations in EI/RRI/PI stations in the Prayagraj (Pryj.) Division of NCR. The project is scheduled to be completed within 24 months from the date of the LoA. The estimated order value, as per the LoA, stands at Rs 35,54,82,968. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. The company further stated that the contract does not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. RailTel was incorporated in 2000, with the objective of creating nationwide broadband and VPN services, telecom, and multimedia networks to modernize the train control operation and safety system of Indian Railways. The company’s standalone net profit declined 4.07% to Rs 62.40 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.05 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 18.99% YoY to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of RailTel Corporation of India shed 0.55% to Rs 327.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quant Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quant-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1678841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678841</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Quant Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 20 February 2026.

Quant Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 20 February 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Money Managers [Fund Managers] Revised Money Managers [Fund Managers] Quant Aggressive Hybrid Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Business Cycle Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Flexi Cap Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Focused Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Infrastructure Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Large Cap Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Manufacturing Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Multi Cap Fund - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Lokesh Garg - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Sandeep Tandon - Ankit Pande - Varun Pattani - Ayusha Kumbhat - Yug Tibrewal - Sameer Kate - Sanjeev Sharma - Jignesh Shah Quant Gilt Fund - Sanjeev Sharma - Harshvardhan Bharatia - Sanjeev Sharma - Haroonvardhan Sirohi Quant Liquid Fund - Sanjeev Sharma - Harshvardhan Bharatia - Sanjeev Sharma - Haroonvardhan Sirohi Quant Overnight Fund - Sanjeev Sharma - Harshvardhan Bharatia - Sanjeev Sharma - Haroonvardhan Sirohi Quant Arbitrage Fund - Sameer Kate - Yug Tibrewal - Sanjeev Sharma - Sameer Kate - Yug Tibrewal - Sanjeev Sharma - Harshvardhan Bharatia

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty tad above 25,550; PSU bank shares in demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-tad-above-25550-psu-bank-shares-in-demand/1678837</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678837</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade. The Nifty traded tad above the 25,550 mark. PSU bank shares advanced after declining in the past trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 271.24 points or 0.33% to 82,769.38. The Nifty 50 index rose 99.85 points or 0.39% to 25,554.20. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.30% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.08%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,851 shares rose and 1,726 shares fell. A total of 215 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index rose 0.93% to 9,593.90. The index declined 1.24% in the past trading session. Union Bank of India (up 1.91%), Indian Bank (up 1.59%), Punjab National Bank (up 1.52%), Bank of Maharashtra (up 1.24%), Canara Bank (up 1.16%), Bank of India (up 1.05%), Indian Overseas Bank (up 0.97%), UCO Bank (up 0.87%), Central Bank of India (up 0.74%) and Bank of Baroda (up 0.49%) rose. Stocks in Spotlight: Pace Digitek added 2.35% after it secured an order worth Rs 890.69 million from RailTel Corporation of India (RCIL) for the supply, installation, and commissioning of IP-based video surveillance systems in LHB coaches. IFGL Refractories added 1.09% after the company announced that a new line for the manufacturing of plastic refractories at the company’s Visakhapatnam manufacturing facility has commenced commercial operations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ABB India jumps after Q3 PAT rises 6% sequentially; order book jumps 51% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/abb-india-jumps-after-q3-pat-rises-6-sequentially-order-book-jumps-51-yoy/1678836</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678836</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 18.08% while revenue from operations climbed 5.71% in CY2025.

On a year on year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 18.08% while revenue from operations climbed 5.71% in CY2025. Profitability was affected by higher material costs, forex, QCO related imported material usage, and Labor Code impact, which was partly offset through commodity hedging and efficiency gains. Revenue recorded positive growth during the quarter, driven by higher export revenues in the electrification segment, particularly from distribution solutions and smart power divisions, as well as all other divisions of electrification business area registered revenue growth. In motion segment, higher revenues across the divisions were offset by reduction in Motion Service division. Profit before tax (PBT) fell 18.09% YoY to Rs 577.59 crore during the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The order book stood at Rs 4,096 crore in Q4 CY25, up 52% YoY, due to a strong development in the base business with additional support from the timing of large orders. During the quarter, the company benefitted from large orders in the data center, automotive, building and infra, railways and metals segments. As of December 31, 2025, the company’s order backlog stood at Rs 10,471 crore, reflecting a 12% year-on-year increase. This strong backlog provides clear revenue visibility and is well aligned with the company’s growth plans for the upcoming periods. On a calendar year (CY) 2025 basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 10.95% to Rs 1,669.40 crore despite a 8.32% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 13,202.73 crore in CY2025 over CY204. On outlook front, the company said that as it enters 2026, it is supported by strong demand momentum and a resilient local-for-local manufacturing base. Its diversified presence across 23 market segments positions it well benefit from sustained investments in infrastructure, rail, grid modernization, and renewables, while also capturing opportunities in metals, mining, energy, chemicals, data centers, and electronics. Continued capex across chemicals, pharmaceuticals, automotive, power distribution, water, and digitalization align with its core strengths and reinforces its long-term growth outlook. Further, the company noted that it continues to monitor global geopolitical developments and their influence on domestic demand, investment sentiment, inflation, FX, and climate-related risks, while remaining focused on operational excellence, disciplined execution, and sustainable, profitable growth. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared a dividend of Rs 29.59 per share with a face value of Rs 2 per share for FY26. The record date for determining shareholders’ eligibility has been fixed as on 2 May 2026. The dividend will be paid after May 09, 2026. ABB India is a leading global technology company. Its business areas include electrification, process automation, motion (drives and motors), and robotics & discrete automation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABB_25842664874_242.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IFGL Refractories rises after plastic refractories manufacturing segment commences operations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ifgl-refractories-rises-after-plastic-refractories-manufacturing-segment-commences-operations/1678832</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678832</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[This new line was set up with the help of technical know-how from company’s material subsidiary, Sheffield Refractories, UK.

This new line was set up with the help of technical know-how from company’s material subsidiary, Sheffield Refractories, UK. With addition of comprehensive range of Plastic Refractories, the Company will be in a position to meet ever increasing demand from ferrous and non ferrous industries. These plastic refractories would strengthen company’s robustmonolithics portfolio comprising castables, precast, shotcrete and ramming mass and thus reaffirm Company’s commitment to delivering high performance refractory solutions manufactured in India for advancing self-reliance and driving industrial progress. The capital outlay involved for this expansion project has been about Rs 2.10 crore financed largely by internal accruals. The total installed capacity is 10,000 MT per annum. "With very few domestic manufacturers currently in this sector, Company’s entry marks a significant step toward strengthening indigenous capacity and reducing reliance on imports,” IFGL Refractories said in a statement. IFGL Refractories is one of the fastest growing brands in the global refractory industry. The company offers a wide range of specialised refractory products and operating systems for its products to customers worldwide. The company’s expertise lies in the iron making, steelmaking and continuous casting areas with particular emphasis in slide gate systems, purging systems, ladle lining & ladle refractories, tundish furniture's & tundish refractories, and others. The company had reported a net loss of Rs 3.1 crore in Q3 FY26 as against a net loss of Rs 2.2 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total income rose by 23% YoY to Rs 470 crore during the period under review.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IFGLRefractoriesLtd._91419471_71579.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>