<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:59:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Apollo Hospitals gains after Q3 PAT jumps 35% YoY to Rs 502 cr; board declares Rs 10 interim dividend]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apollo-hospitals-gains-after-q3-pat-jumps-35-yoy-to-rs-502-cr-board-declares-rs-10-interim-dividend/1675034</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675034</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 27.19% YoY to Rs 682 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 27.19% YoY to Rs 682 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. EBITDA grew by 26.64% to Rs 965 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 762 crore in Q3 FY25. This includes Apollo 24/7 costs of Rs 124 crore during the quarter (including Rs 38 crore in non-cash ESOP charges), compared to Rs 141 crore in Q3 FY25. On a segmental front, revenue from Healthcare Services rose 14% YoY to Rs 3,183 crore. Revenue from Apollo Health and Lifestyle (AHLL) stood at Rs 467 crore, up 20% YoY, while revenue from Apollo HealthCo reached Rs 2,827 crore, also up 20% YoY. As on 31 December 2025, Apollo Hospitals had 8,072 operating beds across the network (excluding AHLL & managed beds). The overall occupancy for hospitals was at 67% in Q3FY26 vs 68% in the same period in the previous year. Dr. Prathap C Reddy, Chairman, Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd. said, “Q3FY26 reflects the fundamental strength and clinical depth of Apollo’s integrated care model. Across our network, teams are consistently delivering strong outcomes through disciplined execution in patient safety, quality, and experience. This quarter, sustained investments in advanced clinical capability translated into meaningful progress across key specialties from Apollo OMR completing 150 robotic joint replacement surgeries in its first 150 days, to the expansion of our stroke care network in Chennai with nine advanced stroke labs, strengthening rapidaccess care and outcomes. We further reinforced our differentiated leadership in neurosciences with the launch of a dedicated Centre of Excellence for Parkinson’s disease and Deep Brain Stimulation care in Chennai, strengthened comprehensive oncology care through the ‘Save My Stomach’ early detection programme at Apollo Cancer Centres, and expanded high-acuity capability with a dedicated heart and lung transplant unit in Karnataka. In parallel, partnerships such as the MoU with Coal India reflect Apollo’s vision to expand access to standardized, high-quality healthcare by building integrated preventive and tertiary care pathways for large workforce populations. Apollo’s transplant programme reflects the depth, scale, and discipline of our clinical systems. As one of the world’s busiest solid organ transplant programmes, our teams now perform an average of five solid organ transplants each day. Cumulatively, we have completed more than 21,000 kidney transplants and over 5,000 liver transplants—becoming the first hospital group in India and the region to reach this landmark—along with 159 heart transplants and 232 lung transplants. These outcomes are the result of standardized clinical pathways, multidisciplinary expertise, and a sustained commitment to patient safety, ethics, and long-term outcomes. The Union Budget provides an important tailwind to India’s aspiration to become a global destination for healthcare. The proposal to support states in establishing five regional medical hubs through public– private partnership is a strategic step toward building a high-quality, well-coordinated Medical Value Travel ecosystem. At Apollo, we view Medical Value Travel as a long-term national mission that reflects India’s depth of clinical expertise, outcomes excellence, and cost advantage. We will continue to work closely with policymakers and state partners to strengthen international patient pathways, expand high-acuity capacity, and ensure seamless coordination across pre-travel evaluation, clinical care, and post-discharge followup.” The board has declared an interim dividend of Rs 10 per share for the financial year 2026. The record date for the same has been fixed as February 16 and it will be paid on or before February 27. Apollo Hospitals was established in 1983 by Dr. Prathap C Reddy, renowned architect of modern healthcare in India. As the nation’s first corporate hospital, Apollo Hospitals is acclaimed for pioneering the private healthcare revolution in the country. Apollo Hospitals has emerged as Asia’s foremost integrated healthcare services provider and has a robust presence across the healthcare ecosystem, including Hospitals, Pharmacies, Primary Care & Diagnostic Clinics and several Retail Health models.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ApolloHospitals_45306952472_636.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends upside amid weak dollar, FPI inflows]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-upside-amid-weak-dollar-fpi-inflows/1675007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675007</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee is regaining momentum in opening trades on Wednesday tracking dollar weakness overseas and cheering return of foreign investment inflows.

The Indian rupee is regaining momentum in opening trades on Wednesday tracking dollar weakness overseas and cheering return of foreign investment inflows. INR opened at Rs 90.56 per dollar and hit a high of 90.46 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee pared initial losses and settled on a positive note, higher by 9 paise at 90.57 against the US dollar, supported by positive cues from domestic equities. NIFTY50 index extended the upmove as United States and India reached a framework for an Interim Agreement on reciprocal trade. The index has zoomed near 26000 mark today and is keeping INR supported. The benchmark BSE Sensex rose by 208.17 points, or 0.25 percent, to 84,273.92, extending its rally into a third consecutive session. The broader NSE Nifty index ended up 67.85 points, or 0.26 percent, at 25,935.15 amid the weekly expiry of options contracts. Meanwhile, US dollar index tanked in global markets yesterday and was trading under 97 mark, lingering near one-week low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jubilant FoodWorks posts nearly 69% YoY rise in Q3 PAT; store count rises to 3,594 outlets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jubilant-foodworks-posts-nearly-69-yoy-rise-in-q3-pat-store-count-rises-to-3594-outlets/1675009</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675009</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While operating EBITDA improved by 20% to Rs 482.3 crore, operating EBITDA margin expanded by 110 basis points YoY to 19.8% in Q3 FY26.

While operating EBITDA improved by 20% to Rs 482.3 crore, operating EBITDA margin expanded by 110 basis points YoY to 19.8% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 115.26 crore, up by 57.2% from Rs 73.30 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Jubilant FoodWorks said that it has recorded a strong performance in Q3 FY26 marked by double digit revenue growth, robust margin expansion fuelled by improved operational efficiency, and accelerated store expansion across markets. The store network increased by 114 net new stores, which was the highest quarterly store additions during the last 4 quarters, taking the total store count to 3,594 across brands and geographies. The India business reported revenue from operations of Rs 1,801.5 crore, a growth of 11.8% YoY. It was driven by a 5.0% LFL growth in Domino’s, high double-digit growth in Popeyes, new additions to the menu and rapid expansion of store network in India. During the quarter, the company added 78 net new stores across all brands, including 75 new Domino’s and 5 new Popeyes stores, ending the quarter with 2,528 stores in India. The Turkey business continued to record high growth in topline. The revenue from operations increased by 15% YoY to Rs 580.1 crore. Sri Lanka and Bangladesh businesses also continued to report strong topline growth YoY. Net addition of 36 stores across all brands, ending the period with 1,066 stores in the international markets Shyam S. Bhartia, chairman and Hari S. Bhartia, co-chairman, Jubilant FoodWorks, commented: “We are elated with our performance in the quarter gone by. Our consolidated topline continues to grow at a very healthy rate. Our margins at all levels have improved significantly over last year. We are also delighted with our Turkey business, which is now servicing the acquisition debt obligations through its own cash flows. Sri Lanka and Bangladesh businesses also continue to deliver strong growth.” Jubilant FoodWorks ranks among the leading emerging markets’ food-tech companies. Its Group network comprises 3,594 stores across six markets – India, Turkey, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Azerbaijan and Georgia. The scrip shed 0.14% to currently trade at Rs 552.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JubilantFood_44171671816_14548.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Mech Projects Q3 PAT rises 15% YoY to Rs 94 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-mech-projects-q3-pat-rises-15-yoy-to-rs-94-cr/1674992</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674992</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (net sales) rose 6.1% YoY to Rs 1,419.56 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 1,337.97 crore in the corresponding period last year.

Revenue from operations (net sales) rose 6.1% YoY to Rs 1,419.56 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 1,337.97 crore in the corresponding period last year. Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 123.86 crore in Q3 FY26, up 2.1% from the Rs 121.32 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 6.78% to Rs 1,309.10 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 1,225.98 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of raw material consumed stood at Rs 233.26 crore (up 8.84% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 191.86 crore (up 11.85% YoY) during the period under review. Power Mech Projects is an engineering and construction company providing integrated service in erection, testing, and commissioning (ETC) of boilers, turbines, and generators and balance of plant (BOP), civil works, and operation and maintenance (O&M). The counter slipped 3.56% to Rs 2,191.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerMechProj_11108641403_34787.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge higher; breadth positive 	]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-higher-breadth-positive/1674991</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674991</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with marginal gains as investors engaged in mild profit booking while continuing to monitor the ongoing earnings season.

The domestic equity indices traded with marginal gains as investors engaged in mild profit booking while continuing to monitor the ongoing earnings season. The Nifty traded above the 25,950 mark. Auto, consumer durables and FMCG shares advanced while realty, media and IT shares declined. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 69.51 points or 0.08% to 84,334.83. The Nifty 50 index rose 48.25 points or 0.19% to 25,983.40. The broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.21% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index shed 0.09%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,571 shares rose and 1,565 shares fell. A total of 176 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 69.45 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,174.21 crore in the Indian equity market on 10 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Titan Company added 1.20% after the company reported a 60.84% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,684 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,047 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 43.26% YoY to Rs 25,416 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 17,740 crore in Q3 FY25. Eicher Motors rallied 6.42% after the company reported a 21.36% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,170.5 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 22.94% YoY to Rs 6,114.04 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,973.12 crore in the year-ago period. ZF Commercial Vehicle Control Systems India added 2.20% after the company reported an 11.72% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.17 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 125.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 11.68% YoY to Rs 1,074.91 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 962.42 crore a year earlier. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.06% to 6.731 compared with previous session close of 6.727. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.4625 compared with its close of 90.5600 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.73% to Rs 157,947. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.22% to 96.65. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.34% to 4.133. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 53 cents or 0.77% to $69.33 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market advanced on Wednesday, continuing their rally even as China's consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier, China’s National Bureau of Statistics data showed Wednesday. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. In U.S, December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. Overnight, the S&P 500 slipped on Tuesday as investors reacted to weaker-than-expected retail sales data and grew concerned about the threat artificial intelligence poses to the financial sector. The broad-based index lost 0.33% and ended at 6,941.81, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.59% and closed at 23,102.47. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 52.27 points, or 0.10%, posting a closing record of 50,188.14. Financial stocks also took a hit Tuesday after tech platform Altruist launched a new AI-powered tax planning tool. Shares of LPL Financial declined 8.3%, while shares of Charles Schwab dropped 7.4% and Morgan Stanley dipped more than 2%. Investors await the release of big jobs report due on Wednesday, and the consumer price index data on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Titan Company Ltd Spurts 2.26%, BSE Consumer Durables index Gains 1.06%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/titan-company-ltd-spurts-226-bse-consumer-durables-index-gains-106/1674978</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674978</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Titan Company Ltd gained 2.26% today to trade at Rs 4363.4.

Titan Company Ltd gained 2.26% today to trade at Rs 4363.4. The BSE Consumer Durables index is up 1.06% to quote at 59825.39. The index is down 3.25 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Voltas Ltd increased 0.54% and Asian Paints Ltd added 0.19% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went up 6.18 % over last one year compared to the 10.55% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Titan Company Ltd has added 3.12% over last one month compared to 3.25% fall in BSE Consumer Durables index and 0.55% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 13319 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 32939 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 4379.95 on 11 Feb 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 2947.55 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TitanCompany_20146423894_1016.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eicher Motors rises after Q3 PAT climbs 21% YoY to Rs 1,421 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eicher-motors-rises-after-q3-pat-climbs-21-yoy-to-rs-1421-cr/1674976</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674976</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operations surged 22.94% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,114.04 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total revenue from operations surged 22.94% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,114.04 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. During the quarter, profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 1,848.65 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 1,460.82 crore recorded in the same period a year ago. The company had reported an exceptional loss of Rs 55.45 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous fiscal year, arising from a one-time provision made following the notification of the four New Labour Codes by the Government of India, effective November 21, 2025. The company reported an EBITDA of Rs 1,557 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 29.6% year-on-year increase. During the quarter, Royal Enfield recorded its quarterly sales volume of 325,773 motorcycles, up 21% from 269,039 motorcycles sold during Q3 FY 2024-25. VE Commercial Vehicles’s (VECV) revenue from operations in Q3 FY 2025-26 stood at Rs 7,019 crore, up 21% from Rs 5,801 crore. EBITDA for the third quarter rose 26% to Rs 652 crore, from Rs 517 crore a year ago. Profit after tax stood at Rs 338 crore as against Rs 299 crore last year. VECV recorded sales of 26,086 vehicles in the third quarter, up from 21,010 vehicles last year. B. Govindarajan, managing director of Eicher Motors and chief executive officer of Royal Enfield, said, “This quarter continues the steady momentum that we have built over the previous six quarters and disciplined execution across Eicher Motors, with encouraging performance from both Royal Enfield and VECV. At Royal Enfield, we continued to see healthy demand across markets, alongside consistent progress in strengthening our product pipeline, capacity building, and engagement with the riding community. The quarter was also significant from a brand and strategy perspective, as we kickstarted celebrations for our historic 125-year milestone at EICMA 2025. With the unveiling of Bullet 650 and Flying Flea S6 and the launch of Himalayan Mana Black and Meteor 350 Sundowner, we showcased our legacy-powered yet innovative mindset. We also expanded our cultural footprint beyond motorcycling with the second edition of ‘Journeying Across the Himalayas,’ which grew in scale and impact. Our performance over the quarter, particularly during the festive months, is the outcome of consistent efforts, with the GST rationalization further improving accessibility in certain segments.” Speaking about the capacity expansion, he added, “This investment will augment our existing annual production capacity and allow us to meet the expanding existing and projected future demand. By scaling our existing Cheyyar plant, we are ensuring a faster capacity ramp-up and cost-efficient operations. This project is aligned with our consistent growth focus and underscores our commitment to the evolving needs of our global community.” Vinod Aggarwal, MD and CEO of VECV and vice chairman of Eicher Motors, said, “The third quarter was marked by a strong recovery in the commercial vehicle industry following a prolonged monsoon. GST reforms, coinciding with the traditional festive buying season, helped revive consumer sentiment and consumption-led demand for transportation. VECV delivered its best-ever third-quarter performance, with sales of 26,086 vehicles, representing a growth of 24.2% over the corresponding period last year. We sustained our industry leadership in the LMD truck segment (5–18T GVW) while also recording growth across bus and heavy-duty truck segments. The service and parts business also grew during the quarter, reflecting higher service penetration and vehicle utilization across our truck and bus park. During the quarter, we expanded our product portfolio with the launch of the diesel variant of the Eicher Pro X small truck, purpose-built for city and near-city applications, as well as the LNG-powered Volvo Road Train, representing a paradigm shift in long-haul distribution. Continuing our focus on uptime and customer centricity, we added 25 new touchpoints across India, expanding service coverage at an average pace of two locations per week. For the quarter, EBITDA stood at 9.5% and EBIT at 6.8%, reflecting a focus on price realization supported by enhanced value delivery to our customers.” Meanwhile, the board approved a Rs 958-crore brownfield investment to expand Royal Enfield’s manufacturing capacity at its Cheyyar plant in Tamil Nadu, raising total annual capacity from about 14.6 lakh units to up to 20 lakh units. The phased expansion will begin in Q1 FY27 and is expected to be completed by FY28, funded through internal accruals, the company said. Eicher Motors is the listed parent of Royal Enfield, the global leader in middleweight motorcycles. In addition to motorcycles, Eicher has a joint venture with Sweden's AB Volvo—Volvo Eicher Commercial Vehicles, which operates in India's commercial vehicle space.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EicherMotors_60312767308_151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HBL Engg gains on securing Rs 800-cr KAVACH contract from BLW]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hbl-engg-gains-on-securing-rs-800-cr-kavach-contract-from-blw/1674974</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674974</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is to be executed within a period of 12 months.

The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is to be executed within a period of 12 months. The company said that none of the promoters has any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions. HBL Engineering (formerly known as HBL Power Systems) manufactures different types of batteries, including lead acid, NiCad, silver zinc, lithium, and railway & defense electronics and other products. The company reported a more than fourfold jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 387.27 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 87.26 crore in the same quarter last year. Revenue from operations surged 134.7% YoY to Rs 1,222.90 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HBLPowerSystem_94746576490_2401.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at green start for equities; China's consumer inflation rises 0.2% in Jan'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-green-start-for-equities-chinas-consumer-inflation-rises-02-in-jan26/1674969</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674969</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 20.50 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 20.50 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 69.45 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,174.21 crore in the Indian equity market on 10 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 4,969.62 crore so far in February (till 10 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia market traded mostly higher Wednesday, continuing their rally despite AI fears and weak economic data spooking U.S. investors. The U.S. December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. In Asia, investors are assessing the latest data coming out from China. The country’s consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier, China’s National Bureau of Statistics data showed Wednesday. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 slipped on Tuesday as investors reacted to weaker-than-expected retail sales data and grew concerned about the threat artificial intelligence poses to the financial sector. The broad-based index lost 0.33% and ended at 6,941.81, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.59% and closed at 23,102.47. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 52.27 points, or 0.10%, posting a closing record of 50,188.14. Financial stocks also took a hit Tuesday after tech platform Altruist launched a new AI-powered tax planning tool. Shares of LPL Financial declined 8.3%, while shares of Charles Schwab dropped 7.4% and Morgan Stanley dipped more than 2%. Investors await the release of big jobs report due on Wednesday, and the consumer price index data on Friday. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks closed with moderate gains, extending their winning streak to a third straight session. Sentiment was supported by foreign institutional investor buying, positive global cues and optimism around the India-US interim trade deal. The Nifty ended above the 25,900 mark, led by strength in auto stocks. After a positive start, the market failed to sustain higher levels. Trading turned range-bound for most of the session, with the Nifty facing stiff resistance near the 26,000 level. The S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 208.17 points or 0.25% to 84,273.92. The Nifty 50 index rallied 67.85 points or 0.26% to 25,935.15. In the three consecutive trading sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.15% and 1.14%, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Titan Company, Eicher Motors,  Apollo Hospitals Ent, Grasim Industries, Torrent Power]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-titan-company-eicher-motors-apollo-hospitals-ent-grasim-industries-torrent-power/1674809</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674809</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&O trading on 11 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&O trading on 11 February 2026. Result Today: Mahindra & Mahindra, LG Electronics India, Lenskart Solutions, Ashok Leyland, Aarey Drugs & Pharmaceuticals, Amagi Media Labs, Amara Raja Energy & Mobility, AstraZeneca Pharma India, Avanti Feeds, CARE Ratings, Carraro India, Divis Laboratories, Godrej Industries, International Gemmological Institute (India), Max Financial Services, Patanjali Foods, TBO Tek, and Yatra Online will announce their quarterly earnings today. Key Events to Watch: The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) will conduct Rs 34,000 crore in T-bill auctions. IPO Data: Fractal Analytics IPO: Subscribed 20% overall on Day 2, with retail investors leading with 60% subscription. Aye Finance IPO: Subscribed 16% overall on Day 2, with retail investors at 47%, and QIBs at 13%. Stocks to Watch: Titan Company reported a 60.84% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,684 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,047 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 43.26% YoY to Rs 25,416 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 17,740 crore in Q3 FY25. Eicher Motors reported a 21.36% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,170.5 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 22.94% YoY to Rs 6,114.04 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,973.12 crore in the year-ago period. ZF Commercial Vehicle Control Systems India reported an 11.72% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.17 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 125.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 11.68% YoY to Rs 1,074.91 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 962.42 crore a year earlier. Jubilant FoodWorks reported a 65.22% year-on-year jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 70.9 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 42.91 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 13.31% YoY to Rs 2,437.21 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,150.76 crore in the year-ago quarter Torrent Power reported a 35.19% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 643.08 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 475.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 4.28% YoY to Rs 6,777.87 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6,499.38 crore in the year-ago quarter. Gujarat Pipavav Port reported an 8.59% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 107.91 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 99.37 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 11.16% YoY to Rs 292.25 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 262.89 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Grasim Industries reported a 26.39% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,036.59 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 820.12 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 25.25% YoY to Rs 44,311.97 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 35,378.34 crore in the year-ago quarter. Apollo Hospitals Enterprise reported a 34.91% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 502 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 372 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 17.19% YoY to Rs 6,477 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5,527 crore a year earlier.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GHV Infra Projects bags Rs 135-cr civil works order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ghv-infra-projects-bags-rs-135-cr-civil-works-order/1674808</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674808</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is to be executed within a period of 22 months.

The project is to be executed within a period of 22 months. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and involves civil construction works. The company said that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity, and the contract does not fall under related-party transactions. GHV Infra Projects is in the business of infrastructure and construction. The company’s standalone net profit surged 3,907.1% to Rs 11.22 crore on a 17,401.9% soar in revenue from operations to Rs 183.77 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of GHV Infra Projects rose 5% to close at Rs 249.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GHVInfraProjectsLtd_41118322_6087.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>