<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:57:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Finolex Cables spurts as Q3 PAT jumps 11% YoY to Rs 164 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/finolex-cables-spurts-as-q3-pat-jumps-11-yoy-to-rs-164-cr/1674573</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674573</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax jumped 12.37% to Rs 216.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 192.56 crore in recorded in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax jumped 12.37% to Rs 216.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 192.56 crore in recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from Electrical Cables segment stood at Rs 1,400.44 crore in Q3 FY26, up 44.05% YoY. Revenue from Communication Cables segment stood at Rs 122.76 crore in Q3 FY26, down 5.75% YoY. Revenue from Copper Rods segment stood at Rs 678.20 in Q3 FY26, up 50.37%. In volume terms, Electrical Wires showed a 28% growth; within Communication Cables segment, volume of metal-based products was lower than the corresponding quarter of the previous period, but Optic Fiber Cable volumes grew by 34% during the quarter. Volume growth in the new product categories was impacted by changes to the energy efficiency norms which would become effective from Jan 2026 and hence there was resistance from trade in purchasing additional material. Finolex Cables is India's largest and leading manufacturer of Electrical and Communication cables. Finolex offers a wide range of Electrical and Communication cables. Its wire and cable products are used in applications such as automobile, lighting, cable TV, telephone and computers to industrial applications touching every person in his daily life. Finolex has added Electrical Switches, LED based Lamps, Fans, low voltage MCBs, Water Heaters and Electric Irons to its range of products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FinolexCables_4887540546_171.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Wakefit Innovations climbs after Q3 PAT turns positive]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wakefit-innovations-climbs-after-q3-pat-turns-positive/1674570</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674570</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a standalone basis, revenue from operations stood at Rs 421.34 crore in Q3 FY26, up 9.4% YoY from Rs 385.18 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a standalone basis, revenue from operations stood at Rs 421.34 crore in Q3 FY26, up 9.4% YoY from Rs 385.18 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit after tax turned positive at Rs 31.86 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 2.41 crore in Q3 FY25. PAT margin improved to 7.6% from -0.6% in Q3 FY25. Reported EBITDA excluding other income surged to Rs 59.18 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 20 crore a year ago, marking a 195.9% YoY increase, with EBITDA margin expanding sharply to 14% from 5.2%. On an Ind AS basis, EBITDA including other income stood at Rs 70.34 crore, up 158.1% YoY, with margin improving to 16.7% from 7.1% in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA rose more than five-fold to Rs 41.64 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 7.97 crore in Q3 FY25, translating into a 422.7% YoY increase. Operating EBITDA margin improved to 9.9% from 2.1% in the corresponding quarter last year. During the quarter, the company reported its highest-ever quarterly sales, despite a year-on-year shift in festive demand, as Diwali fell earlier and some purchases were pulled forward into Q2 FY26. Management said GST 2.0 had no impact on Wakefit’s major product categories, with GST rates remaining unchanged at 18%, though Q3 demand saw marginal pressure due to temporary consumption shifts toward categories benefiting from GST reductions. To provide a normalised growth perspective, the company said year-on-year sales growth for the September-December 2025 period stood at around 14%. Demand trends in Q4 FY26 indicate a healthy recovery, with the second half of the year typically being stronger for the business. Gross margin in Q3 FY26 was impacted by seasonal offers and discounts, although it still improved by 230 bps YoY. The company noted that elevated marketing spends by competitors have increased cost intensity in recent quarters, but expects its marketing spends to normalise to 8-9% of sales over the medium term. From a business mix perspective, mattresses contributed 62.3% of Q3 FY26 sales, furniture 28.7%, and furnishings 9.0%. Own channels accounted for 64.5% of sales, while external channels contributed 35.5%. As of 31 December 2025, Wakefit operated 137 active Company-Owned, Company-Operated (COCO) stores across India. Wakefit Innovations’ chairman, CEO and executive director Ankit Garg said that early indicators point to a stronger Q4 FY26, with the company targeting mid- to high-teen revenue growth and further improvement in operating EBITDA margins. He added that post IPO, the company's balance sheet has strengthened significantly, with investable cash of Rs 889.18 crore as of 31 December 2025. Executive director Chaitanya Ramalingegowda said the company continued to leverage its own direct-to-consumer channels to drive growth, with the core mattress business growing 11.7% YoY in the September to December 2025 period, while furniture and furnishings grew a faster 35.6% YoY. He highlighted that this diversification is improving customer repeat behaviour and lifetime value, supported by ongoing retail expansion, with 137 active COCO stores at the end of the quarter. He added that Wakefit remains focused on strengthening its omnichannel model, brand-led growth and operational capabilities to capture long-term opportunities in India’s under-penetrated home and furnishings market. Bengaluru-based Wakefit Innovations is one of India’s largest and fastest-growing D2C home and furnishing solutions companies, with a diversified product portfolio spanning mattresses, furniture and home furnishings, and a growing omnichannel presence. Shares of Wakefit Innovations made their stock market debut on 15 December 2025. The stock listed at Rs 194.10 on the BSE, a marginal discount of 0.46% to the issue price of Rs 195. The company’s initial public offering was subscribed 2.52 times. The IPO opened for bidding on 8 December 2025, and closed on 10 December 2025, with the price band fixed at Rs 185-195 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WakefitInnovationsLtd_45867540_76878.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pearl Global Industries Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pearl-global-industries-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1674567</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674567</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kiri Industries Ltd, Gokaldas Exports Ltd, Aurobindo Pharma Ltd and Kitex Garments Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 10 February 2026.

Kiri Industries Ltd, Gokaldas Exports Ltd, Aurobindo Pharma Ltd and Kitex Garments Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 10 February 2026. Pearl Global Industries Ltd tumbled 8.65% to Rs 1639.2 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 9113 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19606 shares in the past one month. Kiri Industries Ltd crashed 8.32% to Rs 474.35. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.82 lakh shares in the past one month. Gokaldas Exports Ltd lost 7.26% to Rs 778.75. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.89 lakh shares in the past one month. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd shed 7.22% to Rs 1114.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.93 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 67359 shares in the past one month. Kitex Garments Ltd pared 6.30% to Rs 202.85. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.72 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PearlGlobalInd_7533044884_27614.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold consolidates in narrow range ahead of critical US releases]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-consolidates-in-narrow-range-ahead-of-critical-us-releases/1674566</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674566</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures edged lower on Tuesday, slipping below the $5,070 per ounce mark as a firmer US dollar and pre-data caution weighed on prices.

Gold futures edged lower on Tuesday, slipping below the $5,070 per ounce mark as a firmer US dollar and pre-data caution weighed on prices. Market focus has shifted squarely to upcoming US labour and inflation readings, which are expected to refine expectations around the Federal Reserve’s policy trajectory. While geopolitical tensions continue to lend underlying support to safe-haven demand, near-term price action remains restrained as investors await clarity on the timing and magnitude of potential rate cuts. On the domestic front, MCX April gold futures eased 0.3% to ₹1,57,669 per 10 grams, and is seen consolidating in narrow range after record rally to Rs 190000 late last month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR gains steadily as equities extend winning run]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-gains-steadily-as-equities-extend-winning-run/1674564</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674564</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee stayed mostly supported today as the local equities edged up impressively.

Indian Rupee stayed mostly supported today as the local equities edged up impressively. NIFTY50 index extended the upmove as United States and India reached a framework for an Interim Agreement on reciprocal trade. The index has zoomed near 26000 mark today and is keeping INR. INR is currently up 12 paise at 90.54 per US dollar. The US dollar index tanked in global markets yesterday and currently quotes flat at 96.71, lingering near one-week low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Khandwala Securities Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/khandwala-securities-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1674562</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674562</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Suratwwala Business Group Ltd, Barak Valley Cements Ltd, Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd and CL Educate Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 10 February 2026.

Suratwwala Business Group Ltd, Barak Valley Cements Ltd, Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd and CL Educate Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 10 February 2026. Khandwala Securities Ltd tumbled 11.90% to Rs 19.1 at 14:25 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 3356 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13798 shares in the past one month. Suratwwala Business Group Ltd crashed 10.03% to Rs 28.52. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2114 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4797 shares in the past one month. Barak Valley Cements Ltd lost 8.85% to Rs 47.4. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 7871 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12611 shares in the past one month. Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd slipped 8.32% to Rs 1945.9. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 751 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 388 shares in the past one month. CL Educate Ltd shed 7.77% to Rs 54. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 12968 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16766 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KhandwalaSec_32610072671_7255.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 181 pts; IT shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-181-pts-it-shares-advance/1674559</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674559</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade, supported by foreign institutional investor (FII) buying, firm global cues, and optimism surrounding an interim India–US trade deal.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade, supported by foreign institutional investor (FII) buying, firm global cues, and optimism surrounding an interim India–US trade deal. The Nifty traded above the 25,900 level. IT shares extended gains for a second consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 180.64 points or 0.21% to 84,246.39. The Nifty 50 index fell 55.70 points or 0.21% to 25,920.20. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.52%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,595 shares rose and 1,560 shares fell. A total of 177 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index rose 0.45% to 35,778.50. The index rose 0.47% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Tech Mahindra (up 1.51%), Tata Consultancy Services (up 1.38%), Oracle Financial Services Software (up 1.13%), Coforge (up 0.86%), Wipro (up 0.77%), LTIMindtree (up 0.52%), Persistent Systems (up 0.31%), Infosys (up 0.25%) and Mphasis (up 0.12%) rose. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.09% to 6.767 compared with previous session close of 6.671. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.5450 compared with its close of 90.6600 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 0.52% to Rs 157,248. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.05% to 96.90. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.38% to 4.178. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement shed 8 cents or 0.12% to $68.96 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Gulf Oil Lubricants India added 2.05%. The company reported a 21.77% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 76.13 crore despite a 10.56% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,017.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Happiest Minds Technologies rose 0.03%. The company reported a 25.4% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 40.30 crore despite a 2.4% increase in revenues to Rs 587.56 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Pfizer Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-pfizer-ltd-counter/1674558</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674558</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Praj Industries Ltd, Linde India Ltd, Bata India Ltd, Sun TV Network Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 10 February 2026.

Praj Industries Ltd, Linde India Ltd, Bata India Ltd, Sun TV Network Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 10 February 2026. Pfizer Ltd recorded volume of 8.5 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 86 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9886 shares. The stock gained 5.43% to Rs.5,022.90. Volumes stood at 14435 shares in the last session. Praj Industries Ltd witnessed volume of 274.3 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 36.72 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 7.47 lakh shares. The stock increased 13.91% to Rs.336.95. Volumes stood at 11.31 lakh shares in the last session. Linde India Ltd notched up volume of 6.43 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 25.75 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 24963 shares. The stock rose 3.80% to Rs.6,531.50. Volumes stood at 59564 shares in the last session. Bata India Ltd notched up volume of 18.04 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 17.23 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.05 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.02% to Rs.919.75. Volumes stood at 1.58 lakh shares in the last session. Sun TV Network Ltd registered volume of 24.3 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 13.35 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.82 lakh shares. The stock rose 8.13% to Rs.616.25. Volumes stood at 4.98 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Pfizer_34853668517_434.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nelcast soars after Q3 PAT soars 166.1% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nelcast-soars-after-q3-pat-soars-1661-yoy/1674557</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674557</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[For Q3 FY26, consolidated profit after tax stood at Rs 15.9 crore, up 166.1% YoY from Rs 6 crore in Q3 FY25.

For Q3 FY26, consolidated profit after tax stood at Rs 15.9 crore, up 166.1% YoY from Rs 6 crore in Q3 FY25. PAT margin improved sharply to 4.8% from 2.0% in the corresponding quarter last year. Revenue for the quarter rose 11.8% YoY to Rs 332.2 crore, compared with Rs 297.1 crore in the year-ago period. EBITDA increased 56.5% YoY to Rs 35.9 crore from Rs 22.9 crore, with EBITDA margin expanding by 308 bps to 10.8%, compared with 7.7% in Q3 FY25. EBITDA per kg improved 35% YoY to Rs 15.9. Looking ahead, the company said it expects healthy domestic demand and a gradual recovery in exports. Backed by a strong new-product pipeline and improved operational efficiency, Nelcast said it remains confident of sustaining long-term growth. Nelcast’s managing director and CEO Deepak Reddy Ponnavolu said Q3 FY26 was a strong quarter, driven by healthy domestic demand in the M&HCV and tractor segments, with improved volumes and profitability aided by cost-optimisation efforts that lifted EBITDA per kg to Rs 15.9. He noted that while exports are yet to fully recover, customer schedules are stabilising and recent US tariff relief for engineering and auto products has improved sentiment and is expected to support export demand over the medium term. Looking ahead, he highlighted progress on the company’s high-value new-product pipeline, particularly at the Pedapariya facility, and said Nelcast remains well positioned for sustained growth and margin improvement as domestic CV demand stays strong into early FY27. Nelcast manufactures grey and ductile castings for the medium and heavy commercial vehicle and tractor segments, with 30-35% of its revenues coming from exports. Its product portfolio includes differential carriers, differential cases, bogie suspension brackets and conventional brackets for M&HCVs, transmission casing, centre housing, axle housing and hydraulic lift covers for tractors, and specialised components such as base plates and brake discs for metro rail and railway applications.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Nelcast_56911850524_15196.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United States and India committed to strengthen economic security alignment, says White House]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-states-and-india-committed-to-strengthen-economic-security-alignment-says-white-house/1674525</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674525</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[White House has released a fact sheet regarding trade deal between the United States and India.

White House has released a fact sheet regarding trade deal between the United States and India. It noted that leaders of both countries reached a framework for an Interim Agreement on reciprocal trade and reaffirmed their commitment to broader U.S.-India Bilateral Trade Agreement (BTA) negotiations. The United States and India committed to strengthen economic security alignment to enhance supply chain resilience and innovation through complementary actions to address non-market policies of third parties as well as cooperating on inbound and outbound investment reviews and export controls. The United States and India will significantly increase bilateral trade in technology products and expand joint technology cooperation. In line with the roadmap set out in the Terms of Reference for the BTA, the United States and India will continue negotiations to address the remaining tariff barriers, additional non-tariff barriers, technical barriers to trade, customs and trade facilitation, good regulatory practices, trade remedies, services and investment, intellectual property, labor, environment, government procurement, and trade-distorting or unfair practices of state-owned enterprises.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/hands-2088954__340_board_meetings.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gulf Oil Lubricants records PAT of Rs 76.13 crore in Q3; EBITDA rises 7.80% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gulf-oil-lubricants-records-pat-of-rs-7613-crore-in-q3-ebitda-rises-780-yoy/1674508</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674508</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While EBITDA improved by 7.80% to Rs 132.46 crore, EBITDA margin declined by 33 basis points YoY to 13.02% in Q3 FY26.

While EBITDA improved by 7.80% to Rs 132.46 crore, EBITDA margin declined by 33 basis points YoY to 13.02% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 102.10 crore, down by 20.89% from Rs 129.06 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Ravi Chewla, managing director & CEO, Gulf Oil Lubricants India, commented: "Demand and sales picked up in the second half of the quarter post the prolonged monsoon and festivities. Overall lubricants volume grew by 8%, clearly outperforming industry growth by 2x, supported by double-digit growth in key segments of 82C led by Passenger Car Motor Oil (PCMO) & Agri and across B2B segments. The OEM Franchise Workshops (FWS) business delivered high double-digit growth, driven by strong momentum from existing partnerships. Growth was broad-based across categories, with PCMO registering high double-digit growth, while the Agri segment also recorded good double-digit increase. We expect overall demand momentum to continue in the coming quarter, enabling us to close the year on a strong note. GST rationalisation for ICE vehicles has improved the affordability providing a renewed sense of optimism among the consumer, creating additional growth opportunities. Continued focus on rural and agri markets will remain a key driver in sustaining growth trajectory. In addition, our EV subsidiary Tirex is charging ahead, acquiring new marquee customers and delivering strong financial performance. The business is on track to close the year in line with the expectations and remains well aligned with our long-term strategy to scale and strengthen the EV segment as a core pillar for us. Tirex closed Q3 with top-line growth of 83%, while delivering 78% growth over the nine-month period.” Gulf Oil Lubricants India (GOLIL), part of the Hinduja Group and Gulf Oil International, is a leading player in India's lubricant market offering a comprehensive product portfolio in automotive and industrial lubricants. The scrip rose 1.33% to currently trade at Rs 1181.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GulfOilLubric_49865113351_45765.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with minor gains; media shares outperforms; VIX slumps 3.50%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-minor-gains-media-shares-outperforms-vix-slumps-350/1674507</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674507</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the afternoon trade amid strong global cues and continuing foreign inflows.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the afternoon trade amid strong global cues and continuing foreign inflows. The Nifty traded below the 25,900 level. Media, auto and metal shares advanced while pharma, PSU bank and FMCG shares declined. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 260.95 points or 0.30% to 84,323.41. The Nifty 50 index rose 72.60 points or 0.26% to 25,934.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.17% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.54%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,606 shares rose and 1,490 shares fell. A total of 198 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 3.50% to 11.76. Gainers & Losers: Eternal (up 5.73%), Tata Steel (up 2.81%), Bajaj Auto (up 2.46%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.90%) and Tata Consultancy Services (up 1.70%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Shriram Finance (down 1.52%), Bajaj Finance (down 1.49%), Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories (down 1.36%), Tata Consumer Products (down 1.14%) and Asian Paints (down 0.98%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: NRB Bearings jumped 4.44% after the company's consolidated net profit increased 34.17% to Rs 28.62 crore on 17.73% rise in net sales to Rs 327.92 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) rose 1.27% after the company said its transportation infrastructure vertical has secured a road development contract in Dubai, UAE. Gravita India advanced 1.21% after the company announced the signing of a binding term sheet for the proposed acquisition of equity stake upto 100% in Rasthriya Metal Industries (RMIL) by way of a share purchase agreement (SPA). Texmaco Rail & Engineering slipped 2.31% after the company reported a 44.65% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 42.27 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 76.38 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets opened mixed on Tuesday as investors brace for a flurry of corporate earnings. Asian markets traded higher as Japan’s Nikkei 225 continued its post-election rally and reached new highs. The Japanese market continues to ride the "Takaichi trade” in the wake of Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s landslide victory in the Lower House. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 rose on Monday, boosted by technology stocks, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average reached new heights as investors awaited critical economic data and another batch of earnings reports. The broad-based index advanced for a second straight day, rising 0.47% and ending at 6,964.82. The blue-chip Dow eked out a 20.20-point gain, or 0.04%, and settled at 50,135.87. The Nasdaq Composite jumped 0.9%, closing at 23,238.67. Investors will also be watching for the delayed January jobs report from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, which is due out Wednesday. The release was initially scheduled for last Friday but was postponed due to the partial government shutdown. It also comes after ADP reported last week that private payrolls increased by a mere 22,000 in January. The January consumer price index reading—which was also delayed by the shutdown—is due out Friday, with the consensus looking for a 2.5% annual rate.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's overall retail sales grow 17.6% on year in January]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-overall-retail-sales-grow-176-on-year-in-january/1674506</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674506</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Federation of Automobile Dealers Associations (FADA) today released Vehicle Retail Data for January'26.

The Federation of Automobile Dealers Associations (FADA) today released Vehicle Retail Data for January'26. According to FADA, January’26 delivered a strong, broad-based start to the calendar year, with overall vehicle retail at 27,22,558 units, registering +17.61% Y-o-Y. Two-Wheelers led the charge with 18,52,870 units (+20.82% Y-o-Y). Importantly, the demand engine remains anchored in Bharat, with the rural share at 56% (urban 44%). While rural volumes stayed robust (Rural: +19.77% Y-o-Y). Commercial Vehicles clocked 1,07,486 units (+15.07% Y-o-Y), reflecting improving freight sentiment and replacement-led buying. Passenger Vehicles recorded 5,13,475 units (+7.22% Y-o-Y). The mix remains urban-led at 59.2%, with rural at 40.8%; however, the growth story is increasingly being written in non-metro India—Rural PV grew +14.43% Y-o-Y, significantly ahead of Urban at +2.75% Y-o-Y. Crucially, PV inventory levels continued to soften to 32–34 days, which is a constructive indicator of healthier channel discipline and improved working-capital efficiency across the network.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/truck-2526825__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shanti Gold International posts PAT of Rs 40.08 crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shanti-gold-international-posts-pat-of-rs-4008-crore-in-q3/1674504</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674504</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operation for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs.

Revenue from operation for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs. 636.93 crore, as against Rs. 303.22 crore in Q3 FY25, reflecting a 110.06% growth on a year-on-year basis. The growth in revenue was fuelled by robust festive and wedding demand, with October recording one of the highest monthly sales in the company’s history. Volume growth stood at 31% YoY and 25% QoQ, underscoring strong customer traction. EBITDA for the quarter grew by 113.83%, reaching Rs. 60.18 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs. 28.14 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA more than doubled YoY, led by favorable gold prices and a stronger product mix, reflecting our ability to capture market opportunities while staying disciplined. EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 was 9.45% in Q3 FY26 as against 9.28% in Q3 FY25. Pankajkumar Jagawat, chairman & managing director, Shanti Gold International, said: "The quarter marked a period of strong business momentum for the company, driven by sustained demand from organized jewellery retailers across markets. The ongoing shift towards organized retail, coupled with higher consumer preference for design led and assured quality jewellery, continues to create meaningful opportunities for scalable manufacturing partners such as us. During the quarter, we also announced an additional capacity expansion of approximately 4,000 kg. This expansion is aligned with our medium-term growth strategy and is aimed at strengthening our ability to service our customers better, manage demand more efficiently, and be the preferred supplier for organised retail partners. The added capacity positions us well to capitalise on growing outsourcing opportunities within the jewellery manufacturing ecosystem.” Shanti Gold International is one of India’s most trusted jewellery manufacturers. The company’s modern manufacturing facility in Mumbai spans over 13,448 square feet and integrates traditional craftsmanship with advanced technology to deliver elegant, precise, and contemporary designs. The scrip fell 1.86% to currently trade at Rs 216.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SHANTIGOLDINTERNATIONALLIMITED_22271490_94412.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Happiest Minds records over 25% sequential drop in Q3 PAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/happiest-minds-records-over-25-sequential-drop-in-q3-pat/1674501</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674501</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In dollar terms, the revenue was higher by 1.0% while in constant currency terms, it rose by 1.2% sequentially.

In dollar terms, the revenue was higher by 1.0% while in constant currency terms, it rose by 1.2% sequentially. Operating margin improved by 3.6% to Rs 100.87 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 97.33 crore in Q2 FY26. Operating margin as percent of sales for Q3 FY26 was 17.4% as against 17.0% in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 54.21 crore, down by 25.4% from Rs 72.66 crore in Q2 FY26. The company added 11 clients during the quarter, taking to total count to 297 as on 31 December 2025. At the end of the December 2025 quarter, employee headcount stood at 6,548 and trailing 12-month attrition rate was 17.4%. Ashok Soota, chairman & chief mentor, said: “With AI First. Agile Always., we have launched AI First as our 11th strategic transformation, supported by 11 strategic programs that together define how Happiest Minds will build, deliver, and scale value in an AI-driven world. We have already made considerable progress across several of these programs, and we expect this momentum to accelerate the growth of Happiest Minds. This is clearly visible in how AI is being operationalized across our company and for our clients. I would also like to take cognisance of a recent AI-related announcement that has created some turbulence in global markets for software companies. I want to assert that this development represents an opportunity, not a threat, for Happiest Minds and, we believe, for other IT services companies as well.” Happiest Minds Technologies and IT Solutions Company enables digital transformation for enterprises and technology providers by delivering seamless customer experiences, business efficiency, and actionable insights. The scrip rose 0.51% to currently trade at Rs 397.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HappiestMindsechnologiesLtd_22622375_70299.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd spurts 1.11%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-bank-ltd-spurts-111-gains-for-third-straight-session/1674491</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674491</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 433.55, up 1.11% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.45% on the day, quoting at 25984.15. The Sensex is at 84465.17, up 0.48%. Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd has risen around 1.61% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 2.24% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60669.35, up 0.19% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 94.84 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 182.24 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 432.65, up 0.85% on the day. Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd is up 12.99% in last one year as compared to a 12.62% spurt in NIFTY and a 23.04% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 31.5 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KotakMahBank_47062626511_2330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd spurts 2.08%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-spurts-208-gains-for-third-straight-session/1674492</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674492</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3684.6, up 2.08% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.45% on the day, quoting at 25984.15. The Sensex is at 84465.17, up 0.48%. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd has risen around 0.07% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 0.79% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27791.45, up 1.59% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 9.83 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 27.28 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3691.3, up 1.9% on the day. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd is up 19.4% in last one year as compared to a 12.62% spurt in NIFTY and a 25.07% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 32.06 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE Ltd gains for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-ltd-gains-for-third-consecutive-session/1674493</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674493</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[BSE Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

BSE Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3115, up 4.35% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.45% on the day, quoting at 25984.15. The Sensex is at 84465.17, up 0.48%. BSE Ltd has risen around 11.62% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which BSE Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 2.58% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28154.05, up 0.26% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 124.81 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 51.23 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3141.2, up 4.85% on the day. BSE Ltd is up 80.16% in last one year as compared to a 12.62% spurt in NIFTY and a 22.25% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 72.91 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BSELtd_11315994_21236.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd spurts 2.4%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/muthoot-finance-ltd-spurts-24-gains-for-third-straight-session/1674494</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674494</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Muthoot Finance Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 3870.4, up 2.4% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.45% on the day, quoting at 25984.15. The Sensex is at 84465.17, up 0.48%. Muthoot Finance Ltd has dropped around 0.99% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Muthoot Finance Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 2.58% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28154.05, up 0.26% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.34 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.81 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3885.4, up 2.57% on the day. Muthoot Finance Ltd is up 76.88% in last one year as compared to a 12.62% spurt in NIFTY and a 22.25% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 20.9 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MuthootFinance_48499437395_24769.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Breweries Ltd soars 1.91%, rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-breweries-ltd-soars-191-rises-for-third-straight-session/1674495</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674495</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[United Breweries Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

United Breweries Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1562.9, up 1.91% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.45% on the day, quoting at 25984.15. The Sensex is at 84465.17, up 0.48%. United Breweries Ltd has added around 3.01% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which United Breweries Ltd is a constituent, has added around 1.35% in last one month and is currently quoting at 52047.3, down 0.02% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 41317 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.43 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 106.66 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnitedBreweries_49738308528_23220.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>