<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:28:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Central govt approves wage revision of PSU general insurers, NABARD, RBI employees, pensioners, says finance ministry ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/central-govt-approves-wage-revision-of-psu-general-insurers-nabard-rbi-employees-pensioners-says-finance-ministry/1667013</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667013</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The central government has approved wage revisions for PSU General Insurance companies and the National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (NABARD), as well as a pension revision for retirees of the Reserve Bank of India and NABARD.

The central government has approved wage revisions for PSU General Insurance companies and the National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (NABARD), as well as a pension revision for retirees of the Reserve Bank of India and NABARD. A total of 46,322 employees, 23,570 pensioners and 23,260 family pensioners will benefit from the wage revision, the finance ministry said on Friday. Regarding the wage revision of PSU General Insurance companies, the ministry said it will be effective from August 1, 2022. The total outgo will be to the tune of Rs 8,170.30 crore, which includes Rs 5,822.68 crore towards wage arrears under the wage revision, Rs 250.15 crore for NPS, and Rs 2097.47 crore for family pension.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/power-of-money-picture-id155389485_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s private sector growth rebounds in January, PMI data shows]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-private-sector-growth-rebounds-in-january-pmi-data-shows/1667007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667007</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Growth across India's private sector economy bounced back in January after losing some momentum at the end of the 2025 calendar year.

Growth across India's private sector economy bounced back in January after losing some momentum at the end of the 2025 calendar year. The HSBC Flash PMI figures showed quicker increases in new orders and output, alongside the reinstatement of job creation and a rebound in business confidence. Rising from an 11-month low reading of 57.8 in December to 59.5 in January, the HSBC Flash India Composite Output Index – a seasonally adjusted index that measures the month-on-month change in the combined output of India's manufacturing and service sectors – indicated a sharp rate of expansion that was above the long-run series average. The HSBC Flash India Manufacturing PMI rose from 55.0 in December to 56.8 in January. This signalled the best improvement in operating conditions since last October.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/female-manager-working-on-tablet-in-factory-picture-id52704_commodities.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen near one-week low against USD; Bank of Japan retains key interest rate]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-near-one-week-low-against-usd-bank-of-japan-retains-key-interest-rate/1667006</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667006</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese Yen (JPY) remains depressed near the weekly low against its American counterpart following the Bank of Japan's (BoJ) widely expected decision to leave short term rate on hold.

The Japanese Yen (JPY) remains depressed near the weekly low against its American counterpart following the Bank of Japan's (BoJ) widely expected decision to leave short term rate on hold. The USD/JPY cpunter is quoting at 158.7 per dollar on Friday. The Bank of Japan retained its key interest rate, as widely expected, and raised its economic growth outlook on Friday. The policy board, headed by Ueda Kazuo, voted 8-1 to hold the uncollateralized overnight call rate at around 0.75 percent. Previously, the bank had raised its rate by 25 basis points in December, taking it to the highest since 1995. In the Outlook for Economic Activity and Prices report, the bank said, "Japan's economy is likely to continue growing moderately, with overseas economies returning to a growth path, and as a virtuous cycle from income to spending gradually intensifies." Real GDP growth for fiscal 2025 was upgraded to 0.9 percent from 0.7 percent and the projection for the fiscal 2026 was lifted to 1.0 percent from 0.7 percent citing the effects of government's economic measures. However, the bank lowered its fiscal 2027 growth outlook to 0.8 percent from 1.0 percent. The bank said inflation is likely to decelerate below 2 percent in the first half of this year with the waning of the effects of the rise in food prices. Inflation is estimated at 2.7 percent in the fiscal 2025, unchanged from the previous projection, while the forecast for the fiscal 2026 was raised marginally to 1.9 percent from 1.8 percent. Inflation outlook for the fiscal 2027 was retained at 2.0 percent

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slides 68 pts; realty shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slides-68-pts-realty-shares-decline/1667005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667005</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor cuts in the mid-morning trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor cuts in the mid-morning trade. Sentiment drew some support from broader Asian market strength and easing geopolitical tensions linked to Greenland, but sustained foreign fund outflows and mixed corporate earnings kept investor sentiment cautious. The Nifty traded above the 25,200 level. Realty shares extended losses for the fifth consecutive trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 67.91 points or 0.08% to 82,239.46. The Nifty 50 index fell 15.70 points or 0.06% to 25,275.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.05% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.78%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,657 shares rose and 2,139 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 0.93% to 775.20. The index tumbled 9.12% over the past five consecutive trading sessions. Anant Raj (down 2.54%), Brigade Enterprises (down 2.37%), Lodha Developers (down 1.9%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 1.7%), Godrej Properties (down 1.3%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.97%), DLF (down 0.51%), Sobha (down 0.25%), Oberoi Realty (down 0.11%) and Phoenix Mills (down 0.07%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Bandhan Bank jumped 4.66% after the bank reported an 83.9% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 205.99 crore on a 7.8% increase in total income to Rs 6,122.24 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. InfoBeans Technologies tumbled 5.45% after the company reported a 15% drop in net profit to Rs 19 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 23 crore in Q2 FY26. Premier Energies fell 3.64%. The company reported a 53.44% surge in consolidated net profit of Rs 391.62 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 255.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.02% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,936.46 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: Asian markets rose on Friday, tracking Wall Street gains as geopolitical concerns eased and investors looked ahead to the Bank of Japan’s decision. The central bank is expected to hold rates at 0.75%, according to media reports. Japan’s headline inflation rate in December slowed sharply to 2.1%, its lowest level since March 2022. Its core inflation rate came in at 2.4% on the year. Some tech stocks in Asia fell after shares of California-based Intel plummeted 13% in after-hours U.S. trading on its soft guidance for the current quarter, despite posting fourth-quarter earnings beats Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the main benchmarks extended their gains from the previous session after Greenland tensions eased. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 306.78 points, or 0.63%, and closed at 49,384.01. The 30-stock index recovered from the losses seen earlier this week following President Donald Trump’s new Europe tariffs announcement. The S&P 500 climbed 0.55% and ended at 6,913.35. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.91% and settled at 23,436.02, supported by gains in Nvidia, Microsoft, and Meta Platforms.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Aritas Vinyl's market entry meets early turbulence]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-aritas-vinyls-market-entry-meets-early-turbulence/1666992</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666992</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 47, in line with the initial public offer price, but later slipped to its lower circuit of 5% from the listing level.

The scrip listed at Rs 47, in line with the initial public offer price, but later slipped to its lower circuit of 5% from the listing level. The stock touched a high of Rs 47 and a low of Rs 44.65, with around 3.63 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Aritas Vinyl's IPO was subscribed 2.15 times. The issue opened for bidding on 16 January 2026 and it closed on 20 January 2025. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 40 to Rs 47 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 69,98,600 equity shares and offer for sale (OFS) of 9,84,400 equity shares by existing shareholders. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 27.99% from 47.22% pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for capital expenditure for solar power project, working capital for general corporate purpose. Aritas Vinyl manufactures and trades technical textiles with a focus on PU synthetic leather and PVC-coated leather, using transfer coating technology to produce durable artificial leather products for industries such as automotive, fashion, footwear, upholstery and interior design. Based in Ahmedabad, the company operates a manufacturing facility with an annual capacity of about 7.8 million square metres and supplies to distributors and manufacturers across domestic and international markets, including the Middle East, Europe, the US and SEZs, while promoting sustainable alternatives to animal leather. As of 26 December 2025, the company had 89 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 40.58 crore and net profit of Rs 2.42 crore for the period ended 31 August 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AritasVinylLtd_52629133_95393.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Krystal Integrated Services Q3 PAT jumps 5% YoY to Rs 16 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/krystal-integrated-services-q3-pat-jumps-5-yoy-to-rs-16-cr/1666970</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666970</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rallied 10.66% to Rs 305.85 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 276.37 crore posted in the corresponding quarter last year.

Revenue from operations rallied 10.66% to Rs 305.85 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 276.37 crore posted in the corresponding quarter last year. Profit before tax stood at Rs 18.21 crore in Q3 FY26, 6.67% higher than Rs 17.07 crore recorded in the same period last year. EBITDA rose 15.8% to Rs 20.5 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 17.69 crore in Q3 FY25, driven by disciplined bidding, improved contract selectivity, and higher contribution from the corporate business. EBITDA margin expanded to 6.7% in Q3 FY26, up from 6.4% a year ago, supported by better operating leverage, margin protection measures, and an improving business mix despite cost pressures. Total expenses jumped 11.08% to Rs 292.30 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 263.13 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 47.06 crore (up 77.17% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 227.37 crore (down 0.27% YoY) during the period under review. For Q3 FY26, the revenue from the Manpower & Related Services was Rs 264.69 crore (up 4.06% YoY), Information Technology Enabled Services revenue was Rs 1.56 crore (down 83.27% YoY) and Catering Services revenue was Rs 13.58 crore (up 92.62 % YoY). Sanjay Dighe, CEO & Whole-Time Director, Krystal Integrated Services, said: “The company has adopted a disciplined strategy focused on profitable growth and working capital efficiency, rather than pure volume-led expansion. As a result, our participation in government tenders has become strategically selective, avoiding low-margin or capital-intensive bids despite available volumes. This has led to a material improvement in win efficiency, highlighting strong execution capabilities while preserving profitability and balance sheet discipline. At the same time, Krystal has accelerated its shift toward higher-margin corporate business and specialised infrastructure-linked service verticals, supported by investments in skilled and semi-skilled manpower, internal capability building, and increased mechanisation—including technology-enabled and robotics-supported service delivery—to reduce dependence on unskilled labour and enhance operating leverage. The corporate segment continues to gain traction, backed by improved client quality and deeper sectoral penetration. We added 38 new corporate clients in Q3 FY26, compared with 30 in Q3 FY25, and 127 clients year-to-date, up from 49 in 9MFY25. The total corporate client base increased 38% YoY to 391 as of December 31, 2025, reflecting our focus on higher-value, higher-margin engagements. In parallel, the company is expanding into higher-margin adjacencies such as wastewater and solid waste management. While this strategic recalibration may moderate near-term revenue growth, our focus remains on building a resilient, margin-led operating model with better capital efficiency and returns. The impact of this transition is expected to become more visible in the company’s financials and disclosures in the coming quarters, with a clearer picture of the evolved business mix and profitability trajectory by year-end.” The company’s board has approved an increase in the authorised share capital from Rs 15 crore to Rs 19 crore. The authorised share capital will now comprise 1.90 crore equity shares of Rs 10 each, up from 1.50 crore equity shares, all ranking pari passu with the existing equity shares. The board also approved a consequential amendment to the capital clause of the Memorandum of Association, subject to receipt of requisite shareholder and statutory approvals, as applicable. Further, the board has approved raising up to Rs 300 crore through the issuance of equity shares via Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP), in accordance with SEBI ICDR Regulations and other applicable laws. The fund-raising may be undertaken in one or more tranches at prices permitted under prevailing regulations, subject to shareholder and statutory approvals. The board has also constituted a QIP committee, authorising it to undertake all necessary actions in connection with the proposed issue, subject to requisite approvals. KISL is a well-diversified service provider in integrated facility management services, staffing solutions, security services, catering and waste management across India. The Company specializes in sectors such as healthcare, education, City infrastructure, Waste Management and Manufacturing segment—including state government entities, Corporate clients, municipal bodies and other government offices—airports, railways, metro infrastructure and retail. Shares of Krystal Integrated Services rose 0.27% to Rs 604.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KrystalIntegratedServicesLtd_75405406_77085.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Tanla Platforms Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-tanla-platforms-ltd-counter/1666916</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666916</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PB Fintech Ltd, Lodha Developers Ltd, Bandhan Bank Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 23 January 2026.

PB Fintech Ltd, Lodha Developers Ltd, Bandhan Bank Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 23 January 2026. Tanla Platforms Ltd witnessed volume of 10.51 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 33.98 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 30921 shares. The stock increased 11.73% to Rs.501.15. Volumes stood at 24038 shares in the last session. PB Fintech Ltd notched up volume of 4.27 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 10.92 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 39074 shares. The stock slipped 1.43% to Rs.1,690.10. Volumes stood at 10933 shares in the last session. Lodha Developers Ltd witnessed volume of 11.69 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 10.76 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.09 lakh shares. The stock dropped 2.21% to Rs.926.60. Volumes stood at 5.18 lakh shares in the last session. Bandhan Bank Ltd registered volume of 18.96 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.18 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.06 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.73% to Rs.149.40. Volumes stood at 3.22 lakh shares in the last session. Home First Finance Company India Ltd saw volume of 56156 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.14 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6900 shares. The stock increased 5.60% to Rs.1,108.55. Volumes stood at 2419 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TanlaSolutions_48102096060_24392.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies IPO ends with 2.72 times subscription]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shadowfax-technologies-ipo-ends-with-272-times-subscription/1666943</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666943</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 24,23,88,360 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer.

Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 24,23,88,360 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 2.72 times. The Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 3.81 times, the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 2.31 times and the Non-Institutional Investors category was subscribed 0.84 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 January 2026 and it closed on 22 January 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. The Rs 1,907 crore IPO had comprised a fresh issue of 80.6 million equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,000 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 73.2 million equity shares worth up to Rs 907.27 crore. Existing investors—Flipkart India, Eight Roads Investments Mauritius II, International Finance Corporation, Qualcomm Asia Pacific, Nokia Growth Partners, NewQuest Asia Fund and Mirae Asset—had offloaded part of their holdings through the OFS. Shadowfax had planned to utilize Rs 423.43 crore from the net proceeds of the fresh issue to enhance network infrastructure capacity, Rs 138.64 crore towards lease payments for new first-mile, last-mile, and sort centres, and Rs 88.57 crore for branding, marketing and communication initiatives. The balance had been earmarked for unidentified inorganic acquisitions and general corporate purposes. Shadowfax Technologies is a leading Indian logistics and 3PL player providing e-commerce, D2C, quick commerce and hyperlocal delivery services. It operates a nationwide network covering over 14,700 pin codes and serves major clients such as Flipkart, Meesho, Swiggy, Zomato, Blinkit, and Nykaa. The company is among the fastest-growing large-scale logistics providers, with rising market share and strong order growth. Ahead of the IPO of Shadowfax Technologies on 19 January 2026, the company raised Rs 856.02 crore from anchor investors by allotting 6.90 crore shares at Rs 124 each to 39 anchor investors. For the three months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 21.04 crore and sales of Rs 1,805.64 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Canara Robeco Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/canara-robeco-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1666915</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666915</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Canara Robeco mutual fund Canara Robeco Asset Management Company Limited (the “AMC”) hereby informs that Ms.

Canara Robeco mutual fund Canara Robeco Asset Management Company Limited (the “AMC”) hereby informs that Ms. Radha Shah has been appointed as Head – Legal and Key Personnel of the AMC with effect from January 15, 2026 Details of Ms. Radha Shah Age: 41 years Designation: Head - Legal Qualification: Bachelor of Legal Science (BLS) and Bachelor of Laws (LLB)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tanla Platforms jumps on steady Q3 FY26 growth]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tanla-platforms-jumps-on-steady-q3-fy26-growth/1666914</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666914</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net profit rose 10.8% YoY to Rs 131.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 118.5 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net profit rose 10.8% YoY to Rs 131.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 118.5 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit increased 5.1% QoQ from Rs 125 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 12.1% YoY to Rs 1,121 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 1,000.4 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, revenue grew 3.9% QoQ from Rs 1,078.5 crore. Gross profit stood at Rs 309.3 crore, up 18.7% YoY from Rs 260.7 crore. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, gross profit rose 7.8% from Rs 286.8 crore. Gross margin improved to 27.6% in Q3 FY26 from 26.07% in Q3 FY25 and 26.59% in Q2 FY26 Profit before tax stood at Rs 164.8 crore in Q3 FY26, up 12.3% vs year-ago quarter and 6.0% vs previous quarter. EBITDA stood at Rs 190.5 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.6% YoY from Rs 163.4 crore and 7.4% QoQ from Rs 177.5 crore. EBITDA margin improved to 17% in Q3 FY26 from 16.33% in Q3 FY25 and 16.46% in Q2 FY26. Cost of services increased 9.7% YoY to Rs 811.7 crore. Indirect expenses rose 22.1% YoY to Rs 118.8 crore. Depreciation and amortisation climbed 32.3% YoY to Rs 32.5 crore, while finance costs remained low at Rs 1.2 crore. Free cash flow for the quarter stood at Rs 137 crore, translating to 104% of PAT, reflecting strong cash conversion. Uday Reddy, founder chairman & CEO, said, "Q3 marks a milestone, with revenue crossing Rs 1,100 Cr for the first time and growth delivered across all key financial metrics. Both business segments continue to perform well. We will remain focused on investing in Wisely.ai to build innovative solutions for telcos and enterprises." Hyderabad-based Tanla Platforms is an AI-native SaaS company focused on enabling secure and scalable digital communications for enterprises and users. The company works closely with leading telecom operators to strengthen data security, privacy, and protection against spam and fraud, and serves over 2,500 enterprises across sectors, including global technology companies such as Google, Meta and Truecaller.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TanlaSolutions_48102096060_24392.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Deep Structural Reforms supporting India’s economic resilience]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/deep-structural-reforms-supporting-indias-economic-resilience/1666912</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666912</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Minister for Railways, Communications, Electronics & Information Technology, Ashwini Vaishnaw stated that India’s reform momentum is firmly on track, driven by deep structural reforms which have transformed the Indian economy into a high-growth, resilient and globally trusted destination.

Union Minister for Railways, Communications, Electronics & Information Technology, Ashwini Vaishnaw stated that India’s reform momentum is firmly on track, driven by deep structural reforms which have transformed the Indian economy into a high-growth, resilient and globally trusted destination. Speaking on the sidelines of the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting at Davos, the Minister stated that landmark reforms undertaken in recent years including labour code reforms, simplification of the Goods and Services Tax, reforms in the energy sector and opening up of nuclear energy to the private sector, are generating strong investor confidence across sectors. The Minister noted that a continuous reform process is underway across all sectors of the economy, adding that investors are extremely encouraged by the policy environment in India and are increasingly expanding their commitments. He cited several instances, including IKEA announcing plans to double its investment and Qualcomm significantly expanding its workforce in India. He noted that companies across sectors are increasingly viewing the present period as an opportune time to invest in India. Highlighting India’s macroeconomic fundamentals, Vaishnaw stated that India is today the fastest-growing major economy in the world, with a consistent growth trajectory of 6–8 per cent projected over the next five years. He underlined that the combination of moderate inflation and high growth reflects the economic transformation achieved under the leadership of the Prime Minister over the past decade, which is drawing global attention.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-1549702_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Chemicals and petrochemicals sector act as backbone of India’s manufacturing ecosystem]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/chemicals-and-petrochemicals-sector-act-as-backbone-of-indias-manufacturing-ecosystem/1666887</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666887</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Anupriya Patel, Union Minister of State for Chemicals & Fertilizers has highlighted the critical role of the chemicals and petrochemicals sector as the backbone of India’s manufacturing ecosystem, supporting key industries such as agriculture, pharmaceuticals, textiles, infrastructure, mobility, and clean energy.

Anupriya Patel, Union Minister of State for Chemicals & Fertilizers has highlighted the critical role of the chemicals and petrochemicals sector as the backbone of India’s manufacturing ecosystem, supporting key industries such as agriculture, pharmaceuticals, textiles, infrastructure, mobility, and clean energy. The Minister outlined key initiatives including GST rationalisation, significant reduction in compliance burdens through regulatory reforms, energy and labour sector reforms, and policy measures promoting innovation, sustainability, and integration with global value chains, aligned with the vision of Viksit Bharat.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id5822566_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan Bank rallies after Q3 PAT climbs 84% QoQ to Rs 206 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-bank-rallies-after-q3-pat-climbs-84-qoq-to-rs-206-cr/1666879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666879</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Operating profit was Rs 1,445 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 1,310 crore in Q2 FY26, up 10% .

Operating profit was Rs 1,445 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 1,310 crore in Q2 FY26, up 10% . The provisions (other than tax) & contingencies charged to the Profit and Loss for Q3 FY26 were at Rs 1,155 crore, flat QoQ Net interest income (NII) as of Q3 FY26, stood at Rs 2,688 crore compared to Rs 2,589 crore as of Q2 FY26, representing a growth of 3.8% QoQ. Net Interest Margin (NIM) for the quarter was 5.9% in Q3 FY26, compared to 5.8% in Q2 FY26 On asset quality front, gross non-performing assets (GNPA) reduced by 169 bps to 3.3% in Q3 FY26 from 5% in Q2 FY26. Net NPA fell by 38 bps to 1% in Q3 FY26 from 1.4% in Q2 FY26. On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s standalone net profit and total income declined 51.79% and 7.11%, respectively in Q3 FY26. As of December 31, 2025, total deposits stood at Rs 1.57 lakh crore, compared to Rs 1.41 lakh crore in the previous year, reflecting a year-on-year growth of 11%. CASA Deposits stood at Rs 42,730 crore and CASA Ratio stood at 27%, CASA + Retail TD to total deposit ratio stands above 72%. Gross advances jumped 10% to Rs 1.45 lakh crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 1.32 lakh crore as of 31st December 2024. On a YoY basis, Retail book (other than housing) grew 57%, Wholesale Banking grew 32%, and the Housing book showed a growth of 10% (excluding IBPC). The collection efficiency for EEB loans was higher at 98.2% for Q3 FY26. Provision Coverage Ratio (Including Technical Write-offs) as of December 31, 2025, is 84.3%. MD & CEO, Partha Pratim Sengupta said, "Bandhan Bank’s third quarter performance over the last quarters reflects the strengthening fundamentals and steady turn around. In Q4, we are set to accelerate multiple digital initiatives aimed at enhancing customer experience, operational efficiency, and scalability. We remain fully committed to building a strong, more resilient and more diversified bank. These efforts position us well for sustainable and profitable growth going forward.” Bandhan Bank is a private sector bank. The bank’s distribution network spans more than 6,350 outlets. The Bank currently has more than 74,500 employees.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BandhanBankLtd_94952261769_68090.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade sideways; metal shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-sideways-metal-shares-advance/1666877</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666877</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded sideways in the morning trade.

The domestic equity indices traded sideways in the morning trade. The Nifty traded a tad above the 25,300 level. Metal shares extended gains for the third consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 71.15 points or 0.09% to 82,236.22. The Nifty 50 index rose 12.05 points or 0.05% to 25,302.65. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.20% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.37%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,709 shares rose and 1,868 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Adani Green Energy (down 1.54%), Atul (up 0.59%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (up 1.58%), Cipla (up 0.20%), DCB Bank (down 0.82%), Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) (down 1.04%), Godrej Consumer Products (down 0.45%), Granules India (up 1.06%), India Cements (down 0.87%), IndusInd Bank (up 0.37%), Innova Captab (down 0.53%), JSW Energy (down 0.63%), JSW Steel (up 0.09%), Kirloskar Pneumatic Company (down 0.41%), Laurus Labs (up 2.15%), Multi Commodity Exchange of India (up 0.65%), Nuvama Wealth Management (down 1.17%), Paras Defence and Space Technologies (down 0.68%), Prime Focus (up 0.80%), Piramal Finance (down 0.26%), SG Mart (up 1.69%), Shriram Finance (up 0.30%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 0.75%), Sterlite Technologies (up 0.48%), Stylam Industries (down 0.93%), Urban Company (down 0.54%), Welspun Specialty Solutions (up 0.45%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index advanced 1.51% to 11,748.00. The index rose 3.28% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Zinc (up 5.15%), National Aluminium Company (up 4.31%), APL Apollo Tubes (up 2.99%), Hindustan Copper (up 2.92%), Vedanta (up 2.66%), Steel Authority of India (up 2.63%), Jindal Steel (up 1.83%), Hindalco Industries (up 1.78%), Tata Steel (up 0.9%) and Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 0.22%) rose. Stocks in Spotlight: Adani Energy Solutions fell 2.08% after the company reported a 1.68% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 552.31 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 561.78 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 15.73% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,729.65 crore in Q3 FY26. InterGlobe Aviation (IndiGo) declined 2.31% after the company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 77.55% to Rs 549.8 crore despite a 6.16% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 23,471.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Premier Energies Q3 PAT climbs 53% YoY to Rs 392 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/premier-energies-q3-pat-climbs-53-yoy-to-rs-392-cr/1666876</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666876</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 13.02% YoY to Rs 1,936.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 13.02% YoY to Rs 1,936.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 505.17 crore, registering a growth of 43.93% on a YoY basis. Total expenses rose 4.45% YoY to Rs 146.08 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 113.90 crore (up 20.83% YoY), employee benefits expense was at Rs 46.11 crore (up 79.76% YoY) and finance costs were Rs 47.44 crore (down 0.95% YoY) during the period under review. Operating EBITDA grew 15.5% YoY to Rs 593.20 crore in the third quarter of FY26. The EBITDA margin improved to 30.6% in Q3 FY26 from 30.0% in Q3 FY25. As of 31 December 2025, the company’s order book stood at Rs 1,372.35 crore. Meanwhile, the company said that, pursuant to an extension letter received from the seller and the target company, the board has approved an extension of the long-stop date for the fulfilment of conditions precedent by a further 30 days, up to 20 February 2026, in connection with the proposed acquisition of a 51% equity stake in Ksolare Energy. The extension is in line with the Board’s approval and the company’s letter dated 23 October 2025, which envisaged acquiring the target company in association with Syrma SGS Technologies. Further, the company informed that through its wholly owned subsidiary, Premier Energies Photovoltaic Private Limited, it has successfully commissioned a 400 MW solar photovoltaic cell (Mono PERC) manufacturing facility at its E-City plant in Maheshwaram, Telangana. This commissioning forms part of a brownfield expansion of the company’s existing cell manufacturing operations and was achieved through the installation of additional equipment while leveraging existing infrastructure and utilities. Post commissioning, the operational cell manufacturing capacity stands at 3.6 GW. Premier Energies is an integrated manufacturer of solar PV cells and solar modules, including custom-made modules for specific applications. The scrip slipped 4.27% to Rs 707.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PremierEnergiesLtd_39693029_76751.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baroda-bnp-paribas-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1666875</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666875</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 27 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes.

Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 27 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.12 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.14 per unit Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.39 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Multi Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.42 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.16 per unit. Baroda BNP Paribas Balanced Advantage Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.18 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1666874</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666874</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 27 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 27 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit. Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1666871</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666871</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 27 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW in the following scheme.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 27 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW in the following scheme. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: HDFC Balanced Advantage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.250 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.250

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Energy slides as Q3 PAT decline 2% YoY to Rs 552 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-energy-slides-as-q3-pat-decline-2-yoy-to-rs-552-cr/1666869</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666869</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations jumped 15.73% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,729.65 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by improved operating performance and higher SCA (Service Concession Arrangement) income following increased capex.

However, revenue from operations jumped 15.73% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,729.65 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by improved operating performance and higher SCA (Service Concession Arrangement) income following increased capex. Profit before tax rose 43.2% YoY to Rs 801 crore in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, EBITDA rose 20.7% year-on-year to a record high of Rs 2,210 crore, led by robust growth in the transmission and smart metering segments and steady performance in the distribution segment. On the segmental front, the operational revenue from transmission business stood at Rs 2,426.36 crore, (up 19.24%YoY) and the revenue from distribution business was at Rs 3,103.62 crore (up 4.41%YoY) during the period under review. The company reported strong operational parameters during the quarter, with an average system availability of over 99.7%. Robust line availability resulted in an incentive income of Rs 33 crore in Q3 FY26 reflecting the superior O&M practices. With KPS III (Khavda South Olpad) HVDC project win in Q3, the company’s aggregate transmission under construction pipeline reached Rs 77,787 crore. During the quarter, the company fully commissioned the North Karanpura Transmission Line (NKTL) project and operationalized 299 ckm. In AEML, the Mumbai distribution arm, total units sold stood at 2,487 MUs in the quarter, compared with 2,574 MUs in Q3 FY25. Distribution losses in the AEML network were among the lowest at 4.03% in Q3 FY26. The company has an under-construction pipeline of 13 transmission projects valued at Rs 77,787 crore, while near-term tendering opportunities remain strong at around Rs 1 lakh crore. The distribution business reported a steady performance. AEML’s Regulated Asset Base (RAB) stood at Rs 9,342 crore as of Q3 FY26—including equity of Rs 5,088 crore and debt of Rs 4,254 crore—marking a 22% year-on-year growth. The company has installed 92.5 lakh smart meters cumulatively as of 9MFY26 and is on track to exceed its guidance of 1 crore meters by FY26-end. The under-implementation pipeline comprises 24.6 million smart meters across 10 projects, with a revenue potential of over Rs 29,519 crore. “We delivered another strong quarter despite operating challenges, supported by robust on-ground execution, focused O&M and disciplined capital management, which drove steady progress in project development. During the year, we commissioned four transmission projects and scaled cumulative smart meter installations to around 92.5 lakh, the highest by any player in the country at a benchmark daily installation rate. Looking ahead, the growth outlook across our businesses remains robust, with a sharp ramp-up in asset capitalisation across core segments and strong momentum in bidding activity over the short to medium term,” said Kandarp Patel, CEO, Adani Energy Solutions. AESL, part of the Adani portfolio, is a multidimensional organization with presence in various facets of the energy domain, namely power transmission, distribution, smart metering, and cooling solutions. AESL is India's largest private transmission company.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[InfoBeans Technologies slumps after Q3 PAT falls 15% sequentially]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/infobeans-technologies-slumps-after-q3-pat-falls-15-sequentially/1666870</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666870</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue for the period under review was Rs 138 crore, up 6% QoQ.

Revenue for the period under review was Rs 138 crore, up 6% QoQ. EBITDA was Rs 33 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 36 crore in Q2 FY26, down 6% QoQ. As compared with Q3 FY25, the company’s PAT and revenue are higher by 173% and 38%, respectively. The company’s board has approved the issue of bonus equity shares in the ratio of 3:1, i.e three bonus equity shares for every one equity share held as on the record date. The record date for determining the entitlement of the members of the company to receive bonus equity shares is 27 February 2026. Avinash Sethi, co-founder, InfoBeans Technologies, said: “During this reporting period, InfoBeans expanded its client base by successfully onboarding three new clients and grew its internal capacity by welcoming 77 new team members. Looking ahead, the company is committed to an aggressive investment strategy. This strategy is centered on scaling sales initiatives, cultivating specialized high-growth teams, and intensifying focus on engaging with large enterprise clients. InfoBeans specializes in AI-led software solutions for its enterprise clients to solve their most complex business problems. Strengthened by the partnership with Salesforce, ServiceNow, Microsoft, and agineo, our services enable corporations to transform their businesses and gain a competitive advantage digitally.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InfoBeansTechnologiesLtd_28430630090_65878.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>