<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:59:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/akme-fintrade-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1679108</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679108</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Arihant Capital Markets Ltd, DEE Development Engineers Ltd, V R Films & Studios Ltd and Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 February 2026.

Arihant Capital Markets Ltd, DEE Development Engineers Ltd, V R Films & Studios Ltd and Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 February 2026. Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd surged 19.39% to Rs 7.02 at 23-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 8.74 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.21 lakh shares in the past one month. Arihant Capital Markets Ltd soared 13.99% to Rs 85.45. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 65074 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14319 shares in the past one month. DEE Development Engineers Ltd spiked 13.17% to Rs 262. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 13.53 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10210 shares in the past one month. V R Films & Studios Ltd spurt 11.70% to Rs 14.7. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 359 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1585 shares in the past one month. Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd jumped 10.71% to Rs 62. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 3149 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 716 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AkmeFintradeIndiaLtd_46552741_74863.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Morepen Laboratories Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/morepen-laboratories-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1679102</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679102</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, CIE Automotive India Ltd and Kitex Garments Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026.

Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, CIE Automotive India Ltd and Kitex Garments Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026. Morepen Laboratories Ltd surged 15.01% to Rs 45.21 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 46.1 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.4 lakh shares in the past one month. Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd soared 9.95% to Rs 390.8. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 88032 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 31068 shares in the past one month. BLS International Services Ltd spiked 8.23% to Rs 290.65. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 13.23 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5.42 lakh shares in the past one month. CIE Automotive India Ltd exploded 7.07% to Rs 502.7. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.5 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15656 shares in the past one month. Kitex Garments Ltd added 6.15% to Rs 197.55. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 4.24 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.48 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MorepenLabs_34238238875_2685.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lotus Chocolate drops as Telangana facility to halt operations for 15 days]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lotus-chocolate-drops-as-telangana-facility-to-halt-operations-for-15-days/1679099</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679099</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said it will undertake a detailed and systematic assessment of the current operational capacity and infrastructure at Sangareddy plant.

The company said it will undertake a detailed and systematic assessment of the current operational capacity and infrastructure at Sangareddy plant. The said facility described as a legacy plant, manufactures various chocolate-based products, including choco chips and choco slabs, mainly catering to business-to-business customers. During this period, the company anticipates intermittent disruption to normal plant operations. However it does not anticipate any material impact on the sales. Lotus Chocolate Company manufactures the finest chocolates, cocoa products, and cocoa derivatives. Its products are supplied to chocolate makers and chocolate users across the world, from local bakeries to multinational companies. It is owned by Reliance Consumer Products (RCPL), which is the FMCG arm and a wholly owned subsidiary of Reliance Retail Ventures (RRVL), which is a subsidiary of Reliance Industries (RIL). The company’s standalone net profit tumbled 96.22% to Rs 0.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3.71 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 18.90% to Rs 133.63 crore in the third quarter of FY26 from Rs 146.69 crore recorded in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LotusChocolate_22571601181_2252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IDFC First Bank tumbles after disclosing Rs 590-crore fraud at Chandigarh branch]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/idfc-first-bank-tumbles-after-disclosing-rs-590-crore-fraud-at-chandigarh-branch/1679107</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679107</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing made on Sunday, the private sector bank said that based on a preliminary internal assessment (upon receipt of communication from a particular Department of Government of Haryana), the bank has identified an incident involving unauthorized and fraudulent activities by certain employees at a particular branch in Chandigarh and potentially involving other counterparties.

In a regulatory filing made on Sunday, the private sector bank said that based on a preliminary internal assessment (upon receipt of communication from a particular Department of Government of Haryana), the bank has identified an incident involving unauthorized and fraudulent activities by certain employees at a particular branch in Chandigarh and potentially involving other counterparties. Detailing the events that led to the aforementioned discover, the bank stated that it had received a request from a particular Department of Haryana Government for closure of its account and transfer of funds to another bank. In the process, certain discrepancies were observed in the amount mentioned vis-à-vis the balance in the account. From 18 February 2026 onwards, certain other Haryana Government entities engaged with the Bank with regard to their respective accounts with the bank. During this process, differences were observed between the balances in the account and the balances as mentioned by the said Haryana Government entities holding accounts with the bank. Based on the preliminary internal review conducted, the bank said that the matter was confined to a specific group of government-linked accounts within Haryana Government operated through the said branch in Chandigarh and do not extend to other customers of the Chandigarh Branch. The aggregate amount under reconciliation across the identified accounts at the above mentioned Branch is approximately Rs 590 crore, the bank stated. The impact may be determined based on receipt of further information, validation of claims, recoveries of any nature including those made through the process of marking lien on fraudulent beneficiary accounts maintained with other banks, liabilities of other entities involved in the fraudulent transactions, and the legal recovery process. The bank has placed four suspected officials under suspension pending investigation. The bank will pursue strict disciplinary, civil and criminal action against the employees and other external individuals responsible, in accordance with applicable law. A meeting of the special committee of the board for Monitoring and Follow-up of Cases of Frauds (SCBMF) was convened on 20 February 2026 and the matter was placed before the committee. The meeting of the audit committee and the board of directors were convened on 21 February 2026 to apprise on the matter. The statutory auditors have been informed. The bank has filed a complaint with the Police authorities and will extend full cooperation to the investigating agencies. The bank has sent recall request to certain beneficiary banks to lien mark balance in suspicious accounts held in these banks. In a separate filing, IDFC First Bank said that the bank has appointed KPMG to initiate an independent forensic audit in aforementioned matter. IDFC Bank is a universal bank, offering financial solutions through its nationwide branches, Internet, and mobile. The bank provides customized financial solutions to corporations, individuals, small and micro enterprises (SMEs), entrepreneurs, financial institutions, and the government.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDFCBank_27126132357_54759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex gains 323 pts; financial services shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-gains-323-pts-financial-services-shares-advance/1679098</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679098</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Frontline indices trimmed some of their early gains but continued to trade moderately higher in mid-morning deals after the Supreme Court of the United States on Friday struck down President Donald Trump’s sweeping global tariffs.

Frontline indices trimmed some of their early gains but continued to trade moderately higher in mid-morning deals after the Supreme Court of the United States on Friday struck down President Donald Trump’s sweeping global tariffs. The Nifty hovered above the 25,650 mark, while financial services stocks rebounded after declining in the previous trading session. At 11:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 322.72 points or 0.36% to 83,137.43. The Nifty 50 index surged 85.20 points or 0.34% to 25,656.10. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.51% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index added 0.24%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,116 shares rose and 1,635 shares fell. A total of 250 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 2,40,62,535 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 1.65 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it will close on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 3,61,872 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.03 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 6,46,758 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.03 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Financial Services index rose 0.96% to 28,480.20. The index declined 1.38% in the past trading session. Axis Bank (up 2.10%), HDFC Life Insurance Company (up 1.97%), ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company (up 1.87%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (up 1.73%), Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company (up 1.67%), SBI Life Insurance Company (up 1.63%), ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company (up 1.2%), State Bank of India (up 1%), HDFC Bank (up 0.99%) and Shriram Finance (up 0.72%) advanced. On the other hand, Jio Financial Services (down 0.56%), REC (down 0.52%) and Bajaj Finserv (down 0.30%) edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: R&B Denims 1.86% after the company secured sales orders aggregating to around Rs 215.88 crore for the supply of around 12,000,000 meters of denim fabric products from established merchant exporters. JSW Infrastructure added 1.84% after the company‘s board approved the issuance of 25 crore equity shares with face value of Rs 2 each, to fund its multi-year expansion program Global Markets: Asian stock markets traded mostly with gains on Monday as investors monitored developments related to the United States tariffs. While the Supreme Court ruled on Friday that the Trump administration unlawfully imposed the measures last year, US President Donald Trump used different legal means to raise global levies to 15% from 10% over the weekend. Markets in China and Japan were closed for a holiday. On Friday, U.S. stocks rose after the Supreme Court ruling, potentially providing relief for companies burdened by higher costs from the duties and easing concern about sticky inflation still plaguing the U.S. economy. The S&P 500 advanced 0.69% and closed at 6,909.51, while the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9% and settled at 22,886.07. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 230.81 points, or 0.47%, and ended at 49,625.97. The 30-stock index recovered from a 200-point loss earlier in the session on disappointing economic data. Data released on Friday showed that the US economy expanded an annualized 1.4% in Q4 2025, the least since Q1 2025, following a 4.4% growth in Q3 and well below widely reported forecasts of 3%, the advance estimate showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEPC order book surges to Rs 10,455-cr amid strong mining, construction wins]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sepc-order-book-surges-to-rs-10455-cr-amid-strong-mining-construction-wins/1679097</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679097</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a standalone basis, excluding SEPC FZE, the company’s order book stood at Rs 7,255 crore, marking a sharp increase from Rs 4,501 crore as on 31 March 2025.

On a standalone basis, excluding SEPC FZE, the company’s order book stood at Rs 7,255 crore, marking a sharp increase from Rs 4,501 crore as on 31 March 2025. The nearly 61% expansion within nine months’ underscores accelerated order conversion, improved market credibility and increasing participation in execution-intensive projects. SEPC continues to maintain a domestic-led growth profile while retaining a meaningful global footprint. Of its consolidated order book of Rs 10,455 crore, domestic projects account for Rs 5,055 crore (48%), while international projects contribute Rs 5,400 crore, including Rs 2,200 crore under SEPC and Rs 3,200 crore through SEPC FZE. The strong domestic exposure positions the company to benefit from India’s ongoing infrastructure upcycle and sustained public sector capital expenditure, while the overseas portfolio adds geographic diversification and cross-border execution capabilities. During FY26 (up to 31 December 2025), the company secured fresh orders worth Rs 5,954 crore, reflecting robust bidding momentum and rising client confidence. The expanded order pipeline enhances multi-year revenue visibility and strengthens execution visibility, with disciplined project selection and improved scale expected to support sustained revenue growth, better operating leverage and stronger balance sheet resilience. Commenting on the strengthening order book, Venkataramani Jaiganesh, MD of SEPC, said: “We are encouraged by the strong order momentum we are witnessing this year. It reflects the confidence our clients have in our execution capabilities and the focused efforts of our teams across projects. The broader infrastructure push and continued industry tailwinds are creating meaningful opportunities, and we are approaching them with discipline and clarity. Our priority remains efficient execution, prudent financial management, and building a resilient business that can sustain growth over the long term.” SEPC The company provides end-to-end solutions to engineering challenges, offering multi disciplinary design, engineering, procurement, construction and project management services. The company’s consolidated zoomed 236.9% to Rs 14.96 crore on 156.3% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 340.97 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of SEPC rose 0.62% to currently trade at Rs 8.13 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShriramEPC_87688887012_28369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index speculators turn net long]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-speculators-turn-net-long/1679095</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679095</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index speculators turned net long, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

US dollar index speculators turned net long, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of US dollar index futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net long position of 328 contracts in the data reported through February 17, 2026, showing an increase of 1057 net long positions compared to the previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[R&B Denims rises after securing Rs 216-cr denim fabric orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rb-denims-rises-after-securing-rs-216-cr-denim-fabric-orders/1679092</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679092</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders are to be executed within six months as per agreed technical specifications, quality standards, and delivery schedules.

The orders are to be executed within six months as per agreed technical specifications, quality standards, and delivery schedules. The supplies are domestic in nature, and payment and other commercial terms have been mutually agreed upon between the parties. The company stated that the order inflow strengthens revenue visibility, enhances capacity utilization, and reinforces its order book position. The promoter group has no interest in the awarding entities, and the transactions do not fall under related party transactions. R&B Denims is engaged in the business of manufacturing and selling quality denim textile products. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 17.9% to Rs 8.29 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 10.10 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 17.8% YoY to Rs 111.14 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RBDenims_19552660015_44425.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Foreign portfolio investments and Indian rupee staged a comeback on India-EU free trade agreement and interim India-US trade deal: RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/foreign-portfolio-investments-and-indian-rupee-staged-a-comeback-on-india-eu-free-trade-agreement-and-interim-india-us-trade-deal-rbi/1679088</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679088</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Foreign portfolio investments and Indian rupee staged a comeback with investor sentiments turning around following the India-EU free trade agreement and the interim India-US trade deal, RBI noted in its monthly bulletin.

Foreign portfolio investments and Indian rupee staged a comeback with investor sentiments turning around following the India-EU free trade agreement and the interim India-US trade deal, RBI noted in its monthly bulletin. The completion of the India-EU free trade negotiations in end-January and the subsequent interim trade agreement between India and US are likely to play a significant role in the coming years by improving market access, enhancing export competitiveness, and integrating Indian firms more deeply into global value chains. In the immediate term, it has led to a change in investor sentiments. Foreign portfolio investment into equity and debt segment staged a comeback in February, the central bank noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at IDFC First Bank Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-idfc-first-bank-ltd-counter/1679084</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679084</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Medplus Health Services Ltd, AU Small Finance Bank Ltd, Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, Ajanta Pharma Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 23 February 2026.

Medplus Health Services Ltd, AU Small Finance Bank Ltd, Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, Ajanta Pharma Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 23 February 2026. IDFC First Bank Ltd recorded volume of 215.43 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 21.64 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9.96 lakh shares. The stock lost 16.38% to Rs.69.87. Volumes stood at 4.13 lakh shares in the last session. Medplus Health Services Ltd clocked volume of 51178 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 12 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4264 shares. The stock gained 0.41% to Rs.833.35. Volumes stood at 2669 shares in the last session. AU Small Finance Bank Ltd witnessed volume of 9.21 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.62 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 95797 shares. The stock dropped 7.01% to Rs.956.85. Volumes stood at 34110 shares in the last session. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd registered volume of 2.75 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7.88 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 34915 shares. The stock slipped 0.02% to Rs.1,724.05. Volumes stood at 62803 shares in the last session. Ajanta Pharma Ltd witnessed volume of 1.01 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7.33 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 13757 shares. The stock increased 1.18% to Rs.2,971.60. Volumes stood at 678 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDFCBank_27126132357_54759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI net sold USD 10.02 billion in December amid sustained pressure on rupee]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-net-sold-usd-1002-billion-in-december-amid-sustained-pressure-on-rupee/1679082</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679082</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) net sold USD 10.02 billion in December due to high volatility in the Indian rupee amid geopolitical tensions and uncertainties over US tariffs, the central bank monthly data showed.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) net sold USD 10.02 billion in December due to high volatility in the Indian rupee amid geopolitical tensions and uncertainties over US tariffs, the central bank monthly data showed. December becomes the seventh consecutive month of net dollar sales by the central bank in the spot currency market. According to the RBI's monthly bulletin data, the central bank net sold USD 9.710 billion in November, USD 11.877 billion in October, USD 7.910 billion in September, USD 7.695 billion in August, USD 2.540 billion in July, and USD 3.661 billion in June.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty tad above 25,700 level; PSU bank shares in demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-tad-above-25700-level-psu-bank-shares-in-demand/1679079</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679079</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in the morning trade after the US Supreme Court on Friday struck down President Donald Trump’s sweeping global tariffs.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in the morning trade after the US Supreme Court on Friday struck down President Donald Trump’s sweeping global tariffs. The Nifty traded above the 25,700 level. PSU bank shares advanced after declining in the past trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 419.22 points or 0.52% to 83,233.83. The Nifty 50 index surged 130.21 points or 0.51% to 25,701.40. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index shed 0.11% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index gained 0.51%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,116 shares rose and 1,635 shares fell. A total of 250 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index jumped 1.73% to 9,833. The index declined 1.38% in the past trading session. SBI Life Insurance Company (up 2.19%), Axis Bank (up 2.13%), Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company (up 2.08%), HDFC Life Insurance Company (up 2%), Muthoot Finance (up 1.93%), ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company (up 1.76%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (up 1.46%), Shriram Finance (up 1.35%), ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company (up 1.29%) and HDFC Bank (up 1.18%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone advanced 2.72% after the company’s subsidiary Adani Gangavaram Port signed a memorandum of understanding with NMDC, a Government of India enterprise, and Vale S.A., Brazil. RailTel Corporation of India rose 0.97%. The company secured a contract worth Rs 1,136.18 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JSW Infra gains after board OKs fundraising proposal to back expansion ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jsw-infra-gains-after-board-oks-fundraising-proposal-to-back-expansion/1679080</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679080</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The fundraising may be undertaken through one or more of following modes such as qualified institutional placement (QIP), further public offer (FPO), rights issue or through any other permissible mode.

The fundraising may be undertaken through one or more of following modes such as qualified institutional placement (QIP), further public offer (FPO), rights issue or through any other permissible mode. The issuance of shares will also enable compliance with SEBI’s Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) requirement. The board has authorised the finance committee of the company to inter-alia take necessary steps including deciding the timing, price, terms and conditions of the issuance of the equity shares. The company is executing a Rs 39,000 crore integrated capex plan across ports and logistics, targeting a scale up of port capacity from 177 MTPA to 400 MTPA by FY2030 through brownfield expansions, connectivity projects and greenfield developments in Odisha, Karnataka, Maharashtra and Oman. In parallel, the company is investing Rs 9,000 crore to build a fully integrated ports to hinterland logistics ecosystem—which forms an integral part of the overall Rs 39,000 crore capex programme. As previously guided, the company remains on a strong growth trajectory, with operating EBITDA expected to double by FY28 from FY26 levels to reach around Rs 5,000 crore. This outlook is underpinned by clear execution visibility across the under-construction Projects in the Ports segment and the transition of rolling assets from capex to EBITDA contribution within the Logistics segment. Rinkesh Roy, joint managing director & CEO, JSWIL, said, “The fund raising initiative marks a pivotal step in the Company’s journey to build a world class ports and logistics ecosystem for India. Beyond supporting our growth projects and strengthening our national footprint, it will also enable us to meet the Minimum Public Shareholding requirement within the mandated timeline. This underscores our commitment to governance excellence, deeper market participation, and long term value creation as we shape the country’s future maritime trade and logistics landscape.” JSW Infrastructure, a part of JSW Group, is the second largest commercial port operator in India in terms of cargo handling capacity. It develops and operates ports and port terminals pursuant to port concessions. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 8.71% to Rs 364.85 crore on 14.2% revenue from operations to Rs 1,349.66 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JSWInfrastructureLtd_46143694_42944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Capitalmind Mutual Fund announces change in Exit Load Structure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/capitalmind-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-exit-load-structure/1679081</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679081</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Capitalmind Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following scheme stands revised with effect from February 23, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Exit Load Revised Exit Load Capitalmind Multi Asset Allocation Fund If Units redeemed or switched within 12 months from the date of allotment – 1% of the applicable NAV If redeemed/switched out after 12 months from the date of allotment – Nil If Units redeemed or switched within 30 days from the date of allotment – 1% of the applicable NAV If redeemed/switched out after 30 days from the date of allotment – Nil

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves soar by $8.66 billion to hit an all-time high of $725.7 billion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-soar-by-866-billion-to-hit-an-all-time-high-of-7257-billion/1679078</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679078</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's foreign exchange reserves rose by $8.66 billion from a week earlier to hit an all-time high of $725.727 billion in the week ending February 13, latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) showed on Friday.

India's foreign exchange reserves rose by $8.66 billion from a week earlier to hit an all-time high of $725.727 billion in the week ending February 13, latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) showed on Friday. For the week ending February 13, foreign currency assets rose by $3.55 billion, gold by $4.99 billion and Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) by $103 million, the official data showed. India's reserve position with the IMF was also up by $19 million to $4.734 billion in the reporting week, RBI data showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-2891849__340_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India and Brazil aim for $30 billion trade partnership by 2030]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-and-brazil-aim-for-30-billion-trade-partnership-by-2030/1679076</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679076</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Brazilian President Mr Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva said that bilateral trade between India and Brazil could reach $30 billion by 2030 — doubling current volumes — as he addressed the India-Brazil Business Forum.

Brazilian President Mr Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva said that bilateral trade between India and Brazil could reach $30 billion by 2030 — doubling current volumes — as he addressed the India-Brazil Business Forum. The declaration came against a backdrop of rapidly deepening ties. Bilateral trade stood at a mere $2.4 billion in 2006 when both nations formalised their strategic partnership. It has since risen to $15 billion — a 25 per cent increase last year alone — yet both leaders described the figure as falling well short of potential. "The distance between Brazil and India is merely a detail in the face of the potential of friendship between our two nations," said Lula, adding that both countries had for too long directed their commercial attention towards other countries at the expense of each other. "We have now resolved to change that behaviour." Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal echoed the ambition but was equally candid about the gap. "Our bilateral trade, even though it grew by 25 per cent to $15 billion, is truly suboptimal," he said. "We have to be significantly more ambitious today." Minister Goyal pointed to the structural complementarities underpinning the relationship — Brazil's reserves of niobium, lithium and iron ore alongside its agricultural dominance, and India's technological depth and manufacturing capacity. "Together we have the potential to reshape global value chains, with resources, innovation and a forward-looking vision," he said, inviting Brazilian companies to co-invest and co-create in India. "Brazil is a global agriculture powerhouse producing several products that help feed billions. Its aerospace, automotive and digital technology industries are rapidly evolving, offering abundant opportunities for collaboration. All of this comes together to make Brazil our strategic partner in global supply chains," Goyal added.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hsbc-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1679077</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679077</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

HSBC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The quantum of dividend (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.190 HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.215 HSBC Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.122 HSBC Balanced Advantage Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.143 HSBC Multi Asset Allocation Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.200 HSBC Multi Asset Allocation Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.440 HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – Annual IDCW Option: 1.500 HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – Annual IDCW Option: 1.700 HSBC Flexi Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 4.000 HSBC Flexi Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.150 HSBC Asia Pacific (Ex Japan) DYF – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 2.150 HSBC Asia Pacific (Ex Japan) DYF – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 2.150

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1679073</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679073</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW in the following schemes.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW in the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: HDFC Balanced Advantage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.250 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.250

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Morepen Labs surges after bagging Rs 825 crore CDMO contract from global pharma firm]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/morepen-labs-surges-after-bagging-rs-825-crore-cdmo-contract-from-global-pharma-firm/1679075</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679075</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company stated that the supplies under the said mandate are expected to commence within the next 4–5 months, with execution scheduled through Q1 of the following financial year, subject to customary operational and regulatory processes.

The company stated that the supplies under the said mandate are expected to commence within the next 4–5 months, with execution scheduled through Q1 of the following financial year, subject to customary operational and regulatory processes. Morepen Labs further said that this engagement marks one of the most significant single CDMO mandates in the Company’s history, as it scales its global manufacturing footprint. Sushil Suri, chairman & managing director, said: "This mandate represents an important milestone in the evolution of Morepen’s manufacturing platform. We view CDMO as a natural extension of our established API strengths, creating additional avenues of scale, stability, and long-term value creation while continuing to reinforce our core businesses." Morepen Laboratories is a vertically integrated pharmaceutical and healthcare company delivering APIs, branded generics, medical devices, and consumer wellness products worldwide. The company's consolidated net profit rose 3.07% to Rs 27.51 crore on a 6.93% increase in revenue to Rs 484.16 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. On the BSE, over 20.92 lakh shares of the company had changed hands at the counter as compared with the average trading volume of 1.56 lakh shares. In the last one year, the scrip has lost 12.08% while the benchmark S&P BSE Sesnex and the S&P BSE Healthcare index have gained 11.90% and 9.85%, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MorepenLabs_34238238875_2685.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel Corp gains after bagging Rs 1,136-cr Maharashtra contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-corp-gains-after-bagging-rs-1136-cr-maharashtra-contract/1679065</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679065</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RailTel, in consortium with Ashoka Buildcon, has been selected as the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for the modernization of offices of the Inspector General of Registration (IGR) and Controller of Stamps under the Government of Maharashtra.

RailTel, in consortium with Ashoka Buildcon, has been selected as the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for the modernization of offices of the Inspector General of Registration (IGR) and Controller of Stamps under the Government of Maharashtra. As per the letter of intent (LoI), the accepted rate is Rs 24.75 per page. The average number of pages scanned annually over the past five years, as per the Request for Proposal (RFP), stood at 9.18 crore pages. Based on this volume, the estimated financial impact over the five-year contract period is approximately Rs 1,136.18 crore. RailTel was incorporated in 2000, with the objective of creating nationwide broadband and VPN services, telecom, and multimedia networks to modernize the train control operation and safety system of Indian Railways. The company’s standalone net profit declined 4.07% to Rs 62.40 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.05 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 18.99% YoY to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>