<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:49:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman Launches National Monetisation Pipeline 2.0]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/finance-minister-nirmala-sitharaman-launches-national-monetisation-pipeline-20/1679235</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679235</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has launched the second phase of asset monetisation pipeline of Central ministries and public sector entities in New Delhi.

Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has launched the second phase of asset monetisation pipeline of Central ministries and public sector entities in New Delhi. The second phase of the pipeline has been developed by NITI Aayog, in consultation with infrastructure line ministries, based on the mandate for ‘Asset Monetisation Plan 2025-30’ as announced in the Union Budget 2025-26. The National Monetisation Pipeline 2.0 estimates aggregate monetisation potential of 16.72 lakh crore rupees, including private sector investment of 5.8 lakh crore rupees under asset monetisation pipeline of Central ministries and public sector entities, over the five-year period from Financial Year 2025-26 to Financial Year 2029-30. In her address, Ms Sitharaman complimented all the ministries and departments of the Government and NITI Aayog for meeting nearly 90 percent of the target of six lakh crore rupees set for four years in the implementation of the National Monetisation Pipeline 1.0. She said NMP 2.0 is aligned with the mission of achieving Viksit Bharat through accelerated infrastructure development and it has the potential to fuel India’s growth momentum. The National Monetisation Pipeline 2.0 was released in presence of CEO, NITI Aayog and the Secretaries of infrastructure line ministries, along with the Secretaries of the Ministry of Finance, the Ministry of Law and the Chief Economic Adviser.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/people-5-1163707_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India halves RoDTEP export rebates, raising cost pressures on exporters]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-halves-rodtep-export-rebates-raising-cost-pressures-on-exporters/1679232</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679232</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India has reduced the benefits available to exporters under the Remission of Duties and Taxes on Exported Products (RoDTEP) scheme by 50 per cent, a move that is expected to impact operating margins across sectors.

India has reduced the benefits available to exporters under the Remission of Duties and Taxes on Exported Products (RoDTEP) scheme by 50 per cent, a move that is expected to impact operating margins across sectors. In a recent notification, the government said that RoDTEP benefits will now be limited to half of the earlier notified rates and value caps with immediate effect. RoDTEP is designed to refund various duties, taxes and levies paid at the central, state and local levels on exported goods. It covers 8,555 tariff lines, with rebate rates ranging from 0.01 per cent for some gems and jewellery items to 4.3 per cent for woven fabrics. Following the revision, both the rebate rates and the maximum value caps have been reduced by half. For example, the rebate on unginned raw cotton of staple length up to 20 mm has been cut from 3.1 per cent (capped at Rs 1.60 per kg) to 1.55 per cent (capped at Rs 0.80 per kg). Trade experts warn that even a small rise in costs can affect competitiveness in price-sensitive markets, especially at a time of weak global demand and strong competition from countries such as Vietnam and Bangladesh. Frequent changes in rates may also make long-term pricing decisions more challenging for exporters. WTO rules permit such remission because it merely neutralizes domestic taxes on exports. Cutting these rates therefore raises exporters’ costs at a time when India’s shipments are already facing weak global demand, supply disruptions and rising compliance burdens, eroding competitiveness in price-sensitive markets. Further, revising RoDTEP rates frequently makes it difficult to build rebates into long-term pricing and contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Organic Recycling jumps on bagging large-scale CBG project order in Madhya Pradesh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/organic-recycling-jumps-on-bagging-large-scale-cbg-project-order-in-madhya-pradesh/1679210</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679210</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order has been classified as a large-scale contract, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 50–100 crore.

The order has been classified as a large-scale contract, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 50–100 crore. The proposed facility will have a production capacity of 10 tonnes per day (TPD) of CBG using agro-based feedstock and will form part of a larger integrated modern gaushala project, the company said. Under the contract, ORSL will undertake equity participation and execute the project on an end-to-end EPC basis. The scope includes detailed engineering, technology integration, supply of critical equipment, construction, installation and commissioning of the plant. The project marks a strategic collaboration between the two companies and is part of a broader plan to deploy 10 such integrated projects across various locations in Madhya Pradesh over the next three years. The total planned investment for these projects is estimated at Rs 500–600 crores. The development strengthens ORSL’s presence in the compressed bio-gas and sustainable waste-to-energy segment. Sarang Bhand, Managing Director, ORSL, said: "This project reinforces ORSL’s commitment to delivering scalable, future-ready infrastructure that bridges agriculture, sustainability, and renewable energy. Our collaboration with Shreyam Manek Agro Product demonstrates the growing industry confidence in integrated circular economy solutions, and we look forward to executing this project with the highest standards of engineering excellence." Pankaj Tanwar, CEO - Bioenergy of ORSL, said: “This project reflects the strength of ORSL’s integrated agri-energy infrastructure where engineering excellence meets long-term operational sustainability. We remain focused on delivering reliable, highperformance solutions that create measurable environmental and economic value for all stakeholders.”. Organic Recycling Systems engaged in the business of providing Infrastructural Facilities. On a full-year basis, the company’s standalone net profit declined 8.6% to Rs 3.42 crore in FY25, even as revenue from operations surged 39.2% to Rs 25.23 crore compared with FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OrganicRecyclingSystemsLtd_47725929_73927.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Signpost India gains on securing Rs 450-cr KMC outdoor ad contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/signpost-india-gains-on-securing-rs-450-cr-kmc-outdoor-ad-contract/1679217</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679217</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract covers prominent stretches including Park Street (Mother Teresa Sarani) from Jawaharlal Nehru Road to Mullick Bazar Crossing, Camac Street (Abanindranath Sarani), Theatre Road (Shakespeare Sarani), and Park-o-Mat.

The contract covers prominent stretches including Park Street (Mother Teresa Sarani) from Jawaharlal Nehru Road to Mullick Bazar Crossing, Camac Street (Abanindranath Sarani), Theatre Road (Shakespeare Sarani), and Park-o-Mat. The concession period is 10 years, extendable by two years. Under the agreement, Signpost will pay KMC an annual fixed fee of Rs 16.38 crore, with a 5% escalation every three years. The total projected revenue to KMC, including state GST, is estimated at around Rs 250 crore over the concession tenure. The company’s consolidated profit after tax jumped sharply to Rs 18.13 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 215.3% YoY increase over Rs 5.75 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 26.85% YoY to Rs 142.34 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 112.21 crore in the year-ago quarter. Signpost India is engaged in the advertising business, with a focus on outdoor media across formats such as hoardings, bus panels, railway media, bus shelters, airports, newspapers, and souvenir publications.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SignpostIndiaLtd_66037594_69820.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR slumps amid dollar rebound overseas; muted start to local equities weigh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-slumps-amid-dollar-rebound-overseas-muted-start-to-local-equities-weigh/1679207</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679207</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee lost momentum and fell against the dollar in opening trades on Tuesday.

The Indian rupee lost momentum and fell against the dollar in opening trades on Tuesday. INR opened at Rs 90.91 per dollar and fell to a low of 90.96 so far during the day. Dollar rebound and muted start to local equities weighed on the counter. Yesterday, rupee gained 7 paise to settle at 90.87 against the US dollar. The US Dollar faced intense selling pressure as investors turned anxious over the United States (US) trade policy outlook, following the Supreme Court (SC) ruling against President Donald Trump's tariff policy. However, foreign fund outflows, coupled with geopolitical concerns, capped gains for the local unit. Equity benchmark indices Sensex and Nifty closed higher on Monday, tracking gains in PSU bank, auto and financial stocks, as investors' sentiments improved after the US Supreme Court struck down the Trump administration's sweeping tariffs. The 30-share BSE Sensex climbed 479.95 points, or 0.58 per cent, to settle at 83,294.66. The 50-share NSE Nifty advanced 141.75 points, or 0.55 per cent, to close at 25,713.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waaree Energies bags 500-MW solar module supply order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waaree-energies-bags-500-mw-solar-module-supply-order/1679205</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679205</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The one-time order will be executed in FY2026–27.

The one-time order will be executed in FY2026–27. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity. The company said the promoter or promoter group has no interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not fall under related party transactions. Mumbai-based Waaree Energies is a renewable energy company. It offers innovative solar solutions, including panel manufacturing, EPC services, project development, and rooftop systems. The company reported a 115.64% year-on-year (YoY) jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,062.46 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 492.69 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Revenue from operations soared 118.81% YoY to Rs 7,565.05 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of Waaree Energies shed 0.27% to Rs 2,907.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WaareeEnergiesLtd_42747859_39763.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers drops in early trade; breadth weak]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-drops-in-early-trade-breadth-weak/1679206</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679206</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks opened the session sharply lower, dragged down by heavy selling in index heavyweight Bharti Airtel and weakness across IT stocks.

The headline equity benchmarks opened the session sharply lower, dragged down by heavy selling in index heavyweight Bharti Airtel and weakness across IT stocks. Investor sentiment remained subdued after U.S. President Donald Trump’s renewed tariff threats rattled global markets, while the expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE added to the volatility in early trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,550 mark. IT, realty and media shares declined, while metal and oil & gas shares advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 603.44 points or 0.72% to 82,691.22. The Nifty 50 index lost 178.28 points or 0.68% to 25,535.25. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.69% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.93%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 963 shares rose and 2023 shares fell. A total of 184 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,483.70 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 1,292.24 crore in the Indian equity market on 23 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharti Airtel slipped 2.03%. The company announced major plans for its non-banking financial company (NBFC), Airtel Money, underscoring its commitment to narrowing the credit gap in India. The NBFC subsidiary will be capitalized with Rs 20,000 crore, to be injected over the next few years. Airtel will contribute 70 percent, while the promoter group, through Bharti Enterprises, will bring in the remaining 30%. HUDCO (down 0.93%), Piramal Pharma (down 1.36%), Tata Technologies (down 2.12%) and Torrent Power (down 2.12) to be excluded from F&O The National Stock Exchange (NSE) has decided to exclude Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO), Piramal Pharma, Tata Technologies, and Torrent Power from the Futures & Options (F&O) segment with effect from 29 April 2026. IDFC First Bank added 0.61%. The company said the recent volatility in its share price followed the detection of a Rs 590-crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch. The bank added that reports regarding government de-empanelment are part of the ordinary course of business. Numbers to Track: The yield on India’s 10-year benchmark federal paper was unchanged at 6.699%. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9575 compared with its close of 90.8950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 0.58% to Rs 160,668. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.13% to 97.77. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.47% to 4.045. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 59 cents or 0.83% to $72.08 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian markets traded mixed on Tuesday as investors weighed renewed tariff threats from U.S. President Donald Trump and concerns that artificial intelligence could disrupt software companies. Trump posted on Truth Social Monday that any country that wants to “play games” with the Supreme Court decision “will be met with a much higher tariff.” The comments followed a Supreme Court decision Friday striking down tariffs enacted under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act. In response, Trump said he would impose a 15% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act. Investors in Asia were also assessing China’s loan prime rate (LPR) decision. China’s central bank on Tuesday kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged at 3% for the one-year LPR and 3.5% for the five-year LPR. Overnight on Wall Street, U.S. equities tumbled on Monday as investors grappled with persistent fears around artificial intelligence disruptions to various industries and President Donald Trump’s decision to raise his global tariffs. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 821.91 points, or 1.66%, to close at 48,804.06, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.13% and ended at 22,627.27. The S&P 500 shed 1.04% and closed at 6,837.75, putting it into the red once again for 2026. The 30-stock Dow was dragged down by IBM shares, which declined 13% on the heels of Anthropic outlining new programming capabilities for its Claude Code product. Software stocks such as Microsoft and CrowdStrike were under pressure yet again as AI disruption worries hovered over the market. However, software hasn’t been the only sector to be hit due to AI fears recently: Stocks linked to trucking and logistics, commercial real estate and financial services have similarly suffered losses this month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin secures European Commission approval for Ranluspec]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-secures-european-commission-approval-for-ranluspec/1679201</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679201</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ranibizumab is a recombinant humanized IgG1 monoclonal antibody fragment that binds and inhibits vascular endothelial growth factor A.

Ranibizumab is a recombinant humanized IgG1 monoclonal antibody fragment that binds and inhibits vascular endothelial growth factor A. Its indications encompass the treatment of patients with neovascular (wet) age-related macular degeneration, macular edema following retinal vein occlusion, diabetic macular edema, proliferative diabetic retinopathy, and choroidal neovascularization. The company’s biosimilar ranibizumab will be commercialized by Sandoz across the European Union (excluding Germany). In France, the product will be commercialized by two companies, Sandoz and Biogaran. Thierry Volle, President EMEA and Emerging Markets, Lupin, said, “We are very pleased to receive the European Commission approval for ranibizumab. This achievement underscores the strength and quality of our scientific capabilities and manufacturing excellence. We remain firmly committed to expanding access to innovative, high-quality, and affordable biologic therapies for underserved patients worldwide.” Dr. Cyrus Karkaria, president Biotechnology, Lupin, said, “The approval from the European Commission for our biosimilar ranibizumab is a milestone that validates our unwavering commitment and scientific standards to making advanced biologic therapies more accessible.” Lupin is a global pharmaceutical leader headquartered in Mumbai, India, with products distributed in over 100 markets. It specializes in pharmaceutical products, including branded and generic formulations, complex generics, biotechnology products, and active pharmaceutical ingredients. The pharmaceutical company reported a 37.46% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,175.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 855.16 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter fell 0.33% to end at Rs 2237.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at green opening for key indices; Trump revives tariff threat after major Supreme Court ruling]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-green-opening-for-key-indices-trump-revives-tariff-threat-after-major-supreme-court-ruling/1679193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679193</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 12.50 points, suggesting a green start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 12.50 points, suggesting a green start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,483.70 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 1,292.24 crore in the Indian equity market on 23 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 1,472.46 crore in the cash market so far in February (till 23 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia markets traded mixed on Tuesday as investors weighed renewed tariff threats from U.S. President Donald Trump and concerns that artificial intelligence could disrupt software companies. Trump posted on Truth Social Monday that any country that wants to “play games” with the Supreme Court decision “will be met with a much higher tariff.” The comments followed a Supreme Court decision Friday striking down tariffs enacted under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act. In response, Trump said he would impose a 15% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act. Investors in Asia were also assessing China’s loan prime rate (LPR) decision. China’s central bank on Tuesday kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged at 3% for the one-year LPR and 3.5% for the five-year LPR. Overnight on Wall Street, U.S. equities tumbled on Monday as investors grappled with persistent fears around artificial intelligence disruptions to various industries and President Donald Trump’s decision to raise his global tariffs. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 821.91 points, or 1.66%, to close at 48,804.06, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.13% and ended at 22,627.27. The S&P 500 shed 1.04% and closed at 6,837.75, putting it into the red once again for 2026. The 30-stock Dow was dragged down by IBM shares, which declined 13% on the heels of Anthropic outlining new programming capabilities for its Claude Code product. Software stocks such as Microsoft and CrowdStrike were under pressure yet again as AI disruption worries hovered over the market. However, software hasn’t been the only sector to be hit due to AI fears recently: Stocks linked to trucking and logistics, commercial real estate and financial services have similarly suffered losses this month. Domestic Market: The key equity indices ended with moderate gains on Monday, extending a two-day rally after the US Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs. Investors will monitor crude oil prices and movements in gold prices. The Nifty settled above the 25,700 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 479.95 points or 0.58% to 83,294.66. The Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Tata Tech, Torrent Power, MobiKwik, Bharti Airtel, IDFC First Bank, BPCL, Chalet Hotels]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-tata-tech-torrent-power-mobikwik-bharti-airtel-idfc-first-bank-bpcl-chalet-hotels/1679192</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679192</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: SAIL shares are banned from F&O trading on 24 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: SAIL shares are banned from F&O trading on 24 February 2026. New listing: In the SME segment, Fractal Industries is scheduled to debut on the bourses today. The company’s IPO was subscribed 5.13 times. The price band for the issue was fixed at Rs 205–216 per share. Stocks to Watch: Bharti Airtel announced major plans for its non-banking financial company (NBFC), Airtel Money, underscoring its commitment to narrowing the credit gap in India. The NBFC subsidiary will be capitalized with Rs 20,000 crore, to be injected over the next few years. Airtel will contribute 70 percent, while the promoter group, through Bharti Enterprises, will bring in the remaining 30 percent. HUDCO, Piramal Pharma, Tata Technologies and Torrent Power to be excluded from F&O The National Stock Exchange (NSE) has decided to exclude Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO), Piramal Pharma, Tata Technologies, and Torrent Power from the Futures & Options (F&O) segment with effect from 29 April 2026. One Mobikwik Systems announced that its subsidiary, Mobikwik Securities Broking, has received approval from the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) to commence its stock broking business. IDFC First Bank said the recent volatility in its share price followed the detection of a Rs 590-crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch. The bank added that reports regarding government de-empanelment are part of the ordinary course of business. Container Corporation of India and Vizhinjam International Seaport, a Government of Kerala undertaking, have signed a non-binding and non-exclusive Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) at Thiruvananthapuram for the development of a Container Freight Station (CFS) near Vizhinjam International Seaport, Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala. Lupin said it has received approval from the European Commission for its biosimilar ranibizumab, Ranluspec (vials and pre-filled syringes), following a positive opinion from the Committee for Medicinal Products for Human Use (CHMP). Pace Digitek said that its subsidiary, Lineage Power, has secured a purchase order worth Rs 158.7 crore from Reliance Industries for the supply of Li-ion battery packs (48V 15S1P 314 AH). Blue Cloud Softech Solutions said its board has approved a definitive agreement framework to acquire a 100% stake in Global Impex Inc. from ConnectM Technology Solutions Inc, a US-based modern energy economy company. PC Jeweller said its arm has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, PCJ Mining SARL, in the Republic of Chad. Samvardhana Motherson International said it has inaugurated a manufacturing facility in Sanand, Gujarat, under its joint venture with Marelli. The advanced plant, set up as a strategic partnership with Marelli, will exclusively manufacture exterior lighting systems, strengthening the group’s capabilities in automotive component manufacturing. Silver Touch Technologies said it has been selected by the Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI) for a strategic digital transformation engagement. The company will act as the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for application development and enhancement, as well as for the operations and maintenance of FSSAI’s portals and applications. Waaree Energies said its arm signed an agreement with ZFI to expand a 2.5-GW electrolyzer project in Uttar Pradesh and bagged a separate 500 MW solar module order from an unnamed producer. Signpost India has received an order worth Rs 450 crore from the Kolkata Municipal Corporation for exclusive outdoor advertising rights on key stretches, including Park Street (Mother Teresa Sarani), Jawaharlal Nehru Road, Camac Street (Abanindranath Sarani), and Theatre Road (Shakespeare Sarani), under the ‘Kolkata Streetscape Renaissance’ project on a PPP basis. Sigma Advanced Systems has secured fresh orders worth about Rs 100 crore from the Ministry of Defence and associated defence PSUs. The contracts relate to ongoing strategic programs across missile systems, naval platforms, and airborne applications, under which the company will supply built-to-spec systems, control electronics, and actuation solutions. Chalet Hotels said its board has approved the development of a proposed 330-room luxury hotel, along with commercial/retail space of 36,255 sq ft, at Madhapur in Hyderabad, with an investment of Rs 632.8 crore. Upon completion, this will be the company’s third hotel in Hyderabad. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) has received a tax demand order worth Rs 1,816.65 crore (duty of Rs 476.94 crore, interest up to date of Rs 1,339.70 crore, and a penalty of Rs 95,000) from the Central Tax & Central Excise Department, Kochi, for the period from September 2004 to May 2010. The major portion of the demand pertains to the pre-merger period of Kochi Refineries (KRL), that is, September 2004 to August 2006, which was pending adjudication. BPCL said it will file an appeal against the order before the Customs, Excise and Service Tax Appellate Tribunal (CESTAT). RBL Bank said the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has approved the reappointment of Chandan Sinha as Non-Executive (Part-time) Chairman for a second term from 21 May 2026 to 20 May 2029. Cholamandalam Investment & Finance said it has allotted 1 lakh non-convertible debentures (NCDs) aggregating to Rs 1,000 crore, including a greenshoe option.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pace Digitek bags Rs 159-cr battery pack order from Reliance Industries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pace-digitek-bags-rs-159-cr-battery-pack-order-from-reliance-industries/1679186</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679186</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract entails the supply of Li-ion battery packs of specification 48V, 15S1P, 314 AH, the company said in a regulatory filing.

The contract entails the supply of Li-ion battery packs of specification 48V, 15S1P, 314 AH, the company said in a regulatory filing. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and is to be executed by 31 August 2026. Pace Digitek clarified that neither its promoters nor promoter group companies have any interest in the awarding entity. The company further stated that the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Pace Digitek provides solutions for telecom infra and solar industries. It is involved in the manufacturing, installation and commissioning of DC Power systems, lithium batteries, monitoring systems and inverter. The company reported a rise in consolidated net profit of 8.1% year-on-year to Rs 75.84 crore on a 13.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 643.97 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip fell 1.06% to end at Rs 182.10 on the BSE. Reliance Industries is India's largest private sector company. Its activities span hydrocarbon exploration and production, petroleum refining and marketing, petrochemicals, advanced materials and composites, renewables (solar and hydrogen), retail and digital services. The conglomerate had reported a 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on a 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip rose 0.55% to end at Rs 1,427.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PACEDIGITEKLIMITED_26475505_94643.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>