<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:42:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brainbees Solutions Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brainbees-solutions-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678560</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678560</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IIFL Capital Services Ltd, Hexaware Technologies Ltd, V I P Industries Ltd and Waaree Energies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 18 February 2026.

IIFL Capital Services Ltd, Hexaware Technologies Ltd, V I P Industries Ltd and Waaree Energies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 18 February 2026. Brainbees Solutions Ltd tumbled 5.58% to Rs 217.3 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.37 lakh shares in the past one month. IIFL Capital Services Ltd lost 4.39% to Rs 320.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 36472 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53614 shares in the past one month. Hexaware Technologies Ltd crashed 3.99% to Rs 572.15. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 99049 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.59 lakh shares in the past one month. V I P Industries Ltd pared 3.49% to Rs 369.45. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8412 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9728 shares in the past one month. Waaree Energies Ltd slipped 3.34% to Rs 2952. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.21 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.14 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrainbeesSolutionsLtd_65573979_68149.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[E2E Networks clarifies NVIDIA tie-up; says no new deal beyond earlier disclosure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/e2e-networks-clarifies-nvidia-tie-up-says-no-new-deal-beyond-earlier-disclosure/1678559</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678559</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a filing dated 18 February 2026, the company said it has an existing relationship with NVIDIA that underpins its cloud and AI infrastructure offerings.

In a filing dated 18 February 2026, the company said it has an existing relationship with NVIDIA that underpins its cloud and AI infrastructure offerings. It clarified that the latest media coverage was a reiteration and public acknowledgement of this relationship, and not the result of fresh negotiations, binding agreements or new partnerships. The company pointed out that it had already disclosed the procurement and deployment of NVIDIA B200 GPU clusters in Chennai through a press release dated 9 January 2026. It also referred to statements made by management during analyst and investor conference calls, transcripts of which were filed with the exchange. E2E Networks further stated that there is no undisclosed material information that could explain the recent movement in its share price or trading volumes. It added that the news article does not have any additional material impact on its operations or financial position beyond what has already been communicated to the exchanges. The company reiterated its commitment to regulatory compliance and said it will continue to inform the exchanges of any material developments as required. NVIDIA said that E2E Networks is building a Blackwell GPU cluster on its TIR cloud platform, with the infrastructure being deployed at the L&T Vyoma Data Center in Chennai. The platform will incorporate NVIDIA HGX B200 systems, NVIDIA Enterprise software and NVIDIA Nemotron open models to support sovereign AI development across sectors including healthcare, finance, manufacturing and agriculture. At the AI Impact Summit in New Delhi, NVIDIA also highlighted its broader partnerships in India, aligned with the government’s $1 billion-plus IndiaAI Mission aimed at expanding compute capacity, building sovereign AI models and datasets, and strengthening AI education, startups and responsible AI frameworks. E2E Networks operates as a cloud infrastructure provider in India, offering GPU computing, enterprise cloud solutions and managed services for artificial intelligence and machine learning workloads. On a standalone basis, E2E Networks reported net loss of Rs 5.70 crore in Q3 December 2025 as against net profit of Rs 11.59 crore in Q3 December 2024. Net sales rose 68.32% YoY to Rs 70.02 crore in Q3 December 2025. Shares of E2E Networks were up 10.49% at Rs 2,815.20 on the NSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/E2ENetworksLtd_43382383477_72373.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Netweb Tech sizzles after launching NVIDIA powered-AI supercomputers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/netweb-tech-sizzles-after-launching-nvidia-powered-ai-supercomputers/1678558</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678558</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tyrone Camarero Spark, is the world’s smallest AI supercomputer delivering NVIDIA’s AI stack in a compact desktop form factor.

Tyrone Camarero Spark, is the world’s smallest AI supercomputer delivering NVIDIA’s AI stack in a compact desktop form factor. It combines NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs, NVIDIA Grace CPUs, NVIDIA Networking, NVIDIA CUDA-X libraries and NVIDIA AI software stack, accelerating agentic and physical AI development to address the requirements of millions of AI developers in India. The company has also launched Tyrone AI Supercomputing systems based on NVIDIA Grace Blackwell platforms designed. This product and architecture, built on the NVIDIA GB200 NVL4 platform, delivers revolutionary performance through four NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs connected with an NVLink bridge and two NVIDIA Grace CPUs connected over NVLink-C2C. Compatible with liquid-cooled, NVIDIA MGX™ modular servers, it provides up to 2x performance for scientific computing, AI model training, and inference over the prior generation. Sanjay Lodha, managing director & CEO of Netweb Technologies India, said, “The Tyrone Camarero Spark provides AI developers t 1 Peta Flops of (FP4) performance out of the box in the tiniest form factor of 5.9 in x 5.9 in x 2in inches and with system power supply of just 240 Watts —whereas in 2016 a comparable performance of 170 Tera Flops (FP16) with same memory size of 128GB could be delivered with System Power requirement of 3200 Watts. This milestone revolutionizes AI compute in India by introducing new ways to conduct AI research and development. With this move we have created a whole new customer segment in collaboration with NVIDIA. Our deep collaboration with NVIDIA for the last 15 years has been instrumental in advancing AI infrastructure in India with the nation’s own sovereign-built, latest-generation NVIDIA systems. Make in India Tyrone GB200 systems, coupled with complete sovereign cloud stack and utilities provide a multi-node, liquid-cooled, rack-scale system design for the most compute-intensive workloads. This design will integrate 20 Tyrone GB200 MGX systems within a single liquid-cooled rack, comprising 40 NVIDIA Grace CPUs and 80 NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs, along with NVIDIA BlueField-3 DPUs, high-performance storage, and comprehensive end-to-end security.” Netweb Technologies is India’s leading high-end computing solutions (HCS) provider, with fully integrated design and manufacturing capabilities. The company’s HCS offering comprises HPC, Private cloud and HCI, AI systems and enterprise workstations, High performance storage (HPS) and Data Centre Servers. The company’s standalone net profit soared 146.7% to Rs 73.31 crore on 141% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 804.92 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NetwebTechnologiesIndiaLtd_73333970_78854.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Power India Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-power-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678557</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678557</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd, Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd Partly Paidup, Khandwala Securities Ltd and Creative Eye Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026.

VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd, Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd Partly Paidup, Khandwala Securities Ltd and Creative Eye Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026. GE Power India Ltd crashed 10.00% to Rs 496.85 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 6.44 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.88 lakh shares in the past one month. VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd tumbled 8.78% to Rs 11.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 51282 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 86051 shares in the past one month. Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd Partly Paidup lost 8.28% to Rs 320.1. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 37 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1180 shares in the past one month. Khandwala Securities Ltd plummeted 8.08% to Rs 18.1. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1106 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5736 shares in the past one month. Creative Eye Ltd slipped 7.35% to Rs 6.93. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5834 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1932 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GEPower_62970729410_20944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold finds footing ahead of key US policy signals]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-finds-footing-ahead-of-key-us-policy-signals/1678556</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678556</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures rebounded toward $4,950 per ounce on Wednesday after suffering a sharp selloff in the previous session, as investors repositioned ahead of the latest policy meeting minutes from the Federal Reserve.

Gold futures rebounded toward $4,950 per ounce on Wednesday after suffering a sharp selloff in the previous session, as investors repositioned ahead of the latest policy meeting minutes from the Federal Reserve. Market focus is firmly on Friday’s PCE Price Index and upcoming GDP data, both expected to provide fresh insight into the interest rate outlook. The US dollar strengthened above 97 after recent volatility, tempering gains in the metal. Geopolitical developments also remained in focus, with reports of progress in US–Iran discussions and continued negotiations between Russia and Ukraine reducing immediate safe-haven demand. In domestic trade, MCX gold futures for April delivery climbed nearly 1% to ₹152,783 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers pare losses; PSU bank shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-pare-losses-psu-bank-shares-advance/1678554</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678554</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks pared all early losses and traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks pared all early losses and traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark. PSU Bank shares extended gains for the third consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 199.31 points or 0.24% to 83,650.27. The Nifty 50 index rose 61.15 points or 0.24% to 25,786.55. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.38% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.38%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,183 shares rose and 1,928 shares fell. A total of 188 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index rose 1.39% to 9,633.25. The index rose 5.09% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Punjab National Bank (up 2.84%), Indian Overseas Bank (up 2.23%), Punjab & Sind Bank (up 2.19%), Bank of Maharashtra (up 2.12%), Union Bank of India (up 2.05%), UCO Bank (up 2.01%), Canara Bank (up 1.9%), Indian Bank (up 1.9%), Central Bank of India (up 1.63%) and Bank of India (up 1.14%) rose. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.18% to 6.671 compared with the previous session close of 6.659. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6850 compared with its close of 90.7200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.99% to Rs 152,910. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.21% to 97.32. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.57% to 4.075. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 39 cents or 0.58% to $67.81 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Spandana Sphoorty Financial shed 0.81%. The company announced that its board has approved the appointment of Avinash Yadav as chief information officer (CIO), effective 17 February 2026. Power Mech Projects surged 4.06% after the company secured multiple domestic orders worth Rs 1,005 crore from subsidiaries of Adani Power.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at C.E. Info Systems Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-ce-info-systems-ltd-counter/1678552</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678552</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Apar Industries Ltd, Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Netweb Technologies India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 18 February 2026.

Apar Industries Ltd, Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Netweb Technologies India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 18 February 2026. C.E. Info Systems Ltd notched up volume of 12.62 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.46 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.10 lakh shares. The stock rose 0.38% to Rs.1,158.90. Volumes stood at 1.68 lakh shares in the last session. Apar Industries Ltd registered volume of 3.92 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.85 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 44329 shares. The stock rose 6.27% to Rs.10,155.50. Volumes stood at 31823 shares in the last session. Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd witnessed volume of 13.01 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.05 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.85 lakh shares. The stock increased 5.71% to Rs.1,138.15. Volumes stood at 1.64 lakh shares in the last session. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd recorded volume of 86.32 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.84 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 12.62 lakh shares. The stock gained 15.33% to Rs.2,382.50. Volumes stood at 14.5 lakh shares in the last session. Netweb Technologies India Ltd notched up volume of 71.55 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.58 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 10.87 lakh shares. The stock rose 8.82% to Rs.3,372.00. Volumes stood at 5.66 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/C.E.-Info-Systems-Ltd_18725708_75882.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Spandana Sphoorty gains after appointing Avinash Yadav as chief information officer]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/spandana-sphoorty-gains-after-appointing-avinash-yadav-as-chief-information-officer/1678551</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678551</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The appointment was made based on the recommendation of the nomination and remuneration committee.

The appointment was made based on the recommendation of the nomination and remuneration committee. Avinash Yadav is a seasoned technology leader with expertise in leading high impact technology projects, AI/ML models, technical operations and IT governance. He brings a unique blend of expertise (NBFC, HFC, FinTech’s) and a track record of success in driving IT operations, high-impact technology and digital transformation programs to enable greater customer experience, business growth and operational efficiency. He has been recognised among the Top 50 Tech Leaders in NBFCs by ET Edge and was awarded Best CTO/CIO of the Year 2025 by UBS Forums. Prior to joining Spandana Sphoorty Financial, he was associated with IIFL Samasta Finance. The company also clarified that Yadav is not related to any director on the board. Spandana Sphoorty Financial is primarily engaged in the business of microfinance, providing small-value unsecured loans to low-income customers in semi-urban and rural areas. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 94.97 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 440.20 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income slipped 56.9% year on year to Rs 245.55 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SpandanaSphoortyFinancial_28554243_34046.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Safari Inds signs 20-year Carlton brand licence]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/safari-inds-signs-20-year-carlton-brand-licence/1678539</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678539</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The term of the agreement is 20 years which may be renewed further period of 20 years at the discretion of the company.

The term of the agreement is 20 years which may be renewed further period of 20 years at the discretion of the company. Under the terms, total license fees payable to CRL will be Rs 45 Lakh or 5% of total net sales, whichever is higher, at the end of each license year. In addition, the company will pay an interest-free refundable security deposit of Rs 99.50 crore to CRL. The deposit will be paid in tranches over a specified period, subject to the terms and conditions outlined in the agreement. Safari Industries (India) is engaged in the manufacturing and marketing of luggage and luggage accessories. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 5.6% to Rs 32.89 crore on 15.7% jump in net sales to Rs 512.37 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter fell 1.90% to Rs 1797.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SafariInds_98893928962_710.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Mech rises after securing Rs 1,005-cr thermal power orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-mech-rises-after-securing-rs-1005-cr-thermal-power-orders/1678541</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678541</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contracts have been awarded by Mirzapur Thermal Energy (UP) and Mahan Energen for ultra supercritical thermal power projects.

The contracts have been awarded by Mirzapur Thermal Energy (UP) and Mahan Energen for ultra supercritical thermal power projects. The scope of work includes erection, testing, commissioning and manpower assistance for performance guarantee tests of Steam Generator (SG) and Steam Turbine Generator (STG), along with auxiliaries, for Unit 1 and 2 of the 2x800 MW Mirzapur Phase-I and Mahan Phase-III projects. The Mirzapur order is valued at Rs 515 crore, while the Mahan order is worth Rs 490 crore (excluding GST and applicable taxes). The projects are to be executed within 36 months from the erection start date as notified under the Notice to Proceed (NTP). The company reported a 14.6% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 93.99 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 82.03 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (net sales) rose 6.1% YoY to Rs 1,419.56 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 1,337.97 crore in the corresponding period last year. Power Mech Projects is an engineering and construction company providing integrated service in erection, testing, and commissioning (ETC) of boilers, turbines, and generators and balance of plant (BOP), civil works, and operation and maintenance (O&M).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerMechProj_11108641403_34787.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bosch Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bosch-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1678534</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678534</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bosch Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Bosch Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 35310, down 0.17% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.06% on the day, quoting at 25740.85. The Sensex is at 83490.85, up 0.05%.Bosch Ltd has eased around 3.29% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bosch Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 2% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28174.55, up 0.04% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5428 shares today, compared to the daily average of 20778 shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 35380, down 0.21% on the day. Bosch Ltd jumped 29.36% in last one year as compared to a 12.24% rally in NIFTY and a 29.24% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 45.18 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Bosch_19930465954_378.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-state-petronet-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1678535</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678535</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Gujarat State Petronet Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 302.75, down 0.46% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.06% on the day, quoting at 25740.85. The Sensex is at 83490.85, up 0.05%.Gujarat State Petronet Ltd has gained around 0.08% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Gujarat State Petronet Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 6.82% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36388.45, up 0.15% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.56 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.75 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 24.19 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujStPetronet_95223652929_24065.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Gas Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-gas-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1678536</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678536</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat Gas Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Gujarat Gas Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 411.85, down 0.71% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.06% on the day, quoting at 25740.85. The Sensex is at 83490.85, up 0.05%.Gujarat Gas Ltd has gained around 1.3% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Gujarat Gas Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 6.82% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36388.45, up 0.15% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.61 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.14 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 24.58 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujaratGas_6190462003_43934.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with small cuts; IT shares slumps; VIX tanks 3.01%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-small-cuts-it-shares-slumps-vix-tanks-301/1678533</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678533</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor cuts in the afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor cuts in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,750 mark. IT, Realty and media shared declined while PSU bank, metal and FMCG shares advanced. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex fell 12.62 points or 0.02% to 83,449.41. The Nifty 50 index declined 5.55 points or 0.05% to 25,724.40. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.24% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.37%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,129 shares rose and 1,917 shares fell. A total of 197 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tumbled 3.01% to 12.29. Gainers & Losers: Kwality Wall's (India) (up 4.97%), Tata Steel (up 2.97%), HDFC Life Insurance Company (up 2.29%), ITC (up 1.94%) and Axis Bank (up 1.20%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Wipro (down 2.22%), Tech Mahindra (down 2.18%), Eternal (down 2.18%), Adani Enterprises (down 1.64%) and Infosys (down 1.55%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Dilip Buildcon rose 4.08% after the company announced that it has emerged as the lowest (L-1) bidder for a major infrastructure project in Gujarat. The tender, floated by the Narmada Water Resources, Water Supply & Kalpasar Department, is valued at Rs 702 crore. The project involves the construction of a flood protection embankment on the Narmada River in the Bharuch District. Executed on an engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) basis, the project is scheduled for completion within a 24-month timeframe. Bharti Airtel rose 0.21%. The company announced that its subsidiary, Airtel Money, has received a Certificate of Registration from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to operate as a Type II Non-Deposit Accepting Non-Banking Financial Company [Type II-NBFC-ND (ICC)]. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) rose 0.61%. The company has announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance from Steel Authority of India (SAIL) for executing a Captive Power Plant (CPP) package. Bosch shed 0.18%. The company announced that its board approved the appointment of Tillmann Olsen as the chief financial officer (CFO) with effect from 1 June 2026. Dabur India declined 1.68%. The company announced the appointment of Herjit S. Bhalla as chief executive officer (CEO) India Business, with effect from 15 April 2026, as part of a leadership realignment aimed at sharpening operational focus. Global Markets: European markets higher on Wednesday as investors monitor global market developments. The U.K. inflation rate fell to 3% in January, according to the latest figures from the Office for National Statistics. Asian stocks traded mixed amid renewed concerns over artificial intelligence that continued to weigh on global markets. Mainland China, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan and South Korea were among the markets closed for Lunar New Year holidays. The positive start in Asia followed a lackluster session on Tuesday on Wall Street as investors grappled with the outlook for the AI boom. Concerns that companies are over-investing, along with angst about the extent to which the nascent technology could disrupt labor markets, have fuelled investor jitters in recent weeks. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 0.07% to 49,533.19, the S&P 500 was up 0.10% at 6,843.22, and the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.14% to 22,578.38. The S&P 500 fell 0.88% initially before making up ground to close in positive territory. Brent and West Texas Intermediate crude oil futures were little changed on Wednesday after both slid to close at more than two-week lows in the previous session. Following talks in Geneva on Tuesday, Iran's foreign minister reportedly said Tehran and Washington reached an understanding on main "guiding principles" towards resolving their longstanding nuclear dispute, easing worries about a military conflict near the Strait of Hormuz that could disrupt global oil supply.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[E2E Networks soars on NVIDIA-backed Blackwell AI infrastructure buildout]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/e2e-networks-soars-on-nvidia-backed-blackwell-ai-infrastructure-buildout/1678531</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678531</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Blackwell-based infrastructure is being deployed at the L&T Vyoma Data Center in Chennai.

The Blackwell-based infrastructure is being deployed at the L&T Vyoma Data Center in Chennai. The TIR platform will feature NVIDIA HGX B200 systems, NVIDIA Enterprise software and NVIDIA Nemotron open models, aimed at supporting sovereign AI development across sectors such as healthcare, finance, manufacturing and agriculture. NVIDIA outlined a broader set of partnerships and initiatives in India at the AI Impact Summit in New Delhi, positioning the country as a key hub in the global AI ecosystem. The company said these collaborations support the government’s IndiaAI Mission, a $1 billion-plus programme focused on expanding compute capacity, developing sovereign AI datasets and models, and strengthening AI education, startups and responsible AI frameworks. Meanwhile, the National Stock Exchange has sought clarification from E2E Networks regarding reports of a partnership with NVIDIA. The company's response is awaited. E2E Networks operates as a cloud infrastructure provider in India, offering GPU computing, enterprise cloud solutions and managed services for artificial intelligence and machine learning workloads. On a standalone basis, E2E Networks reported net loss of Rs 5.70 crore in Q3 December 2025 as against net profit of Rs 11.59 crore in Q3 December 2024. Net sales rose 68.32% YoY to Rs 70.02 crore in Q3 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/E2ENetworksLtd_43382383477_72373.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pound extends slide under $1.36 mark as UK inflation cools; GBP/INR futures slip below 123 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pound-extends-slide-under-136-mark-as-uk-inflation-cools-gbpinr-futures-slip-below-123-mark/1678527</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678527</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UK pound is seen extending slide around a two-week low at $1.3560.

UK pound is seen extending slide around a two-week low at $1.3560. The pair lost over half a percent in the previous session. Data today showed UK headline inflation has dropped to 3% on year, from 3.4% in December. The core CPI – which excludes the volatile components of food, energy, alcohol and tobacco – grew expectedly by 3.1%, slower than the previous reading of 3.2%. Month-on-month headline inflation has declined 0.5% after growing 0.4% in December. Meanwhile, a small rebound in dollar index is also adding pressure on the counter. The US Dollar Index which tracks the Greenback’s value against six major currencies, is up 0.12% to near 97.17. Going forward, retail sales data for January and the preliminary S&P Global Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) data for February scheduled to be published on Friday will also be watched for further cues. On the NSE, GBP/INR futures fall 0.30% at $122.93.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Unicommerce jumps as Shipway partners with ElasticRun for faster deliveries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/unicommerce-jumps-as-shipway-partners-with-elasticrun-for-faster-deliveries/1678526</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678526</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The partnership aims to enhance same-day and next-day delivery capabilities for e-commerce and D2C brands.

The partnership aims to enhance same-day and next-day delivery capabilities for e-commerce and D2C brands. The integration combines Shipway's logistics technology with ElasticRun's hyperlocal delivery network, enabling faster last-mile deliveries across Delhi, Mumbai, Bengaluru, Hyderabad, Pune and Kolkata. Brands using Shipway will gain access to ElasticRun's network along with real-time tracking, issue management and performance analytics. The rollout currently covers intra-city hyperlocal shipments. The companies plan to expand the partnership to support inter-city movements in subsequent phases. Sandeep Deshmukh, co-founder & CEO, ElasticRun said, "At ElasticRun, we operate as a technology-first, speed-led fulfilment partner, using AI-driven intelligence to enable faster, more reliable same-day and next-day deliveries at scale. Our integrated platform leverages AI for smarter inventory placement, routing, and last-mile execution across the country. Partnering with Shipway allows us to extend these capabilities to more digital-first brands, helping them meet rising consumer expectations for speed without the complexity of building their own infrastructure." Kapil Makhija, MD & CEO of Unicommerce, added, "As everyday-use categories such as FMCG, personal care, fashion, and essentials become a growing part of India’s retail and e- commerce market, consumer expectations around faster deliveries are increasing. With ElasticRun’s hyperlocal network integrated with Shipway, brands are better placed to meet these needs." Unicommerce eSolutions provides SaaS-based e-commerce enablement solutions, including inventory management, order processing, warehouse management and shipping automation, to brands and online sellers. It serves 7,500+ clients across India, Southeast Asia, and the Middle East, including brands such as FabIndia, Lenskart, Timex, TCNS, Mamaearth, Emami, Urban Company, Healthkart, boAt, TMRW, Mensa, and Landmark Group. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Unicommerce eSolutions rose 16.56% to Rs 7.39 crore while net sales rose 72.24% to Rs 56.39 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnicommerceeSolutionsLtd_29329443_75410.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank up for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/punjab-national-bank-up-for-third-consecutive-session/1678503</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678503</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank is up for a third straight session today.

Punjab National Bank is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 128.04, up 2.58% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25713.95. The Sensex is at 83408.99, down 0.05%. Punjab National Bank has slipped around 0.01% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Punjab National Bank is a constituent, has slipped around 2.38% in last one month and is currently quoting at 61174, up 0.23% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 239.21 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 212.3 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 128.05, up 2.37% on the day. Punjab National Bank is up 37.88% in last one year as compared to a 12.13% jump in NIFTY and a 23.69% jump in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 8.83 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Bank of India spurts 2.28%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-bank-of-india-spurts-228-up-for-third-straight-session/1678504</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678504</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Bank of India rose for a third straight session today.

Union Bank of India rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 193.19, up 2.28% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25713.95. The Sensex is at 83408.99, down 0.05%. Union Bank of India has added around 8.88% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Union Bank of India is a constituent, has added around 2.38% in last one month and is currently quoting at 61174, up 0.23% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 186.3 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 163.78 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 192.96, up 2.25% on the day. Union Bank of India is up 68.11% in last one year as compared to a 12.13% gain in NIFTY and a 23.69% gain in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 7.85 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnionBankI_88937846814_5493.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Canara Bank spurts 1.39%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/canara-bank-spurts-139-gains-for-third-straight-session/1678505</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678505</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Canara Bank is up for a third straight session in a row.

Canara Bank is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 151.18, up 1.39% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25713.95. The Sensex is at 83408.99, down 0.05%. Canara Bank has dropped around 3.62% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Canara Bank is a constituent, has dropped around 2.38% in last one month and is currently quoting at 61174, up 0.23% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 153.36 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 288.28 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 151.56, up 1.7% on the day. Canara Bank is up 76.69% in last one year as compared to a 12.13% spurt in NIFTY and a 23.69% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 6.87 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CanaraBank_17338928867_5471.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>