<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:18:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sathlokhar Synergys E&C Global secures Rs 38-cr orders for civil and PEB works]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sathlokhar-synergys-ec-global-secures-rs-38-cr-orders-for-civil-and-peb-works/1679033</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679033</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The first order, valued at Rs 23.57 crore, has been awarded by APM Terminals India, part of Denmark-based MAERSK.

The first order, valued at Rs 23.57 crore, has been awarded by APM Terminals India, part of Denmark-based MAERSK. The contract involves the execution of a new warehouse and the upgradation of an existing warehouse, along with external facilities including civil, PEB and MEP works, for a proposed factory at the CFS Division in Ponneri, Chennai. The project is scheduled for completion before September 2026. The second order, worth Rs 13.82 crore (including GST), has been received from Elite Natural. The scope of work includes civil works for the main building and toilet blocks, along with PEB works for a proposed factory at the SIPCOT Industrial Complex, Phase 2, Hosur, Tamil Nadu. This project is also expected to be completed before September 2026. The company clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authorities. It further stated that the contracts do not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. Sathlokhar Synergys E&C Global provides specialized engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) services for the construction of buildings and infrastructure facilities. On a full-year basis, the company's net profit surged 63.4% to Rs 42.77 crore on a 61.7% jump in net sales to Rs 399.37 crore in FY25 over FY24. The counter rose 0.28% to end at Rs 378 on the NSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SathlokharSynergysECGlobalLtd_27403841_93133.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI Governor says domestic drivers of growth continue to be robust]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-governor-says-domestic-drivers-of-growth-continue-to-be-robust/1679029</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679029</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) announced minutes of its latest Monetary Policy Committee Meeting yesterday.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) announced minutes of its latest Monetary Policy Committee Meeting yesterday. Committee member Nagesh Kumar noted that the economic outlook for the Indian economy has brightened considerably since the December 2025 MPC Meeting. The inflation outlook continues to remain benign, with headline CPI remaining low at 1.3% in December 2025, and the inflation outlook not showing any concerns of overheating. This leads to a possible changed narrative for monetary policy discussion. Saugata Bhattacharya stated that high frequency indicators signal resilience in economic activity. Bank credit growth to non-retail sectors has gradually increased, which, together with a stable manufacturing capacity utilisation and signs of fiscal stimulus-led consumption demand boost, might be a harbinger of a gradual revival in private sector capex. Assessing the macro-financial environment, while awaiting the new economic data series, the policy rate is appropriate. Prof. Ram Singh noted that despite the 7 per cent plus growth rate, there are no signs of overheating in the economy. CPI inflation for 2025-26 is expected to be 2.1 per cent, with Q4 at 3.2 per cent. CPI inflation for Q1and Q2 of FY27 is projected to be a tad higher at 4.0 per cent and 4.2 per cent, respectively. Filtering out the effect of increases in prices of precious metals (60-70 bps), the underlying inflation pressures are expected to remain muted. Going ahead, robust domestic demand in conjunction with improved capacity utilisation is likely to attract fresh private-sector investment. Indranil Bhattacharyya stated that developments on the inflation front have been largely on expected lines barring the significant increase in prices of precious metals, viz., gold and silver. CPI headline inflation has inched up from its historical low levels although it remains below the lower tolerance threshold. While assessing headline inflation, its underlying trends as well as its likely trajectory going forward, the key elements of its major constituents would have to be delineated. While food has generally recorded deflation in six of the last seven prints, core inflation rose to 4.6 per cent in December, driven by prices in precious metals. The flexible inflation targeting (FIT) framework supports maintaining the current stance as long as inflation expectations remain well-anchored. Poonam Gupta noted that the global environment remains uncertain, with economies, financial markets, and commodity markets facing varied levels of volatility and risks. Yet, from the Indian perspective, the announcement of a trade deal with the US and the signing of a major free trade agreement (FTA) with the EU have resulted in a more favorable external sector outlook. Underpinned by the continued buoyancy of high frequency indicators, and model-based projections, preliminary estimates of growth for 2026-27 by various agencies have been revised upwards. Low inflation continues to be a boon. RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra stated that India’s economic activity, driven primarily by domestic factors, remained resilient with real GDP growth in 2025-26 projected to be higher by 90 bps from 6.5 per cent in 2024-25. The outlook for the ensuing year is also expected to be strong. Domestic drivers of growth continue to be robust. Several growth-supportive measures announced in the Union Budget should further boost growth. Inflation in November and December 2025 continued to remain low and below the lower tolerance threshold. In terms of the overall trajectory, inflation, as projected earlier too, is expected to remain benign.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-growth-1-1057028_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quality Power arm bags Rs 18-cr domestic order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quality-power-arm-bags-rs-18-cr-domestic-order/1679027</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679027</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to a regulatory filing, the name of the awarding entity has not been disclosed due to a non-disclosure agreement (NDA).

According to a regulatory filing, the name of the awarding entity has not been disclosed due to a non-disclosure agreement (NDA). The order, valued at approximately Rs 18 crore excluding taxes, is scheduled to be executed over a period of around eight months. The company said the contract pertains to the supply of instrument transformers and has been classified as a domestic order. It further clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the entity awarding the contract. The company also confirmed that the order does not fall under related party transactions. Quality Power Electrical Equipments is engaged in the business of energy transition equipment and power technologies. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 220.69% to Rs 62.76 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 19.57 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25. The counter advanced 2.66% to end at Rs 883.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/QualityPowerElectricalEquipmentsLtd_48177673_54766.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Danish Power bags inverter duty transformer supply orders from EPC companies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/danish-power-bags-inverter-duty-transformer-supply-orders-from-epc-companies/1679019</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679019</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The said orders include the design, manufacturing, testing, supply & supervision of commissioning of Inverter duty transformers.

The said orders include the design, manufacturing, testing, supply & supervision of commissioning of Inverter duty transformers. The company clarified that the order do not fall within the terms of related party transaction and neither the promoter/promoter group have any interest in the entities awarding the order. Danish Power manufactures various types of transformers, including inverter duty transformers designed for renewable energy application such as solar power plants and wind farms. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 25.9% to Rs 25.15 crore on 6% increase in net sales to Rs 180.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter rose 0.45% to end at Rs 665 on the NSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DanishPowerLtd_51463115_83611.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suraj Estate Developers inks pact to acquire Hally Pacific]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suraj-estate-developers-inks-pact-to-acquire-hally-pacific/1679017</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679017</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hally Pacific incorporated to carry out the business as manufacturers and dealers in all kind of furniture made from woods, brass, steel, fiber glass, plastics, leather, textile furnishing or any other alloys and handicrafts.

Hally Pacific incorporated to carry out the business as manufacturers and dealers in all kind of furniture made from woods, brass, steel, fiber glass, plastics, leather, textile furnishing or any other alloys and handicrafts. The company reported revenue from operations of Rs 17.41 lakh in FY25. Following the acquisition, the company will develop a land parcel admeasuring 717.39 Sq meters situated at Sayani Road, G/South Ward, Prabhadevi, Mumbai. The land is currently owned by Hally Pacific. The company will acquire 5,000 equity shares with a face value of Rs 100 each at a price of Rs 60,800 per share, aggregating to a total consideration of Rs 30.40 crore. The said agreement will be completed within 30 days from the execution of share purchase agreement. Suraj Estate Developers develops real estate across the residential and commercial sectors in South Central Mumbai region. The company has a residential portfolio located in the markets of Mahim, Dadar, Prabhadevi and Parel. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 25.9% to Rs 25.15 crore on 6% rise in net sales to Rs 180.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip rose 1.42% to end at Rs 217.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Suraj-Estate-Developers-Ltd_43877842_76563.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NHPC board clears Rs 5,703-cr hydropower projects in J&K]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nhpc-board-clears-rs-5703-cr-hydropower-projects-in-jk/1679014</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679014</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The board cleared the implementation of Uri-I Stage-II hydro electric (HE) Project (240 MW) at an estimated completion cost of Rs 2,708.95 crore.

The board cleared the implementation of Uri-I Stage-II hydro electric (HE) Project (240 MW) at an estimated completion cost of Rs 2,708.95 crore. The project cost includes Rs 264.31 crore for IDC and grant of Rs 26.20 crore for enabling infrastructure. The construction start date has been considered as March 1, 2026. In addition, the board also approved an investment proposal of Dulhasti Stage-II HE Project (260 MW) at a completion cost of Rs 2,993.96 crore including Rs 289.06 crore for IDC and Rs 245.00 crore for enabling infrastructure, with construction also slated to commence from 1 March 2026. Both investments are subject to the signing of implementation agreement between NHPC and Government of Jammu & Kashmir / JKSPDC & other requisite approvals, if any. NHPC, a Navratna Ratna public sector utility, is the Government of India’s flagship hydroelectric generation company. The company is primarily involved in the generation and sale of bulk power to various power utilities. Its other business includes providing project management/construction contracts/consultancy assignment services and trading of power. The company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 320.60 crore in Q3 FY26, down 2.89% as against Rs 330.13 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income declined 4.74% year-on-year to Rs 2,492.83 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The scrip rose 0.08% to settle at Rs 74.43 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NHPCLtd_36439171799_12584.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India Ratings upgrades ratings of Wheels India to 'A+' with 'stable' outlook]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-ratings-upgrades-ratings-of-wheels-india-to-a-with-stable-outlook/1679011</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679011</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘IND A1’.

The agency has affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘IND A1’. India Ratings and Research stated that the upgrade reflects a notable improvement in WIL’s EBITDA margins, and thus credit metrics at the consolidated level during FY25–9MFY26, supported by sustained revenue diversification and working capital efficiencies. The agency expects this positive momentum to continue over the near to medium term, driven by higher contributions from margin-accretive segments and ongoing cost-optimisation initiatives undertaken by the company. India Ratings further said that a significant improvement in the profitability along with improving profitability from newer segments, while maintaining the gross working capital cycle, and net adjusted leverage reducing below 2.5x, all on a consolidated and sustained basis, could lead to a positive rating action. However, a decline in the profitability margins and/or a stretch in the gross working capital cycle, leading to net adjusted leverage exceeding 3.5x, and deterioration in the liquidity position, could lead to a negative rating action. Wheels India manufactures steel and aluminium wheel rims across the automotive (except two-wheeler), tractor and earth mover segments. It caters to both the domestic and overseas markets. The company also has a presence in air suspension systems for luxury buses in India, supplies fabricated and machined parts for windmills, and produces bogie frame and bogie bolsters for the Indian Railways. The company had reported 44.05% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 36.07 crore on a 21.92% increase in revenue to Rs 1,371.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip had declined 2.03% to end at Rs 899.25 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WheelsIndia_63910222667_609.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WeWork India proposes to add 3,100 desks in Bengaluru by Sept'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wework-india-proposes-to-add-3100-desks-in-bengaluru-by-sept26/1679005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679005</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s existing capacity comprises of 1,21,638 desks, with a utilization rate of 83%.

The company’s existing capacity comprises of 1,21,638 desks, with a utilization rate of 83%. With this new lease deed, the company expects to add a total of 3,100 desks before September 2026. The total cost for the proposed capacity addition is Rs 42 crore, which would be funded either through debt or internal accruals. WeWork India is one of India’s leading premium flexible workspace operators. Since its inception, WeWork India has expanded across 8 cities in Chennai, New Delhi, Gurugram, Noida, Mumbai, Bengaluru, Pune, and Hyderabad, with 73 operational centres spanning 8.2 million square feet (as of December 2025). The company had reported a consolidated net profit of 16.70 crore in the quarter ended December 2025 as against net loss of Rs 83.25 crore during the previous quarter ended December 2024. Sales rose 28.97% to Rs 634.11 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip had declined 1.56% to end at Rs 531.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WeworkIndiaManagementLtd_48346151_76903.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1679002</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679002</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 24 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 24 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit. Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/invesco-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1679000</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679000</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Invesco Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Munesh Khanna has been appointed as an Associate Director with effect from February 17, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Mr. Munesh Khanna Age: 63 years Designation: (Associate Director) Qualification: B.Com., C.A.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gulf Oil Lubricants renews multi-year pact with Mahindra & Mahindra]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gulf-oil-lubricants-renews-multi-year-pact-with-mahindra-mahindra/1678985</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678985</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The renewal reinforces a strategic alliance that began in 2011 with a co-branded initiative alongside Mahindra Automotive and expanded into the Tractors Division in 2014.

The renewal reinforces a strategic alliance that began in 2011 with a co-branded initiative alongside Mahindra Automotive and expanded into the Tractors Division in 2014. Over the past 12 years, the partnership has evolved into one of Gulf Oil's most enduring OEM relationships. The collaboration has been consistently strengthened through investments in digital initiatives, efficient supply chain management, and impactful joint marketing campaigns, delivering growth and value for all stakeholders. Ravi Chawla, managing director & CEO, Gulf Oil Lubricants India, said: “Our renewed partnership with Mahindra Tractors is a testament to the strength of our alliance and the shared values that drive it. In line with our long-term philosophy of partnership for growth, we have, over the past decade, consistently delivered reliable performance and service excellence, adding sustained value to Mahindra & Mahindra.” Gulf Oil Lubricants India (GOLIL), part of the Hinduja Group and Gulf Oil International, is a leading player in India's lubricant market offering a comprehensive product portfolio in automotive and industrial lubricants. The company had reported 21.77% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 76.13 crore despite a 10.56% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,017.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.95% to currently trade at Rs 1081.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GulfOilLubric_49865113351_45765.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>