<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:54:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India and France sign Amending Protocol to update Double Taxation Avoidance Convention]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-and-france-sign-amending-protocol-to-update-double-taxation-avoidance-convention/1679180</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679180</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[During the recent visit of the President of France to India, the Government of the Republic of India and the Government of the French Republic have signed a Protocol amending the India-France Double Taxation Avoidance Convention, signed on 29 September 1992 (‘India-France DTAC’).

During the recent visit of the President of France to India, the Government of the Republic of India and the Government of the French Republic have signed a Protocol amending the India-France Double Taxation Avoidance Convention, signed on 29 September 1992 (‘India-France DTAC’). The Amending Protocol was signed by Ravi Agrawal, Chairperson, Central Board of Direct Taxes, Government of India, and Thierry Mathou, Ambassador of France to India, on behalf of their respective Governments. The Amending Protocol provides full taxing rights in respect of capital gains arising from sale of shares of a company, to the jurisdiction where such company is a resident. The Amending Protocol also deletes the so-called Most-Favoured-Nation (MFN) Clause from the Protocol to the DTAC, thereby bringing to rest all issues relating to it. The Amending Protocol also modifies the taxation of income from dividends by replacing a single rate of 10% of tax with a split rate of 5% for those holding at least ten percent of capital and 15% of tax for all other cases. It also modifies the definition of ‘Fees for Technical Services’ by aligning it with the definition in India US Double Taxation Avoidance Agreement, and expands the scope of ‘Permanent Establishment’ by adding Service PE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-calculator-tax-return-taxes-1241517_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee closes up]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-closes-up/1679178</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679178</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 90.9175 per Dollar on Monday (23 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.9575 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gaudium IVF and Women Health IPO subscribed 3 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gaudium-ivf-and-women-health-ipo-subscribed-3-times/1679176</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679176</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 4,38,24,186 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Friday (20 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 4,38,24,186 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Friday (20 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 3 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (20 February 2026) and it closed on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 189 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The IPO comprises a fresh issue of 1,13,92,500 equity shares, worth up to Rs 90 crore, and an offer for sale of 9,493,700 equity shares, aggregating up to Rs 75 crore, by Dr. Manika Khanna. The objectives for the fresh issue include Rs 50 crore for funding capital expenditure towards the establishment of new IVF centers, Rs 20 crore for repayment and prepayment of certain outstanding loans, and the remaining amount for general corporate purposes. The promoters and promoter group hold an aggregate of 6,13,85,084 equity shares, aggregating to 99.99% of the pre-offer issued and paid-up equity share capital. Their post-IPO shareholding is expected to be around 71.29%. Ahead of the IPO of Gaudium IVF and Women Health on 19 February 2026, the company raised Rs 49.50 crore from anchor investors by allotting 62.65 lakh shares at Rs 79 each to 4 anchor investors. Gaudium IVF and Women Health (est. 2015) is an India-based fertility chain operating 30+ centers under a hub-and-spoke model. It offers IVF, ICSI, IUI, fertility preservation, and related gynecology services. IVF contributes approximately 69% of revenue, with a success rate of 58.74% and average revenue per patient of Rs 2.58 lakh. The company plans to add 19 new centers over FY26–FY28 to expand its footprint. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 4.28 crore and income from operations of Rs 49.50 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions subscribed 34% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/clean-max-enviro-energy-solutions-subscribed-34/1679174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679174</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 75,07,654 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (23 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 75,07,654 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (23 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.34 times. The issue opened for bidding on Monday (23 February 2026) and it will close on Wednesday (25 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 14 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue comprises fresh equity shares, aggregating Rs 1,200 crore, and an offer-for-sale (OFS) of equity shares, aggregating Rs 1900 crore. The OFS by the promoters include equity shares, aggregating Rs 216.799 crore by Kuldeep Jain, Rs 903.898 crore by BGTF One Holdings, and Rs 73 crore by KEMPINC LLP. The OFS by selling shareholders aggregate Rs 541.921 crore and by DSDG Holdings Rs 164.382 crore. Of the net proceeds, Rs 1122.674 crore will be used for repayment and/or pre-payment, in part or full,of all or certain outstanding borrowings and/or certain of subsidiaries, and balance for general corporate purposes. Total borrowings stood at Rs 10,121.46 crore as of 30 September 2025. Ahead of the IPO, Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions on 20 February 2026, the company raised Rs 920.99 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 87.46 lakh shares at Rs 1,053 each to 41 anchor investors. CleanMax is India‘s largest commercial and industrial (C&I) renewable energy provider, with 2799 MW of operational capacity portfolio as of 31 October 2025. Additionally, capacity of 3,044 MW was in an advanced stage, 3,172 MW contracted and 1,914 MW under development. With 15 years of experience since inception, CleanMax specializes in delivering net zero and decarbonization solutions, including supplying renewable power and energy services and carbon credit solutions across data centres, AI and technology industries and C&I enterprises across a range of sectors, including infrastructure, cement, steel, industrial manufacturing, FMCG, pharmaceuticals, real estate, and global capability centres. The company’s s expertise spans across providing energy contracting, engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) services, and operation and maintenance (O&M) services of renewable energy plants including solar, wind and hybrid plants, within the customer‘s premises (onsite) and within inhouse-developed renewable energy (solar, wind and hybrid) farms (offsite). Renewable energy power sales revenue as a percentage of revenue from operations amounted to 77.09% and 74.03% in H1FY2026 and FY 2025. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 15.44 crore and income from operations of Rs 932.95 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shree Ram Twistex IPO subscribed 11%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shree-ram-twistex-ipo-subscribed-11/1679173</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679173</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 12,03,552 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (23 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 12,03,552 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (23 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.11 times. The issue opened for bidding on Monday (23 February 2026) and it closed on Wednesday (25 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 144 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The offer consists of an entirely fresh issue of 1.06 crore equity shares. At the upper price band of Rs 104, the company intends to raise Rs 110.24 crore. Shree Ram Twistex to utilize proceeds from the IPO for the setting up of a 4.2 MW wind power plant for captive use at the expense of Rs 39 crore. Further, Rs 14.89 crore will be used for repayment of certain borrowings, Rs 44 crore for working capital requirements, and the balance towards general corporate purposes. Shree Ram Twistex manufactures cotton yarns, including compact ring spun, combed, and carded varieties for knitting, weaving, and value-added yarns like slub and lycra blends. Operating on a B2B model, it supplies domestic textile manufacturers and exporters, with exports contributing 6–10% of revenue. The Gujarat-based facility has 17 spinning machines and five warehouses with 9,855 MT storage capacity. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 7 crore and income from operations of Rs 132.08 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR seen supported by weak greenback; Positive cues from local equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-seen-supported-by-weak-greenback-positive-cues-from-local-equities/1679172</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679172</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee gained 7 paise to settle at 90.87 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday, aided by a sharp fall in global crude oil prices and a weaker greenback amid renewed global trade-related uncertainties.

The Indian rupee gained 7 paise to settle at 90.87 (provisional) against the US dollar on Monday, aided by a sharp fall in global crude oil prices and a weaker greenback amid renewed global trade-related uncertainties. The US Dollar faced intense selling pressure as investors turned anxious over the United States (US) trade policy outlook, following the Supreme Court (SC) ruling against President Donald Trump's tariff policy. However, foreign fund outflows, coupled with geopolitical concerns, capped gains for the local unit. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 90.76 and traded in the range of 90.67-90.89 against the greenback during the session. Equity benchmark indices Sensex and Nifty closed higher on Monday, tracking gains in PSU bank, auto and financial stocks, as investors' sentiments improved after the US Supreme Court struck down the Trump administration's sweeping tariffs. The 30-share BSE Sensex climbed 479.95 points, or 0.58 per cent, to settle at 83,294.66. The 50-share NSE Nifty advanced 141.75 points, or 0.55 per cent, to close at 25,713.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers extend gains for 2nd day; Nifty tops 25,700 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-extend-gains-for-2nd-day-nifty-tops-25700-level/1679171</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679171</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended with moderate gains on Monday, extending a two-day rally after the US Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.

The key equity indices ended with moderate gains on Monday, extending a two-day rally after the US Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs. Investors will monitor crude oil prices and movements in gold prices. The Nifty settled above the 25,700 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 479.95 points or 0.58% to 83,294.66. The Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.21% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.51%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.35% to 14.17. Two Banks Flag Fraud Cases IDFC First Bank slumped 16.18% after the bank said that it has uncovered fraudulent transactions worth around Rs 590 crore at one of its branches in Chandigarh, allegedly involving a few employees. In a regulatory filing made on Sunday, the private sector bank said that based on a preliminary internal assessment (upon receipt of communication from a particular Department of Government of Haryana), the bank has identified an incident involving unauthorized and fraudulent activities by certain employees at a particular branch in Chandigarh and potentially involving other counterparties. Detailing the events that led to the aforementioned discover, the bank stated that it had received a request from a particular Department of Haryana Government for closure of its account and transfer of funds to another bank. In the process, certain discrepancies were observed in the amount mentioned vis-à-vis the balance in the account. Meanwhile, AU Small Finance Bank slumped 5.20% after the Haryana government decisively removed the bank from its list of empanelled lenders due to serious allegations of fraudulent activities. In a statement, the bank said that on 18 February 2026, it received a separate communication from the department seeking information regarding suspected unauthorised transactions between a government account and another customer account. As of 21 February 2026, deposits from the Government of Haryana with AU Small Finance Bank stood at Rs 538 crore across nearly 200 accounts, accounting for about 0.4% of the bank's overall deposits as of 31 December 2026. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.28% to 6.706 compared with the previous session close of 6.725. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9000 compared with its close of 90.9450 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement advanced 1.90% to Rs 159,850. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.14% to 97.66. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.27% to 4.078. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement lost 41 cents or 0.57% to $71.35 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European markets traded lower on Monday as investors awaited Italy’s inflation data due later this week. Markets in Asia ended mostly higher as investors digested the developments related to the United States tariffs. While the Supreme Court ruled on Friday that the Trump administration unlawfully imposed the measures last year, US President Donald Trump used different legal means to raise global levies to 15% from 10% over the weekend. Markets in China and Japan were closed for a holiday. On Friday, U.S. stocks rose after the Supreme Court ruling, potentially providing relief for companies burdened by higher costs from the duties and easing concern about sticky inflation still plaguing the U.S. economy. The S&P 500 advanced 0.69% and closed at 6,909.51, while the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9% and settled at 22,886.07. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 230.81 points, or 0.47%, and ended at 49,625.97. The 30-stock index recovered from a 200-point loss earlier in the session on disappointing economic data. Data released on Friday showed that the US economy expanded an annualized 1.4% in Q4 2025, the least since Q1 2025, following a 4.4% growth in Q3 and well below widely reported forecasts of 3%, the advance estimate showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Dee Development Engineers surged 16.35% after the company announced that it, along with its material subsidiary, has secured contracts aggregating approximately Rs 173 crore. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone advanced 2.75% after the company’s subsidiary Adani Gangavaram Port signed a memorandum of understanding with NMDC, a Government of India enterprise, and Vale S.A., Brazil. Axis Bank added 1.34% after the bank has clarified that it has neither submitted nor is planning to submit any bid for a stake in CreditAccess Grameen. UPL tumbled 14.15% after the company’s restructuring plan triggered concerns over leverage and the post-rejig capital structure. The company announced restructuring plan to consolidate its India and international crop protection businesses into a new listed entity, UPL Global Sustainable Agri Solutions (UPL Global). Morepen Laboratories zoomed 15.11% after the company announced that it has secured a multi-year contract development and manufacturing organization (CDMO) mandate valued at approximately Rs 825 crore from a leading global pharma major. The company stated that the supplies under the said mandate are expected to commence within the next 4–5 months, with execution scheduled through Q1 of the following financial year, subject to customary operational and regulatory processes. JSW Infrastructure added 1.94% after the company‘s board approved the issuance of 25 crore equity shares with face value of Rs 2 each, to fund its multi year expansion program. The fundraising may be undertaken through one or more of following modes such as qualified institutional placement (QIP), further public offer (FPO), rights issue or through any other permissible mode. The issuance of shares will also enable compliance with SEBI’s Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) requirement. As previously guided, the company remains on a strong growth trajectory, with operating EBITDA expected to double by FY28 from FY26 levels to reach around Rs 5,000 crore. This outlook is underpinned by clear execution visibility across the under-construction Projects in the Ports segment and the transition of rolling assets from capex to EBITDA contribution within the Logistics segment. Lotus Chocolate Company declined 1.97% after the company announced temporary shutdown of its manufacturing facility situated in Sangareddy, Telangana for 15 days from 24 February 2026. R&B Denims rose 1.94% after the company secured sales orders aggregating to around Rs 215.88 crore for the supply of around 12,000,000 meters of denim fabric products from established merchant exporters. Olectra Greentech gained 2.50% after its associate, Evey Trans (EVEY), secured two Letters of Award (LOAs) worth Rs 1,800 crore from the Telangana State Road Transport Corporation (TGSRTC). Patel Engineering rose 2.68% after the company said that it has been declared the lowest bidder (L1) from Himachal Pradesh Power Corporation (HPPCL) for the construction of the Renukaji Dam Project in Himachal Pradesh. The order, valued at Rs 910 crore, is scheduled to be completed within 30 months. IPO Update: Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 4,21,19,784 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:45 IST on Monday (23 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.54 times. The issue was subscribed 2.59 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it will close on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 11,92,464 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:45 IST on Monday (23 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.54 times. The issue was subscribed 0.11 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 75,04,294 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:45 IST on Monday (23 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.54 times. The issue was subscribed 0.34 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at discount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-discount/1679169</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679169</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,700.30, a discount of 12.70 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,713.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,700.30, a discount of 12.70 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,713. in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 1.35% to 14.17. HDFC Bank, Reliance Industries and ICICI Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concor inks MoU with Vizhinjam International Seaport to develop CFS near Vizhinjam port]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concor-inks-mou-with-vizhinjam-international-seaport-to-develop-cfs-near-vizhinjam-port/1679167</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679167</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The MoU was signed on 23 February 2026, at Thiruvananthapuram.

The MoU was signed on 23 February 2026, at Thiruvananthapuram. Under the agreement, VISL will provide land for the proposed CFS on mutually agreed terms, while both entities will jointly work on developing the facility. The proposed CFS is expected to include a customs-bonded area, warehouses, container handling and storage yards, import-export cargo handling facilities, weighbridges and other related infrastructure to enable seamless end-to-end logistics services. Following the MoU, the two parties will enter into a detailed agreement outlining the terms and conditions of their collaboration. The partnership aims to strengthen multimodal logistics capabilities and enhance cargo handling efficiencies at Vizhinjam International Seaport, which is being positioned as a key deep-water transshipment hub and gateway for global maritime trade. The collaboration is also expected to support the development of an integrated logistics ecosystem, contributing to regional and national economic growth. The move further aligns with CONCOR’s strategy to expand its rail-led multimodal logistics network and scale up infrastructure in line with the evolving requirements of India’s EXIM trade. Container Corporation of India (CONCOR) is engaged in the business of providing inland transportation of containers by rail. It also covers the Management of Ports, Air cargo complexes and establishes cold chains. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 8.9% to Rs 333.91 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 366.65 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 4.5% year on year to Rs 2,307.51 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of Container Corporation of India added 0.91% to Rs 507.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ContainerCorpn_89474429441_12607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 480 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,700 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-480-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25700-level/1679158</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679158</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with moderate gains today, extending a two-day rally after the US Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.

The key equity benchmarks ended with moderate gains today, extending a two-day rally after the US Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs. The Nifty settled above the 25,700 mark. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 479.95 points or 0.58% to 83,294.66. The Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.21% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.51%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.35% to 14.17. Among the sectoral indices, the PSU Bank index (up 1.36%), the Nifty Auto index (up 0.83%) and the Nifty FMCG index (up 0.70%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 1.42%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (down 0.26%) and the Nifty Metal index (down 0.23%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.30% to 6.705 compared with the previous session close of 6.725. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.8750 compared with its close of 90.9450 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement advanced 1.83% to Rs 159,750. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.13% to 97.67. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.27% to 4.078. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement lost 38 cents or 0.53% to $71.38 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European markets traded lower on Monday as more uncertainty surrounding U.S. trade tariffs weighed on risk appetite. Most Asian markets ended higher as investors monitored developments related to the United States tariffs. While the Supreme Court ruled on Friday that the Trump administration unlawfully imposed the measures last year, US President Donald Trump used different legal means to raise global levies to 15% from 10% over the weekend. Markets in China and Japan were closed for a holiday. On Friday, U.S. stocks rose after the Supreme Court ruling, potentially providing relief for companies burdened by higher costs from the duties and easing concern about sticky inflation still plaguing the U.S. economy. The S&P 500 advanced 0.69% and closed at 6,909.51, while the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9% and settled at 22,886.07. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 230.81 points, or 0.47%, and ended at 49,625.97. The 30-stock index recovered from a 200-point loss earlier in the session on disappointing economic data. Data released on Friday showed that the US economy expanded an annualized 1.4% in Q4 2025, the least since Q1 2025, following a 4.4% growth in Q3 and well below widely reported forecasts of 3%, the advance estimate showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro speculative net longs stay around two and half year high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-speculative-net-longs-stay-around-two-and-half-year-high/1679156</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679156</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market fell but stayed around a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market fell but stayed around a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Euro futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net long position of 174480 contracts in the data reported through February 17, 2026. This was a weekly decline of 5825 net long contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index falls 1.42%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-falls-142/1679155</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679155</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index ended down 1.42% at 31550.5 today.

Nifty IT index ended down 1.42% at 31550.5 today. The index has slipped 17.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Coforge Ltd shed 3.85%, Mphasis Ltd dropped 2.70% and Persistent Systems Ltd slipped 2.25%. The Nifty IT index has fallen 22.00% over last one year compared to the 12.80% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index gained 1.36% and Nifty MNC index increased 0.97% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.55% to close at 25713 while the SENSEX recorded a gain of 0.58% to close at 83294.66 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market rally for 2nd day; Nifty ends above 25,700]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-rally-for-2nd-day-nifty-ends-above-25700/1679154</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679154</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity indices ended with substantial gains on Monday, extending their rally for a second consecutive session, after the Supreme Court of the United States struck down import levies imposed by President Donald Trump, prompting him to announce a temporary 15% tariff.

Domestic equity indices ended with substantial gains on Monday, extending their rally for a second consecutive session, after the Supreme Court of the United States struck down import levies imposed by President Donald Trump, prompting him to announce a temporary 15% tariff. The Nifty settled above the 25,700 mark. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 479.95 points or 0.58% to 83,294.66. The Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. In the two consecutive trading session, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.21% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.51%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,927 shares rose and 2,385 shares fell. A total of 206 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 3,78,12,663 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 2.59 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it will close on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 9,82,080 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.09 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 74,72,808 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.34 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. Two Banks Flag Fraud Cases IDFC First Bank slumped 16.30% to Rs 69.94 after the bank said that it has uncovered fraudulent transactions worth around Rs 590 crore at one of its branches in Chandigarh, allegedly involving a few employees. In a regulatory filing made on Sunday, the private sector bank said that based on a preliminary internal assessment (upon receipt of communication from a particular Department of Government of Haryana), the bank has identified an incident involving unauthorized and fraudulent activities by certain employees at a particular branch in Chandigarh and potentially involving other counterparties. Detailing the events that led to the aforementioned discover, the bank stated that it had received a request from a particular Department of Haryana Government for closure of its account and transfer of funds to another bank. In the process, certain discrepancies were observed in the amount mentioned vis-à-vis the balance in the account. Meanwhile, AU Small Finance Bank slumped 5.89% to Rs 968.30 after the Haryana government decisively removed the bank from its list of empanelled lenders due to serious allegations of fraudulent activities. In a statement, the bank said that on 18 February 2026, it received a separate communication from the department seeking information regarding suspected unauthorised transactions between a government account and another customer account. As of 21 February 2026, deposits from the Government of Haryana with AU Small Finance Bank stood at Rs 538 crore across nearly 200 accounts, accounting for about 0.4% of the bank's overall deposits as of 31 December 2026. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index jumped 1.36% to 9,796.85. The index rallied 3.06% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Indian Bank (up 3.81%), Union Bank of India (up 1.85%), Canara Bank (up 1.43%), Bank of India (up 1.42%), Bank of Maharashtra (up 1.26%), Bank of Baroda (up 1.25%), State Bank of India (up 0.94%), Indian Overseas Bank (up 0.88%), Central Bank of India (up 0.55%) and Punjab National Bank (up 0.54%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Dee Development Engineers surged 16.35% after the company announced that it, along with its material subsidiary, has secured contracts aggregating approximately Rs 173 crore. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone advanced 2.75% after the company’s subsidiary Adani Gangavaram Port signed a memorandum of understanding with NMDC, a Government of India enterprise, and Vale S.A., Brazil. Axis Bank added 1.34% after the bank has clarified that it has neither submitted nor is planning to submit any bid for a stake in CreditAccess Grameen. UPL tumbled 14.15% after the company’s restructuring plan triggered concerns over leverage and the post-rejig capital structure. Morepen Laboratories zoomed 15.11% after the company announced that it has secured a multi-year contract development and manufacturing organization (CDMO) mandate valued at approximately Rs 825 crore from a leading global pharma major. JSW Infrastructure added 1.94% after the company‘s board approved the issuance of 25 crore equity shares with face value of Rs 2 each, to fund its multi year expansion program Lotus Chocolate Company declined 1.97% after the company announced temporary shutdown of its manufacturing facility situated in Sangareddy, Telangana for 15 days from 24 February 2026. R&B Denims rose 1.94% after the company secured sales orders aggregating to around Rs 215.88 crore for the supply of around 12,000,000 meters of denim fabric products from established merchant exporters. Olectra Greentech gained 2.50% after its associate, Evey Trans (EVEY), secured two Letters of Award (LOAs) worth Rs 1,800 crore from the Telangana State Road Transport Corporation (TGSRTC). Patel Engineering rose 2.68% after the company said that it has been declared the lowest bidder (L1) from Himachal Pradesh Power Corporation (HPPCL) for the construction of the Renukaji Dam Project in Himachal Pradesh. Global Markets: Most European markets traded lower on Monday as more uncertainty surrounding U.S. trade tariffs weighed on risk appetite. Markets in Asia ended mostly higher as investors monitored developments related to the United States tariffs. While the Supreme Court ruled on Friday that the Trump administration unlawfully imposed the measures last year, US President Donald Trump used different legal means to raise global levies to 15% from 10% over the weekend. Markets in China and Japan were closed for a holiday. On Friday, U.S. stocks rose after the Supreme Court ruling, potentially providing relief for companies burdened by higher costs from the duties and easing concern about sticky inflation still plaguing the U.S. economy. The S&P 500 advanced 0.69% and closed at 6,909.51, while the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9% and settled at 22,886.07. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 230.81 points, or 0.47%, and ended at 49,625.97. The 30-stock index recovered from a 200-point loss earlier in the session on disappointing economic data. Data released on Friday showed that the US economy expanded an annualized 1.4% in Q4 2025, the least since Q1 2025, following a 4.4% growth in Q3 and well below widely reported forecasts of 3%, the advance estimate showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/blue-stock-chart-growth-picture-id174673054_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts rise further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-rise-further/1679153</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679153</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators increased net short position in the Pound futures market, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators increased net short position in the Pound futures market, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 42404 contracts in the data reported through February 17, 2026. This was a weekly rise of 16594 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LTIMindtree inks $100 mln multi-year agreement with MedTech]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ltimindtree-inks-100-mln-multi-year-agreement-with-medtech/1679152</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679152</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[This agreement will span over seven years.

This agreement will span over seven years. Towards this, LTM will leverage iNXT, its cross-industry digital transformation and innovation platform designed to help enterprises manage the convergence of the physical and digital worlds. As part of this agreement, LTM will develop and support the MedTech’s primary hearing instrument brands and its private labels. This includes the MedTech’s core wearable devices, the fitting application used by hearing care professionals to configure hearing aids, and the mobile application for device control. LTIMindtree is a global technology consulting and digital solutions company that enables enterprises across industries to reimagine business models, accelerate innovation, and maximize growth by harnessing digital technologies. LTIMindtree is a Larsen & Toubro Group company. The company reported a 30.73% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 970.60 crore despite of a 3.72% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q2 September 2025. The counter declined 1.20% to end at Rs 4829.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LTIMindtreeLtd_76198734_18105.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI Central Board of Directors assesses global and domestic economic landscape]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-central-board-of-directors-assesses-global-and-domestic-economic-landscape/1679151</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679151</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The 621st meeting of the Central Board of Directors of the Reserve Bank of India was held today at New Delhi under the Chairmanship of Sanjay Malhotra, Governor.

The 621st meeting of the Central Board of Directors of the Reserve Bank of India was held today at New Delhi under the Chairmanship of Sanjay Malhotra, Governor. The Board assessed the global and domestic economic landscape, factoring in the challenges arising from geopolitical developments and financial market volatility. Nirmala Sitharaman, Union Minister of Finance and Corporate Affairs, addressed and interacted with the Directors of the Central Board, after the Board meeting. The FM articulated the strategic vision of the Union Budget 2026-27, which was inspired by the three Kartavyas, and delineated expectations from the financial sector toward achieving its goal of Viksit Bharat. The Directors expressed their appreciation for the Budget and shared their perspectives.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/the-boardroom-table-is-set-for-a-meeting-picture-id18502510_AGMS.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharti Airtel partners with Zscaler to launch AI & cyber threat research center]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharti-airtel-partners-with-zscaler-to-launch-ai-cyber-threat-research-center/1679150</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679150</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The multi-stakeholder initiative, designed “In India, For India,” aims to safeguard critical sectors such as telecommunications, banking, and energy while supporting India’s broader digital transformation.

The multi-stakeholder initiative, designed “In India, For India,” aims to safeguard critical sectors such as telecommunications, banking, and energy while supporting India’s broader digital transformation. The centre will serve as a national collaboration platform, bringing together private enterprises, public institutions, academia, and government agencies. Zscaler will deploy a dedicated India-focused threat research team leveraging its Zero Trust Exchange platform, which processes over 500 billion daily transactions to generate actionable threat intelligence. Airtel will contribute deep visibility across IoT and mobile networks to enhance monitoring, accelerate threat detection, and enable coordinated response mechanisms. Gopal Vittal, executive vice-chairman of Bharti Airtel, said the partnership reinforces the company’s commitment to securing customers and strengthening India’s digital backbone. Jay Chaudhry, CEO and Chairman of Zscaler, emphasized the need for a secure-by-design Zero Trust architecture to protect India’s rapidly expanding digital ecosystem. The center will progressively onboard additional partners from India’s public and private sectors to further enhance national cyber preparedness. Bharti Airtel is a global communications solutions provider with over 600 million customers in 15 countries across India and Africa. The company reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Bharti Airtel rose 0.87% to Rs 1,994.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BhartiAirtel_49342333843_15542.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Olectra Greentech gains on bagging Rs 1,800 crore electric bus order from TGSRTC]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/olectra-greentech-gains-on-bagging-rs-1800-crore-electric-bus-order-from-tgsrtc/1679146</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679146</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to a regulatory filing, the LOAs relate to the supply, operation and maintenance of 1,085 electric buses.

According to a regulatory filing, the LOAs relate to the supply, operation and maintenance of 1,085 electric buses. The order includes 1,025 12-metre non-AC buses and 60 12-metre AC buses. The contract has been awarded under the Gross Cost Contract (GCC) / OPEX model for a period of 12 years. EVEY will procure the buses from Olectra, with deliveries scheduled over 20 months. Olectra said the supply value of the 1,085 buses is estimated at approximately Rs 1,800 crore. The company will also undertake maintenance of the buses during the contract period. The company clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It added that the proposed transactions between Olectra and EVEY qualify as related party transactions and will be conducted on an arm’s length basis. Olectra Greentech is engaged in the manufacturing of composite polymer insulators, electric buses, and electric trucks. The company's consolidated net profit rose 4.18% to Rs 49.55 crore while net sales rose 25.39% to Rs 656.62 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlectraGreentec_59554403015_22012.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patel Engg gains after securing  Rs 910-cr project in Himachal Pradesh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/patel-engg-gains-after-securing-rs-910-cr-project-in-himachal-pradesh/1679144</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679144</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scope of works under this package comprises the construction of three diversion tunnels, each with a diameter of 9.5 meters and lengths of 1379 meters, 1468 meters, and 1590 meters respectively.

The scope of works under this package comprises the construction of three diversion tunnels, each with a diameter of 9.5 meters and lengths of 1379 meters, 1468 meters, and 1590 meters respectively. The package also covers the development of three inlet and outlet portals for the diversion tunnels, along with the construction of access roads spanning 6 kilometers. In addition, the project involves the installation of hydro-mechanical gates for the diversion tunnels and the execution of instrumentation works to ensure operational efficiency and safety. The Renuka Ji Dam Project is a critical initiative aimed at enhancing water storage capacity, ensuring reliable water supply, and supporting hydropower generation. The order, valued at Rs 910 crore, is scheduled to be completed within 30 months. Kavita Shirvaikar, managing director, Patel Engineering said: "Being declared the L1 bidder for the Renuka Ji Dam Project is a proud milestone for us, reaffirming our strong capabilities in delivering large-scale infrastructure projects and our role as a trusted partner in India’s growth journey. This project not only strengthens our portfolio but also positions us to contribute meaningfully to sustainable water management and hydropower development. Looking ahead, we remain committed to leveraging innovation, engineering excellence, and execution efficiency to deliver projects that create lasting value for communities and drive the nation’s infrastructure forward." Patel Engineering operates in the hydropower, tunneling and irrigation segments. The company has executed projects in India and overseas, including more than 85 dams, 40 hydroelectric projects and over 300 km of tunneling for central PSUs and state government agencies. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 11.8% to Rs 70.35 crore despite a 2.8% increase in net sales to Rs 1,239.35 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PatelEngg_45399352434_1320.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IDFC First Bank Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/idfc-first-bank-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679140</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679140</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UPL Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Swan Corp Ltd and 63 Moons Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026.

UPL Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Swan Corp Ltd and 63 Moons Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026. IDFC First Bank Ltd crashed 16.34% to Rs 69.91 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 324.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.23 lakh shares in the past one month. UPL Ltd tumbled 14.85% to Rs 640.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 58346 shares in the past one month. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd lost 12.00% to Rs 2192. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2.14 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.57 lakh shares in the past one month. Swan Corp Ltd plummeted 6.75% to Rs 379.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.38 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 38621 shares in the past one month. 63 Moons Technologies Ltd corrected 6.71% to Rs 598.75. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11852 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10701 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDFCBank_27126132357_54759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>