<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:37:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pound off one-week low in global markets but tumbles against INR]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pound-off-one-week-low-in-global-markets-but-tumbles-against-inr/1670843</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670843</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound has gained after recent losses and GBP/USD pair is currently trading up 0.23% at 1.3689.

British Pound has gained after recent losses and GBP/USD pair is currently trading up 0.23% at 1.3689. The counter had toppled to one-week low in last session but cut losses amid supportive risk appetite today. Economic cues also remain positive for the pair as the UK manufacturing sector strengthened in January with growth in both output and new orders accelerating, final data from S&P Global showed Monday. The final manufacturing Purchasing Managers' Index rose to a 17-month high of 51.8 in January from 50.6 in December. Market is now waiting for the monetary policy announcement from the Bank of England. However, Pound has eased in local markets as INR is soaring following the announcement of India-US trade deal. GBP/INR futures are currently trading at 123.45, down 1.70% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PB Fintech Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pb-fintech-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1670842</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670842</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Zydus Wellness Ltd, Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd and Varun Beverages Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 03 February 2026.

AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Zydus Wellness Ltd, Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd and Varun Beverages Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 03 February 2026. PB Fintech Ltd lost 5.76% to Rs 1472.3 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 35.99 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.01 lakh shares in the past one month. AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd crashed 3.69% to Rs 374.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 21305 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5464 shares in the past one month. Zydus Wellness Ltd tumbled 3.49% to Rs 419.8. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 40703 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13148 shares in the past one month. Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd dropped 3.36% to Rs 66.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.41 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.48 lakh shares in the past one month. Varun Beverages Ltd corrected 3.12% to Rs 451.95. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 16.84 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.76 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PB-Fintech-Ltd_61882656_41343.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahalaxmi Rubtech Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahalaxmi-rubtech-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1670820</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670820</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Paras Petrofils Ltd, Artemis Medicare Services Ltd, TECIL Chemical & Hydro Power Ltd and MPS Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 03 February 2026.

Paras Petrofils Ltd, Artemis Medicare Services Ltd, TECIL Chemical & Hydro Power Ltd and MPS Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 03 February 2026. Mahalaxmi Rubtech Ltd crashed 13.20% to Rs 190.95 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1096 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 88 shares in the past one month. Paras Petrofils Ltd tumbled 9.72% to Rs 2.6. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.46 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.97 lakh shares in the past one month. Artemis Medicare Services Ltd lost 8.33% to Rs 219.45. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 27810 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5622 shares in the past one month. TECIL Chemical & Hydro Power Ltd fell 5.76% to Rs 15.55. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 438 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1164 shares in the past one month. MPS Ltd slipped 5.73% to Rs 1788. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3848 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1458 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahalaxmiRubtec_32623583074_4319.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bullion jumps after historic selloff, eyes $5,000]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bullion-jumps-after-historic-selloff-eyes-5000/1670819</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670819</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures surged nearly 7% in electronic trade on Tuesday, rebounding toward the $5,000 per ounce mark as bargain hunting emerged after two sessions of intense selling.

Gold futures surged nearly 7% in electronic trade on Tuesday, rebounding toward the $5,000 per ounce mark as bargain hunting emerged after two sessions of intense selling. The rally followed a steep slump that saw prices fall almost 5% a day earlier, marking the sharpest decline in more than a decade. Sentiment improved despite lingering concerns over US monetary policy after President Trump nominated Kevin Warsh, seen as a hawkish choice for Federal Reserve Chair. Support also came from a softer US dollar, which helped lift dollar-denominated commodities, even as strong US economic data pointed to resilience in growth. On the domestic front, MCX April gold futures jumped around 6% to Rs 152,659 per 10 grams. Markets now await the US monthly jobs report later this week, though its release may be delayed by a partial government shutdown.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with robust gains; metal shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-robust-gains-metal-shares-advance/1670817</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670817</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major gains in the mid- afternoon trade as investors cheered the long-awaited trade agreement between India and the United States.

The domestic equity indices traded with major gains in the mid- afternoon trade as investors cheered the long-awaited trade agreement between India and the United States. The announcement sparked broad-based buying across sectors, enabling domestic markets to recoup losses triggered by the recent Union Budget. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark. Metal shares extended gains for second consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 2,205.63 points or 2.71% to 83,877.20. The Nifty 50 index added 678.75 points or 2.71% to 25,767.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 2.97% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.99%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,339 shares rose and 885 shares fell. A total of 158 shares were unchanged. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index added 3.53% to 11,969.50. The index jumped 5.47% in the two consecutive trading session. Adani Enterprises (up 10.61%), Welspun Corp (up 8.34%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 6.2%), Steel Authority of India (up 4.65%), Hindalco Industries (up 4%), Hindustan Zinc (up 3.59%), Tata Steel (up 3.2%), APL Apollo Tubes (up 3.19%), JSW Steel (up 3%) and Vedanta (up 3%) added. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.68% to 6.723 compared with previous session close of 6.769. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higer against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1600 compared with its close of 91.4950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 6.15% to Rs 152,850. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.18% to 97.43. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.12% to 4.283. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell 24 cents or 0.36% to $66.06 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Dev Information Technology (Dev IT) rallied 1.01% after the company secured an order worth around Rs 29 lakh from Gujarat International Finance Tec-City (GIFT), an undertaking of the Government of Gujarat. Bharat Seats jumped 6.77% after the company’s standalone net profit spiked 30.43% to Rs 9.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 7.59 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rallied 60.25% to Rs 491 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 306.39 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at PCBL Chemical Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-pcbl-chemical-ltd-counter/1670807</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670807</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aarti Industries Ltd, Balkrishna Industries Ltd, Welspun Living Ltd, Apar Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 03 February 2026.

Aarti Industries Ltd, Balkrishna Industries Ltd, Welspun Living Ltd, Apar Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 03 February 2026. PCBL Chemical Ltd notched up volume of 213.69 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 25.94 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 8.24 lakh shares. The stock rose 12.30% to Rs.300.45. Volumes stood at 8.91 lakh shares in the last session. Aarti Industries Ltd recorded volume of 126.21 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 19.28 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.55 lakh shares. The stock gained 15.39% to Rs.430.40. Volumes stood at 7.34 lakh shares in the last session. Balkrishna Industries Ltd recorded volume of 20.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.28 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.64 lakh shares. The stock gained 12.17% to Rs.2,573.00. Volumes stood at 1.74 lakh shares in the last session. Welspun Living Ltd saw volume of 277.88 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.25 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 30.05 lakh shares. The stock increased 18.99% to Rs.145.70. Volumes stood at 8.1 lakh shares in the last session. Apar Industries Ltd saw volume of 8.45 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.04 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 93458 shares. The stock increased 18.22% to Rs.9,650.00. Volumes stood at 78971 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PhillipsCarbon_73022525479_435.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zydus Wellness declines after weak Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zydus-wellness-declines-after-weak-q3-performance/1670805</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670805</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales more than doubled to Rs 963.3 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 450.8 crore in the same period last year.

Net sales more than doubled to Rs 963.3 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 450.8 crore in the same period last year. EBITDA was Rs 61 crore in Q3 FY26, which is steeply higher as compared with Rs 14.8 crore registered in Q3 FY25. For the third quarter, finance costs were Rs 41.2 crore, depreciation & amortisation charges were Rs 55.5 crore and advertisement & promotion expenses were Rs 178.8 crore. Accordingly, the company recorded a pre-tax loss of Rs 41.5 crore in Q3 FY26 as against a pre-tax profit of Rs 10.1 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Zydus Wellness is a leading Indian consumer company dedicated to health and wellness through its two core segments: food & nutrition and personal care.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZydusWellness_96134066137_6367.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dev IT gains on bagging Rs 29 lakh order from GIFT City]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dev-it-gains-on-bagging-rs-29-lakh-order-from-gift-city/1670793</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670793</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order entails the procurement of AutoCAD licenses along with a three-year subscription for operations in the DTA area of GIFT City.

The order entails the procurement of AutoCAD licenses along with a three-year subscription for operations in the DTA area of GIFT City. The contract has been awarded on a fixed-cost basis and is to be executed over a period of approximately three years. Dev Information Technology (Dev IT) is in the business of providing IT-enabled services, offering solutions across cloud services, digital transformation, enterprise applications, and managed IT services. Its product portfolio includes offerings such as Talligence and ByteSigner. The company's consolidated net profit climbed 786.3% to Rs 71.88 crore on a 35% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 48.51 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DevInformationTechnologyLtd_93091952440_70312.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,750; European mrkt advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25750-european-mrkt-advance/1670788</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670788</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with robust gains in the afternoon trade as investors cheered the long-awaited trade agreement between India and the United States.

The key equity benchmarks traded with robust gains in the afternoon trade as investors cheered the long-awaited trade agreement between India and the United States. The announcement sparked broad-based buying across sectors, enabling domestic markets to recoup losses triggered by the recent Union Budget. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark. All the sectoral indices traded in the green on the NSE, with metal, pharma, and auto shares gaining the most. At 1:30 ST, the S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 2,200.62 points or 2.69% to 83,867.08. The Nifty 50 index added 683.25 points or 2.72% to 25,776.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 2.71% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.87%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,264 shares rose and 899 shares fell. A total of 169 shares were unchanged. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. Gainers & Losers: Adani Enterprises (up 10.75%), Jio Financial Services (up 8.83%), Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (up 7.55%), Bajaj Finance (up 6.47%), and Shriram Finance (up 5.46%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. There were no major losers on the Nifty50, with the index witnessing broad-based buying interest. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharat Wire Ropes rallied 6.70% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 22.58% to Rs 18.24 crore despite an 11.75% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 142.81 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. SMC Global Securities rose 1.01% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 47.82% to Rs 30.54 crore on a 12.06% rise in total income to Rs 495.53 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Dhampur Sugar Mills gained 2.16% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 75.2% to Rs 26.49 crore on 9.54% increase in revenue from operations (excluding net excise duty) to Rs 451.18 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December. City Union Bank surged 5.89% after reporting a standalone net profit of Rs 332.16 crore, up 16.14% YoY, on the back of a 17.22% rise in total income to Rs 2,001.03 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. Transrail Lighting rallied 8.98% after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 17.7% to Rs 109.74 crore on a 32.6% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,777.19 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European stocks advanced on Tuesday as global markets settled following a short-lived sell-off in cryptocurrencies and precious metals. Most Asian indices rose after the U.S. and India trade deal, sparking a sharp risk-on move across the region. Japan's Nikkei 225 jumped nearly 3%, and the Topix rose over 2%. South Korea’s Kospi surged about 5%, triggering a buy-side trading curb. U.S. stocks climbed overnight as Wall Street kicked off the new month on a positive note, with investors looking past recent volatility in silver and bitcoin and turning their focus to the upcoming earnings slate. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.05%, the S&P 500 gained 0.54%, and the Nasdaq Composite added 0.56%. Markets are also tracking key economic signals and cues from the Federal Reserve on interest rates, even as efforts continue in Washington to avert a partial government shutdown. Data releases have been disrupted, with the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics postponing the January jobs report and other labour data until federal operations resume.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Seats rises as Q3 PAT jumps 30% YoY to Rs 10 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-seats-rises-as-q3-pat-jumps-30-yoy-to-rs-10-cr/1670787</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670787</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rallied 60.25% to Rs 491 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 306.39 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations rallied 60.25% to Rs 491 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 306.39 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax was at Rs 414.41 crore in Q3 FY26, up 62.22% as against Rs 255.46 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased by 14.82% YoY to Rs 14.82 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed was at Rs 477.12 crore (up 60.78% YoY), employee benefits expense stood at Rs 16.44 crore (up 23.60% YoY) and finance cost stood at Rs 2.23 crore (down 3.46% YoY) during the period under review. Bharat Seats manufactures complete seating system and interior component for the automotive and surface transport.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatSeats_93662176653_1138.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cg-power-industrial-solutions-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1670781</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670781</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 665.8, up 9.44% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 2.77% on the day, quoting at 25784.1. The Sensex is at 83941.05, up 2.79%. CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd has gained around 3.18% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.28% in last one month and is currently quoting at 34613.3, up 2.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 114.35 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 64.26 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 666.2, up 9.28% on the day. CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd is up 10.26% in last one year as compared to a 8.61% jump in NIFTY and a 8.19% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 79.42 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CGPowerIndu_42121517029_125.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Finance Corporation Ltd soars 1.61%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-finance-corporation-ltd-soars-161-gains-for-third-straight-session/1670782</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670782</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Power Finance Corporation Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Power Finance Corporation Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 391.85, up 1.61% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 2.77% on the day, quoting at 25784.1. The Sensex is at 83941.05, up 2.79%. Power Finance Corporation Ltd has added around 4.48% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Power Finance Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has added around 0.51% in last one month and is currently quoting at 26799, up 3.4% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 65.46 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 84.6 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 390.1, up 1.76% on the day. Power Finance Corporation Ltd is down 3.27% in last one year as compared to a 8.61% gain in NIFTY and a 17.31% gain in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 6.98 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerFinCorpn_2130951000_12068.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd soars 3.63%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/persistent-systems-ltd-soars-363-gains-for-third-straight-session/1670783</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670783</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Persistent Systems Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 6303, up 3.63% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 2.77% on the day, quoting at 25784.1. The Sensex is at 83941.05, up 2.79%. Persistent Systems Ltd has added around 1.6% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Persistent Systems Ltd is a constituent, has added around 2.73% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38074.15, up 1.91% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.97 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.83 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 6315, up 3.63% on the day. Persistent Systems Ltd is up 3.13% in last one year as compared to a 8.61% gain in NIFTY and a 9.47% gain in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 60.99 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PersistentSys_70071143_18286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coforge Ltd gains for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coforge-ltd-gains-for-third-consecutive-session/1670784</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670784</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Coforge Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Coforge Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1716.2, up 2.88% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 2.77% on the day, quoting at 25784.1. The Sensex is at 83941.05, up 2.79%. Coforge Ltd has risen around 4.52% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Coforge Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 2.73% in last one month and is currently quoting at 38074.15, up 1.91% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 8.85 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 19.54 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1722.1, up 3.36% on the day. Coforge Ltd is up 1.44% in last one year as compared to a 8.61% spurt in NIFTY and a 9.47% spurt in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 77.11 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoforgeLtd_47640546_24978.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welspun Corp Ltd soars 7.81%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/welspun-corp-ltd-soars-781/1670785</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670785</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Welspun Corp Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Welspun Corp Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 814, up 7.81% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 2.77% on the day, quoting at 25784.1. The Sensex is at 83941.05, up 2.79%. Welspun Corp Ltd has risen around 1.41% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Welspun Corp Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 3.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11561.55, up 3.14% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 12.74 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.05 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 26.16 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WelspunCorp_23409759814_7947.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[APL Apollo Tubes Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apl-apollo-tubes-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1670786</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670786</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[APL Apollo Tubes Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

APL Apollo Tubes Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2114.8, up 1.71% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 2.77% on the day, quoting at 25784.1. The Sensex is at 83941.05, up 2.79%. APL Apollo Tubes Ltd has risen around 7.56% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which APL Apollo Tubes Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 3.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11561.55, up 3.14% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.63 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 8.39 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2126.7, up 2.08% on the day. APL Apollo Tubes Ltd is up 47.11% in last one year as compared to a 8.61% spurt in NIFTY and a 43.64% spurt in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 117.13 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/APLApollo_78059449708_12334.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Properties soars after over Rs 1,000-cr plot sales at Panipat launch]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-properties-soars-after-over-rs-1000-cr-plot-sales-at-panipat-launch/1670780</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670780</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said it has sold plots worth over Rs 1,000 crore at the project since its launch in December 2025.

The company said it has sold plots worth over Rs 1,000 crore at the project since its launch in December 2025. More than 600 plots, covering around 8 lakh square feet of saleable area. This marks Godrej Properties’ first project in Panipat and its most successful plotted development launch to date in terms of sales value. Evora Estate is spread across 43 acres in Sector 40, Panipat, and is strategically located on NH-44A. The project features a Mediterranean-themed design and offers premium lifestyle amenities, including a luxury clubhouse. It is the company’s fourth residential plotted township in North India. The company said Panipat’s evolution as a micro-market has been driven by sustained infrastructure improvements, including enhanced connectivity via NH-44 and a stronger transport and industrial network. These developments are steadily positioning the city as an attractive residential catchment in North India. Gaurav Pandey, MD & CEO, Godrej Properties, said, “We are deeply encouraged by the response to Evora Estate, our first plotted development in Panipat. This milestone reinforces our belief that customers across emerging markets are seeking thoughtfully designed neighbourhoods that offer long-term value and a meaningful quality of life. We are grateful for the trust our customers and partners continue to place in us. As we expand our presence in Haryana, our focus will remain on creating high-quality, sustainable living environments that contribute positively to the communities we serve.” Godrej Properties is a leading national real estate developer. It is a real estate arm of the Godrej Group. The company currently operates in various cities and focuses on residential, commercial, and township development. The company's consolidated net profit jumped 20.84% to Rs 405.08 crore, despite a 32.27% fall in net sales to Rs 470.38 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejPropert_34796940031_15613.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Wire Ropes surges after Q3 PAT climbs 22% YoY to Rs 18 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-wire-ropes-surges-after-q3-pat-climbs-22-yoy-to-rs-18-cr/1670779</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670779</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 21.59% YoY to Rs 24.39 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 21.59% YoY to Rs 24.39 crore during the quarter. Total expenses fell 16.43% to Rs 118.59 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 141.91 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 71.42 crore (down 23.34% YoY), finance cost stood at Rs 2.35 crore (down 34.72% YoY) while employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 19.56 crore (up 15.4% YoY) during the period under review. Bharat Wire Ropes is engaged solely in the business of manufacture and sale of Wire & Wire Ropes.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatWireRopesLtd_65603643022_66768.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aditya Birla Capital jumps as housing finance arm raises Rs 2,750 crore from Advent]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aditya-birla-capital-jumps-as-housing-finance-arm-raises-rs-2750-crore-from-advent/1670744</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670744</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The boards of Aditya Birla Capital and Aditya Birla Housing Finance approved the primary capital infusion from Indriya, an Advent entity.

The boards of Aditya Birla Capital and Aditya Birla Housing Finance approved the primary capital infusion from Indriya, an Advent entity. The transaction, subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals, values Aditya Birla Housing Finance at Rs 19,250 crore on a post-money basis. Following completion, Aditya Birla Capital will hold about 85.7% stake in the housing finance arm, while Advent will own around 14.3%. Aditya Birla Housing Finance is among the fastest-growing housing finance companies in India and ranks among the top three players in terms of incremental loan book growth. Its assets under management expanded at a CAGR of 48% over the last three years to Rs 42,204 crore as of 31 December 2025. The company reported strong asset quality, with a gross stage 3 ratio of 0.54% and a net stage 3 ratio of 0.23%. The fresh capital will be used to sustain growth momentum and increase market share. Kumar Mangalam Birla, chairman of the Aditya Birla Group, said the capital infusion comes at a time when India's housing sector is at an inflection point, supported by policy initiatives such as Pradhan Mantri Awas Yojana and rising demand across income segments. He said the investment would strengthen the company’s financial foundation and enable deeper market penetration. Vishakha Mulye, MD and CEO of Aditya Birla Capital, said the housing finance arm has built a full-stack franchise across prime, affordable and construction finance, supported by technology-led distribution and a pan-India presence. The proposed capital raise, she added, marks the next phase of expansion with a focus on sustaining growth and gaining market share. Shweta Jalan said Advent is pleased to partner once again with the Aditya Birla Group, citing strong structural tailwinds in India’s mortgage market and the housing finance company’s robust risk practices and governance standards. Aditya Birla Housing Finance, registered with the National Housing Bank, manages assets of over Rs 42,204 crore and operates through 168 branches. The company carries long-term credit ratings of AAA (Stable) and short-term ratings of A1+ from CRISIL, ICRA and India Ratings. Aditya Birla Capital is a systemically important non-deposit taking non-banking financial company (NBFC) and the holding company of the financial services businesses. Through its subsidiaries/JVs, ABCL provides a comprehensive suite of financial solutions across loans, investments, insurance, and payments. The company's board will consider Q3 results on 3 February 2026. On a consolidated basis, Aditya Birla Capital's net profit fell 14.08% to Rs 855.24 crore on 2.30% increase in total income to Rs 10,686.62 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdityaBirlaCapitalLtd_956643460_40903.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Varun Beverages surges after PAT rises to Rs 260 crore in Q4]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/varun-beverages-surges-after-pat-rises-to-rs-260-crore-in-q4/1670745</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670745</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations grew 14% YoY to Rs 4,204.42 crore in Q4 2025 as compared to Rs 3,688.79 crore in Q4 CY2024.

Revenue from operations grew 14% YoY to Rs 4,204.42 crore in Q4 2025 as compared to Rs 3,688.79 crore in Q4 CY2024. Consolidated sales volume grew by 10.2% to 237.1 million cases from 215.1 million cases in Q4 CY2024. Sales volumes in India grew by 10.5%, and International markets grew by 10.0%. EBITDA increased by 10.2% to Rs 639.26 crore in Q4 2025 from Rs 579.97 crore in Q4 2024. Varun Beverages has recorded 16.2% increase in net profit to Rs 3,062.04 crore on an 8.4% rise in net revenue from operations to Rs 21,685.38 crore in CY2025 as compared with CY2024. Ravi Jaipuria, chairman, Varun Beverages, said: "CY2025 was marked by steady execution, despite weather-related disruptions in India during the peak summer season. Volume growth in India was impacted during parts of the year due to unprecedented heavy rainfall throughout the year. However, performance improved meaningfully in Q4, with domestic volumes growing by 10.5%, reflecting the strength of our wide distribution network and strong brand portfolio. The greenfield plants and backward integration facilities commissioned during the year are progressively stabilising and are expected to support higher volumes and operating leverage in the upcoming season. Our international operations continued to scale well, led by Africa. International volumes grew by 10.0% in Q4, with South Africa delivering healthy volume growth, supported by expansion in general trade reach, addition of visi-coolers and continued progress on backward integration and capacity enhancement, strengthening supply chain efficiency and cost competitiveness. During the year, we announced the proposed acquisition of Twizza in South Africa subject to regulatory and other approvals. The company has 3 manufacturing facilities including backward integration which will significantly enhance our manufacturing footprint and route-to-market capabilities in Africa’s largest soft drinks market, while offering meaningful synergies with our existing operations. We also continued to expand our product portfolio and categories. The snacks business in Morocco has ramped up well, distribution of snacks in Zimbabwe and Zambia is gaining traction." Varun Beverages is a key player in beverage industry and one of the largest franchisee of PepsiCo in the world (outside USA). The company produces and distributes a wide range of carbonated soft drinks (CSDs), as well as a large selection of non-carbonated beverages (NCBs), including packaged drinking water sold under trademarks owned by PepsiCo.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VarunBeveragesLtd_58326939712_24608.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>