<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Route Mobile gains as Q3 PAT spurts 18% YoY to Rs 98 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/route-mobile-gains-as-q3-pat-spurts-18-yoy-to-rs-98-cr/1674333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674333</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations declined 6.48% to Rs 1,107.06 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,183.79 crore in Q3 FY25.

However, revenue from operations declined 6.48% to Rs 1,107.06 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,183.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax jumped 26.42% to Rs 135.21 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 106.95 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses fell 9.28% to Rs 984.72 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,085.47 crore posted in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 73.74 crore (up 2.91% YoY), and finance costs stood at Rs 1.42 crore (down 84.66% YoY) during the quarter under review. Seckin Arikan, Chairman of the Board, Route Mobile and CEO, Proximus Global, commented, “Our performance this quarter reflects solid profitable growth. Despite a transitional period in parts of the portfolio, disciplined execution drove solid margin expansion thanks to strong seasonal contributions across regions. I would like to congratulate Mr. Agnihotri on his appointment as CEO and am confident his industry experience will drive our continued growth. I also extend sincere thanks to Mr. Gupta for his leadership in shaping Route Mobile’s success and look forward to benefiting from his continued expertise as Managing Director and Advisor to the Board. As we advance our strategy, we remain committed to building a scalable, differentiated business supported by a solid pipeline and the strengths of Proximus Global.” Rajdipkumar Gupta, MD, Route Mobile, added, “Q3 25-26 saw slightly downward revenue as we managed a transitional period in certain segments of our business. More importantly, our gross margins have strengthened considerably, driven by new customer additions in higher-margin segments, demonstrating the effectiveness of our portfolio optimization strategy. I am grateful to our teams across geographies for their dedication and agility in executing this strategic shift while delivering consistent service quality to our customers.” The Board of Route Mobile has approved the redesignation of Rajdipkumar Gupta as managing director, effective 9 February 2026, as he steps down from the role of CEO. Gupta will continue as a Key Managerial Personnel, with all other terms of his appointment unchanged. Simultaneously, Tushar Agnihotri has been appointed as chief executive officer and key managerial personnel, effective 9 February 2026. Previously Executive Vice President – India & APAC, Agnihotri will oversee overall operations and drive strategic initiatives, working closely with Mr. Gupta to accelerate growth and profitability. The company’s board has approved a third interim dividend of Rs 3 per equity share of Rs 10 each for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for eligibility is February 13, 2026, and the dividend will be paid to shareholders on the approved payment date. Route Mobile ("RML") is a cloud communications platform service provider, catering to enterprises, over-the-top (OTT) players, and mobile network operators (MNO). RML's portfolio comprises solutions in messaging, voice, email, SMS filtering, analytics, and monetization. RML has a diverse enterprise client base across a broad range of industries, including social media companies, banks and financial institutions, e-commerce entities, and travel aggregators. RML is headquartered in Mumbai, India, with a global presence in the Asia Pacific, the Middle East, Africa, Europe, and North America.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RouteMobileLtd_13116451_72028.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ceigall India spurts after bagging Rs 1,700 crore solar project in Madhya Pradesh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ceigall-india-spurts-after-bagging-rs-1700-crore-solar-project-in-madhya-pradesh/1674334</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674334</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project, awarded on a tariff-based competitive bidding mechanism, comprises a 220 MW solar power project integrated with a battery energy storage system (BESS).

The project, awarded on a tariff-based competitive bidding mechanism, comprises a 220 MW solar power project integrated with a battery energy storage system (BESS). The tariff quoted for the project is ₹2.70 per kWh, with an approximate project value of Rs 1,700 crore. The construction period for the project is 24 months, followed by an operational period of 25 years. The Morena Solar Park is a key renewable energy initiative in Madhya Pradesh and is designed to enhance grid stability through integrated storage solutions. The addition of BESS alongside solar generation will enable efficient peak power management and improved dispatch reliability. The company stated that this order would further strengthens its growing order book and mark a strategic expansion into large-scale renewable energy infrastructure. Ramneek Sehgal, Chairman & Managing Director, Ceigall India Limited, said: "We are pleased to secure the 220 MW Solar and BESS project at Morena Solar Park from Rewa Ultra Mega Solar Limited. This project strengthens our presence in the clean energy segment, and we are committed to executing it efficiently while supporting India’s energy transition and decarbonisation objectives." Ceigall India has also announced its earnings for the quarter ended on 31 December 2025. The company has reported 1.2% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 74.11 crore on a 19.3% increase in net revenue to Rs 991.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. While EBITDA improved by 12.7% to Rs 139.1 crore, EBITDA margin declined by 90 basis points YoY to 14.0% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 97.05 crore, up by 2.7% from Rs 94.53 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Ceigall India is an infrastructure engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) company undertaking specialized structural works such as elevated roads, flyovers, bridges, railway overbridges, tunnels, highways, expressways, and runways. The principal business operations are broadly divided into EPC projects and hybrid annuity model (HAM) projects.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CeigallIndiaLtd_68678209_85110.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE zooms after recording PAT of Rs 601 crore in Q3; EBITDA margin expands to 59% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-zooms-after-recording-pat-of-rs-601-crore-in-q3-ebitda-margin-expands-to-59/1674331</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674331</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In the trading segment, Cash Market volumes stood at Rs 7,645 crore in Q3 FY26, while Index Derivatives achieved a record average daily premium turnover of Rs 19,459 crore—driven by continued growth in Sensex Index Options.

In the trading segment, Cash Market volumes stood at Rs 7,645 crore in Q3 FY26, while Index Derivatives achieved a record average daily premium turnover of Rs 19,459 crore—driven by continued growth in Sensex Index Options. BSE StAR MF recorded 14% year-on-year growth in revenues to Rs 72.5 crore and total transactions increased by 21% to 21.7 crore. The platform also processed a record 7.97 crore transactions in January 2026. ICCL, BSE’s clearing subsidiary, reported strong performance with Equity Settled Turnover of Rs 8.14 lakh crore and Equity Derivatives Premium Turnover of Rs 12.57 lakh crore, settling 364 crore derivatives contracts in Q3 FY26. Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 511.96 crore, down 3.9% YoY. Consolidated operating EBITDA rose by 211% year on year to Rs 732 crore, with margins expanding sharply to 59% in Q3 FY26 from 31% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 795.33 crore, up by 176.2% from Rs 287.97 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The MD & CEO, BSE, said: “BSE’s strong Q3 performance is a testament to the strength of our platforms and the confidence the marketplaces in BSE. With record SME listings, growing index derivatives activity and continued success of StAR MF, we are accelerating innovation across all our businesses." BSE is Asia’s oldest exchange and the world’s largest exchange in terms of the number of listed companies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BSELtd_11315994_21236.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends downside: Positive cues from equities likely to limit losses]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-downside-positive-cues-from-equities-likely-to-limit-losses/1674326</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674326</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.77 against the US dollar in early trade on Tuesday as the currency market continues to price in caution following the India-US interim trade framework.

The Indian rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.77 against the US dollar in early trade on Tuesday as the currency market continues to price in caution following the India-US interim trade framework. At the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 90.63 against the US dollar, then lost some ground to touch 90.77, registering a loss of 11 paise over its previous close. Yesterday, rupee witnessed a volatile trading session and settled for the day on a slightly lower note, down 1 paisa at 90.66 against the US dollar. Indian shares edged higher in opening trades on Tuesday, tracking firm cues from global markets. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.6 percent and 0.7 percent, respectively on Monday after the United States and India unveiled an interim framework designed to reduce tariffs, redefine energy partnerships, and enhance economic collaboration. Foreign institutional investors bought shares worth Rs 2,255 crore on a net basis Monday, while domestic institutional investors bought shares to the extent of Rs 4 crore, according to provisional exchange data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bata India spurts after Q3 PAT jumps 13% YoY to Rs 66 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bata-india-spurts-after-q3-pat-jumps-13-yoy-to-rs-66-cr/1674315</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674315</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before Tax grew by 14.96% to Rs 88.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 77.30 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before Tax grew by 14.96% to Rs 88.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 77.30 crore in Q3 FY25. The results for the quarter also include a one-time exceptional expenditure of Rs 6.66 crore recognized under the new Labour Code. Total expenses jumped 3.30% to Rs 868.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 841.10 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses were at Rs 111.41 crore (up 7.72% YoY), while the cost of material consumed stood at Rs 48.84 crore (down 27.59% YoY) during the period under review. Speaking on Bata India’s Q3 FY26 performance, MD and CEO Gunjan Shah, said, “the improvement in demand post-GST 2.0 rollout continued during the quarter, supported by a few green shoots, resulting in strong EBITDA performance driven by sales and margin growth. All channels delivered growth with solid gross margin management, reflecting disciplined execution of key strategic levers. Premium products, particularly brands like Hush Puppies and Power, showed robust growth, while fresh sales contribution rose quarter-on-quarter. The company added 27 franchise stores, and the Zero Base Merchandising (ZBM) project was scaled to 400+ stores, improving consumer experience and revenue per square foot. Inventory efficiencies in both quantity and quality continued, with gross inventory reduction of 11%. Shah noted that initiatives in decluttering, inventory freshness, and cost optimization helped drive operating margin leverage, and continued marketing investments, along with a focus on strategic levers — product, channels, and inventory — keep the company optimistic for the future under GST 2.0.” Bata India is the largest retailer and manufacturer of footwear in the country. The company is engaged in the business of manufacturing and trading footwear and accessories through their retail and wholesale network. Their products include leather footwear, rubber/canvas footwear, and plastic footwear.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BataIndia_31276004590_60.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge higher in early trade; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-strong/1674313</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674313</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from returning foreign portfolio investors (FPIs).

The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from returning foreign portfolio investors (FPIs). The Nifty traded above the 25,900 level. Media, pharma and private bank shares advanced while PSU Bank, FMCG and IT shared declined. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 174.41 points or 0.21% to 84,238.53. The Nifty 50 index rose 55.60 points or 0.21% to 25,920. The broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.12% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index added 0.69%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,274 shares rose and 834 shares fell. A total of 168 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 2,254.64 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 4.15 crore in the Indian equity market on 09 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Apollo Micro Systems added 1.56% after it has reported a 40.62% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 25.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 18.26 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 69.96% to Rs 252.22 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 148.39 crore in the year-ago period. Neuland Laboratories declined 2.09% after it has reported a 60.06% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 40.57 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 101.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 10.47% to Rs 439.71 crore from Rs 398.03 crore a year ago. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.04% to 6.764 compared with previous session close of 6.671. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7000 compared with its close of 90.6600 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 0.48% to Rs 157,316. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 96.82. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.26% to 4.183. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement shed 16 cents or 0.23% to $68.88 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian market advanced on Tuesday as Japan’s Nikkei 225 continued its post-election rally and reached new highs. The Japanese market continues to ride the "Takaichi trade” in the wake of Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s landslide victory in the Lower House. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 rose on Monday, boosted by technology stocks, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average reached new heights as investors awaited critical economic data and another batch of earnings reports. The broad-based index advanced for a second straight day, rising 0.47% and ending at 6,964.82. The blue-chip Dow eked out a 20.20-point gain, or 0.04%, and settled at 50,135.87. The Nasdaq Composite jumped 0.9%, closing at 23,238.67. Investors will also be watching for the delayed January jobs report from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, which is due out Wednesday. The release was initially scheduled for last Friday but was postponed due to the partial government shutdown. It also comes after ADP reported last week that private payrolls increased by a mere 22,000 in January. The January consumer price index reading — which was also delayed by the shutdown — is due out Friday, with the consensus looking for a 2.5% annual rate.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Amber Enterprises India Ltd Spikes 2.63%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/amber-enterprises-india-ltd-spikes-263/1674311</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674311</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Amber Enterprises India Ltd rose 2.63% today to trade at Rs 7228.3.

Amber Enterprises India Ltd rose 2.63% today to trade at Rs 7228.3. The BSE Consumer Durables index is up 0.68% to quote at 59718.63. The index is down 2.89 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, PG Electroplast Ltd increased 1.64% and Titan Company Ltd added 0.73% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went up 3.84 % over last one year compared to the 8.92% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Amber Enterprises India Ltd has added 14.17% over last one month compared to 2.89% fall in BSE Consumer Durables index and 0.76% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 4427 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 11961 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 8625 on 29 Oct 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 5238.45 on 18 Feb 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AmberEnterprisesIndiaLtd_4767604800_45967.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty indicates flat opening for equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-indicates-flat-opening-for-equities/1674299</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674299</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 11.00 points, suggesting a flat start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 11.00 points, suggesting a flat start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 2,254.64 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 4.15 crore in the Indian equity market on 09 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 4,900.17 crore so far in February (till 09 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian market advanced on Tuesday as Japan’s Nikkei 225 continued its post-election rally and reached new highs. The Japanese market continues to ride the "Takaichi trade” in the wake of Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s landslide victory in the Lower House. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 rose on Monday, boosted by technology stocks, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average reached new heights as investors awaited critical economic data and another batch of earnings reports. The broad-based index advanced for a second straight day, rising 0.47% and ending at 6,964.82. The blue-chip Dow eked out a 20.20-point gain, or 0.04%, and settled at 50,135.87. The Nasdaq Composite jumped 0.9%, closing at 23,238.67. Investors will also be watching for the delayed January jobs report from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, which is due out Wednesday. The release was initially scheduled for last Friday but was postponed due to the partial government shutdown. It also comes after ADP reported last week that private payrolls increased by a mere 22,000 in January. The January consumer price index reading — which was also delayed by the shutdown — is due out Friday, with the consensus looking for a 2.5% annual rate. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks closed sharply higher on Tuesday, extending their winning streak to a second straight session as risk appetite strengthened. Fresh foreign inflows, optimism around the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and supportive Asian market cues powered the rally, while sentiment received an added lift from key agreements signed between India and Malaysia. The Nifty 50 climbed above the 25,850 mark, led by strong buying in consumer durables and PSU banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 485.35 points or 0.58% to 84,065.75. The Nifty 50 index rallied 173.60 points or 0.68% to 25,867.30. In the two consecutive trading sessions, Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.90% and 0.88%, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel bags Rs 455-cr West Central Railway project ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-bags-rs-455-cr-west-central-railway-project/1674215</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674215</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The estimated order value, as per the LoA, stands at Rs 4,54,94,74,871.

The estimated order value, as per the LoA, stands at Rs 4,54,94,74,871. The project is to be executed over a period of 960 days, with completion scheduled by 24 September 2028. Other terms and conditions are as per the LoA. The company said the promoter or promoter group has no interest in the awarding entity, and the order does not qualify as a related-party transaction. RailTel was incorporated in 2000, with the objective of creating nationwide broadband and VPN services, telecom, and multimedia networks to modernize the train control operation and safety system of Indian Railways. The company’s standalone net profit declined 4.07% to Rs 62.40 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.05 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 18.99% YoY to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26. The scrip rose 2.51% to settle at Rs 332.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Apollo Micro Systems, Neuland Laboratories, PNC Infra,  Texmaco Rail , Bata India ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-apollo-micro-systems-neuland-laboratories-pnc-infra-texmaco-rail-bata-india/1674214</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674214</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 10 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 10 February 2026. Result Today: Titan Company, Eicher Motors, Grasim Industries, Apollo Hospitals Enterprise, Britannia Industries, Oil India, Afcons Infrastructure, Balrampur Chini Mills, Dilip Buildcon, Edelweiss Financial Services, Escorts Kubota, Jubilant FoodWorks, Karnataka Bank, Samvardhana Motherson International, Torrent Power, TVS Supply Chain Solutions, United Breweries, Wakefit Innovations, and Wockhardt will release their quarterly earnings today. IPO Data: Aye Finance IPO Subscribed 12% on Day 1 The initial public offering (IPO) of Aye Finance saw an overall subscription of 12% on the first day of bidding. The issue was driven primarily by retail investors, whose portion was subscribed 26%. The qualified institutional buyers (QIBs) segment was subscribed 13%, while the non-institutional investors (NIIs) category saw a muted response with just 1% subscription as of Day 1. Fractal Analytics IPO Subscribed 9% on Day 1 The Fractal Analytics IPO garnered an overall subscription of 9% on the opening day of the issue. Retail investors led the demand, subscribing 35% of their allocated portion. The non-institutional investors (NIIs) segment was subscribed 7% on the first day of bidding, while other categories witnessed relatively subdued participation. Stocks to Watch: Apollo Micro Systems reported a 40.62% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 25.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 18.26 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 69.96% to Rs 252.22 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 148.39 crore in the year-ago period. Neuland Laboratories reported a 60.06% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 40.57 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 101.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 10.47% to Rs 439.71 crore from Rs 398.03 crore a year ago. PNC Infratech reported a 5.67% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 76.73 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 81.35 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue fell 18.33% to Rs 1,200.58 crore from Rs 1,470.01 crore a year ago. Texmaco Rail & Engineering reported a 44.66% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 42.27 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 76.39 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue fell 21.46% to Rs 1,041.6 crore from Rs 1,326.14 crore a year ago. Bata India reported a 12.8% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 66.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 58.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 2.8% to Rs 945 crore from Rs 919 crore a year ago. Gulf Oil Lubricants India reported a 21.9% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 76.4 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 97.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 10.6% to Rs 1,018 crore from Rs 920 crore a year ago. Genus Power Infrastructures reported a 147.51% year-on-year jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.24 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 56.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue surged 85.75% to Rs 1,122.36 crore from Rs 604.2 crore a year ago.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>