<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ideaforge Technology Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ideaforge-technology-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1680101</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680101</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Handson Global Management (HGM) Ltd, Dev Information Technology Ltd, Jindal Drilling & Industries Ltd and N K Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 March 2026.

Handson Global Management (HGM) Ltd, Dev Information Technology Ltd, Jindal Drilling & Industries Ltd and N K Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 March 2026. Ideaforge Technology Ltd soared 13.27% to Rs 466.4 at 12:01 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 4.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15912 shares in the past one month. Handson Global Management (HGM) Ltd spiked 11.15% to Rs 62. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 12 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 698 shares in the past one month. Dev Information Technology Ltd surged 10.40% to Rs 25.91. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 55109 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6178 shares in the past one month. Jindal Drilling & Industries Ltd spurt 9.79% to Rs 489.3. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 41732 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3134 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd added 9.15% to Rs 63.85. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 11 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 266 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IdeaforgeTechnologyLtd_35988136_78688.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KVS Castings spurts as Unit-2 goes live; capacity jumps to 19,200 MTPA]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kvs-castings-spurts-as-unit-2-goes-live-capacity-jumps-to-19200-mtpa/1680099</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680099</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[With the expansion, the company’s total installed production capacity has increased from 7,200 metric tonnes per annum to 19,200 metric tonnes per annum, following the addition of 12,000 metric tonnes per annum.

With the expansion, the company’s total installed production capacity has increased from 7,200 metric tonnes per annum to 19,200 metric tonnes per annum, following the addition of 12,000 metric tonnes per annum. Monthly capacity has risen from 600 metric tonnes to 1,600 metric tonnes. The new plant, located in Kashipur, Uttarakhand, will manufacture cast iron and ductile iron castings. Prior to expansion, existing capacity utilisation stood at 76.20%. The capacity addition is aligned with the company’s IPO objectives for capital expenditure on plant and machinery and is expected to support rising demand, improve operational efficiencies and enhance operating leverage. KVS Castings operates in the ferrous castings segment. The company manufactures cast iron and stainless steel castings. It offers end-to-end casting solutions supported by advanced manufacturing capabilities and focuses on delivering quality products at competitive prices. In H1FY26, the company's standalone net profit rose 42.47% year-on-year to Rs 3.69 crore on 3.19% increase in net sales to Rs 23.91 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KVSCASTINGSLIMITED_54259261_94188.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1680097</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680097</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd, IIFL Capital Services Ltd, Sterlite Technologies Ltd and Solar Industries India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 March 2026.

Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd, IIFL Capital Services Ltd, Sterlite Technologies Ltd and Solar Industries India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 March 2026. Tejas Networks Ltd surged 13.11% to Rs 492.7 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 121.59 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10.5 lakh shares in the past one month. Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd soared 11.19% to Rs 709.7. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 14.27 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 39394 shares in the past one month. IIFL Capital Services Ltd spiked 8.89% to Rs 314.3. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53241 shares in the past one month. Sterlite Technologies Ltd gained 5.79% to Rs 168.2. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8 lakh shares in the past one month. Solar Industries India Ltd spurt 4.14% to Rs 14059. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 9432 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5611 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with sharp losses amid U.S.-Iran tensions; auto share decline ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-sharp-losses-amid-us-iran-tensions-auto-share-decline/1680094</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680094</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the early afternoon as investors reacted to escalating tensions in the Middle East, with reports of intensified U.S.–Israeli strikes on Iran prompting a sharp rise in crude oil prices and triggering risk‑off sentiment that led Indian markets to fall over 1%.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the early afternoon as investors reacted to escalating tensions in the Middle East, with reports of intensified U.S.–Israeli strikes on Iran prompting a sharp rise in crude oil prices and triggering risk‑off sentiment that led Indian markets to fall over 1%. The Nifty traded below the 24,850 mark. Auto shares declined for second consecutive trading sessions. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, plunged 1,261.10 points or 1.55% to 80,026.18. The Nifty 50 index slipped 348.50 points or 1.38% to 24,830.15. The broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index declined 1.45% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 1.99%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 693 shares rose and 3,387 shares fell. A total of 204 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, zoomed 16.05% to 15.90. Middle East Tension: Middle East tensions escalated sharply following unconfirmed reports that Iran’s Supreme Leader Ali Khamenei may have been killed in joint U.S.–Israeli strikes on Tehran, although Iranian authorities have not issued any official confirmation. Media outlets also cited remarks attributed to Donald Trump claiming that several Iranian leaders were killed in ongoing operations, but these assertions remain independently unverified. Social media speculation pointed to Ayatollah Arafi as a possible interim successor, without credible confirmation. Meanwhile, reports indicated that Iran launched missiles toward Israel and other regional locations, heightening concerns of a broader regional conflict. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index fell 2.09% to 27,569.40. The index declined 3.91% in the previous two consecutive trading session. Samvardhana Motherson International (down 3.4%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 3.1%), Uno Minda (down 2.88%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 2.57%), Exide Industries (down 2.42%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 2.39%), Bajaj Auto (down 2.33%), Bosch (down 2.14%), Hero MotoCorp (down 1.82%) and Bharat Forge (down 1.74%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles fell 2.51%. The company has recorded total sales of 63,331 units in February 2026, registering a robust 35% YoY growth over 46,811 units in sold February 2025. Paras Defence and Space Technologies rallied 11.60% after the company announced the incorporation of a new subsidiary, Paras Semiconductors. The newly incorporated entity, registered in India on 27 February 2026, will focus on setting up an advanced heterogeneous packaging and 3D packaging OSAT facility. The unit will cater to high-growth segments such as artificial intelligence, high-performance computing, networking and data center applications. Global Markets: Asian markets traded lower on Monday after the United States and Israel launch their most ambitious attacks on Iran in decades, killing Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei. U.S. and Israeli strikes, and the Iranian retaliation, have sent shockwaves across the Middle East and through sectors from shipping to air travel to oil on warnings of rising energy costs and disruption to business in the Gulf, a strategic waterway and global trade hub. Most Gulf equities fell on Sunday, though Boursa Kuwait suspended trading and the UAE ordered its stock markets closed on Monday, a sign of the growing economic disruption sweeping the Gulf. Oil futures initially jumped 8% before trimming gains to about 4%. West Texas Intermediate futures last traded at $69.68, while Brent crude was at $76.13 per barrel. Gold futures jumped 2.3% as investors piled into the global safe haven. Stock futures tumbled in overnight trading after the weekend strikes in Iran. Futures on the Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 517 points, or 1%. S&P 500 futures lost 1%, and Nasdaq 100 futures declined a little more than 1%. On Friday, stocks saw a sharp sell-off after the latest producer price index data came in much hotter than expected, adding sticky inflation to a list of concerns that has caused market turbulence this month. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 521.28 points, or 1.05%, to close at 48,977.92. The S&P 500 closed down 0.43% at 6,878.88, while the Nasdaq Composite lost 0.92% to settle at 22,668.21. The S&P 500 and Nasdaq finished in the red for February amid growing fears about the impact of artificial intelligence on specific industries and the overall economy. Fueling the downbeat sentiment, January’s producer price index, a measure of wholesale inflation, showed a 0.5% increase for the month. Media reports had suggested that the headline reading could come in at 0.3%. The core PPI reading, which excludes food and energy prices, recorded a 0.8% gain, much more than the 0.3% rise that was widely reported in the media.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hyundai Motor clocks total sales of 66,134 units in Feb'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hyundai-motor-clocks-total-sales-of-66134-units-in-feb26/1680093</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680093</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s total sales for February 2025 were 58,727 units.

The company’s total sales for February 2025 were 58,727 units. While domestic sales rose by 9.8% YoY to 52,407 units, exports increased by 24.8% to 13,727 units in February 2026. Hyundai Motor India manufactures and sells passenger cars, along with vehicle parts and accessories. The company had reported a 6.34% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,234.40 crore on a 7.96% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 17,973.49 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip fell 1.77% to currently trade at Rs 2125.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HyundaiMotorIndiaLtd_73449848_16486.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zydus receives USFDA nod for Ivermectin and Dapsone tablets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zydus-receives-usfda-nod-for-ivermectin-and-dapsone-tablets/1680092</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680092</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg, are indicated for the treatment of intestinal strongyloidiasis and onchocerciasis.

Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg, are indicated for the treatment of intestinal strongyloidiasis and onchocerciasis. The drug will be manufactured at the group’s formulation facility at SEZ, Ahmedabad, and marketed in the US by Viona Pharmaceuticals Inc. The product had annual sales of USD 14.8 million. Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg are indicated for the treatment of leprosy and dermatitis herpetiformis. The tablets will be manufactured at the group’s formulation facility at SEZ-II, Ahmedabad, and distributed by Viona Pharmaceuticals Inc. The product reported annual sales of USD 8.4 million in the United States (IQVIA MAT December 2025). With this approval, the group now has 434 USFDA approvals and has filed 505 ANDAs since the commencement of filings in FY2003-04. Zydus Life Sciences operates as an integrated pharmaceutical company with business encompassing the entire value chain in the research, development, production, marketing, and distribution of pharmaceutical products. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 7.7% to Rs 1,102.64 crore on a 32.3% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,780.40 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Zydus Lifesciences fell 2.09% to Rs 903.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CadilaHealth_93490673476_20883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Omnitech Engineering IPO wraps up with 1.14x subscription ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/omnitech-engineering-ipo-wraps-up-with-114x-subscription/1680090</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680090</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Omnitech Engineering received bids for 2,16,31,632 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer.

Omnitech Engineering received bids for 2,16,31,632 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 1.14 times. The Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 2.86 times, the Non-Institutional Investors (NII) category was subscribed 0.73 times and the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 0.33 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026, and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 66 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue comprises both an offer for sale and a fresh issue of equity shares (of Rs 5 face value) worth aggregating to Rs 165 crore and Rs 418 crore, respectively. The entire portion of the offer for sale is by Udaykumar Arunkumar Parekh. Of the net proceeds, the company proposed to utilize Rs 50 crore towards repayment and/or prepayment, in full or in part, of certain outstanding borrowings availed by the company; Rs 233.558 crore towards setting up of two new manufacturing facilities at Village Chhapara (in Rajkot District) [with Rs 132.844 crore for facility 1 and Rs 100.714 crore for facility 2]; Rs 18.698 crore for funding towards capital expenditure requirements for purchase and installation of solar panels on the rooftop at, and purchase of new equipment/machinery for, the existing manufacturing facility at Village Chhapara; and the balance towards general corporate purposes. Outstanding borrowings at the end of Sep 2025 stood at Rs 382.913 crore. Omnitech Engineering (OEL), promoted by Udaykumar Arunkumar Parekh, is a key player in high-precision components and assemblies, serving global clients across energy, automation, and industrial equipment sectors. The company operates 3 strategically located facilities near Mundra Port, with exports contributing approximately 79% of revenue. As of September 2025, OEL’s order book stood at Rs 1,765 crore, representing 5x FY25 sales, highlighting robust demand and strong business momentum. Ahead of the IPO of Omnitech Engineering on 24 February 2026, the company raised Rs 174.59 crore from anchor investors by allotting 76.91 lakh shares at Rs 227 each to 17 anchor investors. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 27.79 crore and sales of Rs 228.17 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund Announces IDCW & Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-india-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1680089</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680089</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 05 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW under the following schemes.

Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 05 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW under the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Nippon India Growth Mid Cap Fund - Regular Plan – IDCW: 9.0000 Nippon India Growth Mid Cap Fund - Direct Plan – IDCW: 14.0000 Nippon India Growth Mid Cap Fund - Inst (IDCW) - Direct Plan – IDCW: 85.0000

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BCCL slides after coking coal output slumps 2% YoY in Feb’26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bccl-slides-after-coking-coal-output-slumps-2-yoy-in-feb26/1680087</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680087</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, raw coal production edged up 0.1% YoY to 3.50 million tonnes during the month.

However, raw coal production edged up 0.1% YoY to 3.50 million tonnes during the month. Offtake of raw coal stood at 2.16 million tonnes in February 2026, registering de-growth of 28.7% compared with 3.02 million tonnes produced in February 2025. The company listed on the stock exchange on 19 January 2026. The counter debuted at Rs 45.21, reflecting a premium of 96.57% compared with the issue price of Rs 23. Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) produces coking coal, non-coking coal, and washed coal. It is India's largest producer of coking coal and operates primarily in the Jharia coalfields of Jharkhand and the Raniganj coalfields of West Bengal. It is the wholly owned subsidiary of Coal India and was conferred with Mini Ratna status in 2014. The company reported standalone net loss of Rs 22.88 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net profit of Rs 424.99 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales fell 25.4% YoY to Rs 2,584.77 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatCokingCoalLtd_73867136_12380.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's manufacturing sector strengthens in February with 56.9 PMI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-manufacturing-sector-strengthens-in-february-with-569-pmi/1680084</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680084</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s manufacturing sector strengthened in February, driven mainly by strong domestic demand.

India’s manufacturing sector strengthened in February, driven mainly by strong domestic demand. New orders rose sharply, helping production grow at its fastest pace in four months. The HSBC India Manufacturing PMI increased to 56.9 from 55.4 in January, signaling solid improvement in overall business conditions. Local demand remained the key growth driver, supported by marketing efforts and higher client requirements. Export orders continued to grow but at the slowest rate in 17 months, with gains mainly coming from Asia, Europe, the Middle East and the US. To keep up with rising workloads, manufacturers increased purchases of raw materials, expanded inventories and hired more workers. Buying activity grew at a three-month high, while pre-production stocks rose sharply. Employment increased modestly but at the quickest rate in four months, supported by a rise in backlogged orders. Cost pressures remained moderate, similar to January, despite higher spending on labour, materials and transport. However, companies raised selling prices at a faster pace to protect profit margins. Supplier delivery times improved, indicating stable supply conditions. Looking ahead, businesses remain optimistic. Around 16% of firms expect higher output over the next year, supported by continued marketing efforts and healthy demand conditions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/steel-long-pipes-in-crude-oil-factory-during-sunset-picture_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PM Modi chairs cabinet committee on security meeting amid Iran-Israel-US conflict]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pm-modi-chairs-cabinet-committee-on-security-meeting-amid-iran-israel-us-conflict/1680085</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680085</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Cabinet Committee on Security (CCS) under the chairmanship of the Prime Minister reviewed the evolving situation in West Asia.

The Cabinet Committee on Security (CCS) under the chairmanship of the Prime Minister reviewed the evolving situation in West Asia. The Committee on the air strikes in Iran on 28 February and the subsequent escalation, including attacks in several Gulf countries expressed serious concern over the safety and security of the large Indian expatriate community in the region. The CCS also reviewed the difficulties faced by Indian travellers transiting the region and students appearing for scheduled examinations, as well as the broader implications for regional security and economic and commercial activities. The CCS directed all concerned departments to take necessary and feasible measures to assist Indian nationals affected by the developments. It underscored the importance of an early cessation of hostilities and a return to dialogue and diplomacy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SSWL reports 17% YoY rise in net turnover for February 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sswl-reports-17-yoy-rise-in-net-turnover-for-february-2026/1680086</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680086</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s gross turnover rose 9.71% to Rs 549.25 crore in February 2026, up from Rs 500.62 crore posted in the same month last year.

The company’s gross turnover rose 9.71% to Rs 549.25 crore in February 2026, up from Rs 500.62 crore posted in the same month last year. In value terms, the 2&3-wheeler segment recorded a robust 97% YoY growth, while the tractor segment surged 35% YoY. The aluminium segment jumped 16% YoY, the truck segment gained 10% YoY, the passenger car–steel segment dropped 14% YoY, and the overall exports segment plunged 26% YoY in February 2026. In volume terms, the 2 & 3 Wheeler segment surged 108% YoY, the tractor segment increased 35% YoY, the aluminium segment grew 10% YoY and the truck segment jumped 5% YoY, meanwhile, the passenger car–steel segment declined 16% YoY, and the overall exports segment tumbled 53% YoY during the review period. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) is engaged in the manufacturing of steel wheel rims catering to different segments of the automobile industry. The firm operates in the automotive wheel segment. Its geographical segments include India and overseas. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) reported a 2.30% year-on-year (YoY) decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 46.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 47.71 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 22.90% YoY to Rs 1,320.81 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter slipped 1.72% to Rs 210.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SteelStrWheel_50831874606_1338.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Japan and India renew Bilateral Swap Arrangement]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/japan-and-india-renew-bilateral-swap-arrangement/1680080</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680080</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Bank of Japan and the Reserve Bank of India signed the third Amendment and Restatement Agreement of the BSA, RBI stated in an update.

The Bank of Japan and the Reserve Bank of India signed the third Amendment and Restatement Agreement of the BSA, RBI stated in an update. The BSA is a two-way arrangement where both authorities can swap their local currencies in exchange for the US Dollar. The size of the BSA remains unchanged, that is, up to 75 billion US Dollars. Japan and India believe that the BSA, which aims to strengthen and complement other financial safety nets, will further deepen financial cooperation between the two countries and contribute to regional and global financial stability.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank credit grows by 12.2% on year in Dec-25, Credit growth in PSBs consistently outpaces that of private sector banks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-credit-grows-by-122-on-year-in-dec-25-credit-growth-in-psbs-consistently-outpaces-that-of-private-sector-banks/1680079</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680079</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated in a latest update that Scheduled Commercial Banks’ credit growth (y-o-y) improved marginally to 12.2 per cent in December 2025 from 11.8 per cent in December 2024.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated in a latest update that Scheduled Commercial Banks’ credit growth (y-o-y) improved marginally to 12.2 per cent in December 2025 from 11.8 per cent in December 2024. Bank branches located in rural, semi-urban and urban centres recorded higher credit growth than metropolitan branches, with their combined share in total credit increased to 40.4 per cent in December 2025 from 36.9 per cent in December 2020. Since December 2024, credit growth in metropolitan branches has remained lower than branches in other population groups. RBI stated that Public sector banks (PSBs) recorded credit growth of 14.1 per cent (y-o-y) for December 2025, exceeding the overall bank credit growth. Credit growth in PSBs has consistently outpaced that of private sector banks (PVBs) in last five quarters. The weighted average lending rate (WALR) on outstanding credit continued to ease across major sectors since December 2024 and stood at 9.35 per cent as on December 2025 (10.19 per cent on December 2024), in which the WALR on personal loans softened the most, followed by industry. Following the easing of policy rates, the share of loans bearing interest rate ‘below 9 per cent’ increased from 42.2 per cent in December 2024 to 62.4 per cent on December 2025, reflecting a shift in the interest rate distribution of bank credit. Credit growth accelerated in agriculture, industry and trade sectors for December 2025 relative to December 2024. In contrast, transport operators, personal loans and professional services sectors recorded a moderation in credit growth during the same period. Personal loans’ growth decelerated to 12.1 per cent for December 2025 from 13.7 per cent in December 2024, converging with overall bank credit growth after a sustained period of outpacing it. Credit to private corporate sector improved to 9.6 per cent (y-o-y) in December 2025 from 9.0 per cent in September 2025 and 7.9 per cent in June 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gross GST collections rise 8.1% to &#8377;1.83 lakh crore in February ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gross-gst-collections-rise-81-to-8377183-lakh-crore-in-february/1680077</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680077</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total gross Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections grew 8.1 per cent to over one lakh 83 thousand crore rupees in February this year as compared to the same month last year.

The total gross Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections grew 8.1 per cent to over one lakh 83 thousand crore rupees in February this year as compared to the same month last year. The total gross GST revenue in February, 2025 was over one lakh 69 thousand crore rupees. The Central GST collection in February this year stood at 37 thousand 473 crore rupees and State GST is at 45 thousand 900 crore rupees. The Integrated IGST collection amounts to over one lakh crore rupees.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at GMR Airports Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-gmr-airports-ltd-counter/1680076</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680076</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Hotels Co Ltd, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd, Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 02 March 2026.

Indian Hotels Co Ltd, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd, Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 02 March 2026. GMR Airports Ltd witnessed volume of 88.72 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 7.7 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 11.52 lakh shares. The stock dropped 3.53% to Rs.97.10. Volumes stood at 1.8 lakh shares in the last session. Indian Hotels Co Ltd notched up volume of 4.83 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 6.11 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 79138 shares. The stock slipped 1.48% to Rs.657.45. Volumes stood at 93961 shares in the last session. Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd registered volume of 87578 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.9 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 17863 shares. The stock slipped 2.47% to Rs.1,214.55. Volumes stood at 8728 shares in the last session. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd recorded volume of 49.97 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.73 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10.57 lakh shares. The stock gained 0.71% to Rs.281.90. Volumes stood at 8.86 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd witnessed volume of 105.38 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.52 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 23.31 lakh shares. The stock increased 13.34% to Rs.493.70. Volumes stood at 132.16 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GMRInfra_70127332467_23039.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves dip around $2 billion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-dip-around-2-billion/1680075</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680075</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s foreign exchange reserves fell by $2.11 billion in the week that ended February 20 to $723.60 billion, after hitting a new all-time high recently, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s latest data.

India’s foreign exchange reserves fell by $2.11 billion in the week that ended February 20 to $723.60 billion, after hitting a new all-time high recently, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s latest data. Foreign exchange reserves dipped in the latest week, driven by a drop in gold reserves and foreign currency assets. Foreign exchange reserves touch record high of $725.72 billion in February. For the reported week, India’s foreign currency assets (FCA), the largest component of foreign exchange reserves, stood at $572.56 billion, down $1.039 billion. The gold reserves are at $127.48 billion, down $977 million from the previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-currency-trading-concept-picture-id504246822_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund Announces IDCW & Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dsp-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1680081</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680081</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund has announced 05 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW under the following schemes.

DSP Mutual Fund has announced 05 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW under the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: DSP Flexi Cap Fund - Regular Plan – IDCW: 5.100000 DSP Flexi Cap Fund - Direct Plan – IDCW: 7.500000 DSP Natural Resources and New Energy Fund - Regular Plan – IDCW: 3.400000 DSP Natural Resources and New Energy Fund - Direct Plan – IDCW: 2.800000 DSP Value Fund - Regular Plan - IDCW: 1.400000 DSP Value Fund - Direct Plan - IDCW: 1.600000

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles registers sales of 63,331 units in Feb'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-registers-sales-of-63331-units-in-feb26/1680068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680068</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The increase in auto sales was supported by broad-based expansion across domestic, international, and electric segments.

The increase in auto sales was supported by broad-based expansion across domestic, international, and electric segments. Domestic PV sales rose 34% YoY to 62,329 units, while International Business (IB) sales surged 167% to 1,002 units in February 2026 as compared with February 2025. Total electric vehicle (EV) sales rose 57% to 8,385 units in February 2026 from 5,343 units in the corresponding month last year, significantly outpacing the 35% growth recorded in overall passenger vehicle (PV) volumes. Further, EVs represented about 13.2% of total sales in February 2026 as against 11.4% in February 2025, reflecting a gradual change in the portfolio mix. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles, part of the $180 billion Tata Group, is one of India’s leading automobile manufacturers, offering a diverse portfolio of cars and SUVs renowned for their design, safety, and performance. The company had reported consolidated net loss of Rs 3,486 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net profit of Rs 5,406 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. The scrip fell 2.60% to currently trade at Rs 373.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataMotors_19446492084_560.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1680067</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680067</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Mutual Fund has announced 04 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option and under the Periodic IDCW Periodic-Payout/Reinvestment) of following schemes.

Tata Mutual Fund has announced 04 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option and under the Periodic IDCW Periodic-Payout/Reinvestment) of following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Tata Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan & Direct Plan: 0.36 each.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>