<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Idea Ltd Spurts 5.48%, BSE Telecommunication index Rises 1.37%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vodafone-idea-ltd-spurts-548-bse-telecommunication-index-rises-137/1663913</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663913</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Idea Ltd rose 5.48% today to trade at Rs 12.13.

Vodafone Idea Ltd rose 5.48% today to trade at Rs 12.13. The BSE Telecommunication index is up 1.37% to quote at 3151.91. The index is up 3.71 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Indus Towers Ltd increased 5.23% and ADC India Communications Ltd added 2.45% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 11.81 % over last one year compared to the 8.25% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Vodafone Idea Ltd has added 13.05% over last one month compared to 3.71% gain in BSE Telecommunication index and 0.44% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 156.58 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 907.85 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 12.8 on 31 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 6.12 on 14 Aug 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VodafoneIdea_33393045864_23040.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Berger Paints India Ltd Slips 1.19%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/berger-paints-india-ltd-slips-119/1663914</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663914</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Berger Paints India Ltd fell 1.19% today to trade at Rs 513.25.

Berger Paints India Ltd fell 1.19% today to trade at Rs 513.25. The BSE Consumer Durables index is down 0.44% to quote at 61524.74. The index is up 4.14 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd decreased 0.73% and Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd lost 0.56% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went down 3.27 % over last one year compared to the 8.25% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Berger Paints India Ltd has lost 6.49% over last one month compared to 4.14% gain in BSE Consumer Durables index and 0.44% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 220 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 18203 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 604.6 on 03 Jul 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 447.05 on 14 Jan 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BergerPaints_94745472314_64.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SML Mahindra commercial vehicle production climbs 39% YoY in Dec’25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sml-mahindra-commercial-vehicle-production-climbs-39-yoy-in-dec25/1663911</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663911</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, commercial vehicle sales surged 76.91% YoY to 1,019 units in December 2025, compared with 576 units in December 2024.

However, commercial vehicle sales surged 76.91% YoY to 1,019 units in December 2025, compared with 576 units in December 2024. Exports tumbled 50% to 25 units in December 2025 as against 50 units in December 2024. SML Mahindra (formerly known as SML Isuzu) is primarily engaged in the business of the manufacture and sale of commercial vehicles and their parts. The company’s standalone net profit declined 3.44% to Rs 21.05 crore, while revenue from operations rose 0.98% to Rs 555.11 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Q2 FY25. Shares of SML Mahindra rose 0.04% to Rs 4,476.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SMLISUZU_60285231401_544.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[A B Infrabuild bags Rs 54-cr road over bridge project from East Coast Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/a-b-infrabuild-bags-rs-54-cr-road-over-bridge-project-from-east-coast-railway/1663904</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663904</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the project involves the construction of a road over bridge (ROB) comprising a 1x36.0-metre composite girder, 2x24.0-metre composite girders and 4x18.75-metre T-beam girders at km 657/29–31.

According to an exchange filing, the project involves the construction of a road over bridge (ROB) comprising a 1x36.0-metre composite girder, 2x24.0-metre composite girders and 4x18.75-metre T-beam girders at km 657/29–31. The bridge will be built in lieu of Level Crossing No. 354 between Baruva (BAV) and Mandasa Road (MMS) railway stations on the Howrah–Visakhapatnam main line under the Khurda Road Division. The total contract value stands at Rs 54,26,17,718.17 and the project is expected to be completed within 24 months. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It added that the order does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. A B Infrabuild engaged in construction, alter, improve, maintain, enlarge, pull down, remove, replace and develop, work, manage, and roads, railways, branches and sidings, bridges; and other constructions related to civil works. The company’s standalone net profit tumbled 43.6% to Rs 2.11 crore, while revenue from operations declined 21% to Rs 37.30 crore in Q2 FY26 compared to Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.62% to Rs 19.29 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABInfrabuild_38628776_73120.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty signals positive opening ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-signals-positive-opening/1663897</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663897</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 28 points, indicating a positive opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 28 points, indicating a positive opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,367.12 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,701.17 crore in the Indian equity market on 07 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 8,017.51 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asian markets advanced despite China’s consumer prices rose 0.8% from a year earlier, according to data from the National Bureau of Statistics on Friday. The reading followed a 0.7% climb in November. In U.S., investors are awaiting two key catalysts on Friday. First, the Supreme Court could issue a ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump’s tariffs, which could have an impact on trade policy and the nation’s fiscal situation. Second, the December jobs report will be out on Friday morning. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose while the Nasdaq Composite came under pressure as investors moved away from technology stocks. The Dow Jones Industrial Average climbed 270.03 points, or 0.55%, and ended at 49,266.11, the S&P 500 advanced 0.01% and closed at 6,921.46, while The tech-heavy Nasdaq dropped 0.44% and settled at 23,480.02 Domestic Market: Bears clawed deeper into Dalal Street as equity benchmarks slid for a fourth straight session on Thursday, with relentless selling dragging the Nifty below the 25,900 level. Indices reeled under a barrage of headwinds, led by sustained foreign fund outflows and rising global uncertainty. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 780.18 points or 0.92% to 84,180.96. The Nifty 50 index dropped 263.90 points or 1.01% to 25,876.85. In four consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 1.84% while the Nifty fell 1.71%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RVNL secures Rs 201-cr order from East Coast Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rvnl-secures-rs-201-cr-order-from-east-coast-railway/1663895</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663895</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the project involves the establishment of a wagon POH workshop with a capacity of 200 wagons.

According to an exchange filing, the project involves the establishment of a wagon POH workshop with a capacity of 200 wagons. The total project cost is Rs 201,23,47,556.55 and the work is expected to be completed within 18 months. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity and that the order does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Rail Vikas Nigam is in the business of executing all types of railway projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, construction of cable-stayed bridges, institution buildings, etc. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 19.73% to Rs 230.29 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 286.88 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5.22% YoY to Rs 5,122.98 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Rail Vikas Nigam dropped 4.16% to Rs 342.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Powergrid, RVNL, Sagar Cements. Astra Micorwave, Bharat Forge]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-powergrid-rvnl-sagar-cements-astra-micorwave-bharat-forge/1663894</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663894</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 9 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 9 January 2026. Initial Public Offer (IPO): Bharat Coking Coal India IPO opens for subscription on 9 January 2026 to 13 January 2026. The IPO price band has been set between Rs 21 to Rs 23 per share with a lot size of 600 shares. Result Today: Globus Spirits, Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) and Tejas Networks will declare their quarterly results later today. Stocks to Watch: Indian energy Exchange (IEX) will be in focus today as the Electricity Appellate Tribunal (APTEL) is scheduled to hear the market coupling case on Friday, January 9 at 10:30 AM. Power Grid Corporation of India has been declared as successful bidder under Tariff Based Competitive Bidding to establish 3GW transmission project situated in Davanagere, Karnataka. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) has received a letter of award(LoA) from East Coast Railway for setting up of wagon POH workshop of 200 Nos. capacity at Kantabanji. Sagar Cements’ board approved the offer for sale of up to 75,00,000 equity shares of face value of Rs 10 each equivalent to 8.14% of the total issued equity share capital of its subsidiary, Andhra Cements, through the stock exchange mechanism and in accordance with the OFS Guidelines. Astra Microwave Products’ joint venture, Astra Rafael Comsys has received Rs 275.27 crore order from Indian Air Force for integration of software defined radio (SDR) and installation of network centric application (NCO) on MiG-29 aircraft. Bharat Forge has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Agile Robots S.E. to jointly explore the space of AI driven robotics and intelligent industrial automatiom. Venus Remedies has obtained marketing authorisation in Indonesia for its antibiotic combination Ceftazidime and Avibactam.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>