<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:28:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 26,150 mark; IT shares rally for 2nd day ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-26150-mark-it-shares-rally-for-2nd-day/1663578</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663578</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded minor cuts in the mid-morning as geopolitical tensions and tariff-related concerns tempered optimism over the earnings outlook, keeping the Sensex and Nifty just shy of record highs.

The key equity indices traded minor cuts in the mid-morning as geopolitical tensions and tariff-related concerns tempered optimism over the earnings outlook, keeping the Sensex and Nifty just shy of record highs. The Nifty traded below 26,150 mark. IT shares extended gains for second consecutive trading sessions. At 11:29 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 120.12 points or 0.15% to 84,938.44. The Nifty 50 index fell 32.50 points or 0.09% to 26,146.20. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.30% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.04%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,983 shares rose and 1,836 shares fell. A total of 22 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index added 1.51% to 38,549.05. The index added 2.59% in the two consecutive trading session. Persistent Systems (up 2.92%), Wipro (up 2.37%), LTIMindtree (up 2.19%), Coforge (up 1.85%), Tech Mahindra (up 1.76%), HCL Technologies (up 1.59%), Oracle Financial Services Software (up 1.55%), Infosys (up 1.3%), Tata Consultancy Services (up 0.96%) and Mphasis (up 0.94%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Titan Company rose 4.29% after the company reported a strong business update for Q3 FY26, led by robust growth in its jewellery segment and a sharp expansion in international operations. Jubilant FoodWorks fell 1.15%. The company said its consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 2,438.7 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 13.4% year-on-year (YoY) increase. IRB Infrastructure Developers added 1.17% after the company has emerged as the selected bidder and received an LoA from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for tolling, operation, maintenance, and transfer of the Chandikhole–Bhadrak section of NH-16 in Odisha. Global Markets: Asian market traded mixed, with regional defense stocks snapping two-day winning streak on Wednesday, as investors continued to assess geopolitical risks after the U.S. attack on Venezuela and renewed rhetoric over Greenland. White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt reportedly said on Tuesday that President Donald Trump and his team were considering “a range of options” in order to acquire Greenland — including “utilizing the U.S. Military.” The statement further escalates the Trump administration’s already aggressive rhetoric about Greenland, which the president has long sought to make a part of the United States. U.S. crude futures fell 1.3% to $56.39 per barrel after U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro. Overnight in the United States, stocks advanced as investors appeared to look past the Venezuela operation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CreditAccess Grameen registers nearly 9% YoY rise in disbursements in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/creditaccess-grameen-registers-nearly-9-yoy-rise-in-disbursements-in-q3/1663579</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663579</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The disbursements are higher by 14.2% as compared with the figure of Rs 5,085 crore registered in Q3 FY25.

The disbursements are higher by 14.2% as compared with the figure of Rs 5,085 crore registered in Q3 FY25. The gross loan portfolio (GLP) as on 31 December 2025 was Rs 26,566 crore, up 7.1% YoY and up 2.6% QoQ. The company added 2.1 lakh borrowers in Q3 FY26 as against 2.2 lakh borrowers added in Q2 FY26. Its network expanded to 2,222 branches at the end of December 2025 from 2,209 branches at the end of September 2025. The company witnessed normalisation of asset quality across geographies, with X-Bucket collection efficiency (CE) rising to 99.71% in December 2025. Karnataka emerged as one of the best performing states, marking a return to its earlier asset quality trends The portfolio at risk (PAR) 0–30 improved materially during the period, declining from 100 basis points to 60 basis points, driven primarily by a reduction in fresh delinquency accretion. This indicates better early-stage repayment behavior and improved credit quality among recent borrowers. At the same time, however, the subsequent PAR buckets continued to witness forward movement, reflecting the natural aging of existing delinquencies as accounts migrated to later stages of stress. CreditAccess Grameen is a leading Indian microfinance institution headquartered in Bengaluru, focused on providing micro-loans to women customers predominantly in rural areas across India. The company had reported 32.38% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 125.81 crore even as revenue rose by 3.79% to Rs 1508.35 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip shed 0.85% to currently trade at Rs 1318.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CreditAccessGrameenLtd_17343154102_37419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CMS Info Systems climbs on Rs 1,000 crore SBI ATM contract win]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cms-info-systems-climbs-on-rs-1000-crore-sbi-atm-contract-win/1663570</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663570</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, CMS said the 10-year contract covers around 5,000 bank-owned ATMs across India and is the first direct large-scale cash outsourcing mandate awarded by a public sector bank.

In a regulatory filing, CMS said the 10-year contract covers around 5,000 bank-owned ATMs across India and is the first direct large-scale cash outsourcing mandate awarded by a public sector bank. The project, which goes live in January 2026, will include managed services aimed at improving cash efficiency and enhancing ATM uptime. The company said the contract is expected to contribute incremental revenue of around Rs 500 crore over its tenure. CMS added that the win reflects a growing preference among banks for integrated outsourcing solutions and further strengthens its long-standing relationship with SBI. CMS Info Systems provides cash logistics, managed services and technology solutions to banks, financial institutions, organised retail and e-commerce companies across India. On a consolidated basis, net profit of CMS Info Systems declined 19.32% to Rs 73.35 crore while net sales declined 2.55% to Rs 608.62 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/cms-info-systems_80678221_44662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Royal Orchid Hotels inks Regenta Suites & Residences in Jaipur]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/royal-orchid-hotels-inks-regenta-suites-residences-in-jaipur/1663569</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663569</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The hotel will be operated under a hotel management agreement, strengthening the company’s asset-light expansion strategy and reinforcing its presence in key urban and leisure-driven destinations.

The hotel will be operated under a hotel management agreement, strengthening the company’s asset-light expansion strategy and reinforcing its presence in key urban and leisure-driven destinations. Designed in a suites-and-residences format, the property will cater to long-stay guests, business travellers, and families seeking spacious accommodations with enhanced comfort and convenience. Regenta Suites & Residences Jaipur is being developed by SSBC Group, owned by Madan Lal Yadav, and is strategically positioned to offer seamless access to Jaipur’s commercial hubs, lifestyle districts, and cultural landmarks. The hotel is expected to open by April 2026, adding a contemporary hospitality offering to the Pink City under the trusted Regenta brand. Chander K. Baljee, chairman & managing director, Royal Orchid & Regenta Hotels, said “Jaipur continues to be a strong market for us, driven by consistent demand across business, leisure, and extended-stay segments. The signing of Regenta Suites & Residences Jaipur aligns perfectly with our growth strategy and brand promise of delivering comfort-led hospitality in prime city locations.” Madan Lal Yadav, Owner, SSBC Group, said, “We are pleased to partner with Royal Orchid & Regenta Hotels for this project. Their operational expertise and strong brand equity make them the right partner to bring a modern suites and residences hotel to Jaipur. We look forward to creating a preferred address for discerning travellers in the city.” Royal Orchid Hotels operates and manages hotels/resorts and provides related services through its portfolio of hotel properties. The company’s consolidated net profit dropped 42.9% to Rs 4.28 crore on a 12.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 79.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Royal Orchid Hotels rose 0.85% to currently trade at Rs 402.23 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RoyalOrchHotel_11218221105_22048.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kalyan Jewellers rallies after revenue jumps 42% YoY in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kalyan-jewellers-rallies-after-revenue-jumps-42-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663568</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663568</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s India operations witnessed revenue growth of approximately 42% during Q3 FY26 as compared to Q3 FY25, driven primarily by strong festive demand.

The company’s India operations witnessed revenue growth of approximately 42% during Q3 FY26 as compared to Q3 FY25, driven primarily by strong festive demand. Demand after Diwali remained resilient despite volatility in gold prices, with growth broad-based across both plain gold and studded jewellery segments. The quarter recorded healthy same-store-sales-growth of approximately 27%. International operations recorded revenue growth of approximately 36% YoY during the quarter. In the Middle East, revenue rose approximately 28% in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25, largely driven by strong same-store sales growth. International markets contributed approximately 11% to the company’s consolidated revenue during the quarter. The company’s digital-first jewellery platform, Candere, recorded a revenue growth of approximately 147% during the quarter as compared to the same period during the last year. During the quarter, the company launched 21 Kalyan showroom. Headquartered in Thrissur in the state of Kerala, Kalyan Jewellers is one of the largest jewellery retailers in India with a presence in the Middle East and the US. As of December 31, 2025, the company’s total number of showrooms across India and international markets stood at 469 (Kalyan India – 318, Kalyan Middle East – 38, Kalyan USA – 2, Kalyan UK – 1, Candere – 110).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KalyanJewellersIndia_46056464.1248805_42402.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-counter/1663566</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663566</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Concord Biotech Ltd, Godrej Consumer Products Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, Tata Technologies Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 07 January 2026.

Concord Biotech Ltd, Godrej Consumer Products Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, Tata Technologies Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 07 January 2026. SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd witnessed volume of 4.56 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 18.92 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 24082 shares. The stock increased 0.63% to Rs.2,108.00. Volumes stood at 1.32 lakh shares in the last session. Concord Biotech Ltd saw volume of 26483 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7.61 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3478 shares. The stock increased 2.64% to Rs.1,390.45. Volumes stood at 8977 shares in the last session. Godrej Consumer Products Ltd clocked volume of 1.25 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.77 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 18539 shares. The stock lost 0.39% to Rs.1,248.80. Volumes stood at 11492 shares in the last session. Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd notched up volume of 8.52 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.76 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.26 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.23% to Rs.521.80. Volumes stood at 1.39 lakh shares in the last session. Tata Technologies Ltd recorded volume of 2.48 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.93 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 41874 shares. The stock gained 4.78% to Rs.679.90. Volumes stood at 50107 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SBILifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_43034021988_22045.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Titan Company jumps after strong Q3 FY26 business update]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/titan-company-jumps-after-strong-q3-fy26-business-update/1663565</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663565</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s domestic consumer businesses recorded around 40% year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26, with jewellery emerging as the biggest contributor.

The company’s domestic consumer businesses recorded around 40% year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26, with jewellery emerging as the biggest contributor. The jewellery portfolio posted about 41% YoY growth, supported by strong wedding and festive demand and improved performance across gold studded jewellery and gold coins. Like-to-like growth across jewellery retail formats stood in the low-thirties. During the quarter, Titan added a net 47 jewellery stores in India across Tanishq, Mia, Zoya, CaratLane and the newly launched lab-grown diamond brand beYon. The watches division reported around 13% YoY growth, led by analog watches, which benefited from premiumisation trends and festive demand. The Titan brand recorded double-digit growth, while Sonata and Fastrack also posted strong value growth. Smartwatches, however, declined around 26% YoY due to lower volumes. The division added 22 net new stores during the quarter. Titan EyeCare delivered approximately 16% YoY growth, aided by strong demand for international brands, sunglasses and prescription lenses, along with rising e-commerce contribution. As part of network optimisation, the division opened 11 new stores, renovated 20 stores and closed 30 stores during the quarter. Emerging businesses showed a mixed performance. Fragrances grew about 22% YoY, while women’s bags surged 111% YoY on strong volume growth. Taneira reported a decline of around 6% YoY as lower volumes offset higher average selling prices. The company added two Irth stores during the quarter in Delhi and Kolkata. International businesses posted strong growth of nearly 80% YoY, led by jewellery brands across GCC countries, Singapore and North America. During the quarter, Tanishq opened two new stores in the US, located in Boston and Orlando. Titan added a total of 56 net stores during Q3 FY26, taking its overall retail network to 3,433 stores as of December 2025. The company said the quarterly numbers are provisional and subject to limited review by its statutory auditors. Titan is India's leading lifestyle company. It ha established leading positions in the jewellery, watches and eyecare categories. It has also diversified into wearables, indian dress wear and fragrances & fashion accessories. Titan Company's consolidated revenue jumped 28.5% year-on-year to Rs 18,837 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 14,656 crore in Q2 FY25, driven by festive-led jewellery demand, robust international expansion, and double-digit growth across segments. Its profit after tax (PAT) surged 59% YoY to Rs 1,120 crore, translating to a PAT margin of 6.8%, up 163 basis points from the prior year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TitanCompany_20146423894_1016.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jubilant FoodWorks reports 13% YoY revenue growth in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jubilant-foodworks-reports-13-yoy-revenue-growth-in-q3-fy26/1663564</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663564</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s standalone revenue from operations advanced 11.8% YoY to Rs 1,801.5 crore in Q3 FY26.

The company’s standalone revenue from operations advanced 11.8% YoY to Rs 1,801.5 crore in Q3 FY26. The firm added that Domino’s India like-for-like (LFL) growth came in at 5%, while Domino’s Turkey LFL growth (post Ind AS 29) was a positive 6.3%. As of the quarter’s end, the JFL Group network reached 3,594 stores, with a net addition of 114 stores during the quarter. Domino’s India opened 75 net new stores, ending the quarter with 2,396 stores, while Domino’s Turkey opened 15 new stores, ending the quarter with 783 stores. Jubilant FoodWorks is part of the Jubilant Bhartia Group and is among India’s leading food service companies. The company holds the master franchise exclusive rights for international brands such as Domino’s, Dunkin', and Popeye’s to develop and operate restaurants. The company reported a 190.4% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 186.03 crore on a 19.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2,340.15 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Q2 FY25. Shares of Jubilant FoodWorks shed 0.78% to Rs 541.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JubilantFood_44171671816_14548.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index largely unmoved; Focus shifts to US non farms data]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-largely-unmoved-focus-shifts-to-us-non-farms-data/1663561</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663561</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index is staying largely unmoved around 98 mark as safe haven demand amid geopolitical tensions are seen offset by expectations of larger than expected Federal rate cuts.

The dollar index is staying largely unmoved around 98 mark as safe haven demand amid geopolitical tensions are seen offset by expectations of larger than expected Federal rate cuts. Latest data from the Institute for Supply Management on Monday showed its reading on U.S. manufacturing activity unexpectedly decreased in the month of December. ISM said its manufacturing PMI edged down to 47.9 in December after slipping to 48.2 in November. With the unexpected dip, the manufacturing PMI dropped to its lowest reading of 2025. Focus now shifts to US ISM Services Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) report that will be published later today and US December employment report on Friday for further cues on interest rates. Meanwhile, Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran is reportedly calling for aggressive rate cuts exceeding 100 basis points in 2026, arguing that current monetary policy remains restrictive and is holding back economic growth. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 98.30, almost flat on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[A B Infrabuild gains after bagging orders worth Rs 62 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/a-b-infrabuild-gains-after-bagging-orders-worth-rs-62-crore/1663563</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663563</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the company received an order worth Rs 51.43 crore from East Coast Railways, Indian Railways.

According to an exchange filing, the company received an order worth Rs 51.43 crore from East Coast Railways, Indian Railways. The order involves the construction of a road over bridge (ROB) comprising a 36-metre composite girder, two 24-metre composite girders, and four 18.75-metre T-beam girders at km 655/25–27, in lieu of Level Crossing No. 353, between Mandasa and Baruva railway stations on the Howrah–Visakhapatnam main line under the Khurda Road division. The project is to be executed within 24 months. The company also secured another order worth Rs 10.75 crore from the Madhya Pradesh Road Development Corporation (MPRDC). The project involves the construction of additional lanes to be used as truck parking and lay-bys in the Sohagi Ghat stretch on the Mangawan to MP–UP border section of NH-30 in Madhya Pradesh, to be executed on an EPC basis. The project is scheduled for completion within nine months. A B Infrabuild clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entities, and both contracts do not qualify as related-party transactions under applicable regulatory norms. A B Infrabuild engaged in construction, alter, improve, maintain, enlarge, pull down, remove, replace and develop, work, manage, and roads, railways, branches and sidings, bridges; and other constructions related to civil works. The company’s standalone net profit tumbled 43.6% to Rs 2.11 crore, while revenue from operations declined 21% to Rs 37.30 crore in Q2 FY26 compared to Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABInfrabuild_38628776_73120.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI invites public comments on draft rules for dividend payout by banks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-invites-public-comments-on-draft-rules-for-dividend-payout-by-banks/1663552</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663552</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has invited public comments on the draft "Reserve Bank of India (Prudential Norms on Dividend and Remittance of Profit) Directions, 2026", proposing a revised framework for declaration of dividends and remittance of profits by banks.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has invited public comments on the draft "Reserve Bank of India (Prudential Norms on Dividend and Remittance of Profit) Directions, 2026", proposing a revised framework for declaration of dividends and remittance of profits by banks. The central bank had undertaken a review of the existing guidelines on prudential norms governing declaration of dividend and remittance of profits by foreign banks operating in branch mode in India. Accordingly, a draft of the revised framework was earlier issued for public comments on January 2, 2024. RBI has now issued fresh draft Directions proposing a new methodology for computing the maximum eligible dividend payout. These draft Directions have been placed in the public domain for comments. RBI noted that under the draft Directions for commercial banks, a bank will be eligible to declare dividends or remit profits only if it meets certain prudential requirements. These include compliance with applicable regulatory capital requirements at the end of the previous financial year and continued compliance during the year in which the dividend is proposed. The regulatory capital should not fall below the prescribed requirement even after the dividend payout. Further, banks incorporated in India must have positive adjusted Profit After Tax (PAT) for the period for which the dividend is proposed, while foreign banks operating in branch mode must have positive PAT for the period for which profits are proposed to be remitted. Similar prudential conditions have been proposed for Small Finance Banks, Payment Banks, Regional Rural Banks and Local Area Banks. These banks must comply with regulatory capital requirements before and after dividend payment, have positive adjusted PAT for the relevant financial year, and should not be under any explicit restriction on dividend declaration from the RBI or any other authority.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IRB Infra receives NHAI LoA for NH-16 project in Odisha]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/irb-infra-receives-nhai-loa-for-nh-16-project-in-odisha/1663551</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663551</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the concession, IRB Infrastructure Trust will pay an upfront concession fee of Rs 3,087 crore to NHAI for a revenue-linked concession period of 20 years.

Under the concession, IRB Infrastructure Trust will pay an upfront concession fee of Rs 3,087 crore to NHAI for a revenue-linked concession period of 20 years. The project forms part of NHAI’s asset monetization program and marks IRB’s entry into Odisha. The LoA covers a 74.5-km stretch of the Chandikhole–Bhadrak corridor, part of the government’s Golden Quadrilateral Project. Virendra D. Mhaiskar, chairman & managing director of IRB Infrastructure Developers, said, “This award places us on a fast track to building an asset portfolio of Rs 1 lakh crore in the near future, the largest by any private toll road developer in India. The addition of TOT-17 and TOT-18 together will enhance the toll revenues by about Rs 1,000 crore in FY27.” IRB Infrastructure Developers is India’s first integrated multinational transport infrastructure developer in the roads & highways segment. As the largest integrated private toll road and highway infrastructure developer in India, IRB has an asset base of approx. Rs 94,000 crore in 13 states across the parent company and two InvITs. The company reported a 41% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.82 crore on a 10.42% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 1,751.02 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of IRB Infrastructure Developers rose 0.86% to Rs 42.24 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IRBInfraDevl_42061995161_28365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade with minor cuts; private bank shares decline for 3rd day in row]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-minor-cuts-private-bank-shares-decline-for-3rd-day-in-row/1663550</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663550</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in the in the morning trade as geopolitical tensions and tariff-related concerns tempered optimism over the earnings outlook, keeping the Sensex and Nifty just shy of record highs.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in the in the morning trade as geopolitical tensions and tariff-related concerns tempered optimism over the earnings outlook, keeping the Sensex and Nifty just shy of record highs. The Nifty traded below the 26,150 mark, while private bank shares extended losses for a third consecutive session. At 10:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 160.13 points or 0.18% to 84,881.44. The Nifty 50 index fell 22.50 points or 0.09% to 26,156.20. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.30% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.04%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,946 shares rose and 1,673 shares fell. A total of 215 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Private Bank index fell 0.35% to 28,780. The index declined 0.42% in the three consecutive trading session. RBL Bank (down 1.95%), HDFC Bank (down 1.11%), Federal Bank (down 0.82%), IndusInd Bank (down 0.75%) and Kotak Mahindra Bank (down 0.7%), Bandhan Bank (down 0.66%), Axis Bank (down 0.51%) declined. On the other hand, Yes Bank (up 1.05%), IDFC First Bank (up 0.94%) and ICICI Bank (up 0.13%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing rose 1.22% after the company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Innomech Aerospace Toolings, has secured an order worth Rs 72.20 crore from Nuclear Power Corporation of India (NPCIL). Senco Gold surged 11.88% after the company reported a 51% revenue growth in Q3 FY26, driven by robust performances across its businesses. The retail business reported around 49% growth while SSSG growth stood at 39%. Godrej Consumer Products shed 0.69%. The company said that its standalone business is well positioned to deliver double-digit revenue growth for the quarter, underpinned by close to double-digit underlying volume growth (UVG), albeit on a supportive comparator. Personal Care is expected to record mid-single-digit value growth, driven by a marked recovery in the soaps category.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas MF announces IDCW & Monthly Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baroda-bnp-paribas-mf-announces-idcw-monthly-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1663548</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663548</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 08 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme.

Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 08 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme. The amount IDCW (Rs. per unit) will be: Baroda BNP Paribas Arbitrage Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option & Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs. 0.06 each

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Senco Gold surges on strong Q3 FY26 business update]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/senco-gold-surges-on-strong-q3-fy26-business-update/1663532</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663532</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The strong Q3 performance was supported by around 49% growth in the retail business and same-store sales growth (SSSG) of approximately 39%.

The strong Q3 performance was supported by around 49% growth in the retail business and same-store sales growth (SSSG) of approximately 39%. Diamond jewellery sales also maintained strong momentum, recording nearly 36% year-on-year growth during the quarter. The company has launched 4 new franchise showrooms in Q3 FY26, taking the total showroom network to 196 (inclusive of 8 Sennes and 2 international showrooms). The newly launched franchise stores are located in Hazaribagh (Jharkhand), Etawah (Uttar Pradesh), Burdwan (West Bengal) and Bikaner (Rajasthan). On outlook front, the company is prepared for the upcoming Q4 wedding season, Valentine's Day and International Women's Day, and other local festivals and targeting growth in the studded category through curated collections with between 18% to 20% growth. The company remains firmly on course to meet its annual target of 20 new showroom openings for FY26. It plans to launch another 3 to 4 showrooms under the COCO and FOCO models to achieve the milestone of 200 showrooms and have a robust pipeline for H1 next year. Backed by a 31% YoY growth in the first nine months, the company remains confident of delivering over 25% YoY growth in FY26. Senco Gold is a leading pan-India jewellery retailer. It offers an extensive range of jewellery, including gold, diamond, Polki, Platinum, Kundan, Jadau, silver, as well as precious and semi-precious stones. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 302.5% to Rs 48.78 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 12.12 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales rose 2.4% YoY to Rs 1,536.12 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Senco-Gold-Ltd_73495169_33975.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Panorama Studios International jumps on Rs 100 crore Malayalam film deal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/panorama-studios-international-jumps-on-rs-100-crore-malayalam-film-deal/1663531</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663531</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said it has signed Nivin Pauly for a slate of Malayalam feature films, marking a first-of-its-kind multi-film deal in the Malayalam film industry.

In a regulatory filing, the company said it has signed Nivin Pauly for a slate of Malayalam feature films, marking a first-of-its-kind multi-film deal in the Malayalam film industry. The films will be produced by Kumar Mangat Pathak and Abhishek Pathak for Panorama Studios, with Nivin Pauly also serving as producer. The proposed slate will span multiple genres and is aimed at audiences across India and international markets. The company said the collaboration aligns with its strategy of expanding its footprint in regional cinema while focusing on content-driven and commercially viable projects. Panorama Studios has produced and distributed several successful Hindi films, including Omkara, Pyaar Ka Punchnama, Drishyam, Raid and Shaitaan, and is currently working on Drishyam 3. The company said the new partnership is expected to strengthen its presence in the southern film industry, particularly Malayalam cinema. Panorama Studios International is one of India’s leading film production and distribution houses. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Panorama Studios International declined 66.06% to Rs 2.04 crore while net sales declined 5.21% to Rs 77.86 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PanoramaStudiosIntl.Ltd._22125612_67074.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/motilal-oswal-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1663547</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663547</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 07 January 2026.

Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 07 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Proposed Motilal Oswal Balanced Advantage Fund Mr. Niket Shah Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar Mr. Niket Shah Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar Mr. Sandeep Jain Motilal Oswal Large and Midcap Fund Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar Mr. Sandeep Jain

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Unimech Aerospace rises after bagging Rs 72.20-cr NPCIL order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/unimech-aerospace-rises-after-bagging-rs-7220-cr-npcil-order/1663513</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663513</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the supply and delivery of support equipment for Tarapur Atomic Power Station Units-3 and 4.

The order involves the supply and delivery of support equipment for Tarapur Atomic Power Station Units-3 and 4. The project will be executed through staggered deliveries, with completion scheduled up to December 2028. Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing is a precision engineering company engaged in the design, manufacture, and supply of critical parts and components, including aero tooling, ground support equipment, electro-mechanical sub-assemblies, and related products. Its offerings cater to the aerospace, defence, energy, and semiconductor industries. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 13.2% to Rs 15.67 crore despite a 0.9% jump in net sales to Rs 61.98 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnimechAerospaceandManufacturingLtd_69486914_93631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drift lower in early trade; VIX jumps 1.89%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drift-lower-in-early-trade-vix-jumps-189/1663486</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663486</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices trade with minor losses in early trade, declining for third day in a row.

The domestic equity indices trade with minor losses in early trade, declining for third day in a row. The Nifty traded below the 26,150 mark. Consumer durables, IT and metal shares advanced while realty, private bank and media shares declined. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 172.11 points or 0.21% to 84,871.04. The Nifty 50 index fell 57.80 points or 0.22% to 26,120.90. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.20% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.09%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 1,656 shares rose and 1,275 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 1.24% to 10.14. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 107.63 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,749.35 crore in the Indian equity market on 06 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Titan Company added 3.71% after the company’s consumer business registered a growth of 40% YoY in Q3FY26. A total of 56 stores (net) were added during the quarter expanding Titan’s combined retail network presence to 3,433 stores. Lodha Developer added 1.06% after the company’s pre sales jumped 25% to Rs 56,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 45,100 crore in Q3 FY25. Collections declined 17% YoY to Rs 35,600 crore in Q3 FY26. Jubilant Foodworks shed 0.41%. The company’s consolidated revenue stood at Rs 2,438.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 13.4% YoY. Domino’s recorded a Like-For-Like (LFL) growth of 5%. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.29% to 6.631 compared with previous session close of 6.633. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1950 compared with its close of 90.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.22% to Rs 138,780. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.08% to 98.52. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.38% to 4.164. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 57 cents or 0.94% to $60.13 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian market traded mixed, with regional defense stocks snapping two-day winning streak on Wednesday, as investors continued to assess geopolitical risks after the U.S. attack on Venezuela and renewed rhetoric over Greenland. White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt reportedly said on Tuesday that President Donald Trump and his team were considering “a range of options” in order to acquire Greenland — including “utilizing the U.S. Military.” The statement further escalates the Trump administration’s already aggressive rhetoric about Greenland, which the president has long sought to make a part of the United States. U.S. crude futures fell 1.3% to $56.39 per barrel after U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro. Overnight in the United States, stocks advanced as investors appeared to look past the Venezuela operation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Titan Company Ltd Spikes 2.55%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/titan-company-ltd-spikes-255/1663484</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663484</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Titan Company Ltd rose 2.55% today to trade at Rs 4215.8.

Titan Company Ltd rose 2.55% today to trade at Rs 4215.8. The BSE Consumer Durables index is up 0.62% to quote at 61885.4. The index is up 3.36 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd increased 1.34% and PG Electroplast Ltd added 0.5% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went down 5.28 % over last one year compared to the 8.21% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Titan Company Ltd has added 11.97% over last one month compared to 3.36% gain in BSE Consumer Durables index and 0.57% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 8570 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 27946 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 4264.8 on 07 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 2947.55 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TitanCompany_20146423894_1016.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>