<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:16:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures edge close to 122 mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-edge-close-to-122-mark/1665727</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665727</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures added 0.10% to end at 90.96.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures added 0.10% to end at 90.96. GBP/INR gained 0.18% to 121.99 while EUR/INR climbed 0.22% to 105.83. JPY/INR gained 0.43% to end at 57.85.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee worse-run continues]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-worse-run-continues/1665728</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665728</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.960090.9600 per Dollar on Monday (19 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.8325 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR slumps briefly beyond Rs 91 /$ mark during intraday moves, Recovers after IMF lifts India FY26 growth forecast]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-slumps-briefly-beyond-rs-91-mark-during-intraday-moves-recovers-after-imf-lifts-india-fy26-growth-forecast/1665682</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665682</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee slumped past RS 91 per dollar mark on Monday amid renewed concerns over global trade uncertainties accelerated foreign fund withdrawal.

Indian rupee slumped past RS 91 per dollar mark on Monday amid renewed concerns over global trade uncertainties accelerated foreign fund withdrawal. Investors were also concerned after US President Donald Trump announced tariffs on European countries if they resisted his plan to control Greenland. Weaker greenback and lower crude oil prices also failed to support the counter. Rupee opened at Rs 90.68 and fell to a low of 91.01 before recovering slightly to end at 90.90. Recovery in INR came after the International Monetary Fund (IMF) raised India's GDP growth forecast for FY26 by 70 basis points to 7.3 percent, citing strong momentum in the third quarter. The benchmark BSE Sensex hit an intraday low of 82,898.31 before recovering significant ground to close at 83,246.18, down 324.17 points, or 0.39 percent, from its previous close. The broader NSE Nifty index ended down 108.85 points, or 0.42 percent, at 25,585.50, after having hit a low of 25494.35 in intraday trade.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper up around half a percent, equities moslty weak]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-up-around-half-a-percent-equities-moslty-weak/1665681</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665681</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures rebounded from one-week low as China’s economic growth in 2025 met the government’s target, with annual GDP expanding 5% year-on-year.

COMEX Copper futures rebounded from one-week low as China’s economic growth in 2025 met the government’s target, with annual GDP expanding 5% year-on-year. This pushed the metal above $5.90 per pound but the counter eased from these highs amid mostly weak equities. Shanghai Composite index added 0.29% while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index lost 1%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index shed 0.65%, falling for third straight session. European stocks fell amid rising tensions between the US and Europe over Greenland. German DAX lost more than 1%. Copper futures currently quote at $5.86 per pound, up half a percent on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty slip as global cues sour and heavyweight earnings disappoint]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-slip-as-global-cues-sour-and-heavyweight-earnings-disappoint/1665678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665678</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Equity benchmarks closed lower on Monday as investor sentiment turned cautious amid renewed global trade tensions and disappointing earnings from index heavyweights.

Equity benchmarks closed lower on Monday as investor sentiment turned cautious amid renewed global trade tensions and disappointing earnings from index heavyweights. The Nifty slipping below the 25,600 mark, dragged by energy stocks. Traders were unsettled after US President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on eight European countries over their opposition to his Greenland bid, raising fears of an escalation in global trade wars and triggering volatility across global markets. Sentiment was further dented by uncertainty over the next US Federal Reserve chair after Trump signalled Kevin Hassett may continue in his current role, tempering expectations of aggressive rate cuts in 2026. Back home, persistent foreign institutional selling weighed on sentiment, with FIIs remaining net sellers for a ninth straight session. Market mood was further hit by weak December-quarter earnings. Wipro's subdued outlook for the March quarter added to the caution. ICICI Bank also came under pressure after reporting higher-than-expected provisions for bad loans. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 324.17 points or 0.39% to 83,246.18. The Nifty 50 index declined 108.85 points or 0.42% to 25,585.50. Wipro (down 7.95%), Reliance Industries (down 3.04%) and ICICI Bank (down 2.26%) were major Nifty drags today. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.43% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index lost 1.28%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,226 shares rose and 3,075 shares fell. A total of 191 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 4% to 11.83. Economy: The International Monetary Fund (IMF) on Monday raised its economic growth forecast for India for the 2025-26 financial year, citing stronger-than-expected momentum in recent quarters. IMF has revised India's GDP growth estimate for FY26 upward by 0.7% to 7.3%, reflecting a better-than-anticipated performance in the third quarter and sustained strength heading into the fourth. However, the IMF expects growth to ease to 6.4% in 2026 and 2027 as temporary and cyclical factors supporting the economy begin to wane. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.07% to 6.683 compared with previous session close of 6.678. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9200 compared with its close of 90.7875 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 1.81% to Rs 145,102. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.21% to 99.18. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.54% to 4.256. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement fell 77 cents or 1.20% to $63.36 a barrel. Global Markets: European indices traded lower Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened economic sanctions on a number of countries in the region if they oppose his plans to acquire Greenland. The December Eurozone annual CPI figure is expected to be 2.0%, hitting the European Central Bank’s target for the first time since mid-2025, down from 2.1% in November. Most Asian indices ended lower on Monday as investors assessed threats from the Trump administration toward Greenland over the weekend, as well as key economic data from China out Monday. Over the weekend, U.S. President Donald Trump and European leaders exchanged tense rhetoric over the Arctic territory, with Trump threatening tariffs on eight European countries and demanding control of Greenland, which is part of Denmark. European leaders responded by calling the threats "completely wrong" and "unacceptable." In Asia, China released its fourth-quarter GDP numbers, along with December figures for retail sales, urban investment and industrial output. China’s economic growth slowed to its weakest pace in nearly three years in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, though full-year growth matched Beijing’s target despite growing trade frictions with the U.S. and a prolonged real estate slump. Gross domestic product grew 4.5% in the October-to-December period, data from the National Statistics Bureau showed Monday. That marked a slowdown from 4.8% in the third quarter and was the weakest reading since the first quarter of 2023, when growth also came in at 4.5%. The full-year economic output came in at 5%, meeting the official target of around 5%. On Friday in the U.S., the S&P 500 ended just below the flatline and posted a losing week, while the Nasdaq Composite also inched down 0.06%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.17%. The three major indexes hit their session lows after Trump said in the White House on Friday that he’d rather have National Economic Council Director Kevin Hassett stay in his current role and that he might not be chosen to become the next U.S. Fed chair. Hassett has been seen as the more market-friendly option to replace current Fed chair than the new frontrunner nominee, former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, and is expected to be more willing to keep rates low. New Listing: Shares of Bharat Coking Coal ended at Rs 40.66 on the BSE, a premium of 76.78% compared with the issue price of Rs 23. The stock debuted at Rs 45.21, a premium of 96.57% to the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 45.21 and a low of 40.13. On the BSE, 11.97 crore shares of the company were traded in the counter. Stocks in Spotlight: Wipro tumbled 7.95% after the company reported a 3.92% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,119 crore despite a 3.78% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 23,555.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Looking ahead, the company said that it expects revenue from IT Services business segment to be in the range of $2,635 million to $2,688 million. This translates to sequential guidance of 0% to 2.0% in constant currency terms. Reliance Industries (RIL) slipped 3.04% after the company reported a 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on a 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ICICI Bank slipped 2.26% after the bank reported a 4.02% fall in standalone net profit to Rs 11,318 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 11,792 crore in Q3 FY25. Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26. Net interest margin was 4.30% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.25% in Q3 FY25. Provisions (excluding provision for tax) were Rs 2,556 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 1,227 crore in Q3 FY25. HDFC Bank shed 0.38%. The company reported an 11.46% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 18,563.75 crore on a 2.91% increase in total income to Rs 90,005 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) shed 0.94%. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 189.82% to Rs 403.42 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 134.70 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 16.43% year-on-year to Rs 8,473.10 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Mahindra EPC Irrigation shed 0.92%. The company reported consolidated net profit rose 2.20% to Rs 6.49 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 6.35 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rallied 14.75% to Rs 93.47 crore in Q3 FY26, against Rs 81.45 crore posted in the same quarter last year. Hatsun Agro Product rose 2.92% after the company reported a steady set of numbers for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, revenue from operations increased 17.6% YoY to Rs 2,363.72 crore, compared with Rs 2,009.75 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue declined 2.6% QoQ from Rs 2,427.59 crore in the September quarter. Profit after tax (PAT) rose 48% YoY to Rs 60.58 crore, compared with Rs 40.94 crore in the same quarter last year. On a sequential basis, PAT declined 44.70% from Rs 109.54 crore in Q2 FY26. Polycab India climbed 3.98% after the company reported a solid top-line performance for Q3 FY26. Revenue from operations surged 46% YoY and 18% QoQ to Rs 7,636.1 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 5,226.1 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 6,477.2 crore in Q2 FY26. Net profit declined 9% QoQ but rose 36% YoY to Rs 630.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 693 crore in Q2 FY26 and Rs 464.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Nureca jumped 4.90% after net profit stood at Rs 3.73 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 2.80 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, PAT rose 2.8% from Rs 3.63 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations jumped 49.8% YoY to Rs 39.64 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 26.46 crore a year ago. Sequentially, revenue increased 5.0% from Rs 37.74 crore in Q2 FY26. JK Cement declined 1.59% after the company reported an 8.56% tumble in consolidated net profit to Rs 173.61 crore as against Rs 189.87 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 18.18% to Rs 3,463.07 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,930.28 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Netweb Technologies India rose 1.58% after the company’s standalone net profit soared 146.7% to Rs 73.31 crore on a 141% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 804.92 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JB Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals gained 0.75%. The company reported a 21.79% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 197.89 crore, supported by a 10.51% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,064.72 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at discount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-discount/1665671</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665671</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,574, a discount of 11.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,585.50 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,574, a discount of 11.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,585.50 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index declined 108.85 points or 0.42% to 25,585.50. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 4% to 11.83. HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank and Reliance Industries were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Polycab India jumps after strong Q3 revenue growth]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/polycab-india-jumps-after-strong-q3-revenue-growth/1665668</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665668</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations surged 46% YoY and 18% QoQ to Rs 7,636.1 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 5,226.1 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 6,477.2 crore in Q2 FY26.

Revenue from operations surged 46% YoY and 18% QoQ to Rs 7,636.1 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 5,226.1 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 6,477.2 crore in Q2 FY26. The strong growth was driven by robust execution in Wires & Cables (W&C) business, supported by healthy growth momentum in Fast-Moving Electrical Goods (FMEG) business. The W&C segment delivered 53% YoY growth for the quarter, driven by exceptional domestic performance with 59% growth, supported by robust demand and sustained commodity price inflation. The FMEG segment demonstrated continued momentum, recording 17% YoY growth in the quarter. The EPC business reported revenues of Rs 406.9 crore, a 4% YoY increase. Net profit declined 9% QoQ but rose 36% YoY to Rs 630.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 693 crore in Q2 FY26 and Rs 464.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 842 crore in Q3 FY26, down 9% QoQ and up 37% YoY. EBITDA came in at Rs 966 crore in Q3 FY26, down 5% QoQ but up 34% YoY, while EBITDA margin slipped to 12.7% from 15.8% in Q2 FY26 and 13.8% in Q3 FY25. Total operating expenses increased 24.3% QoQ and 46.4% YoY to Rs 915 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 736 crore in Q2 FY26 and Rs 625 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee costs rose 2.8% QoQ and 19.2% YoY to Rs 237 crore, while other operating expenses jumped 34.3% QoQ and 59.0% YoY to Rs 678 crore. Finance costs increased 42.6% QoQ and 38.6% YoY to Rs 69 crore, while depreciation rose 9.5% QoQ and 34.9% YoY to Rs 106 crore during the quarter. Polycab India is India's largest manufacturer of wires and cables and one of the fastest growing FMEG companies. Its business operations span across India through 27 manufacturing facilities, 15 offices and 34 warehouses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PolycabIndiaLtd_84608181_26603.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil gives up gains after recent advances]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-gives-up-gains-after-recent-advances/1665666</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665666</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures edged lower below $59 per barrel on Monday, paring gains after a four-week advance as easing geopolitical tensions surrounding Iran diminished immediate supply-side anxieties.

WTI crude oil futures edged lower below $59 per barrel on Monday, paring gains after a four-week advance as easing geopolitical tensions surrounding Iran diminished immediate supply-side anxieties. At the same time, energy markets turned cautious as renewed trade tensions resurfaced, with the announcement of a 10% tariff on goods from eight European countries—potentially rising to 25%—raising concerns over global demand. In domestic trade, MCX crude oil futures for February delivery declined nearly 1% to Rs 5,399 per barrel, while the US dollar index slipped below 99, retreating from recent highs and lending support to safe-haven currencies such as the yen and Swiss franc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices end with modest losses; realty index underperforms; VIX jumps 4% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-end-with-modest-losses-realty-index-underperforms-vix-jumps-4/1665665</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665665</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with moderate losses today, weighed down by renewed concerns over global trade tensions and mixed earnings from index heavyweights.

The key equity benchmarks ended with moderate losses today, weighed down by renewed concerns over global trade tensions and mixed earnings from index heavyweights. Investor sentiment also remained cautious amid global uncertainty after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened to impose tariffs on several European countries following their opposition to his bid to acquire Greenland. The Nifty closed below the 25,600 level. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 324.17 points or 0.39% to 83,246.18. The Nifty 50 index declined 108.85 points or 0.42% to 25,585.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.43% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index lost 1.28%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 4% to 11.83. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty FMCG index (up 0.67%) and the Nifty Auto index (up 0.13%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Realty index (down 1.99%), the Nifty Media index (down 1.84%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 1.56%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: The International Monetary Fund (IMF) on Monday raised its economic growth forecast for India for the 2025–26 financial year, citing stronger-than-expected momentum in recent quarters. IMF has revised India's GDP growth estimate for FY26 upward by 0.7 percentage points to 7.3 percent, reflecting a better-than-anticipated performance in the third quarter and sustained strength heading into the fourth. However, the IMF expects growth to ease to 6.4 percent in 2026 and 2027 as temporary and cyclical factors supporting the economy begin to wane. World Economic Forum: As the World Economic Forum’s Annual Meeting at Davos 2026 begins against the backdrop of global economic challenges, policymakers and business leaders are expected to push for greater dialogue and cooperation. The gathering is likely to set the tone for international collaboration and provide key cues for global markets in the year ahead. The World Economic Forum's annual meeting will take place from January 19 to 23. Several global leaders across fields will share their views on global issues and the way forward. US President Donald Trump is expected to address the World Economic Forum at Davos on Wednesday. According to media reports, his remarks are likely to focus on housing affordability. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.07% to 6.683 compared with previous session close of 6.678. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9200 compared with its close of 90.7875 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 1.81% to Rs 145,102. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.21% to 99.18. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.54% to 4.256. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement fell 77 cents or 1.20% to $63.36 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets traded lower Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened economic sanctions on a number of countries in the region if they oppose his plans to acquire Greenland. The December Eurozone annual CPI figure is expected to be 2.0%, hitting the European Central Bank’s target for the first time since mid-2025, down from 2.1% in November. Asian markets ended lower on Monday as investors assessed threats from the Trump administration toward Greenland over the weekend, as well as key economic data from China out Monday. Over the weekend, U.S. President Donald Trump and European leaders exchanged tense rhetoric over the Arctic territory, with Trump threatening tariffs on eight European countries and demanding control of Greenland, which is part of Denmark. European leaders responded by calling the threats “completely wrong” and “unacceptable.” In Asia, China released its fourth-quarter GDP numbers, along with December figures for retail sales, urban investment and industrial output. China’s economic growth slowed to its weakest pace in nearly three years in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, though full-year growth matched Beijing’s target despite growing trade frictions with the U.S. and a prolonged real estate slump. Gross domestic product grew 4.5% in the October-to-December period, data from the National Statistics Bureau showed Monday. That marked a slowdown from 4.8% in the third quarter and was the weakest reading since the first quarter of 2023, when growth also came in at 4.5%. The full-year economic output came in at 5%, meeting the official target of around 5%. On Friday in the U.S., the S&P 500 ended just below the flatline and posted a losing week, while the Nasdaq Composite also inched down 0.06%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.17%. The three major indexes hit their session lows after Trump said in the White House on Friday that he’d rather have National Economic Council Director Kevin Hassett stay in his current role and that he might not be chosen to become the next U.S. Fed chair. Hassett has been seen as the more market-friendly option to replace current Fed chair than the new frontrunner nominee, former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, and is expected to be more willing to keep rates low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index registers a drop of 1.99%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-registers-a-drop-of-199/1665663</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665663</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index closed down 1.99% at 836 today.

Nifty Realty index closed down 1.99% at 836 today. The index has lost 6.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Godrej Properties Ltd fell 4.83%, Brigade Enterprises Ltd shed 3.62% and SignatureGlobal India Ltd slipped 2.97%. The Nifty Realty index has decreased 11.00% over last one year compared to the 10.27% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Media index has slid 1.84% and Nifty Infrastructure index is down 0.90% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 0.42% to close at 25585.5 while the SENSEX has declined 0.39% to close at 83246.18 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 324 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,600 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-324-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25600-level/1665661</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665661</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts today, pressured by renewed worries over global trade tensions and mixed earnings from index heavyweights.

The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts today, pressured by renewed worries over global trade tensions and mixed earnings from index heavyweights. Investors are tracking the Q3 earnings season and cues from the World Economic Forum annual meeting. The Nifty settled below the 26,050 mark. Realty, media and oil & gas stocks declined, while FMCG and auto advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 324.17 points or 0.39% to 83,246.18. The Nifty 50 index lost 108.85 points or 0.42% to 25,585.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.43% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 1.28%. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 4% to 11.83. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,229 shares rose and 3,072 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. Economy: The International Monetary Fund (IMF) on Monday raised its economic growth forecast for India for the 2025–26 financial year, citing stronger-than-expected momentum in recent quarters. IMF has revised India's GDP growth estimate for FY26 upward by 0.7 percentage points to 7.3 percent, reflecting a better-than-anticipated performance in the third quarter and sustained strength heading into the fourth. However, the IMF expects growth to ease to 6.4 percent in 2026 and 2027 as temporary and cyclical factors supporting the economy begin to wane. World Economic Forum: As the World Economic Forum’s Annual Meeting at Davos 2026 begins against the backdrop of global economic challenges, policymakers and business leaders are expected to push for greater dialogue and cooperation. The gathering is likely to set the tone for international collaboration and provide key cues for global markets in the year ahead. The World Economic Forum’s Annual Meeting is scheduled to be held from January 19 to 23, 2026. Several global leaders across fields will share their views on global issues and the way forward. US President Donald Trump is expected to address the World Economic Forum at Davos on Wednesday. According to media reports, his remarks are likely to focus on housing affordability. New Listing: Shares of Bharat Coking Coal ended at Rs 40.66 on the BSE, representing a premium of 76.78% as compared with the issue price of Rs 23. The stock debuted at Rs 45.21, marking a premium of 96.57% to the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 45.21 and a low of 40.13. On the BSE, over 1,197.01 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 1.99% to 836. The index rose 0.35% in the past trading session. Godrej Properties (down 4.83%), Brigade Enterprises (down 3.62%), SignatureGlobal India (down 2.97%), Lodha Developers (down 2.51%), Sobha (down 2.23%), Anant Raj (down 1.69%), DLF (down 1.23%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 1.14%), Phoenix Mills (down 0.97%) and Oberoi Realty (down 0.58%) tumbled. Sobha fell 2.26% after the company reported a 28.85% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 154.28 crore on a 22.95% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 943.11 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Stocks in Spotlight: Wipro tumbled 7.95% after the company reported a 3.92% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,119 crore despite a 3.78% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 23,555.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Reliance Industries (RIL) slipped 3.04% after the company reported a 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on a 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) shed 0.94%. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 189.82% to Rs 403.42 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 134.70 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 16.43% year-on-year to Rs 8,473.10 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Mahindra EPC Irrigation shed 0.92%. The company reported consolidated net profit rose 2.20% to Rs 6.49 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 6.35 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rallied 14.75% to Rs 93.47 crore in Q3 FY26, against Rs 81.45 crore posted in the same quarter last year. Nureca jumped 4.90% after net profit stood at Rs 3.73 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 2.80 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, PAT rose 2.8% from Rs 3.63 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations jumped 49.8% YoY to Rs 39.64 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 26.46 crore a year ago. Sequentially, revenue increased 5.0% from Rs 37.74 crore in Q2 FY26. JK Cement declined 1.59% after the company reported an 8.56% tumble in consolidated net profit to Rs 173.61 crore as against Rs 189.87 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 18.18% to Rs 3,463.07 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,930.28 crore posted in Q3 FY25. ICICI Bank slipped 2.26% after the bank reported a 4.02% fall in standalone net profit to Rs 11,318 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 11,792 crore in Q3 FY25. Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26. Net interest margin was 4.30% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.25% in Q3 FY25. HDFC Bank shed 0.38%. The company reported an 11.46% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 18,563.75 crore on a 2.91% increase in total income to Rs 90,005 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Netweb Technologies India rallied 1.58% after the company’s standalone net profit soared 146.7% to Rs 73.31 crore on a 141% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 804.92 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JB Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals gained 0.75%. The company reported a 21.79% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 197.89 crore, supported by a 10.51% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,064.72 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European shares traded lower on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened economic sanctions on a number of countries in the region if they oppose his plans to acquire Greenland. The December Eurozone annual CPI figure is expected to be 2.0%, hitting the European Central Bank’s target for the first time since mid-2025, down from 2.1% in November. Asian markets ended mixed as investors weighed the Trump administration’s threats toward Greenland over the weekend and key economic data released from China on Monday. Over the weekend, U.S. President Donald Trump and European leaders exchanged tense rhetoric over the Arctic territory, with Trump threatening tariffs on eight European countries and demanding control of Greenland, which is part of Denmark. European leaders responded by calling the threats “completely wrong” and “unacceptable.” In Asia, China released its fourth-quarter GDP numbers, along with December figures for retail sales, urban investment, and industrial output. China’s economic growth slowed to its weakest pace in nearly three years in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, though full-year growth matched Beijing’s target despite growing trade frictions with the U.S. and a prolonged real estate slump. Gross domestic product grew 4.5% in the October-to-December period, data from the National Statistics Bureau showed Monday. That marked a slowdown from 4.8% in the third quarter and was the weakest reading since the first quarter of 2023, when growth also came in at 4.5%. The full-year economic output came in at 5%, meeting the official target of around 5%. On Friday in the U.S., the S&P 500 ended just below the flatline and posted a losing week, while the Nasdaq Composite also inched down 0.06%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.17%. The three major indexes hit their session lows after Trump said in the White House on Friday that he’d rather have National Economic Council Director Kevin Hassett stay in his current role and that he might not be chosen to become the next U.S. Fed chair. Hassett has been seen as the more market-friendly option to replace the current Fed chair than the new frontrunner nominee, former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, and is expected to be more willing to keep rates low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IMF raises India GDP growth forecast to 7.3%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/imf-raises-india-gdp-growth-forecast-to-73/1665660</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665660</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund (IMF) on Monday raised its economic growth forecast for India for the 2025–26 financial year, citing stronger-than-expected momentum in recent quarters.

The International Monetary Fund (IMF) on Monday raised its economic growth forecast for India for the 2025–26 financial year, citing stronger-than-expected momentum in recent quarters. IMF has revised India's GDP growth estimate for FY26 upward by 0.7 percentage points to 7.3 per cent, reflecting a better-than-anticipated performance in the third quarter and sustained strength heading into the fourth. However, IMF expects growth to ease to 6.4 per cent in 2026 and 2027 as temporary and cyclical factors supporting the economy begin to wane.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/growth-951606__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JSW Infra climbs after Q3 PAT rises 9% YoY to Rs 365 cr in]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jsw-infra-climbs-after-q3-pat-rises-9-yoy-to-rs-365-cr-in/1665659</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665659</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 59.17% to Rs 439.17 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 59.17% to Rs 439.17 crore during the quarter. Operating EBITDA increased 10% YoY to Rs 644 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 586 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Operating EBITDA margin stood at 47.7% in Q3 FY26. Total cargo handled stood 31.7 milllion tonnes (MT) in Q3 FY26, up 8% YoY. Volume growth was primarily supported by strong performances at the South West Port and Dharamtar Port. Interim operations at the Tuticorin terminal and the JNPA liquid terminal also contributed positively. However, overall growth was partially offset by lower volumes at the Paradip Iron Ore and Coal terminals. In Q3 FY26, cash and cash equivalents stood at Rs 3,455 crore. As previously announced the company has embarked on a growth plan to increase its cargo handling capacity to 400 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) by FY 2030 or earlier, up from the current capacity of 177 MTPA. To achieve this, it has outlined a comprehensive capital expenditure (capex) plan of Rs 30,000 crore. Additionally, the company has earmarked Rs 9,000 crore for expanding its logistics segment. This expansion aims to build on the Navkar acquisition to develop a robust pan-India logistics network. The company is targeting consolidated operating revenue of Rs 5,400 crore and operating EBITDA of Rs 2,600 crore for FY2026. Building on this base, EBITDA is expected to grow by around 15% in FY2027 and nearly double by FY2028. JSW Infrastructure, a part of JSW Group, is the second largest commercial port operator in India in terms of cargo handling capacity. It develops and operates ports and port terminals pursuant to port concessions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JSWInfrastructureLtd_46143694_42944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India stands at cusp of transformative growth in its reinsurance sector]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-stands-at-cusp-of-transformative-growth-in-its-reinsurance-sector/1665652</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665652</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[M.

M. Nagaraju, Secretary, DFS, while addressing the 3rd Edition of the IFSC–IRDAI–GIFT City Global Reinsurance Summit in Mumbai, noted that India stands at the cusp of transformative growth in its reinsurance sector. He opined that Indian insurance sector, an integral part of the financial system, plays a significant role in the economy by providing protection against mortality, property and casualty risks, encouraging savings, and providing long-term funds for infrastructure development and other long-gestation projects. During FY 2024–25, the sector issued 41.84 crore policies, collected premiums of Rs 11.93 lakh crore, paid claims of Rs 8.36 lakh crore, and reported assets under management of Rs 74.44 lakh crore as on 31 March 2025. The total reinsurance market in India stood at Rs 1.12 lakh crore in 2024–25. The government and the insurance regulator have enabled policy frameworks and structural reforms to further growth and insurance accessibility. Foreign Direct Investment in the insurance sector has been raised to 100 per cent, a new reinsurer was registered last year, and the Sabka Bima Sabki Raksha (Amendment of Insurance Laws) Act, 2025 provides for the formation of a Policyholders’ Education and Protection Fund, aligns data protection with the Digital Personal Data Protection Act, 2023, and enhances IRDAI’s regulatory powers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/news-761409__340_insurance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts fall further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-fall-further/1665649</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665649</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 25270 contracts in the data reported through January 13, 2026. This was a weekly drop of 5268 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold hits record high after Trump unveils new Europe tariffs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-hits-record-high-after-trump-unveils-new-europe-tariffs/1665645</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665645</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices vaulted toward the $4,700 per ounce mark in Asian trading on Monday, touching a fresh record as investors scrambled for safe-haven assets following President Donald Trump’s announcement of new tariffs on European countries.

Gold prices vaulted toward the $4,700 per ounce mark in Asian trading on Monday, touching a fresh record as investors scrambled for safe-haven assets following President Donald Trump’s announcement of new tariffs on European countries. Trump said a 10% tariff on goods from eight European nations would take effect from February 1, with the rate potentially rising to 25% by June if no agreement is reached over US control of Greenland. The tariff threat sent the dollar index below 99, retreating from multi-week highs and weakening against traditional safe-haven currencies such as the yen and Swiss franc. Reflecting the global rally, MCX bullion futures for February delivery climbed nearly 2% to Rs 1,45,090 per 10 grams, as gold continued to benefit from a potent mix of geopolitical risk, robust safe-haven demand and strong underlying fundamentals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Wipro Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wipro-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1665643</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665643</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RBL Bank Ltd, Indigo Paints Ltd, Subex Ltd and IDBI Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 January 2026.

RBL Bank Ltd, Indigo Paints Ltd, Subex Ltd and IDBI Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 January 2026. Wipro Ltd tumbled 7.91% to Rs 246.1 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 40.96 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.23 lakh shares in the past one month. RBL Bank Ltd lost 6.47% to Rs 304.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8.96 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5.1 lakh shares in the past one month. Indigo Paints Ltd crashed 6.25% to Rs 1160.9. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2682 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2252 shares in the past one month. Subex Ltd fell 5.96% to Rs 10.25. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.31 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.64 lakh shares in the past one month. IDBI Bank Ltd corrected 5.31% to Rs 99. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 17.71 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10.86 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Wipro_36546468_614.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nureca jumps on strong Q3 turnaround]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nureca-jumps-on-strong-q3-turnaround/1665642</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665642</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net profit stood at Rs 3.73 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 2.80 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net profit stood at Rs 3.73 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 2.80 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, PAT rose 2.8% from Rs 3.63 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations jumped 49.8% YoY to Rs 39.64 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 26.46 crore a year ago. Sequentially, revenue increased 5.0% from Rs 37.74 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 4.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 3.25 crore in the year-ago quarter, and was broadly flat sequentially versus Rs 4.60 crore in Q2 FY26. Total expenditure rose 19.4% YoY to Rs 36.39 crore during the quarter. Employee expenses increased 12.5% YoY to Rs 4.32 crore, while raw material costs surged 158.50% to Rs 10.34 crore from Rs 4.0 crore last year. Interest expense rose 55.56% YoY to Rs 0.28 crore from Rs 0.18 crore, while depreciation eased 7.4% YoY to Rs 0.50 crore. The management stated that the financial performance was primarily driven by enhanced operational efficiencies, improved sourcing strategies, and strengthened manufacturing capabilities. Focused cost optimization, tighter supply chain controls, and productivity improvements enabled better margins, while scalable manufacturing capabilities supported sustainable growth and consistent execution. Nureca continues to operate a digital-first, asset-light model, with over 90% of revenues generated through online channels. The company remains debt-free and maintains a healthy liquidity position. Nureca is a digital healthcare company focused on home healthcare and wellness products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Nureca_23032827.9742104_75228.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jayaswal Neco Industries Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jayaswal-neco-industries-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1665639</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665639</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[S.M.

S.M. Gold Ltd, Krishival Foods Ltd Partly Paidup, Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd and Diligent Media Corporation Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 January 2026. Jayaswal Neco Industries Ltd crashed 9.99% to Rs 78.3 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 12.11 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9.41 lakh shares in the past one month. S.M. Gold Ltd tumbled 9.98% to Rs 16.33. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 76904 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.19 lakh shares in the past one month. Krishival Foods Ltd Partly Paidup lost 9.98% to Rs 108.3. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9764 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1516 shares in the past one month. Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd fell 9.96% to Rs 1070.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 242 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 184 shares in the past one month. Diligent Media Corporation Ltd plummeted 9.73% to Rs 4.08. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.06 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18853 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JayaswalNeco_44936423925_4506.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops over 250 pts; PSU bank shares slide]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-over-250-pts-psu-bank-shares-slide/1665638</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665638</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade. Investors are closely tracking the ongoing Q3 earnings season and developments from the World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting, scheduled from 19 January 2025 to 23 January 2026. The Nifty traded below the 25,650 mark. Auto shares extended losses for the second consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 249.58 points or 0.30% to 83,320.77. The Nifty 50 index lost 92.60 points or 0.36% to 25,602.50. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.59% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 1.22%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,179 shares rose and 3,043 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index declined 0.55% to 8,964.40. The index jumped 4.42% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Punjab National Bank (down 2.79%), Punjab & Sind Bank (down 2.04%), Indian Overseas Bank (down 1.75%), Central Bank of India (down 0.47%), Bank of Baroda (down 0.36%), State Bank of India (down 0.12%), Canara Bank (down 0.12%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was up 0.15% to 6.688 as compared with the previous close of 6.678. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9650 compared with its close of 90.7875 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 1.76% to Rs 1,45,030. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.22% to 99.17. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.38% to 4.249. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 63 cents or 0.98% to $63.50 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Tech Mahindra rose 3.55%. The company reported a 6.07% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,122 crore on a 2.85% increase in net sales to Rs 14,393.2 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. However, as compared with Q3 FY25, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 14.12% while revenue grew 8.34%. RBL Bank declined 7.06% to Rs 301.35 after the company reported a 28% rise in provisions (other than tax) and contingencies to Rs 639 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 500 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>