<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:36:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Newgen Software Technologies Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/newgen-software-technologies-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678915</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678915</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Firstsource Solutions Ltd, Latent View Analytics Ltd, OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd and Le Travenues Technology Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 20 February 2026.

Firstsource Solutions Ltd, Latent View Analytics Ltd, OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd and Le Travenues Technology Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 20 February 2026. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd crashed 8.72% to Rs 567.5 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 21.68 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8.17 lakh shares in the past one month. Firstsource Solutions Ltd lost 5.62% to Rs 242.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2.15 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.01 lakh shares in the past one month. Latent View Analytics Ltd tumbled 4.55% to Rs 368. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 25748 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 79038 shares in the past one month. OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd slipped 4.47% to Rs 1272.55. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 15503 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 48020 shares in the past one month. Le Travenues Technology Ltd pared 4.41% to Rs 188.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 38480 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.9 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewgenSoftwareTechnologiesLtd_46602882106_13722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude eases after hitting highest in six-and-half months]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-eases-after-hitting-highest-in-six-and-half-months/1678914</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678914</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures rose above $67 per barrel in electronic trade on Friday, supported by a sharp fall in US crude inventories and rising geopolitical tensions.

WTI crude oil futures rose above $67 per barrel in electronic trade on Friday, supported by a sharp fall in US crude inventories and rising geopolitical tensions. President Donald Trump said a decision on a potential nuclear agreement with Iran could be made within the next 10 days, while the US expanded its military presence in the Middle East, increasing concerns over possible supply disruptions. Markets are particularly focused on the risk of restricted oil flows through the Strait of Hormuz, a key route for global crude exports. Adding to bullish sentiment, government data showed US crude inventories fell by 9 million barrels last week to 419.8 million barrels, around 5% below the five-year average, following a smaller decline reported a day earlier by industry data. Oil eased bit though as six and half month highs triggered some selling. It currently trades down 0.27% at $66.22 per barrel.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-petrochemical-plant-equipment-picture-id627839_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ASM Tech inks pact to acquire 20% stake in Myelin Foundry]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/asm-tech-inks-pact-to-acquire-20-stake-in-myelin-foundry/1678913</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678913</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The partnership will integrate Myelin’s “edge-first" AI stack—specializing in predictive intelligence and multimodal analytics—directly into ASM’s engineering design led manufacturing portfolio.

The partnership will integrate Myelin’s “edge-first" AI stack—specializing in predictive intelligence and multimodal analytics—directly into ASM’s engineering design led manufacturing portfolio. The collaboration is expected to address evolving requirements across semiconductor, electronics, solar and engineering sectors, where real-time operational intelligence and equipment reliability are increasingly critical. As part of this initiative, the rollout will concentrate on several key areas. It will begin with predictive maintenance, shifting from reactive repairs to data-driven forecasting to minimize unplanned downtime. In additional, the partnership leverages multi –modal analytics, integrating data from sensors, vision, and acoustics for a 360-degree view of machine health. Further, it will advance AI-augmented operations by equipping human operators with real-time, intelligent assistance to improve safety and precision. Finally a strong emphasis will be placed on sustainability & efficiency optimizing energy consumption and resource utilization through autonomous system adjustments. Rabindra Srikantan, managing director, ASM Technologies Ltd, said, “ASM has been progressively integrating AI across our engineering design-led manufacturing and automation solutions. This strategic investment in Myelin Foundry strengthens our technology foundation by adding advanced edge-based AI capabilities. The collaboration will enable us to deliver intelligent capital equipment for semiconductor, electronics, solar and engineering ecosystems as they move towards smarter manufacturing environments that enhance yield, through put, equipment reliability with predictive real time intelligence. Gopichand Katragadda, founder and CEO, Myelin Foundry, said, “Industrial AI must operate reliably in real production settings where decisions are made in real time. The investment from ASM Technologies allows us to scale our multimodal AI platforms across global manufacturing ecosystems and demonstrate the impact of edge intelligence at the machine level. Together, we aim to accelerate the shift towards autonomous, efficient and data-driven manufacturing.” ASM Technologies has been providing consulting and product development services in the areas of engineering services and product R&D. The company operates offshore development and support centres in India and overseas, catering to a diverse global clientele.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ASMTechnologies_80476465505_3734.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikram Solar Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikram-solar-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678911</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678911</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NDL Ventures Ltd, Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd, Creative Eye Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 February 2026.

NDL Ventures Ltd, Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd, Creative Eye Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 February 2026. Vikram Solar Ltd lost 10.33% to Rs 193.65 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.57 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 86869 shares in the past one month. NDL Ventures Ltd tumbled 9.13% to Rs 114.1. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9818 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10583 shares in the past one month. Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd crashed 8.72% to Rs 144.4. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5723 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2781 shares in the past one month. Creative Eye Ltd corrected 8.03% to Rs 6.3. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 8982 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2201 shares in the past one month. Shyam Telecom Ltd shed 7.83% to Rs 9.77. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1844 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vikram-Solar-Ltd_64374838_68162.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex gains 435 pts; realty shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-gains-435-pts-realty-shares-advance/1678909</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678909</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade. The Nifty traded tad above the 25,600 level. Realty shares advanced after declining in the past trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 435.24 points or 0.53% to 82,933.38. The Nifty 50 index rose 146.35 points or 0.57% to 25,602.70. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.56% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.10%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,449 shares rose and 2,610 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index rose 0.60% to 822.75. The index advanced 2.56% in the past trading session. Sobha (up 1.34%), Lodha Developers (up 1.28%), DLF (up 1.23%), Oberoi Realty (up 1.06%), Anant Raj (up 0.87%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.35%) and Godrej Properties (up 0.03%) rose. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.61% to 6.715 compared with the previous session close of 6.674. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9825 compared with its close of 90.6850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.96% to Rs 156,272. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.11% to 97.94. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.10% to 4.071. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 19 cents or 0.27% to $71.47 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Dee Development Engineers rallied 6.89% after the company received a letter of intent for the supply of heat recovery steam generator (HRSG) pipes from one of the largest international OEMs based in the US. CIE Automotive India rose 0.85%. The company reported a 10.4% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 204.31 crore on a 13.4% increase in net sales to Rs 2,393 crore in Q4 2025 as compared with Q4 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold extends three-day rally as markets await PCE, GDP]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-extends-three-day-rally-as-markets-await-pce-gdp/1678903</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678903</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures climbed toward $5,050 per ounce on Friday, extending gains for a third straight session as geopolitical tensions and uncertainty over US monetary policy boosted safe-haven demand.

Gold futures climbed toward $5,050 per ounce on Friday, extending gains for a third straight session as geopolitical tensions and uncertainty over US monetary policy boosted safe-haven demand. Rising strains between the United States and Iran supported buying interest, even as a stronger dollar limited upside. Investors are closely watching upcoming US GDP and PCE inflation data, while recent FOMC minutes highlighted a divided policy outlook, with some officials open to further rate hikes if inflation stays elevated. On MCX, April gold futures rose nearly 1% to around Rs 1,56,249 per 10 grams, while overseas April contracts on Comex gained close to 1%. Expectations for aggressive rate cuts have eased, though markets still price in two quarter-point cuts before the end of the year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at ABB India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-abb-india-ltd-counter/1678901</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678901</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Brainbees Solutions Ltd, Data Patterns (India) Ltd, Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Siemens Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 20 February 2026.

Brainbees Solutions Ltd, Data Patterns (India) Ltd, Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Siemens Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 20 February 2026. ABB India Ltd recorded volume of 28.9 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 19.62 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.47 lakh shares. The stock gained 8.95% to Rs.6,231.50. Volumes stood at 1.36 lakh shares in the last session. Brainbees Solutions Ltd saw volume of 412.79 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.31 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 36.50 lakh shares. The stock increased 4.58% to Rs.223.55. Volumes stood at 78.67 lakh shares in the last session. Data Patterns (India) Ltd notched up volume of 27.32 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.54 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4.93 lakh shares. The stock rose 3.07% to Rs.3,003.50. Volumes stood at 6.59 lakh shares in the last session. Tata Investment Corporation Ltd notched up volume of 135.71 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.46 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 30.46 lakh shares. The stock rose 2.41% to Rs.708.95. Volumes stood at 231.63 lakh shares in the last session. Siemens Ltd clocked volume of 9.16 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 2.96 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3.09 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.36% to Rs.3,304.80. Volumes stood at 1.77 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABB_25842664874_242.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mason Infratech jumps on bagging Rs 54-cr civil works order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mason-infratech-jumps-on-bagging-rs-54-cr-civil-works-order/1678900</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678900</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves carrying out main civil works for Auris Ilaria Tower 6B, including balance floor RCC work up to LMR and OHT, AAC block masonry for all floors, internal plastering for kitchens, toilets, staircases, lobbies, ducts, and shafts, and external plastering for LMR, OHT, and terrace areas.

The order involves carrying out main civil works for Auris Ilaria Tower 6B, including balance floor RCC work up to LMR and OHT, AAC block masonry for all floors, internal plastering for kitchens, toilets, staircases, lobbies, ducts, and shafts, and external plastering for LMR, OHT, and terrace areas. The contract is domestic in nature, valued at approximately Rs 53.68 crore, and is to be executed over a period of 17 months from the date of work order issuance. The company clarified that neither the promoters nor the promoter group have any interest in the entity awarding the contract, and the transaction is not a related-party deal, being executed at arm’s length. Mason Infratech is engaged in the business of Infrastructure & Construction activity in the State of Maharashtra. On a full-year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit rose 46.7% to Rs 17.09 crore on a 19.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 112.10 crore in FY25 compared with FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MasonInfratechLtd_25914778_92836.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India composite PMI rises to 59.3 in February]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-composite-pmi-rises-to-593-in-february/1678897</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678897</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's private sector activity expanded at the quickest pace in three months in February amid robust growth in new orders, flash survey results from S&P Global showed on Friday.

India's private sector activity expanded at the quickest pace in three months in February amid robust growth in new orders, flash survey results from S&P Global showed on Friday. The HSBC flash composite output index rose to 59.3 in February from 58.4 in January. A score above 50 indicates expansion in the sector. The acceleration in growth was driven by a quicker upturn in manufacturing production. The Manufacturing PMI climbed to a 4-month high of 57.5 in February from 55.4 in January. Meanwhile, the services activity expanded at a broadly similar rate to that seen in January, as the Services PMI business activity index stood at 58.4 in February versus 58.5 in January. New orders received by the Indian private sector grew at the fastest pace in three months, buoyed by demand strength, local tourism, marketing efforts, and rising client inquiries. Export orders also logged the strongest expansion since September 2025. Total sales growth at goods producers was a 4-month high, while that in the services sector retreated to a 13-month low. In line with rising orders and outstanding business volumes, private sector companies raised their employment levels at the quickest pace in three months. They also scaled up purchasing activity, with the rate of growth accelerating to a 4-month high. On the price front, input price inflation accelerated to a 15-month high in February amid higher costs for chemicals, eggs, freight, labor, machinery, meat, metals, packaging materials, and vegetables. Consequently, selling prices rose at the fastest pace in six months.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex zooms 355 pts; PSU bank shares advance; VIX zooms 7.52%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-zooms-355-pts-psu-bank-shares-advance-vix-zooms-752/1678892</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678892</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with significant gains in the afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with significant gains in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,500 level. Barring IT index shared while all other indices traded in green with PSU Bank, metal and FMCG shares gaining the most. At 13:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 354.85 points or 0.43% to 82,861.86. The Nifty 50 index jumped 91.65 points or 0.36% to 25,546. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.42% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index dropped 0.16%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,943 shares rose and 2,054 shares fell. A total of 207 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, zoomed 7.52% to 14.47. Economy: HSBC India Services PMI eased to 58.4 in February 2026 compared with 58.5 in January 2026, with exports rising fastest since August 2025, domestic demand easing, modestly faster hiring, and input costs hitting a 2.5-year high. Selling prices and business sentiment rose to a one-year peak. HSBC India Manufacturing PMI climbed to 57.5 in February 2026 compared with 55.4 in January 2026, led by strong domestic demand, modest export growth, higher employment, inputs, and inventories. Input and output prices rose, while sentiment remained positive. HSBC India Composite PMI hit 59.3 in February 2026 as against 58.4 in January 2026, the highest since last November, as factory output, new orders, and foreign sales strengthened. Hiring improved, input costs rose to a 15-month high, selling prices to a six-month peak, and sentiment reached a one-year high on investment optimism. India AI Impact Summit 2026: The AI Impact Summit, held from February 16–20, brings together over 500 global AI leaders, 150 academicians and researchers, and 400 chief technology officers, vice-presidents, and philanthropists. The Pax Silica declaration was signed between India and the US. “It is an honour to stand before all of you at this historic moment as we welcome India into Pax Silica. What struck me most was not just India's scale, although that is breathtaking—it is India's resolve, the determination to chart your own course. I keep talking about the limitless potential between our two nations, and I truly mean it. From the trade deal to Pax Silica to defence cooperation, the potential for our two nations to work together is truly limitless. I aim to fulfill that over the next three years that I’m here,” said US Ambassador Sergio Gor. Maharashtra CM Devendra Fadnavis spoke at the India AI Impact Summit, highlighting the state’s achievements in technology. He emphasized that AI is designed to benefit farmers. “Across the world, food systems are under strain. Climate volatility is intensifying, water tables are falling, soil health is deteriorating, supply chains are fragile, and global markets are unpredictable. For countries from the Global South, agriculture is not merely an economic sector—it is livelihood, social stability, and national security. India understands this very deeply. Under the visionary leadership of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, India has placed digital public infrastructure and responsible AI at the centre,” said Devendra Fadnavis. Gainers & Losers: Hindalco Industries (up 2.71%), NTPC (up 2.04%), Hindustan Unilever (up 2.02%), Larsen & Toubro (up 1.67%) and Tata Steel (up 1.56%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Kwality Wall's (down 1.71%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.03%), Infosys (down 0.99%), HDFC Bank (down 0.75%) and Eternal (down 0.70%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: CIE Automotive India fell 0.99%. The company has reported 10.4% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 204.31 crore on a 13.4% increase in net sales to Rs 2,393 crore in Q4 2025 as compared with Q4 2024. Paras Defence and Space Technologies added 1.67% after the company said that it has acquired 49% stake of Himanshi Thermal Solutions from DefSpace Technologies for total consideration of Rs 49,000. ABB India rallied 8.29% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 5.82% to Rs 432.85 crore on 7.44% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3557.01 crore in Q4 CY25 over Q4 CY24. Zydus Lifesciences shed 0.32%. The company said the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) has completed a pre-approval inspection (PAI) at its Injectable Medical Devices facility in Ahmedabad with nil observations. Global Markets: European markets opened higher on Friday as traders awaited key economic data and additional earnings reports, while keeping an eye on escalating tensions between the U.S. and Iran. In the U.K., retail sales rose 1.8% in January from December, exceeding expectations and marking the largest increase since May 2024. Germany saw producer prices decline 3% year-on-year in January, while France’s inflation slowed to 0.3% year-on-year, down from 0.8% in December. Asian markets traded mixed, after all three major Wall Street indexes declined overnight, pressured by a drop in private credit stocks and Iran-U.S. tensions. Prospects of a strike on Iran have risen with U.S. President Donald Trump reportedly saying that he would take a call to decide on military action against Tehran in the next 10 days. This pushed Brent Crude higher, gaining 0.26%, to settle at $71.92. In Asia, investors assessed Japan's latest inflation data. The island nation's headline inflation rate fell from 2.1% in December to 1.5% in January, its lowest level since March 2022. The reading ended a run of 45 straight months in which inflation had remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target. The core inflation rate, which excludes fresh food prices, eased to 2%, the lowest level since January 2024. It was down from 2.4% in December. As per reports, despite the slowdown in headline inflation, the Bank of Japan is unlikely to delay rate hikes as fresh-food prices remain volatile, while energy costs fell after Japan scrapped its fuel tax in December. Japan’s manufacturing activity improved in February, with the S&P Global Japan Manufacturing PMI rising to 52.8 from 51.5 in January, marking the strongest expansion since May 2022. Growth was supported by firm domestic and overseas demand, with export orders rising at the fastest pace in eight years. While hiring growth eased from January’s peak, it remained solid. Input costs increased at a slightly faster pace. Manufacturers stayed optimistic about the year-ahead outlook, backed by stronger demand, semiconductor and AI-related orders, and ongoing product launches. Overnight on Wall Street, the US stocks closed lower on Thursday, pulling the S&P 500 close to flat for the year, as investors rotated out of financials and monitored escalating tensions between the US and Iran. Reflecting a surge in imports and a slump in exports, the Commerce Department released a report on Thursday showing the U.S. trade deficit unexpectedly widened in the month of December. The Commerce Department said the trade deficit grew to $70.3 billion in December from a revised $53.0 billion in November. The unexpectedly wider trade deficit partly reflected a continued surge in the value of imports, which shot up by 3.6 percent to $357.6 billion in December after spiking by 4.2 percent to $345.3 billion in November. The report also showed a continued slump in the value of exports, which tumbled by 1.7 percent to $287.3 billion in December after plunging by 3.4 percent to $292.3 billion in November. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 267.50 points, or 0.54%, closing at 49,395.16. The S&P 500 declined 0.28%, ending at 6,861.89, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.31% to 22,682.73. Financial stocks led the decline after Blue Owl Capital said it would tighten investor liquidity following the sale of $1.4 billion in loan assets, raising concerns about potential losses in the private credit market. Shares of Blue Owl dropped about 6%, while Blackstone and Apollo Global Management each fell more than 5%. Software stocks also remained under pressure amid persistent worries about artificial intelligence disruption. The sector has struggled in recent weeks as investors assess how AI could reshape enterprise software demand.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dee Development surges after bagging order over $40 mln from US-based OEM ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dee-development-surges-after-bagging-order-over-40-mln-from-us-based-oem/1678889</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678889</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the agreement, the company will supply 16 HRSG Pipes to one largest international OEM conglomerate in power sector, headquarters in the US.

Under the agreement, the company will supply 16 HRSG Pipes to one largest international OEM conglomerate in power sector, headquarters in the US. However, due to commercial confidentiality, the name of customer has not been disclosed. The aggregate value of the order will be more than $40 million and the LoI will remain valid till 18 February 2027. DEE Development Engineers (DDEL) is an engineering company providing specialized process piping solutions for industries such as oil and gas, power (including nuclear), process industries, and chemicals through engineering, procurement, and manufacturing services. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 18.28 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 13.33 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales increased 77% YoY to Rs 298.67 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DeeDevelopmentEngineersLtd_25916295_34369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IIFL Finance to consider NCD issuance on 24 February ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/iifl-finance-to-consider-ncd-issuance-on-24-february/1678887</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678887</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an earlier exchange filing dated 8 May 2025, the company had stated that it plans to raise funds through the issuance of NCDs on a private placement basis, with an aggregate limit of up to Rs 10,000 crore.

In an earlier exchange filing dated 8 May 2025, the company had stated that it plans to raise funds through the issuance of NCDs on a private placement basis, with an aggregate limit of up to Rs 10,000 crore. IIFL Finance is one of India's leading retail-focused diversified NBFCs, engaged in the business of loans and mortgages through its subsidiaries, IIFL Home Finance and IIFL Samasta Finance. The company offers a wide spectrum of products, including home loans, gold loans, business loans, microfinance, capital market finance, and developer & construction finance, serving over 8 million customers through a pan-India network of 4,900+ branches and digital channels. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 513.6% to Rs 501.35 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 81.71 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income jumped 40.2% YoY to Rs 3,432.79 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of IIFL Finance slipped 1.68% to settle at Rs 488.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IIFLHoldings_90646143_23296.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd soars 2.16%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tube-investments-of-india-ltd-soars-216-gains-for-third-straight-session/1678883</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678883</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Tube Investments of India Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 2542, up 2.16% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.61% on the day, quoting at 25608.55. The Sensex is at 82943.55, up 0.54%. Tube Investments of India Ltd has added around 11.84% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Tube Investments of India Ltd is a constituent, has added around 3.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27734, up 0.55% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.39 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.04 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2533.2, up 1.98% on the day. Tube Investments of India Ltd is down 5.35% in last one year as compared to a 12.34% gain in NIFTY and a 29.67% gain in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 34.72 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TubeInvestmentsofIndiaLtd_81529932771_40963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd spurts 2.84%, rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindalco-industries-ltd-spurts-284-rises-for-third-straight-session/1678884</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678884</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindalco Industries Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Hindalco Industries Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 931.35, up 2.84% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.61% on the day, quoting at 25608.55. The Sensex is at 82943.55, up 0.54%. Hindalco Industries Ltd has dropped around 0.84% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Hindalco Industries Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 4.89% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11842.4, up 1.32% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 29.8 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 72.78 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 931.2, up 2.71% on the day. Hindalco Industries Ltd is up 42.51% in last one year as compared to a 12.34% gain in NIFTY and a 39.36% gain in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 23.37 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindalcoInds_40254437488_252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd spurts 0.03%, up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-life-insurance-company-ltd-spurts-003-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1678882</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678882</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 733.4, up 0.03% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.6% on the day, quoting at 25606.8. The Sensex is at 82934.9, up 0.53%. HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd has added around 1.25% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd is a constituent, has added around 4.68% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28069.5, up 0.56% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.49 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 29.15 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 731.15, down 0.25% on the day. HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd is up 17.75% in last one year as compared to a 12.33% gain in NIFTY and a 21.8% gain in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 83.73 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCLifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_86429089807_21997.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade higher; FMCG shares rally  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-higher-fmcg-shares-rally/1678871</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678871</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with major gains in early afternoon trade despite rising geopolitical tensions and uncertainty over global growth prospects.

The key equity indices traded with major gains in early afternoon trade despite rising geopolitical tensions and uncertainty over global growth prospects. Investors are also closely monitoring developments at the AI Summit 2026 in Delhi. FMCG shares jumped after declining in the past trading session. At 12:25 PM ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 596.40 points or 0.72% to 83,094.54. The Nifty 50 index jumped 201.40 points or 0.79% to 25,655.75. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.68% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index dropped 0.46%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,471 shares rose and 2,413 shares fell. A total of 217 shares were unchanged. Economy: HSBC India Services PMI eased to 58.4 in February 2026 compared with 58.5 in January 2026, with exports rising fastest since August 2025, domestic demand easing, modestly faster hiring, and input costs hitting a 2.5-year high. Selling prices and business sentiment rose to a one-year peak. HSBC India Manufacturing PMI climbed to 57.5 in February 2026 compared with 55.4 in January 2026, led by strong domestic demand, modest export growth, higher employment, inputs, and inventories. Input and output prices rose, while sentiment remained positive. HSBC India Composite PMI hit 59.3 in February 2026 as against 58.4 in January 2026, the highest since last November, as factory output, new orders, and foreign sales strengthened. Hiring improved, input costs rose to a 15-month high, selling prices to a six-month peak, and sentiment reached a one-year high on investment optimism. India AI Impact Summit 2026 Being held from February 16-20, the AI Impact Summit brings together more than 500 global AI leaders, 150 academicians and researchers, and 400 chief technology officers, vice-presidents, and philanthropists Pax Silica declaration signed between India And US. “It is an honour to stand before all of you here today at this historic moment as we welcome India into Pax Silica... What struck me most was not just India's scale, although that is breathtaking. It is India's resolve, the determination to chart your own course. I keep talking about the limitless potential between our two nations, and I truly mean it. From the trade deal to Pax Silica to defence cooperation, the potential for our two nations to work together is truly limitless. I aim to fulfil that over the next three years that I'm here,” says US Ambassador Sergio Gor. Maharashtra CM Devendra Fadnavis speaks at the India AI Impact Summit and highlighted the state's achievements in the technology. He said that AI is designed for farmers. “Across the world, food systems are under strain. Climate volatility is intensifying. Water tables are falling. Soil health is deteriorating. Supply chains are fragile, and global markets are unpredictable. For countries from the global south, agriculture is not merely an economic sector. It is livelihood, social stability and national security. India understands this very deeply. Under the visionary leadership of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, India has placed digital public infrastructure and responsible AI at the centre,” says Devendra Fadnavis. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 6.57% to 14.35. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures were trading at 25,660.50, at a premium of 4.75 points as compared with the spot at 25,655.75. The Nifty option chain for the 24 February 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 1.66 crore contracts at the 26,000 strike price. Maximum put OI of 1.61 crore contracts was seen at the 25,500 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index advanced 0.81% to 51,902.60. The index declined 1.76% in the past trading session. Hindustan Unilever (up 1.83%), Dabur India (up 1.75%), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (up 1.67%), Nestle India (up 1.51%) and Godrej Consumer Products (up 1.49%) were the top gainers. Among the other gainers were Marico (up 1.16%), United Breweries (up 0.51%), Tata Consumer Products (up 0.51%), ITC (up 0.32%) and Britannia Industries (up 0.11%). Stocks in Spotlight: CIE Automotive India advanced 1.37% after the company has reported 10.4% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 204.31 crore on a 13.4% increase in net sales to Rs 2,393 crore in Q4 2025 as compared with Q4 2024. Paras Defence and Space Technologies added 2.48% after the company said that it has acquired 49% stake of Himanshi Thermal Solutions from DefSpace Technologies for total consideration of Rs 49,000.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Texmaco Rail & Engineering forms strategic JV with RVNL ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/texmaco-rail-engineering-forms-strategic-jv-with-rvnl/1678870</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678870</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The partnership aims to build a rolling stock powerhouse and expand Texmaco’s rail EPC footprint across India.

The partnership aims to build a rolling stock powerhouse and expand Texmaco’s rail EPC footprint across India. Officials said the collaboration will accelerate the country’s rail manufacturing capabilities and strengthen its position as a global infrastructure solutions provider. The JV marks a significant step in India’s push to enhance domestic rail production and meet growing demand for modern, efficient rail systems. The JV will focus on advanced rolling stock, lifecycle maintenance, asset management, and large-scale EPC projects in India and abroad. Combining Texmaco’s manufacturing agility (49% stake) with RVNL’s public-sector execution, the partnership aims to deliver cost-competitive, high-quality integrated rail solutions. The JV aims to position India as a global hub for rolling stock and rail infrastructure by promoting technology indigenisation, local supply chains, and export-ready platforms. It is expected to boost industrial activity, support MSMEs, create thousands of skilled jobs, and integrate sustainable practices. Beyond India, the venture will pursue projects across Asia, Africa, and the Middle East, delivering end-to-end rail solutions and reinforcing India’s global industrial footprint. Saroj Kumar Poddar, Chairman, Texmaco Rail & Engineering, said, “The alliance brings together Texmaco’s industrial manufacturing scale and export reach with RVNL’s proven execution track record in complex rail EPC projects, creating a powerful institutional platform aligned with the Government of India’s Aatmanirbhar Bharat vision.” Indrajit Mookerjee, Vice Chairman & Executive Director, Texmaco Rail & Engineering, said, “This partnership represents a transformational step in building globally competitive rail capabilities from India. By aligning manufacturing excellence with execution expertise, we are creating a platform that can deliver integrated rail solutions for both national priorities and international markets.” Sudipta Mukherjee, Managing Director, Texmaco Rail & Engineering, stated, “This joint venture represents a unique public–private partnership aligned with the Hon’ble Railway Minister’s pursuit of excellence and the Hon’ble Prime Minister’s dynamic vision of Aatmanirbhar Bharat. It reflects our shared commitment to shaping the future of rail mobility through next-generation freight, locomotive, passenger, and metro systems. The collaboration will accelerate innovation, strengthen export competitiveness, and reinforce India’s position on the global rail map.” Saleem Ahmad, Chairman & Managing Director, Texmaco Rail & Engineering, stated, “This JV is not merely a corporate collaboration but a strategic platform for national infrastructure advancement. It will unlock long-term value through scale, technology adoption, and global project participation.” Texmaco Rail & Engineering (TEXMACO) is a listed company and part of the Adventz Group. Texmaco is a key player in the railway and infrastructure sector. It operates across three business segments: Freight Cars, Rail Infrastructure & Green Energy, and Infrastructure – Electrical. Rail Vikas Nigam is engaged in executing a wide range of railway infrastructure projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, cable-stayed bridges, and institutional buildings. Shares of Texmaco Rail & Engineering slipped 0.93% to Rs 111.25, while Rail Vikas Nigam rose 1.11% to Rs 310.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TexmacoRail_96355740994_27419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen slides past 155 as inflation slows, BoJ gets policy breathing room  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-slides-past-155-as-inflation-slows-boj-gets-policy-breathing-room/1678869</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678869</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The yen weakened past 155.21 per dollar, extending weekly losses beyond 1.5% after inflation data in Japan showed a broad slowdown in price pressures.

The yen weakened past 155.21 per dollar, extending weekly losses beyond 1.5% after inflation data in Japan showed a broad slowdown in price pressures. Headline inflation eased to 1.5% in January from 2.1%, the lowest level since March 2022, while core inflation slowed to 2.0%, in line with the target of the Bank of Japan. The softer inflation backdrop gives the central bank more room to delay interest rate hikes, especially amid a weak economic recovery in the previous quarter. At the same time, the dollar strengthened on solid US economic data and hawkish signals from the Federal Reserve, with markets awaiting upcoming US GDP and PCE inflation data for further direction.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vl-e-governance-it-solutions-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678867</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678867</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Abans Financial Services Ltd, Novartis India Ltd, Centum Electronics Ltd and BLB Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 February 2026.

Abans Financial Services Ltd, Novartis India Ltd, Centum Electronics Ltd and BLB Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 20 February 2026. VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd surged 19.94% to Rs 17.32 at 20-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 7.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.43 lakh shares in the past one month. Abans Financial Services Ltd soared 15.92% to Rs 233. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14179 shares in the past one month. Novartis India Ltd spiked 14.43% to Rs 950.25. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 8.22 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17776 shares in the past one month. Centum Electronics Ltd jumped 14.22% to Rs 2623.45. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 35572 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5040 shares in the past one month. BLB Ltd added 13.33% to Rs 20.4. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.05 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 26852 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VLEGovernanceITSolutionsLtd_93531239_76164.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AI has the potential to lift global annual GDP growth by up to 0.8 percentage points, says IMF’s Kristalina Georgieva ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ai-has-the-potential-to-lift-global-annual-gdp-growth-by-up-to-08-percentage-points-says-imfs-kristalina-georgieva/1678866</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678866</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[AI has arrived; it is here.

AI has arrived; it is here. Investment is surging into data centers, power plants, and neural networks. It is like when the world was building the railways: the old ways of doing things will be changed forever, and this time it will be much faster, said IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva at the India AI Impact Summit. AI will bring opportunity and challenge—and it is for us to maximize the benefits, she noted. IMF estimates, AI has the potential to lift global annual GDP growth by up to 0.8 percentage points. This is a vast upside potential, she stated but will massively transform the world of work. There will also be dislocation linked to the sheer pace of change—many jobs in the middle that AI will not enhance but rather replace, she noted. I worry about a hollowing out of the middle, for young call-center workers that may be replaced by bots, for IT graduates potentially replaced by algorithms. We must prepare, and the best preparation is to be open-eyed about the risks of AI and invest in people, IMF chief noted. Nevertheless, given the huge challenges of global AI diffusion, India knows the good it can do for others—with its digital interfaces and human ingenuity, it is on the forefront of making things happen, offering a unique focus on democratizing AI. And India has extensive experience in creating practical solutions for rural and urban communities, which can benefit low-income and developing countries across the world, she further noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/welcome-word-written-on-computer-keyboard-picture-id8567109_Analyst-Meet.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>