<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:29:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shyam Metalics Q3 PAT drops 25% QoQ to Rs 197 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shyam-metalics-q3-pat-drops-25-qoq-to-rs-197-cr/1667599</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667599</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations declined 1.02% QoQ to Rs 4,421.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations declined 1.02% QoQ to Rs 4,421.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit declined marginally by 0.23%, while revenue from operations jumped 17.70% in Q3 FY26. Total expenses increased 19.20% YoY to Rs 3,934.35 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of raw materials consumed stood at Rs 3,251.07 crore, registering a growth of 6.77% YoY. Employee benefit expenses amounted to Rs 125.52 crore, up 14.24% YoY. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 270.04 crore in the December quarter, up 2.64% from Rs 263.09 crore recorded during the same period last year. EBITDA stood at Rs 539 crore, registering a growth of 6.3% from Rs 507 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. However, the EBITDA margin declined to 12.2% in Q3 FY26 from 13.5% in Q3 FY25. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit increased 8.96% YoY to Rs 751.15 crore, while revenue jumped 20.89% YoY to Rs 13,311.85 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Brij Bhushan Agarwal, chairman & managing director said “Shyam Metalics has delivered another exceptional quarter, with Q3 FY26 delivering a strong 25% volume growth and 18% growth in revenues. Over the nine months, we have achieved significant growth in both topline and EBITDA, reflecting the effectiveness of our strategic initiatives and our sustained focus on operational excellence in a constantly evolving market environment. We continue to expand our share of value-added products, further strengthening our competitive position and improving our profitability. This underscores our ability to execute with precision and agility. I am also pleased to announce that the board has approved fresh capital investment of Rs. 6,660 crores to drive value-added growth and enhance margins. The planned CAPEX will be directed towards capacity expansion and strengthening the Company’s integrated operating model. These investments are aligned with our strategy of deepening backward integration, improving cost competitiveness and building scale to support the next phase of growth. During the quarter, we successfully commissioned and commenced commercial production of 0.45 MTPA blast furnace at our Kharagpur plant. This milestone significantly enhances our steelmaking capacity. Strengthens our integrated manufacturing footprint and supports our long-term growth ambitions. With disciplined execution, prudent capital allocation and strategic diversification, we are confident of closing FY26 on a strong note. Our continued focus on innovation and financial discipline will guide us to shape our growth momentum and strengthen our position as an industry leader.” Meanwhile, the company’s board of directors has approved the voluntary liquidation of Shyam Metalics International DMCC (SMIDMCC), a wholly owned subsidiary of Shyam SEL and Power Limited (SSPL) and a step-down subsidiary of the company, incorporated in Dubai, UAE. The decision was taken as the proposed business activities of SMIDMCC could not be materialised due to prevailing geopolitical uncertainties. Since its incorporation, SMIDMCC has remained non-operational and has not commenced any business activities. Consequently, the entity continues to incur recurring operational and statutory compliance costs without generating any commercial or strategic benefits, rendering it financially and strategically unviable. In addition, the Board has approved the appointment of Subrata Bhattacharya as an additional director in the Independent category, not liable to retire by rotation, for a period of five consecutive years, commencing from 1 February 2026 to 31 January 2031. The company affirmed that the director is not debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other authority. Shyam Metalics and Energy is a leading integrated metal producing company based in India with a focus on long steel products and ferro alloys. The company is amongst the largest producers of ferro alloys, one of the leading players in terms of pellet capacity and the fourth largest player in the sponge iron industry in terms of sponge iron capacity in India. The counter rose 1.38% to Rs 789.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShyamMetaliks_54345482_45268.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Bank gains as Q3 PAT jumps 3% YoY to Rs 6,490 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-bank-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-3-yoy-to-rs-6490-cr/1667598</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667598</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26.

Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26. Operating profit rose 3.24% to Rs 10,875.70 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 10,533.85 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. The bank’s net interest income (NII) stood at Rs 14,287 crore in Q3 FY26, up 5% YoY. Net Interest Margin (NIM) for Q3 FY26 stood at 3.64%. Provision and contingencies for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 2,246 crore. Specific loan loss provisions for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 2,307 crore. Total deposits climbed 15% to 12,60,786 crore as on 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 10,95,883 crore as on 31 December 2024. CASA deposits increased 14% to Rs 4,93,073 crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 4,32,855 crore as of 31 December 2024. CASA deposits constitute 39% of the total deposits as of 31 December 2025. The bank’s advances grew 14% YoY to Rs 11,59,052 crore as on 31 December 2025. Retail loans grew 6% YoY to Rs 6,44,575 crore, accounting for 56% of the bank’s net advances. As on 30th September 2025 the bank’s reported Gross NPA and Net NPA levels were 1.46% and 0.44% respectively, as against 1.57% and 0.45% as on 30th June 2025. The shareholders’ funds of the bank grew 15% YoY, reaching Rs 1,96,709 crore as of 31 December 2025. The Capital Adequacy Ratio (CAR) and CET1 ratio stood at 16.55% and 14.50%, respectively. Additionally, Rs 5,012 crore of other provisions and Rs 1,231 crore of one-time additional standard asset provisions are not considered in the CAR calculation, providing a cushion of approximately 43 bps over the reported CAR. The book value per equity share increased from Rs 553 on 31 December 2024 to Rs 634 on 31 December 2025. As of 31 December 2025, the bank’s Gross NPA and Net NPA stood at 1.40% and 0.42%, respectively, compared with 1.46% and 0.44% as of 30 September 2025. Recoveries from written-off accounts during the quarter amounted to Rs 799 crore. Reported net slippages, adjusted for recoveries from the written-off pool, were Rs 2,335 crore, comprising retail: Rs 2,506 crore, Corporate & Business Group (CBG) Rs 109 crore, and wholesale Rs 280 crore. As of 31 December 2025, the bank’s provision coverage ratio stood at 70% of Gross NPAs, down from 76% YoY as of 31 December 2024. As of 31 December 2025, the bank’s distribution network comprised 6,110 domestic branches and extension counters and 281 business correspondent banking outlets (BCBOs) across 3,315 centers, up from 5,706 branches and 202 BCBOs in 3,122 centers YoY. The bank also had 12,838 ATMs and cash recyclers nationwide. Its Axis virtual centre operated across eight centers with 1,582 virtual relationship managers as of 31 December 2025. Amitabh Chaudhry, MD & CEO, Axis Bank said: “Our progress this quarter reflects our focus on creating solutions that matter - simplifying access to credit, reimagining digital banking, and investing in talent and ideas that will shape the future. We will keep strengthening our competitive edge by modernising our platforms, empowering our teams, and staying ahead of shifts in customer behavior through smart and revolutionary solutions.” Axis Bank is a private sector bank. It has the third-largest network of branches among private sector banks and an international presence through branches in DIFC (Dubai) and Singapore along with representative offices in Abu Dhabi, Sharjah, Dhaka and Dubai and an offshore banking unit in GIFT City.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AxisBank_99376846491_5554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade sideways; media shares skid for 2nd day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-sideways-media-shares-skid-for-2nd-day/1667595</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667595</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks witnessed a volatile session in mid-morning trade, with the Sensex trading slightly lower while the Nifty inched up.

The key equity benchmarks witnessed a volatile session in mid-morning trade, with the Sensex trading slightly lower while the Nifty inched up. The movement came after India and the European Union clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA) following 18 years of stalled negotiations. Investors awaited key quarterly earnings from Asian Paints, Vodafone Idea, and Motilal Oswal Financial Services, even as traders kept an eye on the rupee and global geopolitical developments. The Nifty traded marginally above the 25,050 mark. Media stocks plunged for second consecutive trading session. At 11:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 94.79 points or 0.12% to 81,442.91. The Nifty 50 index rose 0.35 points or 0.01% to 25,054.60. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.18% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.56%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,462 shares rose and 1,536 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 7.78% to 15.30. India-US Trade Deal: India and the European Union have signed the “mother of all deals”, PM Modi said on Tuesday. Prime Minister Narendra Modi lauded the signing of the free trade agreement between India and the European Union and said that the deal represented “25 per cent of the global GDP and 1/3rd of global trade”. On tariffs overall, Sefcovic said the aim is 97–99% partial or full tariff liberalisation, which could generate savings of around €4 billion a year and help double bilateral trade within five years. The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 2.38% to 1,319.40. The index tumbled 4.83% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Sun TV Network (down 6.74%), D B Corp (down 3.83%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 3.16%), Saregama India (down 1.96%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 1.18%), Nazara Technologies (down 1.12%), Prime Focus (down 1.1%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 0.98%), PVR Inox (down 0.19%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: RailTel Corporation of India advanced 2.30% after the company said that it has bagged an order worth Rs 27.04 crore from Andhra Pradesh Central Power Distribution Corporation (APCPDCL). Chennai Petroleum Corporation rose 1.59% after its standalone profit surged to Rs 987.22 crore in Q3 FY26, sharply higher than Rs 10.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 21.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 15,683.17 crore in Q3 FY26.b Godrej Consumer Products tumbled 6.41% after the company's consolidated net profit remained flat at Rs 497.91 crore in Q3 FY26, even as net sales increased 8.8% year-on-year to Rs 4,079.47 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asian shares advanced on Tuesday despite concerns regarding tariffs resurfaced post US President Donald Trump threatening to increase levies on South Korean goods. Trump said on Truth Social that South Korea's legislature has not approved Seoul’s trade deal with Washington, and that tariffs on the country will climb to 25%, from 15%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index advanced 0.50%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 0.64%. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.43%, supported by jumps of about 3%, 2% and 1% in Apple, Meta Platforms and Microsoft, respectively, ahead of their earnings reports later in the week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel secures Rs 27-cr order from APCPDCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-secures-rs-27-cr-order-from-apcpdcl/1667589</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667589</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the supply, installation, testing, and configuration of software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) devices along with associated hardware and licenses at APCPDCL offices.

The project involves the supply, installation, testing, and configuration of software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) devices along with associated hardware and licenses at APCPDCL offices. The order includes a five-year warranty and support. The project is scheduled to be executed by 24 January 2031. RailTel Corporation, a "Navratna" PSU, is one of the largest neutral telecom infrastructure providers in the country, owning a Pan-India optical fiber network. As of December 2025, the Government of India held a 72.84% stake in the company. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 4.72% to Rs 76.07 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 72.64 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 12.78% YoY to Rs 951.36 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of RailTel Corporation of India rose 0.84% to Rs 330.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WhiteOak Capital Mutual Fund Change in Minimum Application Amount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/whiteoak-capital-mutual-fund-change-in-minimum-application-amount/1667587</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667587</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NOTICE is hereby given that, in addition to the existing frequencies, WhiteOak Capital Mutual Fund (“WOCMF”) / WhiteOak Capital Asset Management Limited (“WOCAMC”) has decided to introduce “Daily frequency” under SIP facility in all the existing Schemes of WOCMF effective from February 01, 2026.

NOTICE is hereby given that, in addition to the existing frequencies, WhiteOak Capital Mutual Fund (“WOCMF”) / WhiteOak Capital Asset Management Limited (“WOCAMC”) has decided to introduce “Daily frequency” under SIP facility in all the existing Schemes of WOCMF effective from February 01, 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Minimum amounts per instalments Minimum number of instalments SIP facility in all the existing Schemes Rs. 100/- and in multiples of Re. 1 In case of Debt Schemes, Rs. 500/- and in multiples of Re. 1 In case of WhiteOak Capital ELSS Tax Saver Fund, Rs. 500/- and in multiples of Rs. 500/- 6

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Aegis Vopak Terminals Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-aegis-vopak-terminals-ltd-counter/1667583</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667583</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd, Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, JSW Energy Ltd, Carborundum Universal Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 27 January 2026.

Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd, Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, JSW Energy Ltd, Carborundum Universal Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 27 January 2026. Aegis Vopak Terminals Ltd recorded volume of 2.82 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.86 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 28628 shares. The stock gained 9.99% to Rs.221.25. Volumes stood at 14182 shares in the last session. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd witnessed volume of 9.87 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.72 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.01 lakh shares. The stock dropped 3.52% to Rs.3,417.95. Volumes stood at 1.09 lakh shares in the last session. Max Healthcare Institute Ltd registered volume of 5.32 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.34 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 56963 shares. The stock slipped 2.12% to Rs.970.45. Volumes stood at 38046 shares in the last session. JSW Energy Ltd saw volume of 5.04 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 7.78 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 64792 shares. The stock dropped 8.11% to Rs.439.75. Volumes stood at 68952 shares in the last session. Carborundum Universal Ltd notched up volume of 3.14 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 7.71 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 40724 shares. The stock slipped 1.11% to Rs.807.30. Volumes stood at 2.35 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisVopakTerminalsLtd_23442647_74261.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Auto stocks slide as India-EU trade deal signals sharp cut in car import duties]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/auto-stocks-slide-as-india-eu-trade-deal-signals-sharp-cut-in-car-import-duties/1667581</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667581</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty Auto index declined 1.25% to 26,469.40.

The Nifty Auto index declined 1.25% to 26,469.40. Mahindra and Mahindra led the losses, sliding 3.47%. Maruti Suzuki India fell 1.81%, while Tube Investments of India declined 1.61%. Other stocks in the red included Ashok Leyland down 1.03%, Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles down 1.00%, Exide Industries down 0.48%, Hero MotoCorp down 0.35%, TVS Motor Company down 0.18%, Bajaj Auto down 0.10% and Bosch down 0.09%. Media reports said India plans to cut import tariffs on cars from the EU to 40% from as high as 110%. The move is part of a broader trade pact that could be announced as early as 27 January. The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Over time, tariffs could fall further to 10%. That would significantly ease market entry for European brands such as Volkswagen, Mercedes-Benz and BMW. European players currently hold less than 4% of India’s car market, which is dominated by Suzuki Motor, Mahindra and Tata Motors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DCB Bank surges after Q3 PAT rises 22% YoY; deposit base rises to Rs 67,754 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dcb-bank-surges-after-q3-pat-rises-22-yoy-deposit-base-rises-to-rs-67754-crore/1667582</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667582</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 625 crore, up 15% YoY.

Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 625 crore, up 15% YoY. Net interest margin was 3.27% for the December 2025 period as against 3.30% for the December 2024 period. Operating expenses rose by 15% to Rs 523 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 456 crore in the December 2024 quarter. Accordingly, the private sector bank registered an operating profit of Rs 323 crore in Q3 FY26, up 19% YoY. Provisions and contingencies expanded by 10% to Rs 74 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 67 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 249 crore, up by 22% from Rs 204 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross NPAs declined to 2.72% as of 31 December 2025, from 3.11% as of 31 December 2024. Net NPAs fell to 1.10% as of 31 December 2025 from 1.18% as of 31 December 2024. The provision coverage ratio (PCR) as on 31 December 2025 was at 75.35% and PCR without considering Gold Loans NPAs was at 76.06%. The bank had a deposit base of Rs 67,754 crore as on 31 December 2025, up 20% YoY. Net advances of the bank as on 31 December 2025 were Rs 56,600 crore, up 18% YoY. Capital adequacy continues to be strong and as on 31 December 2025, the capital adequacy ratio was at 15.84% (with Tier I at 13.45% and Tier II at 2.39% as per Basel III norms). Praveen Kutty, managing director & CEO said: "The growth momentum in both advances and deposits continues to be robust. As indicated in the last quarter, the NIM continues its upward trend in this quarter as well. Fee income momentum continues to remain strong. Credit costs remain benign with slippages reducing and GNPA & NNPA at their three-year lows. The bank has registered the highest ever quarterly PAT, despite taking a one-time impact of Rs. 26.87 crore on account of the 'New Labour Codes’.” DCB Bank is a new generation private sector bank with 469 branches across 20 states and 2 union territories. The bank’s business segments are retail, micro-SMEs, SMEs, mid-corporate, microfinance institutions (MFI), agriculture, commodities, government, public sector, Indian banks, co-operative banks and non-banking finance companies (NBFC).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DCBBank_50897446343_14602.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index lingers around 4-month low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-lingers-around-4-month-low/1667575</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667575</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index is seen nagging under 97 mark on Tuesday, at its lowest level since September 18th ahead of Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision due this week.

The dollar index is seen nagging under 97 mark on Tuesday, at its lowest level since September 18th ahead of Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision due this week. Moreover, concerns over the Federal Reserve (Fed) independence, ongoing geopolitical uncertainty, rising U.S. national debt are all adding pressure on the greenback. Currently, DXY, which measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 96.97, a four-month low. The US Fed will announce its interest rate decision on Wednesday. The US economic outlook and interest rate path laid by Fed will also be closely watched for further cues.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-726884__340_forex.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Chennai Petroleum Corporation jumps as Q3 PAT soars to Rs 987 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/chennai-petroleum-corporation-jumps-as-q3-pat-soars-to-rs-987-crore/1667576</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667576</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 21.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 15,683.17 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 21.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 15,683.17 crore in Q3 FY26. Total expenses for the third quarter rose by 15.80% to Rs 18,150.37 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 1317.03 crore in Q3 FY26, steeply higher from Rs 14.12 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The gross refining margin (GRM) for the quarter improved to US$ 10.97 per barrel, as against a US$ 4.29 per barrel in the same period last year. CPCL delivered strong operational performance in Q3 FY26, recording a crude throughput of 2.79 million metric tonnes (MMT), compared with 2.55 MMT in the corresponding quarter of the previous financial year. This translated into capacity utilisation of 105%, highlighting efficient plant operations and high reliability. On a consolidated basis, the company’s net profit stood at Rs 1,001.59 crore in Q3 FY26, steeply higher than Rs 20.78 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 21.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 15,683.17 crore in Q3 FY26. Chennai Petroleum Corporation is in the business of refining crude oil to produce & supply various petroleum products and manufacture and sale of lubricating oil additives.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CPCL_94179076310_2339.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen holds near 154 as dollar weakens on global risks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-holds-near-154-as-dollar-weakens-on-global-risks/1667572</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667572</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen hovered around 154.6 per dollar on Tuesday, extending gains after a sharp rally of over 3% in the past two sessions.

The Japanese yen hovered around 154.6 per dollar on Tuesday, extending gains after a sharp rally of over 3% in the past two sessions. The currency’s strength came as investors weighed growing speculation about a possible coordinated foreign exchange intervention by Tokyo and Washington, even as Bank of Japan data suggested the surge seen on Friday was unlikely driven by official action. Additional support for the yen came from renewed weakness in the US dollar, as rising geopolitical and trade tensions unsettled markets. Expectations that US President Donald Trump could replace Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell with a more dovish successor further pressured the greenback, reinforcing bets on a softer US monetary policy outlook.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty climbs above 25,150 mark; metal shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-climbs-above-25150-mark-metal-shares-rally/1667574</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667574</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks erased all early losses and traded with modest gains in morning trade as value buying emerged after profit booking.

The key equity benchmarks erased all early losses and traded with modest gains in morning trade as value buying emerged after profit booking. However, investors largely adopted a risk-tolerance approach. The Nifty traded above the 25,150 mark. Metal shares advanced after declining in the past trading session. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 310.06points or 0.38% to 81,847.76. The Nifty 50 index rose 112.70 points or 0.43% to 25,156.70. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.23% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.16%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 2,353 shares rose and 1,524 shares fell. A total of 232 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Asian Paints (up 0.12%), Tata Consumer Products (up 0.92%), Aditya Vision (down 0.51%), Bikaji Foods International (down 0.35%), CG Power and Industrial Solutions (down 0.85%), Vodafone Idea (down 0.81%), International Gemmological Institute India (down 2.16%), Mahindra Logistics (up 0.76%), Marico (up 0.40%), Motilal Oswal Financial Services (down 2.09%), NESCO (down 2.51%), Raymond (up 2.23%), Spandana Sphoorty Financial (down 2.86%), Vishal Mega Mart (down 0.44%), and WeWork India Management (down 3.85%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index advanced 2.39% to 11,751.60. The index declined 0.83% in the past trading session. Adani Enterprises (up 4.92%), APL Apollo Tubes (up 3.67%), JSW Steel (up 3.19%), Hindustan Copper (up 3.1%) and Jindal Stainless (up 2.96%), Hindustan Zinc (up 2.92%), Vedanta (up 2.43%), National Aluminium Company (up 2.24%), Hindalco Industries (up 1.63%) and Tata Steel (up 1.54%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Indusind Bank fell 0.58% after the bank reported 88.5% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 161.16 crore on 13.67% fall in total income to Rs 13,079.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shriram Finance shed 0.29%. The NBFC’s standalone net profit declined 29.36% to Rs 2,521.67 crore on a 13.88% increase in total income to Rs 12,191.58 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DSP MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dsp-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1667578</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667578</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following scheme.

DSP Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following scheme. The amount of IDCW (Rs. per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: DSP Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.220000 DSP Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.220000 DSP Nifty Private Bank Index Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.600000 DSP Nifty Private Bank Index Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.600000 DSP Nifty 50 Equal Weight Index Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.100000 DSP Nifty 50 Equal Weight Index Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.200000 DSP Nifty 50 Index Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.100000 DSP Nifty Next 50 Index Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.100000 DSP Nifty Next 50 Index Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.200000 DSP Nifty Midcap 150 Quality 50 Index Fund – Regular Plan – Option: 0.700000

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GoI announces the sale of one dated security for a notified amount of &#8377;32,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/goi-announces-the-sale-of-one-dated-security-for-a-notified-amount-of-837732000-crore/1667569</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667569</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.48% Government Security 2035” for a notified amount of ₹32,000 crore.

The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.48% Government Security 2035” for a notified amount of ₹32,000 crore. The auction will be conducted using multiple price method on January 30, 2026 (Friday). GoI will have the option to retain additional subscription up to ₹2,000 crore against the security.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Consumer slumps after muted Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-consumer-slumps-after-muted-q3-performance/1667570</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667570</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In constant currency terms, revenue grew by 7% YoY.

In constant currency terms, revenue grew by 7% YoY. The growth in revenue was aided by volume growth of 7%. The company’s standalone business delivered strong performance, with underlying volume growth of 9% YoY and sales growth of 11% YoY. In contrast, the Indonesia business posted a 3% YoY decline in sales, despite underlying volumes expanding at a mid-single-digit rate. Meanwhile, the Africa, USA, and Middle East businesses recorded robust growth, with sales rising 19% YoY in INR terms and 8% YoY in constant currency terms. Total operating expenditure for the period under review was Rs 4,155.01 crore, up 7.9% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 699.98 crore, up by 2.7% from Rs 681.70 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Sudhir Sitapati, managing director, and CEO, GCPL, said: "Q3 FY26 has been a quarter of strong, broad-based performance for Godrej Consumer Products Limited, fully aligned with our expectations and strategic priorities. For the year, we remain confident of achieving high single-digit revenue growth at a consolidated level. Our India business is expected to deliver continued growth performance while holding normative EBITDA margins in the coming quarter. GAUM continues to perform well and deliver on its stated objectives of double-digit revenue and profit growth for the year. At a consolidated level, while temporary macroeconomic and pricing pressures in Indonesia and Latin America may moderate full-year EBITDA growth, we remain confident in a robust exit trajectory and sustained profitability momentum into FY27." Godrej Consumer Products is an Indian consumer goods company. The company's products include soap, hair colorants, toiletries and liquid detergents.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejConsumer_25192758531_21960.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[States' consolidated fiscal deficit widens to 3.3% in FY25: RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/states-consolidated-fiscal-deficit-widens-to-33-in-fy25-rbi/1667568</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667568</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[States' consolidated fiscal deficit has widened to 3.3 per cent of GDP in FY25 after remaining at 3 per cent for the three previous fiscals, the Reserve Bank said on Friday.

States' consolidated fiscal deficit has widened to 3.3 per cent of GDP in FY25 after remaining at 3 per cent for the three previous fiscals, the Reserve Bank said on Friday. The deficit exceeding 3 per cent mainly reflects 50-year interest free loans from the Centre under Special Assistance to States for Capital Investment, which is over and above the normal net borrowing ceiling of the States. In 2025-26, States have budgeted a gross fiscal deficit of 3.3 per cent of GDP, the central bank noted. The thrust on capital expenditure was sustained as capital expenditure remained steady at 2.7 per cent of GDP in 2023-24 and 2024-25 and is budgeted at 3.2 per cent of GDP in 2025-26. The consolidated outstanding liabilities of States remained elevated in the post-pandemic period with a budget estimate of 29.2 per cent of GDP at end-March 2026, RBI said.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund announces change in Exit Load Structure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hsbc-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-exit-load-structure/1667566</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667566</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following schemes stands revised with effect from January 30, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Exit Load Revised Exit Load HSBC Consumption Fund, HSBC Financial Services Fund, HSBC Infrastructure Fund i.

HSBC Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following schemes stands revised with effect from January 30, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Exit Load Revised Exit Load HSBC Consumption Fund, HSBC Financial Services Fund, HSBC Infrastructure Fund i. If the units redeemed or switched out are upto 10% of the units purchased or switched in (“the limit”) within 1 year from the date of allotment – Nil ii. If units redeemed or switched out are over and above the limit within 1 year from the date of allotment – 1% iii. If units are redeemed or switched out on or after 1 year from the date of allotment – Nil. • Withdrawal under SWP may also attract an Exit Load like any Redemption. • No Exit load will be chargeable in case of switches made between different plans and options within the Scheme. • No Exit load will be chargeable in case of Units allotted on account of IDCW reinvestments, if any. • Exit load is not applicable for Segregated Portfolio. i. If the units redeemed or switched out are upto 10% of the units purchased or switched in (“the limit”) within 90 days from the date of allotment – Nil ii. If units redeemed or switched out are over and above the limit within 90 days from the date of allotment – 1% iii. If units are redeemed or switched out on or after 90 days from the date of allotment – Nil. • Withdrawal under SWP may also attract an Exit Load like any Redemption. • No Exit load will be chargeable in case of switches made between different plans and options within the Scheme. • No Exit load will be chargeable in case of Units allotted on account of IDCW reinvestments, if any. • Exit load is not applicable for Segregated Portfolio.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI announces measures to manage liquidity conditions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-announces-measures-to-manage-liquidity-conditions/1667563</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667563</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank has decided to conduct the following operations to inject liquidity into the banking system, on a review of current liquidity and financial conditions.

The Reserve Bank has decided to conduct the following operations to inject liquidity into the banking system, on a review of current liquidity and financial conditions. The measures include a 90-day Variable Rate Repo (VRR) operation for an amount of Rs 25,000 crore to be conducted on January 30, 2026, a USD/INR buy-sell swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of 3 years to be held on February 4, 2026 and OMO purchase auctions of Government of India securities for an aggregate amount of ₹1,00,000 crore in two tranches of ₹50,000 crore each to be held on February 05, 2026, and February 12, 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indusind Bank drops after Q3 PAT plunges 88% YoY; NII slides 13% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indusind-bank-drops-after-q3-pat-plunges-88-yoy-nii-slides-13-yoy/1667556</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667556</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The profit before tax (PBT) fell 88.24% YoY to Rs 218.16 crore during the quarter.

The profit before tax (PBT) fell 88.24% YoY to Rs 218.16 crore during the quarter. The bank's financial results include the financial results of its wholly owned subsidiary, Bharat Financial Inclusion (BFIL), a business correspondent (BC) of the Bank involved in originating small ticket loans for the Bank and IndusInd Marketing and Financial Services Private (IMFS), an associate of the bank. The bank reported a 90.87% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 127.98 crore on 13.7% decline in total income to Rs 13,080.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Pre-provision operating profit (PPOP) stood at Rs 2,270 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 3,601 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net Interest Income (NII) declined 12.74% YoY to Rs 45.62 crore in Q3 FY26.Net interest margin (NIM) reduced to 3.52% in Q3 FY26 as against 3.93% in Q3 FY25. The bank’s deposits declined 3.82% to Rs 3,93,815 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 4,09,438 crore in Q3 FY25. CASA deposits stood at Rs 1,19,104 crore with current account deposits at Rs 31,416 crore and savings account deposits at Rs 87,688 crore. CASA deposits comprised 30% of total deposits as on 31st December 2025. Advances as of December 31, 2025, were Rs 3,17,536 crore, recording de-growth of 13.45% as against Rs 3,66,889 crores previous year Gross NPA were at 3.56% of gross advances as on December 31, 2025, as against 2.25% as Q3 FY25. Net NPA were 1.04% of net advances as on December 31, 2025, as compared to 0.68% as on Q3 FY25. The provision coverage ratio (PCR) was improved at 71.50% as on December 31, 2025. Provisions and contingencies for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, were Rs 2,096 crore as compared to Rs 1,744 crore for the corresponding quarter of previous year. The Bank's total capital adequacy ratio as per Basel III guidelines stands at 16.94% as on December 31, 2025, as compared to 16.46% as on December 31, 2024. Tier 1 CRAR was at 15.74% as on December 31, 2025, compared to 15.18% as on December 31, 2024. Risk-Weighted Assets were at Rs 4,01,497 crore as against Rs 4,20,519 crore a year ago. As of December 31, 2025, the Bank's distribution network included 3,120 branches/ Banking outlets and 3,063 onsite and offsite ATMs, as against 3,063 branches/banking outlets and 2,993 onsite and offsite ATMs, As of December 31, 2024. The client base stood at approx. 42 million as on December 31, 2025. Rajiv Anand, the MD and CEO, IndusInd Bank said: "During Q3FY26, the bank continued focus on optimisation of its balance sheet by letting go unprofitable loans and deposits along with being cautious on microfinance disbursements. The operating performance was steady with Pre-Provision Operating Profit at Rs 2,270 crore growing 11% QoQ. Our asset quality trends have been stable in all core businesses except in microfinance wherein industry is now showing early signs of recovery. Overall, the Bank has returned to profitability with a Profit After Tax of Rs. 128 crore. The Balance sheet remains robust with a healthy capital adequacy, excess liquidity and reducing stressed asset pool. We are optimistic about resilient domestic economy and aim to participate in the growth recovery in a calibrated manner." Indusind Bank offers a wide range of products and services for individuals and corporates, including microfinance, personal loans, personal and commercial vehicle loans, credit cards and SME loans.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndusIndBankLtd_64968625_5531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shriram Finance Q3 PAT slides 29% YoY to Rs 2,522 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shriram-finance-q3-pat-slides-29-yoy-to-rs-2522-cr/1667550</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667550</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 3,360.20 crore in Q3 FY26, down 23.91% as against Rs 4,415.92 crore reported in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 3,360.20 crore in Q3 FY26, down 23.91% as against Rs 4,415.92 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Net interest income grew 16.17% to Rs 6,764.09 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 5,822.69 crore recorded in the same period a year ago. As of 31 December 2025, total assets under management climbed 14.63% to Rs 291,709.03 crore compared to Rs 254,469.69 crore as of 31 December 2024. The liquidity coverage ratio was at 334.93% as of 31 December 2025, as against 265.24% as of 31 December 2024. The cost-to-income ratio increased to 29.66% in Q3 FY26 from 28.59% in Q3 FY25. The firm's return on assets (ROA) (including exceptional items) and return on equity (ROE) (including exceptional items) stood at 3.09% and 4.94%, respectively, in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Operating profit improved by 14.33% to Rs 4,670.52 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,084.98 crore in Q3 FY25. The board of directors had earlier, on 19 December 2025, approved a proposal to raise Rs 39,618 crore through a preferential issue of 47.11 crore fully paid-up equity shares of face value Rs 2 each at an issue price of Rs 840.93 per share to Japan-based MUFG Bank. The proposed allotment represents 20% of the post-preferential equity share capital on a fully diluted basis. The company said the requisite resolutions were approved by shareholders at the extraordinary general meeting held on 14 January 2026. The preferential issue is currently awaiting statutory and regulatory approvals. Upon completion, MUFG Bank will become a minority public shareholder in the company. Shriram Finance said its overseas subsidiary, Shriram Overseas Investments (SOIL), formerly known as Shriram Overseas Investments, became a wholly-owned subsidiary on May 9, 2025. SOIL holds an 81.63% stake in Bharat Investments Pte., Singapore, which has an associate entity in Bahrain. Shriram Finance is India's largest retail asset financing non-banking finance company (NBFC). It is the flagship company of the Shriram Group, which has a significant presence in consumer finance, life insurance, general insurance, housing finance, stock broking, and distribution businesses. Shares of Shriram Finance shed 0.92% to Rs 994.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShriramFinanceLtd_71599469_1745.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>