<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Gabion Technologies steps onto Dalal Street with measured confidence]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-gabion-technologies-steps-onto-dalal-street-with-measured-confidence/1664528</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664528</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 89, a premium of 9.88% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 89, a premium of 9.88% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently down 2.98% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 89 and a low of Rs 84.55. About 15.95 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Gabion Technologies India's IPO was subscribed 768.12 times. The issue opened for bidding on 6 January 2026 and it closed on 8 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 76 to Rs 81 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 36,00,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds to meet working capital requirements, to meet capex requirements for purchasing of plant and machinery and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Gabion Technologies on 5 January 2026, raised Rs 8.28 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 10.22 lakh shares at Rs 81 per share to 8 anchor investors. Gabion Technologies is engaged in the manufacturing, design, trading and installation of gabions, rockfall protection systems and geosynthetic materials used in civil engineering, infrastructure and environmental protection projects. The company operates through three verticals: manufacturing and supply of gabions, rockfall protection systems and geosynthetic products; design and construction of gabion structures, slope stabilisation and ground improvement solutions; and trading of auxiliary products. It caters to government, private and institutional clients and offers turnkey project execution capabilities. As of 30 November 2025, the company had 159 permanent employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 60.42 crore and net profit of Rs 4.30 crore for the period ended 30 November 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GABIONTECHNOLOGIESINDIALIMITED_39698997_94667.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maharashtra Scooters gains as Q3 PAT jumps 25% YoY to Rs 4 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maharashtra-scooters-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-25-yoy-to-rs-4-cr/1664527</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664527</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 5.55 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 28.77% increase from the Rs 4.31 crore reported in the same quarter last year.

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 5.55 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 28.77% increase from the Rs 4.31 crore reported in the same quarter last year. Total expenses declined sharply by 59.17% YoY to Rs 0.89 crore in Q3 FY26. Employee benefit expenses added 9.09% YoY to Rs 0.24 crore, while other expenses fell 55.86% YoY to Rs 0.64 crore in Q3 FY26. Maharashtra Scooters is engaged in the business of manufacturing dies, jigs, fixtures, and die-casting components primarily for the automobile industry.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahScooters_21126978849_363.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market trades near flatline; realty shares decline for 6th day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-trades-near-flatline-realty-shares-decline-for-6th-day/1664524</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664524</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded near the flatline with minor gains in mid-morning trade, as the Nifty hovered around the 25,800 mark amid optimism after the incoming U.S.

The headline equity benchmarks traded near the flatline with minor gains in mid-morning trade, as the Nifty hovered around the 25,800 mark amid optimism after the incoming U.S. ambassador to India announced that trade discussions between the two countries would begin on January 13. Investors were also tracking developments from the ongoing third-quarter earnings season. The Nifty traded near the 25,800 level, while realty shares extended losses for the sixth consecutive trading session. At 11:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 14.13 points or 0.02% to 83,892.30. The Nifty 50 index rose 7.85 points or 0.03% to 25,798.10. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.13% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.51%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,161 shares rose and 1,598 shares fell. A total of 227 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 6,85,110 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:25 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.03 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 41 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 17,10,75,14,400 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:25 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 49.31 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index dropped 1.01% to 854.60. The index tumbled 6.84% in the six consecutive trading sessions. Brigade Enterprises (down 2.57%), Godrej Properties (down 2%), DLF (down 1.71%), Lodha Developers (down 1.33%), Sobha (down 1.25%), Oberoi Realty (down 0.88%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.67%) and Anant Raj (down 0.53%) declined. On the other hand, Phoenix Mills (up 1.05%) and Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.43%) edged higher. Stocks in Spotlight: NLC India added 1.07% after the company’s board approved the listing of its wholly owned subsidiary, NLC India Renewables (NIRL), in line with the Government of India’s National Monetisation Pipeline targets. NBCC (India) slipped 2%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary HSCC (India) has entered into a memorandum of understanding with Bharat Electronics (BEL) to establish a strategic collaboration in the healthcare manufacturing and service ecosystem. Lotus Chocolate Company slumped 7.16% after the company’s standalone net profit tumbled 96.22% to Rs 0.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3.71 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 8.90% to Rs 133.63 crore in the third quarter of FY26 from Rs 146.69 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Most Asian markets traded higher on Tuesday as traders shrugged off geopolitical flashpoints in Iran and Venezuela, as well as a criminal investigation into U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Japan’s benchmark Nikkei 225 jumped 3.4% to lead gains in the region. Japan’s ruling Liberal Democratic Party is expected to dissolve the country’s Lower House later this month and opt for a snap election likely in February, according to media reports. Traders will also be keeping a close eye on oil prices amid ongoing protests in Iran. President Donald Trump is reportedly weighing options for intervention in Iran, according to multiple media reports. Trump in a social media post on Monday stateside reportedly said any country doing business with Iran will face a 25% tariff “on any and all business being done with the United States of America.” That new tariff on imports from Iran’s trading partners is “effective immediately.” Overnight in the U.S., stocks rallied off their session lows, with the S&P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average hitting new all-time highs. The S&P 500 rose 0.16% to end at 6,977.27, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average ticked up 86.13 points, or 0.17%, and settled at 49,590.20. Both indexes touched fresh all-time intraday highs and closed at records. The Nasdaq Composite was up 0.26% and closed at 23,733.90.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zydus Lifesciences’ US arm secures FDA nod for ZYCUBO in Pediatric Menkes Patients]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zydus-lifesciences-us-arm-secures-fda-nod-for-zycubo-in-pediatric-menkes-patients/1664514</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664514</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[This marks the first and only FDA-approved therapy for this rare and fatal genetic disorder in the United States.

This marks the first and only FDA-approved therapy for this rare and fatal genetic disorder in the United States. ZYCUBO® is not indicated for Occipital Horn Syndrome. Menkes disease, an X-linked recessive pediatric condition caused by mutations in the ATP7A gene, prevents patients from absorbing dietary copper, resulting in impaired copper transport across the blood-brain barrier. Untreated patients typically do not survive beyond three years of age. ZYCUBO is a subcutaneous injectable formulation that restores copper homeostasis and maintains copper levels in patients. Clinical trials demonstrated a statistically significant improvement in overall survival, with the early treatment cohort showing median survival of 177.1 months compared to 17.6 months for untreated patients, representing a nearly 80% reduction in risk of death. Common adverse reactions (≥7% incidence) included pneumonia, viral infection, respiratory failure, seizure, bacterial infection, hemorrhage, hypotension, vomiting, tachycardia, pyrexia, volume depletion, fracture, dyspnea, elevated transaminases, diarrhea, fungal infection, anemia, and local administration reactions. Commenting on the approval, Dr. Sharvil P. Patel, MD, Zydus Lifesciences, said, “This milestone marks a transformative moment for the Zydus Group and for families affected by Menkes disease. For the first time, patients have access to an approved therapy, offering hope where no options existed. We are proud to advance patient care and deliver innovative solutions to those who need them most.” Matt Heck, CEO of Sentynl, added, “FDA’s approval serves as compelling affirmation that a safe and effective therapy is now available for patients living with this devastating disease.” Dr. Stephen Kaler, clinical genetics specialist at Columbia University Medical Center, said, “Beginning copper histidinate therapy in affected neonates has been shown to reduce symptoms and prolong life. Increased awareness and rapid testing are critical.” Sentynl, which acquired ZYCUBO® from Cyprium Therapeutics in 2023, advanced the drug through final FDA review, receiving Breakthrough Therapy, Fast Track, Rare Pediatric Disease, and Orphan Drug designations. Copper histidinate has also been granted Orphan Drug status by the European Medicines Agency. This approval is expected to bring new treatment options to the rare disease community, reinforcing Zydus Group’s presence in the global pediatric therapeutics space. The Zydus Group, with an overarching purpose of empowering people with freedom to live healthier and more fulfilled lives, is an innovative, global life-sciences company that discovers, develops, manufactures, and markets a broad range of healthcare therapies. The group employs over 27000 people worldwide and is driven by its mission to unlock new possibilities in life sciences through quality healthcare solutions that impact lives. Zydus Lifesciences reported a 38.12% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,258.60 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 911.2 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 18.07% year on year (YoY) to Rs 6,037.9 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Zydus Lifesciences shed 0.15% to Rs 895 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CadilaHealth_93490673476_20883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Omaxe jumps after Rs 500 crore Ludhiana project announcement]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/omaxe-jumps-after-rs-500-crore-ludhiana-project-announcement/1664515</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664515</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock's gain reflects positive market sentiment around the large-scale commercial and residential project, which spans approximately 5.25 acres and aims to blend high-street retail, luxury residences, dining and entertainment in one integrated destination.

The stock's gain reflects positive market sentiment around the large-scale commercial and residential project, which spans approximately 5.25 acres and aims to blend high-street retail, luxury residences, dining and entertainment in one integrated destination. Omaxe said the land parcel, located in Ludhiana's established Ghumar Mandi commercial zone, was secured through a competitive bid conducted by the Rail Land Development Authority, and is being developed on a leasehold basis. Management highlighted that Omaxe Chowk is designed to offer structured, contemporary urban planning with enhanced connectivity, pedestrian-friendly spaces and significant parking facilities. The development is expected to boost local employment during construction and drive long-term economic activity through increased footfall, brand participation and retail engagement. The share price movement comes as investors react positively to Omaxe’s expanding portfolio and strategic push into experience-led, mixed-use urban destinations. Omaxe is an established real estate company, with over three decades of operating experience. The company operates with a diversified land bank and focuses on planned urban development across key regional markets. On a consolidated basis, Omaxe reported net loss of Rs 166.61 crore in Q2 September 2025 as against net loss of Rs 239.66 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales declined 17.57% YoY to Rs 320.82 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Omaxe_39688239239_27738.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T bags ‘significant’ order for Transportation Infrastructure biz]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-bags-significant-order-for-transportation-infrastructure-biz/1664513</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664513</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore.

As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore. The scope of work includes construction of a 2+2 lane, 3.2-km extradosed cable-stayed bridge with a maximum span of 177 meters, along with a 0.9-km approach road on the Kakdwip side and a 0.65-km approach road on the Sagar Island side. The bridge will be equipped with advanced traffic management systems, a bridge health monitoring system, architectural bridge lighting, and hybrid street lighting, along with all essential road furniture. The bridge will provide direct, all-weather connectivity to Sagar Island, which currently depends on ferry services that are often disrupted during adverse weather conditions. It is expected to benefit over two lakh residents of the island by improving mobility, healthcare access, and economic prospects. The project will also boost pilgrimage by ensuring safe and convenient travel for millions of devotees from across India to the annual Ganga Sagar Mela, the second-largest religious congregation after the Kumbh Mela. Larsen & Toubro is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services. The company reported a 15.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Larsen & Toubro rose 0.01% to currently trade at Rs 4,045.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NLC India gains after board nod to list NLC India Renewables ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nlc-india-gains-after-board-nod-to-list-nlc-india-renewables/1664510</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664510</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The proposed listing of NIRL will carried out through dilution of up to 25% equity stake in one or more tranches through Public Offer, subject to obtaining requisite approvals from the competent authorities.

The proposed listing of NIRL will carried out through dilution of up to 25% equity stake in one or more tranches through Public Offer, subject to obtaining requisite approvals from the competent authorities. The said in-principle approval shall be communicated to the Ministry of Coal for onward submission to the Department of Investment and Public Asset Management (DIPAM) for approval. In addition, the board approved an investment of up to Rs 66.60 crore in one or more tranches in NIRL, by way of subscription to equity shares at face value The funds will be utilised for financing green energy projects to be executed through joint venture companies. The company’s board declared of interim dividend of Rs 3.60 per equity share on the face value of paid-up equity shares of Rs 10 each for FY26. The record date for determining eligible shareholders has been fixed as 16 January 2026. NLC India is a public sector undertaking that is involved in lignite mining, coal mining, power generation and power trading. Government of India held 72.20% stake in the company as on 30 June 2025. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 27.1% to Rs 665.12 crore despite 14.2% jump in net sales to Rs 4,178.41 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NLCIndia_49674266520_2303.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Authum Investment & Infrastructure Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-authum-investment-infrastructure-ltd-counter/1664509</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664509</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[United Spirits Ltd, Max Financial Services Ltd, Coromandel International Ltd, Federal Bank Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 13 January 2026.

United Spirits Ltd, Max Financial Services Ltd, Coromandel International Ltd, Federal Bank Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 13 January 2026. Authum Investment & Infrastructure Ltd recorded volume of 69323 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 10.21 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6791 shares. The stock gained 5.06% to Rs.648.00. Volumes stood at 5998 shares in the last session. United Spirits Ltd witnessed volume of 6.26 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.84 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 63638 shares. The stock dropped 0.42% to Rs.1,322.30. Volumes stood at 8970 shares in the last session. Max Financial Services Ltd recorded volume of 90779 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 6.92 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 13112 shares. The stock lost 0.85% to Rs.1,648.00. Volumes stood at 3302 shares in the last session. Coromandel International Ltd recorded volume of 1.01 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 6.89 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 14732 shares. The stock gained 1.38% to Rs.2,320.00. Volumes stood at 10557 shares in the last session. Federal Bank Ltd saw volume of 8.52 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.66 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.51 lakh shares. The stock dropped 1.25% to Rs.249.80. Volumes stood at 88206 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AuthumInvestmentInfrastructureLtd_92141682878_31631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NBCC arm signs MoU with BEL for healthcare collaboration]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nbcc-arm-signs-mou-with-bel-for-healthcare-collaboration/1664506</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664506</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The collaboration will cover manufacturing and supply of medical devices, healthcare IT and digital solutions, consultancy, project execution, joint procurement, AMC and warranty support, and related advisory services.

The collaboration will cover manufacturing and supply of medical devices, healthcare IT and digital solutions, consultancy, project execution, joint procurement, AMC and warranty support, and related advisory services. Project-specific agreements will be executed separately. The company clarified that the MoU has been entered into in the normal course of business of the subsidiary. NBCC (India) is in business and operates in three major segments, namely project management consultancy, real estate, and engineering procurement & construction. The company's consolidated net profit advanced 25.21% to Rs 156.68 crore on an 18.99% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,910.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of NBCC (India) fell 1.67% to Rs 105.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NBCC_1807915630_13166.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks rebounds on value buying]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-rebounds-on-value-buying/1664504</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664504</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Despite the recovery, the stock remains under significant pressure over the medium to long term.

Despite the recovery, the stock remains under significant pressure over the medium to long term. Tejas Networks is down 33.55% over the past three months, has declined 43.22% in the last six months and has lost 60.11% over the past one year, reflecting sustained weakness in investor sentiment. On 9 January 2026, Tejas Networks reported a sharp deterioration in its quarterly performance, posting a consolidated net loss of Rs 196.55 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 165.67 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations plunged 88.38% year-on-year to Rs 306.79 crore, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Pre-tax loss for the quarter widened to Rs 302.87 crore, against a profit before tax of Rs 211.27 crore a year ago. On the balance sheet front, net debt declined to Rs 3,349 crore from Rs 3,738 crore in the previous quarter, largely due to lower working capital requirements, though partly offset by capital expenditure. Gross debt stood at Rs 885 crore, while cash and cash equivalents were Rs 537 crore. Tejas Networks designs and manufactures high-performance wireline and wireless networking products for telecommunications service providers, internet service providers, utilities, defence and government entities in over 75 countries. Tejas Networks Ltd. is a part of the Tata Group, with Panatone Finvest (a subsidiary of Tata Sons) being the majority shareholder.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India – Germany sign joint declaration of Intent on strengthening bilateral economic cooperation]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-germany-sign-joint-declaration-of-intent-on-strengthening-bilateral-economic-cooperation/1664502</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664502</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[At the invitation of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, Federal Chancellor of the Federal Republic of Germany, Friedrich Merz, paid an official visit to India from 12-13 January 2026.

At the invitation of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, Federal Chancellor of the Federal Republic of Germany, Friedrich Merz, paid an official visit to India from 12-13 January 2026. The Chancellor was accompanied by a high-level delegation including 23 leading German CEOs and industry leaders. This was Chancellor Merz’s first official visit to India and his first visit to Asia as Federal Chancellor, reflecting the high priority Germany attaches to India as a key strategic partner in the Indo-Pacific. The visit followed the successful 7th India–Germany Inter-Governmental Consultations (IGC) held in New Delhi on 25 October 2024, and comes at a high point in the journey of bilateral ties between the two countries, with completion of 25 years of India–Germany Strategic Partnership in 2025, and commemoration of 75 years of diplomatic relations in 2026. Both leaders sincerely appreciated the renewed momentum in bilateral engagement across government, business, civil society and academia that has played an instrumental role in advancing and deepening the Strategic Partnership. The two Leaders addressed India-Germany CEOs Forum and held restricted and delegation-level talks in Ahmedabad on 12 January 2026. They reaffirmed the shared democratic values, commitment to a rules-based international order, and mutual respect underpinning the Strategic Partnership. Both leaders reviewed bilateral relations and discussed regional and global developments. The Leaders welcomed the sustained growth in bilateral trade and investment and noted that bilateral trade reached a record high in 2024, with the positive trend continuing through 2025. India-Germany bilateral trade in goods and services surpassed USD 50 billion in 2024, amounting to over 25% of India’s trade with EU. The leaders noted the strong two-way investments between India and Germany and the positive impacts of such investments in diversifying global supply chains. They reaffirmed their commitment to fully realising untapped economic potential, including through SMEs, startups, digitalization, AI, and innovation-driven enterprises. Prime Minister Modi invited German companies to invest / expand businesses in India to benefit from its strong economic growth, business-friendly environment, large highly-skilled workforce and immense opportunities to scale up operations. Chancellor Merz recommended Germany as an attractive location for investment by Indian companies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lotus Chocolate tanks as Q3 PAT plunges 96% to Rs 0.14 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lotus-chocolate-tanks-as-q3-pat-plunges-96-to-rs-014-cr/1664500</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664500</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations declined 8.90% to Rs 133.63 crore in the third quarter of FY26 from Rs 146.69 crore recorded in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations declined 8.90% to Rs 133.63 crore in the third quarter of FY26 from Rs 146.69 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, profit before tax (PBT) was at Rs 0.52 crore in Q3 FY26, down 85.90% as against with Rs 3.69 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 4.35% to Rs 149.67 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 143.43 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of material consumed stood at Rs 19.71 crore (down 88.62%), employee benefit expenses were at Rs 8.52 crore (up 82.36%) and finance cost was at Rs 4.19 crore (up 97.64% YoY) during the period under review. In Q3 FY26, the company reported an EBITDA of Rs 5.67 crore, slightly lower than Rs 6.29 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. However, the EBITDA margin improved marginally to 4.0% from 3.8% in the year-ago quarter. For Q3 FY26, the company reported a net turnover of Rs 134 crore, down from Rs 147 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross margins stood at 9.31%, slightly lower than 9.78% a year ago, reflecting relative margin resilience despite significant market headwinds. Natarajan M. Venkataraman, Whole-time Director, said, “The company is poised to transition from a commodity-led model to a consumer-led growth engine. In pursuance of this transition, the company is also undertaking a structured review of existing B2B customer contracts to ensure alignment with the evolving consumer-led and integrated business model.” Lotus Chocolate Company manufactures the finest chocolates, cocoa products, and cocoa derivatives. Its products are supplied to chocolate makers and chocolate users across the world, from local bakeries to multinational companies. It is owned by Reliance Consumer Products (RCPL), which is the FMCG arm and a wholly owned subsidiary of Reliance Retail Ventures (RRVL), which is a subsidiary of Reliance Industries (RIL).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LotusChocolate_22571601181_2252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zelio E-Mobility rises after revenue rises 67% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zelio-e-mobility-rises-after-revenue-rises-67-yoy-in-q3/1664519</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664519</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The growth in revenue was supported by festive season demand, deeper penetration in Tier-2 and Tier-3 markets, and a diversified, value-driven product portfolio.

The growth in revenue was supported by festive season demand, deeper penetration in Tier-2 and Tier-3 markets, and a diversified, value-driven product portfolio. Importantly, growth remained broad-based and structural. "The company’s focus on capacity optimisation, cost efficiency, and profitable growth positions it well to sustain momentum into Q4 FY 2025-26 and beyond,” Zelio E-Mobility said. During the Diwali festive period, the company recorded a notable improvement in sales volumes and revenues compared to the corresponding period of the previous year. While the unit sales increased by 74% YoY, revenues grew by 64% YoY during the period under review. With strong demand visibility, company’s is expecting FY25-26 capacity utilization of 85% on its existing 72,000 units per annum base. The company has also executed a 70% capacity expansion plan, scaling total installed capacity to over 1,20,000 units per annum. The company further stated that the Odisha facility is expected to commence commercial operations from February 2026, while the Patan manufacturing facility to become operational by April 2026. Subject to stabilisation of the Odisha and Patan facilities, the company continues to evaluate opportunities for establishing an additional manufacturing / assembly facility in Southern India. In its outlook, the company said that it remains confident about sustained demand momentum in the slow speed EV segment, supported by increasing EV adoption, a favourable policy environment, and Zelio’s strong positioning in Tier-2 and Tier-3 markets. The company expects to remain positively positioned towards achieving a turnover of over Rs 260 crore in FY26, subject to market conditions and execution. Zelio E-Mobility is engaged in the manufacturing, assembling, and supplying of electric vehicles, offering a range of electric two-wheelers (E-2Ws) and three-wheelers (3Ws) available in various designs, colors, and speed variants.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZelioE-MobilityLtd_33924160_95333.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices pare early losses; Nifty trades above 25,800 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-pare-early-losses-nifty-trades-above-25800-level/1664501</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664501</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks reversed all early losses and traded with minor gains in the morning trade, supported by optimism after the incoming U.S.

The domestic equity benchmarks reversed all early losses and traded with minor gains in the morning trade, supported by optimism after the incoming U.S. ambassador to India announced that trade discussions between the two countries would begin on January 13. Investor sentiment was further influenced by the ongoing third-quarter earnings season. The Nifty traded above the 25,800 level, while pharma shares extended losses for the fourth consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 97.11 points or 0.11% to 83,975.28. The Nifty 50 index rose 33.30 points or 0.13% to 25,823.90. In the broader market, The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.03% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rallied 0.73%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 2,276 shares rose and 1,317 shares fell. A total of 237 shares were unchanged. Result Today: ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company (down 0.17%), ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company (down 0.77%), Tata Elxsi (up 0.94%), 5paisa Capital (down 2.20%), Just Dial (up 1.32%), Bank of Maharashtra (up 1.13%), Navkar Corporation (down 1.40%), Oriental Hotels (down 0.01%), Sigma Solve (up 5.15%) and Tokyo Plast International (down 1.85%) will release their quarterly earnings later today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index fell 0.93% to 22,457.50. The index dropped 3.55% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (down 2.6%), Dr Reddys Laboratories (down 1.31%), Cipla (down 1.17%), Ipca Laboratories (down 1.11%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (down 0.88%), Laurus Labs (down 0.81%), Mankind Pharma (down 0.68%), Torrent Pharmaceuticals (down 0.6%), Aurobindo Pharma (down 0.57%) and Divis Laboratories (down 0.53%) declined. On the other hand, Gland Pharma (up 0.49%), Biocon (up 0.42%) and Wockhardt (up 0.14%) edged higher. Stocks in Spotlight: Solex Energy slipped 1.10%. The company secured an order worth Rs 276 crore from a domestic independent power producer for the manufacture and supply of N-type TOPCon solar PV modules, providing fresh visibility to its order book. GTPL Hathway rallied 3.32% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 8.3% to Rs 11.01 crore on 5.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 932.62 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/franklin-templeton-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-scheme/1664505</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664505</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following scheme, With effect from 12 January 2026.

Franklin Templeton Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following scheme, With effect from 12 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager (s) Franklin India Multi Factor Fund • Arihant Jain • Arihant Jain • Mukesh Jain

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[M & B Engineering gains on bagging domestic order ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/m-b-engineering-gains-on-bagging-domestic-order/1664496</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664496</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said the order involves the design, engineering, manufacturing and supply of pre-engineered building and structural steel.

In a regulatory filing, the company said the order involves the design, engineering, manufacturing and supply of pre-engineered building and structural steel. The project is to be executed over a period of 8.5 months. Of the total order value, Rs 12.34 crore relates to erection work to be carried out by its subsidiary, Phenix Building Solutions. M&B Engineering said the order has been awarded by a domestic entity, but the name of the customer could not be disclosed due to confidentiality obligations. M&B Engineering is a design-focused engineering solutions provider in India. It provides turnkey solutions, covering project design, engineering, manufacturing and erection, tailored to meet specific requirements across the industrial and infrastructure sectors. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 7% to Rs 22.20 crore on a 48.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 306.85 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MBEngineeringLtd_29937596_35759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GTPL Hathway jumps after Q2 PAT climbs 8% YoY to Rs 11-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gtpl-hathway-jumps-after-q2-pat-climbs-8-yoy-to-rs-11-cr/1664495</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664495</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 14.7% Yo Y to Rs 15.24 crore in Q3 December 2025 During the quarter, revenue from digital cable TV fell 1.79% YoY to Rs 297 crore while revenue from broadband jumped 3.62% YoY to Rs 143.3 crore.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 14.7% Yo Y to Rs 15.24 crore in Q3 December 2025 During the quarter, revenue from digital cable TV fell 1.79% YoY to Rs 297 crore while revenue from broadband jumped 3.62% YoY to Rs 143.3 crore. EBITDA stood at Rs 118.9 crore in Q3 December 2025, registering the growth of 4.48% compared with Rs 113.8 crore in Q3 December 2024. EBITDA margin remained steady at 13% in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Broadband average revenue per user (ARPU) stood at Rs 465 per month per subscriber in Q3 December 2025. Anirudhsinh Jadeja – managing director, GTPL Hathway, said, “I am pleased to share that we have broadly sustained our active subscriber base across both Cable TV and Broadband businesses, underscoring the resilience of our operating model and the continued trust of our customers in a highly competitive environment. Our strategic focus remains firmly on enhancing customer experience and deepening engagement. We are progressively evolving beyond traditional Cable TV and Broadband by integrating value-added services such as OTT, Gaming and TV Everywhere, either as standalone offerings or in bundled formats, to address the rapidly changing content consumption preferences of our customers.\ Launch of GTPL Infinity, HITS Platform, represents a significant milestone in this journey. Backed by one of the world’s largest C-Band teleports in Ahmedabad, the platform enables seamless nationwide delivery of nearly 800 channels with high reliability. It empowers our partners to go live within 24 hours, optimise costs and unlock incremental growth opportunities.” GTPL Hathway is India’s largest MSO providing digital cable TV services and is one of the largest private wireline broadband service providers in India. The company is the largest digital cable TV and wireline broadband service provider in Gujarat and is a leading digital cable TV service provider in West Bengal.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GTPLHathwayLtd_80345872779_69803.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Government of India announces the sale of two dated securities for a notified amount of &#8377;31,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/government-of-india-announces-the-sale-of-two-dated-securities-for-a-notified-amount-of-837731000-crore/1664486</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664486</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.01% Government Security 2030” for a notified amount of ₹18,000 crore and New GS 2076 for a notified amount of Rs 13,000 crore.

The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.01% Government Security 2030” for a notified amount of ₹18,000 crore and New GS 2076 for a notified amount of Rs 13,000 crore. The auction will be conducted using multiple price method. Both competitive and non-competitive bids for the auction should be submitted in electronic format on the Reserve Bank of India Core Banking Solution (e-Kuber system) on January 16, 2026 (Friday). GoI will have the option to retain additional subscription up to ₹2,000 crore against each security.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TCS Q3 PAT drops 12% QoQ; board declares special dividend of Rs 46/ share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tcs-q3-pat-drops-12-qoq-board-declares-special-dividend-of-rs-46-share/1664478</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664478</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The decline in profitability was impacted due to one-time exceptional charges including Rs 2,120 crore related to the statutory impact of new labour codes and it also made a provision towards a legal claim of of Rs 1,010 crore during the December quarter.

The decline in profitability was impacted due to one-time exceptional charges including Rs 2,120 crore related to the statutory impact of new labour codes and it also made a provision towards a legal claim of of Rs 1,010 crore during the December quarter. On year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 13.92%, while revenue from operations increased 4.87% in Q3 FY26. The company’s YoY performance was supported by growth in key verticals, led by Life Sciences & Healthcare (+2.2%), along with steady gains in Energy, Resources and Utilities (ERU) (+2.2%) and Technology & Services (+1.7%) in Q3 FY26. The company’s order book total contract value (TCV) stood at $9.3 billion in Q3 December 2025, lower than $10 billion in Q2 September 2025 and $9.4 billion in Q1 June 2025. In constant currency terms, revenue growth stood at 0.8% QoQ in the Q3 FY26. Revenue from annualized AI Services stood at $1.8 billion, registering a 17.3% QoQ growth in constant currency. Operating and net margins stood at 25.2% and 20% during the quarter. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared a third interim dividend of Rs 11 per share and special dividend of Rs 46 per equity share of Rs 1 each of the company. The record date has been fixed as on Saturday, 17 January 2026 and payout will be made on Tuesday, 3 February 2026. K Krithivasan, chief executive officer (CEO) and managing director (MD), said “The growth momentum we witnessed in Q2FY26 continued in Q3FY26. We remain steadfast in our ambition to become the world’s largest AI-led technology services company, guided by a comprehensive five-pillar strategy. Our AI services now generate $1.8 billion in annualized revenue, reflecting the significant value we provide to clients through targeted investments across the entire AI stack, from Infrastructure to Intelligence.” Sudeep Kunnumal, chief HR officer, said “Our associates are at the heart of our transformation into an AI first enterprise. As of this quarter, there are over 217,000 associates with advanced AI skills, directly powering client success at scale. We doubled our intake of fresh graduates with higher order skills, rapidly expanding our next-generation talent pool. The passion and commitment our associates show in mastering next-gen capabilities gives us the confidence to innovate responsibly and deliver sustainable value as AI reshapes the services landscape.” TCS is a digital transformation and technology partner of choice for industry-leading organizations worldwide. The counter rose 0.27% to Rs 3,244.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TCS_30661368_5400.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends decline amid sustained weakness in equities ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-decline-amid-sustained-weakness-in-equities/1664470</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664470</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee edged lower in opening trades on Tuesday in line with sustained weakness in equities.

The Indian rupee edged lower in opening trades on Tuesday in line with sustained weakness in equities. Moreover, volatile geopolitical situation is keeping the domestic currency under pressure. INR opened at Rs 90.24 per dollar and fell to a low of 90.27 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee recovered from low levels and settled 2 paise higher at 90.16 against the US dollar on weak American currency and sliding crude oil prices. Equity market sentiment also improved after the new US envoy to India, Sergio Gor, said that both sides are actively engaged in firming up a trade deal. After opening weak and languishing in negative territory till about an hour past noon, Indian shares recovered and moved above the flat line on Monday, lifting the benchmark indexes Sensex and the Nifty50 to a positive close. The benchmark BSE Sensex settled with a gain of 301.93 points or 0.36% at 83,878.17, more than 1,000 points off the day's low of 82,861.07. The National Stock Exchange's Nifty50, which dropped to a low of 25,473.40, settled at 25,790.25, gaining 106.95 points or 0.42%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>