<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:26:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee posts marginal recovery]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-posts-marginal-recovery/1666762</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666762</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed slightly higher at 91.6375 per Dollar on Thursday (22 January 2026), versus its previous close of 91.6700 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies IPO subscribed 2.72 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shadowfax-technologies-ipo-subscribed-272-times/1666761</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666761</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 24,23,88,240 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Thursday (22 January 2026).

Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 24,23,88,240 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Thursday (22 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 2.72 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 January 2026 and it will close on 22 January 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. The Rs 1,907 crore IPO comprises a fresh issue of 80.6 million equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,000 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 73.2 million equity shares worth up to Rs 907.27 crore. Existing investors—Flipkart India, Eight Roads Investments Mauritius II, International Finance Corporation, Qualcomm Asia Pacific, Nokia Growth Partners, NewQuest Asia Fund and Miare Asset—will offload part of their holdings through the OFS. Shadowfax plans to utilize Rs 423.43 crore from the net proceeds of the fresh issue to enhance network infrastructure capacity, Rs 138.64 crore towards lease payments for new first-mile, last-mile and sort centres, and Rs 88.57 crore for branding, marketing and communication initiatives. The balance will be used for unidentified inorganic acquisitions and general corporate purposes. Shadowfax Technologies is a leading Indian logistics and 3PL player providing e-commerce, D2C, quick commerce and hyperlocal delivery services. It operates a nationwide network covering over 14,700 pin codes and serves major clients such as Flipkart, Meesho, Swiggy, Zomato, Blinkit and Nykaa. The company is among the fastest-growing large-scale logistics providers, with rising market share and strong order growth. Ahead of the IPO of Shadowfax Technologies on 19 January 2026, the company raised Rs 856.02 crore from anchor investors by allotting 6.90 crore shares at Rs 124 each to 39 anchor investors. For the three months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 21.04 crore and sales of Rs 1,805.64 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s power transmission network crosses 5 Lakh circuit km of transmission lines]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-power-transmission-network-crosses-5-lakh-circuit-km-of-transmission-lines/1666758</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666758</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s national power transmission network has achieved a critical milestone, crossing over 5 lakh circuit kilometres (ckm) of transmission lines (220 kV and above) along with 1,407 GVA of transformation capacity (220 kV and above).

India’s national power transmission network has achieved a critical milestone, crossing over 5 lakh circuit kilometres (ckm) of transmission lines (220 kV and above) along with 1,407 GVA of transformation capacity (220 kV and above). The world’s largest synchronous national grid achieved this feat on 14th January 2026, with the commissioning of 628 ckm Transmission Line of 765 kV from Bhadla II to Sikar II substation for evacuation of RE power from Rajasthan Renewable Energy Zone. With commissioning of this transmission line additional 1100 MW of power can be evacuated from RE zone of Bhadla, Ramgarh & Fatehgarh Solar Power Complex. Since April 2014, the country’s transmission network has grown by 71.6% with the addition of 2.09lakh ckm of transmission lines (220 kV and above), boosting transformation capacity (220 kV and above) by 876 GVA. The inter-regional power transfer capacity, which now stands at 1,20,340 MW, has enabled seamless transfer of electricity across regions, successfully realizing the vision of “One Nation – One Grid – One Frequency.” The addition to the transmission capacity will help to evacuate the increasing non-fossil power generation which is targeted at 500 GW by 2030.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-city-stock-market-data-and-charts-on-skyscrapers-b_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures inch closer to 123 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-inch-closer-to-123-mark/1666756</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666756</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures inch lower to end at 91.63.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures inch lower to end at 91.63. GBP/INR inched up whereas EUR/INR slipped by 0.21% to end at 122.95 and 107.16 respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR recovers marginally from all-time low levels]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-recovers-marginally-from-all-time-low-levels/1666753</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666753</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee rebounded marginally from its all-time low levels and gained 3 paise to close at 91.62 (provisional) against the US dollar on Thursday amid a positive trend in domestic equities.

The Indian rupee rebounded marginally from its all-time low levels and gained 3 paise to close at 91.62 (provisional) against the US dollar on Thursday amid a positive trend in domestic equities. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 91.54 then gained ground to touch an intraday high of 91.48 against the greenback. It touched a low of 91.68 before settling for the day at 91.62 (provisional), up 3 paise from its all-time low levels. Indian shares rebounded on Thursday to snap a three-day losing streak amid eased EU-U.S. tensions over Greenland. Global cues were positive after U.S. President Donald Trump dropped plans to impose tariffs on several European countries over Greenland, saying a "framework" for a potential agreement with respect to the entire Arctic Region has been reached after talks with Nato. The BSE Sensex hit an intraday high of 82,783.18 before paring some gains to end the session up 397.74 points, or 0.49 percent, at 82,307.37. The broader NSE Nifty index closed up 132.40 points, or 0.53 percent, at 25,289.90, after hitting a high of 25,435.75 earlier.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude tanks under $60 per barrel as markets eye supplies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-tanks-under-60-per-barrel-as-markets-eye-supplies/1666751</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666751</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil futures fell from around one-week high with a dop under $60 per barrel weighing on the sentiments.

WTI Crude oil futures fell from around one-week high with a dop under $60 per barrel weighing on the sentiments. The counter currently trades at $59.57 per barrel, down 1.70% on the day as generous global supply scenario capped gains. According to the latest monthly report released by the International Energy Agency, crude oil markets experienced heightened volatility at the start of the New Year as geopolitical tensions surrounding Iran and Venezuela briefly pushed prices higher. Despite these geopolitical risks, the IEA notes that global oil markets remain well supplied. Benchmark prices are still about $16/bbl lower than a year ago, reflecting a large supply surplus built over the past 12 months. Global oil inventories rose by 470 mb in 2025, supported by strong non-OPEC+ supply growth and rising stocks in China and the United States. With supply projected to increase by a further 2.5 mb/d in 2026 and demand expected to grow by 930 kb/d, ample buffers are likely to keep prices in check in the near term.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/steel-long-pipes-in-crude-oil-factory-during-sunset-picture_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper tanks to two-week low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-tanks-to-two-week-low/1666749</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666749</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures turned lower today.

COMEX Copper futures turned lower today. The metal stayed under sustained pressure amid a rise in LME Copper inventories and tested around two-week low. It currently trades at $5.71 per pound, down 0.86% on the day. Copper fell despite mixed cues from equities. In Asia, Shanghai Composite index added 0.14% while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index gained 0.17%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index spiked 1.73%, bouncing after latest wave of correction. European stocks edged up as geopolitical worries eased. The US stocks saw significant volatility over the course of the trading day on Wednesday. The major indices jumped more than one percent on the day. COMEX Copper futures have shed around 2% this week.it had lost more than 1% in previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices snap three-session slide on global risk-on mood]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-snap-three-session-slide-on-global-risk-on-mood/1666744</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666744</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equities rebounded on Thursday after three consecutive sessions of losses, snapping the recent decline and restoring some investor confidence.

Domestic equities rebounded on Thursday after three consecutive sessions of losses, snapping the recent decline and restoring some investor confidence. The BSE Sensex and the Nifty 50 rose sharply in early trade, tracking a positive global market trend that lifted risk appetite. The Sensex jumped more than 800 points at the day’s high, while the Nifty 50 moved back above the 25,400 level, before trimming part of the gains later in the session. PSU banks and chemical shares advanced while consumer durables and realty shares were under pressure. Market sentiment improved amid a broader rebound in global equities. Comments from Russian President Vladimir Putin helped ease geopolitical concerns, while remarks from former US President Donald Trump raised hopes of progress on a potential US-India trade agreement. Optimism around a possible European Union trade deal also supported risk-taking. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 397.74 points or 0.49% to 82,307.37. The Nifty 50 index rose 132.40 points or 0.53% to 25,289.90. In the previous three sessions, the Sensex slipped 1.99% while the Nifty declined 2.09%. Bharat Electronics (up 3.75%), Adani Ports & SEZ (up 2.57%) and State Bank of India (up 1.95%) boosted the Nifty today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 1.28%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 1.13%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,951 shares rose and 1,280 shares fell. A total of 161 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 3.12% to 13.35. World Economic Forum: Maharashtra Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis said Tata Sons has committed $11 billion to develop the proposed innovation city. While the location has been identified and broad contours finalized, the state expects the planning phase to take another six to eight months before execution begins. The project aims to create a "plug-and-play" ecosystem tailored for startups and innovation-led companies, lowering entry barriers for entrepreneurs as well as global firms. Britain will not sign US President Donald Trump’s proposed Board of Peace treaty on Thursday, Foreign Secretary Yvette Cooper said, citing concerns over Russia’s potential involvement in the initiative aimed at resolving global conflicts. She said the UK would not be among the signatories, as the legal treaty raises broader issues and because of concerns over President Vladimir Putin’s role in a peace initiative. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.24% to 6.639 as compared with the previous close of 6.655. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6000 compared with its close of 90.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement dropped 0.91% to Rs 1,51,469. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.01% to 98.57. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.26% to 4.240. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement lost 71 cents or 1.09% to $64.53 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently up by 194 points, signaling a strong opening for US stocks today. European indices advanced on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said a “framework” agreement had been reached over Greenland, and called off imposing escalating tariffs on a group of European countries. Asian indices ended higher, tracking overnight gains on Wall Street after U.S. President Donald Trump dialed back his threat to impose tariffs on European countries over Greenland. Trump also said at the World Economic Forum in Davos that he would not use force to acquire the Arctic island, calming nerves over a possible U.S. military action, adding that he had “formed the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland,” along with NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. Meanwhile, South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. U.S. equities leaped on Wednesday after President Donald Trump called off new Europe tariffs, saying a deal framework has been reached over Greenland. Meanwhile, Russian President Vladimir Putin said he is not concerned about the issue. "What happens to Greenland is none of our business," Putin said in his televised remarks at the national Security Council meeting late on Wednesday night. The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged 588.64 points, or 1.21%, to end at 49,007.23. The S&P 500 gained 1.16% and closed at 6,875.62, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.18% to settle at 23,224.82. Back in Washington, Supreme Court justices expressed skepticism about whether Trump has the authority to fire Lisa Cook as a Federal Reserve governor. During oral arguments Wednesday, Justice Brett Kavanaugh told a Trump administration lawyer that arguments the president can fire Cook without judicial review “would weaken, if not shatter, the independence of the Federal Reserve." Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Consumer Care was locked in a 20% upper circuit after the company’s net profit rose 83.2% YoY to Rs 46.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 25.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 32.7% YoY to Rs 306.1 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 230.7 crore in Q3 FY25. V-Mart Retail rallied 3.21% after the company reported a standalone net profit of Rs 87.99 crore in Q3 FY26, up 22.83% from Rs 71.63 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 9.70% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,126.38 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Eternal fell 2.61%. The company reported a 72.88% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 102 crore on a 201.85% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 16,315 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dr Reddy’s Laboratories rose 5.34%. The company reported a 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1209.8 crore despite a 4.4% jump in revenue to Rs 8,716.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Anant Raj added 2.66% after the company reported a 30.75% year-on-year (YoY) increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 110.32 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Radico Khaitan jumped 5.69% after the company reported 61.6% increase in net profit to Rs 155.1 crore on a 19.5% rise in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,546.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Bank of India rallied 5.62% after the bank’s standalone net profit jumped 7.47% to Rs 2,705 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,517 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income stood at Rs 21,205.95 crore in Q3 FY26, up 6.25% as against Rs 19,956.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Gravita India declined 2.42%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 25.33% to Rs 97.67 crore on 2.07% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,017.07 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Zee Entertainment Enterprises added 3.86% after the company’s net profit surged 102.99% to Rs 155.29 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 76.5 crore in Q2 FY26. Total income rallied 15.17% to Rs 2,298.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Waaree Energies surged 9.29% after the company reported a 115.64% year-on-year (YoY) jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,062.46 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 492.69 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Indian Bank rallied 5.66% after the bank’s standalone net profit jumped 7.33% to Rs 3,061.48 crore on 9.78% increase in total income to Rs 19,663.34 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 24,18,75,720 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:40 IST on Thursday (22 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 2.71 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan Bank Q3 PAT tumbles 52% YoY to Rs 206 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-bank-q3-pat-tumbles-52-yoy-to-rs-206-cr/1666743</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666743</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As of December 31, 2025, total deposits stood at Rs 1.57 lakh crore, compared to Rs 1.41 lakh crore in the previous year, reflecting a year-on-year growth of 11%.

As of December 31, 2025, total deposits stood at Rs 1.57 lakh crore, compared to Rs 1.41 lakh crore in the previous year, reflecting a year-on-year growth of 11%. CASA Deposits stood at Rs 42,730 crore and CASA Ratio stood at 27%, CASA + Retail TD to total deposit ratio stands above 72%. Gross advances jumped 10% to Rs 1.45 lakh crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 1.32 lakh crore as of 31st December 2024. On a YoY basis, Retail book (other than housing) grew 57%, Wholesale Banking grew 32%, and the Housing book showed a growth of 10% (excluding IBPC). The collection efficiency for EEB loans was higher at 98.2% for Q3 FY26. Provision Coverage Ratio (Including Technical Write-offs) as of December 31, 2025, is 84.3%. On a quarter on quarter (QoQ) basis the bank's standalone net profit and total income jumped 83.9% and 7.8% , respectively in Q3 FY26. Operating profit was Rs 1,445 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 1,310 crore in Q2 FY26, up 10% . The provisions (other than tax) & contingencies charged to the Profit and Loss for Q3 FY26 were at Rs 1,155 crore, flat QoQ Net interest income (NII) as of Q3 FY26, stood at Rs 2,688 crore compared to Rs 2,589 crore as of Q2 FY26, representing a growth of 3.8% QoQ. Net Interest Margin (NIM) for the quarter was 5.9% in Q3 FY26, compared to 5.8% in Q2 FY26 On asset quality front, gross non-performing assets (GNPA) reduced by 169 bps to 3.3% in Q3 FY26 from 5% in Q2 FY26. Net NPA fell by 38 bps to 1% in Q3 FY26 from 1.4% in Q2 FY26. MD & CEO, Partha Pratim Sengupta said, "Bandhan Bank’s third quarter performance over the last quarters reflects the strengthening fundamentals and steady turn around. In Q4, we are set to accelerate multiple digital initiatives aimed at enhancing customer experience, operational efficiency, and scalability. We remain fully committed to building a strong, more resilient and more diversified bank. These efforts position us well for sustainable and profitable growth going forward.” Bandhan Bank is a private sector bank. The Bank’s distribution network spans more than 6,350 outlets. The Bank currently has more than 74,500 employees. The scrip jumped 3.57% to settle at Rs 142.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BandhanBankLtd_94952261769_68090.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at a premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-a-premium/1666742</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666742</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,375, a premium of 85.1 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,289.90 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,375, a premium of 85.1 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,289.90 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index rose 132.40 points or 0.53% to 25,289.90. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 3.12% to 13.35. HDFC Bank, Eternal and Reliance Industries were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex ends 398 pts higher; Nifty settles above 25,250 marks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-ends-398-pts-higher-nifty-settles-above-25250-marks/1666741</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666741</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity indices ended with substantial losses today, breaking a three-day losing streak as selective profit booking and continued FII selling kept investors cautious ahead of key Q3 earnings announcements and cues from the World Economic Forum in Davos.

The headline equity indices ended with substantial losses today, breaking a three-day losing streak as selective profit booking and continued FII selling kept investors cautious ahead of key Q3 earnings announcements and cues from the World Economic Forum in Davos. The Nifty settled above the 25,250 mark. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 397.74 points or 0.49% to 82,307.37. The Nifty 50 index rose 132.40 points or 0.53% to 25,289.90. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 1.28%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 1.13%. The market breadth was strong. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 3.12% to 13.35. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Media index (up 2.39%), the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 2.34%) and the Nifty Chemical (up 1.84%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Consumer Durables index (down 0.87%), Nifty Realty index (down 0.74%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 0.36%) and the underperformed the Nifty 50 index. World Economic Forum: Maharashtra Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis said Tata Sons has committed $11 billion to develop the proposed innovation city. While the location has been identified and broad contours finalized, the state expects the planning phase to take another six to eight months before execution begins. The project aims to create a “plug-and-play” ecosystem tailored for startups and innovation-led companies, lowering entry barriers for entrepreneurs as well as global firms. Britain will not sign US President Donald Trump’s proposed Board of Peace treaty on Thursday, Foreign Secretary Yvette Cooper said, citing concerns over Russia’s potential involvement in the initiative aimed at resolving global conflicts. She said the UK would not be among the signatories, as the legal treaty raises broader issues and because of concerns over President Vladimir Putin’s role in a peace initiative. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.24% to 6.639 as compared with the previous close of 6.655. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6000 compared with its close of 90.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement dropped 0.91% to Rs 1,51,469. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.01% to 98.57. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.26% to 4.240. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement lost 71 cents or 1.09% to $64.53 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets advanced on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said a “framework” agreement had been reached over Greenland, and called off imposing escalating tariffs on a group of European countries. Asian markets ended higher, tracking overnight gains on Wall Street after U.S. President Donald Trump dialed back his threat to impose tariffs on European countries over Greenland. Trump also said at the World Economic Forum in Davos that he would not use force to acquire the Arctic island, calming nerves over a possible U.S. military action, adding that he had “formed the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland,” along with NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. Meanwhile, South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. U.S. equities leaped on Wednesday after President Donald Trump called off new Europe tariffs, saying a deal framework has been reached over Greenland. The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged 588.64 points, or 1.21%, to end at 49,007.23. The S&P 500 gained 1.16% and closed at 6,875.62, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.18% to settle at 23,224.82. Back in Washington, Supreme Court justices expressed skepticism about whether Trump has the authority to fire Lisa Cook as a Federal Reserve governor. During oral arguments Wednesday, Justice Brett Kavanaugh told a Trump administration lawyer that arguments the president can fire Cook without judicial review “would weaken, if not shatter, the independence of the Federal Reserve."

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[V-Mart Retail gains after Q3 PAT climbs 23% YoY to Rs 72 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/v-mart-retail-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-23-yoy-to-rs-72-cr/1666740</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666740</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 9.70% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,126.38 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 9.70% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,126.38 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax was at Rs 115.02 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a growth of 64.92% as against Rs 69.74 crore posted in Q3 FY25. On the segmental front, revenue from the Retail segment was Rs 1,120.23 crore (up 10.23% YoY) and revenue from the Digital Marketplace was Rs 10.67 crore (down 21.71% YoY) in the Dec’26 quarter. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit soared 313.49% YoY to Rs 112.72 crore, while revenue increased 13.93% YoY to Rs 2,818.47 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. V-Mart is engaged in the business of value retailing through the chain of stores situated in various cities in India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VMartRetail_17420315948_34162.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Media Index records a surge of 2.39%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-media-index-records-a-surge-of-239/1666739</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666739</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Media index ended up 2.39% at 1386.35 today.

Nifty Media index ended up 2.39% at 1386.35 today. The index has lost 2.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Prime Focus Ltd rose 5.47%, Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd jumped 4.29% and Nazara Technologies Ltd added 3.19%. The Nifty Media index has decreased 17.00% over last one year compared to the 9.22% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index increased 2.34% and Nifty Pharma index gained 1.59% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.53% to close at 25289.9 while the SENSEX increased 0.49% to close at 82307.37 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finance-108655__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers snap 3-day losses; Nifty ends above 25,250; VIX slides 3.12%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-snap-3-day-losses-nifty-ends-above-25250-vix-slides-312/1666738</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666738</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with modest cuts today, breaking a three-day losing streak as selective profit booking and continued FII selling kept investors cautious ahead of key Q3 earnings announcements and cues from the World Economic Forum in Davos.

The key equity benchmarks ended with modest cuts today, breaking a three-day losing streak as selective profit booking and continued FII selling kept investors cautious ahead of key Q3 earnings announcements and cues from the World Economic Forum in Davos. The Nifty traded above the 25,250 mark. Media, PSU bank and pharma stocks advanced, while consumer durables and realty stocks declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 397.74 points or 0.49% to 82,307.37. The Nifty 50 index rose 132.40 points or 0.53% to 25,289.90. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 1.28%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 1.13%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,957 shares rose and 1,274 shares fell. A total of 154 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 3.12% to 13.35. World Economic Forum: Maharashtra Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis said Tata Sons has committed $11 billion to develop the proposed innovation city. While the location has been identified and broad contours finalized, the state expects the planning phase to take another six to eight months before execution begins. The project aims to create a “plug-and-play” ecosystem tailored for startups and innovation-led companies, lowering entry barriers for entrepreneurs as well as global firms. Britain will not sign US President Donald Trump’s proposed Board of Peace treaty on Thursday, Foreign Secretary Yvette Cooper said, citing concerns over Russia’s potential involvement in the initiative aimed at resolving global conflicts. She said the UK would not be among the signatories, as the legal treaty raises broader issues and because of concerns over President Vladimir Putin’s role in a peace initiative. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 23,95,32,360 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:40 IST on Thursday (22 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 2.69 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index advanced 2.39% to 1,386.35. The index rose 2.06% after declining over the previous four trading sessions. Prime Focus (up 5.47%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 4.29%), Nazara Technologies (up 3.19%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (up 2.73%), Network 18 Media & Investments (up 2.58%), Saregama India (up 2.04%), Sun TV Network (up 1.38%), PVR Inox (up 0.86%), Tips Music (up 0.7%) jumped. Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Consumer Care was locked in a 20% upper circuit after the company’s net profit rose 83.2% YoY to Rs 46.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 25.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 32.7% YoY to Rs 306.1 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 230.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Eternal fell 2.61%. The company reported a 72.88% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 102 crore on a 201.85% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 16,315 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dr Reddy’s Laboratories rose 5.34%. The company reported a 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1209.8 crore despite a 4.4% jump in revenue to Rs 8,716.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Jindal Stainless added 0.65%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 26.56% to Rs 828.79 crore on a 6.16% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 10,517.55 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (HPCL) shed 0.29%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 34.72% to Rs 4,072.49 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3,022.90 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income (excluding excise duty) rose 5.23% YoY to Rs 1,15,740.02 crore during the December 2025 quarter. Anant Raj added 2.66% after the company reported a 30.75% year-on-year (YoY) increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 110.32 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Radico Khaitan jumped 5.69% after the company reported 61.6% increase in net profit to Rs 155.1 crore on a 19.5% rise in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,546.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) rose 0.16%. The company reported a 2.30% year-on-year (YoY) decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 46.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 47.71 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 22.90% YoY to Rs 1,320.81 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Bank of India rallied 5.62% after the bank’s standalone net profit jumped 7.47% to Rs 2,705 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,517 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income stood at Rs 21,205.95 crore in Q3 FY26, up 6.25% as against Rs 19,956.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Gravita India declined 2.42%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 25.33% to Rs 97.67 crore on 2.07% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,017.07 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Zee Entertainment added 3.86% after the company’s net profit surged 102.99% to Rs 155.29 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 76.5 crore in Q2 FY26. Total income rallied 15.17% to Rs 2,298.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Waaree Energies surged 9.29% after the company reported a 115.64% year-on-year (YoY) jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,062.46 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 492.69 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Indian Bank rallied 5.66% after the bank’s standalone net profit jumped 7.33% to Rs 3,061.48 crore on 9.78% increase in total income to Rs 19,663.34 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets advanced on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said a “framework” agreement had been reached over Greenland, and called off imposing escalating tariffs on a group of European countries. Asian markets ended higher, tracking overnight gains on Wall Street after U.S. President Donald Trump dialed back his threat to impose tariffs on European countries over Greenland. Trump also said at the World Economic Forum in Davos that he would not use force to acquire the Arctic island, calming nerves over a possible U.S. military action, adding that he had “formed the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland,” along with NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. Meanwhile, South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. U.S. equities leaped on Wednesday after President Donald Trump called off new Europe tariffs, saying a deal framework has been reached over Greenland. The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged 588.64 points, or 1.21%, to end at 49,007.23. The S&P 500 gained 1.16% and closed at 6,875.62, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.18% to settle at 23,224.82. Back in Washington, Supreme Court justices expressed skepticism about whether Trump has the authority to fire Lisa Cook as a Federal Reserve governor. During oral arguments Wednesday, Justice Brett Kavanaugh told a Trump administration lawyer that arguments the president can fire Cook without judicial review “would weaken, if not shatter, the independence of the Federal Reserve."

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Orient Electric gains as Q3 PAT zooms 115% QoQ to Rs 26 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/orient-electric-gains-as-q3-pat-zooms-115-qoq-to-rs-26-cr/1666731</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666731</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, Orient Electric’s net profit surged 115.4% to Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 12.1 crore in Q2 FY26.

On a consolidated basis, Orient Electric’s net profit surged 115.4% to Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 12.1 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations rallied 906.45% to Rs 29.01 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax soared 167.42% to Rs 43.59 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company's consolidated net profit tanked 4.4% while total income surged 10.97% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax, excluding a one-time exceptional item of Rs 8.7 crore related to the new Labour Codes, increased 19.0% YoY. EBITDA gained 10.6% to Rs 67.7 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 61.2 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin remained unchanged at 7.5% in Q3 FY26, compared with 7.5% in Q3 FY25. Ravindra Singh Negi, MD & CEO, Orient Electric, said, “Orient Electric delivered a resilient and well-balanced performance in Q3 FY26. Despite the seasonal softness in our cooling categories, we achieved 11.0% year on year revenue growth, underscoring the strength of our diversified portfolio and the continued success of our One Orientstrategy. Our Heating category posted strong double-digit growth, complimented by sustained momentum in Lighting, Switchgear & Wires, accelerating our transition towards a multi-engine growth model. Through disciplined cost management and operating leverage, we were able to maintain a steady operating EBITDA margin even as commodity inflation persisted. Our focus continues to be on building a more premium, digital and consumer centric Orient with category leadership in BLDC, luminaries and heating while continuing to build scale in B2B Lighting, Switchgear and Wires.” The company has announced an interim dividend of Rs 0.75 per equity share (face value Rs 1) for FY2025-26 and fixed Thursday, January 29, 2026, as the record date to determine shareholders eligible for the dividend. The interim dividend will be paid to the entitled shareholders within 30 days from the date of declaration. Orient Electric is one of the leading consumer electrical brands in India with a diverse portfolio of fans, lighting, home appliances and switch-gears. The company takes pride in its R&D capabilities, spirit of continuous innovation and commitment to manufacturing cutting-edge lifestyle electrical products that meet the needs and expectations of modern consumers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OrientElectricLtd_17456055300_71670.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Bank climbs after Q3 PAT rises 7% YoY to Rs 3,061 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-bank-climbs-after-q3-pat-rises-7-yoy-to-rs-3061-cr/1666726</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666726</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Operating profit (profit before provisions and contingencies) stood at Rs 5,023.58 crore in Q3 FY26, up 5.77% YoY.

Operating profit (profit before provisions and contingencies) stood at Rs 5,023.58 crore in Q3 FY26, up 5.77% YoY. Net interest income (NII) increased 7.50% YoY to Rs 6,896 crore as of 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 6,415 crore as of 31st December 2024. Total deposits increased 12.62% to Rs 7,90,923 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 702,282 crore in as of 31st December 2024. As of 31st December 2025, current, savings & CASA deposits grew by 19.13%, 8.45%, and 9.86% YoY respectively. Gross advances jumped 14.24% to Rs 638,848 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 559,199 crore as of 31st December 2024. RAM (Retail, Agriculture & MSME) advances grew by 16.65% YoY to Rs 3,90,459 crore as of 31st December 2025 from Rs 3,34,739 crore as of 31st December 2024. RAM contribution to gross domestic advances stood at 66.06% during the quarter. As of 31 December 2025, retail, agriculture, and MSME advances increased 18.54%, 15.14%, and 16.41% YoY, respectively. On asset quality front, gross non-performing assets (GNPA) reduced by 103 bps to 2.23% as of 31st December 2025 as against 3.26% as of 31st December 2024. Net non-performing assets (NNPA) declined by 6 bps to 0.15% as of 31st December 2025, compared with 0.21% as of 31st December 2024. Capital adequacy ratio improved by 66 bps to 16.58% as of 31st December 2025. CET-I improved by 127 bps YoY to 14.54%, Tier I Capital improved by 77 bps YoY to 14.54% in December 2025. Indian Bank has many deposit schemes tailored to suit the needs of its customers, both individuals and organizations. Credit/advances/loan schemes specifically designed for its customers. Also, it offers various novel services to customers, both individuals and organizations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndianBank_77867287520_6061.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Radico Khaitan surges after PAT rises nearly 62% YoY in Q3 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/radico-khaitan-surges-after-pat-rises-nearly-62-yoy-in-q3/1666708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666708</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[For Q3 FY26, total IMFL volume was 9.75 million cases (up 16.7% YoY), Prestige & Above volume was 4.62 million cases (up 25.9% YoY) and Regular & Others volume was 4.70 million cases (up 32.7% YoY).

For Q3 FY26, total IMFL volume was 9.75 million cases (up 16.7% YoY), Prestige & Above volume was 4.62 million cases (up 25.9% YoY) and Regular & Others volume was 4.70 million cases (up 32.7% YoY). Total expenses for the December’25 quarter was Rs 1,333.2 crore, up by 14.4% YoY. EBITDA improved by 44.9% YoY to Rs 265.4 crore while EBITDA margin expanded by 300 basis points to 17.2% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 206.6 crore, up by 59% from Rs 129.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Net debt as on 31 March 2025 stood at Rs 365.0 crore, which is a reduction of Rs 208.5 crore since 31 March 2025. Dr. Lalit Khaitan, chairman & managing director, said: "The Indian spirits sector continues to exhibit strong momentum, underpinned by steady demand and an accelerating shift towards premiumization, trends that were clearly visible during the festive quarter. Q3 FY26 marked a remarkable step-up in Radico Khaitan’s performance, translating favorable consumer trends into the best-ever quarterly results across all key parameters. Driven by a premium-led portfolio, a stable raw material environment and enhanced operating leverage, we delivered meaningful margin expansion and stronger return ratios." Radico Khaitan is among the oldest and one of the largest manufacturers of Indian-made foreign liquor (IMFL) in India. It is one of the few companies in India to have developed its entire brand portfolio organically.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RadicoKhaitan_11315875496_2153.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SSWL Q3 PAT declines 2% YoY to Rs 47 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sswl-q3-pat-declines-2-yoy-to-rs-47-crore/1666705</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666705</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations jumped 22.90% YoY to Rs 1,320.81 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

However, revenue from operations jumped 22.90% YoY to Rs 1,320.81 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax for the third quarter of FY26 stood at Rs 61.65 crore, marking a decline of 4.19% from Rs 64.35 crore in the same period last year. On a full-year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit slipped 3.90% YoY to Rs 129.37 crore, while total revenue surged 210.28% YoY to Rs 3,708.17 crore in FY26 compared with FY25. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) is engaged in the manufacturing of steel wheel rims catering to different segments of the automobile industry. The firm operates in the automotive wheel segment. Its geographical segments include India and overseas. The counter rose 0.19% to Rs 186.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SteelStrWheel_50831874606_1338.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential MF resumes subscriptions in Smallcap Fund from January 23]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mf-resumes-subscriptions-in-smallcap-fund-from-january-23/1666706</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666706</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund said it will resume subscriptions in the ICICI Prudential Smallcap Fund with effect from 23 January 2026, after withdrawing all earlier restrictions on investments at the PAN level.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund said it will resume subscriptions in the ICICI Prudential Smallcap Fund with effect from 23 January 2026, after withdrawing all earlier restrictions on investments at the PAN level. From the effective date, the asset manager will accept transactions across all modes, including fresh and additional lump-sum purchases, switches into the scheme, and new registrations under Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) and Systematic Transfer Plans (STPs). The move follows the fund house’s earlier decision to temporarily suspend subscriptions in its Midcap Fund and Smallcap Fund from 14 March 2024, citing investor protection concerns amid prevailing market conditions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/notebook-with-mutual-funds-sign-on-a-table-business-concept_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold retreats from records levels on firmer dollar; profit taking]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-retreats-from-records-levels-on-firmer-dollar-profit-taking/1666704</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666704</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices pulled back in Asian trade after hitting fresh record highs, slipping below $4,800 per ounce as investors booked profits and the US dollar held firm near 98.6.

Gold prices pulled back in Asian trade after hitting fresh record highs, slipping below $4,800 per ounce as investors booked profits and the US dollar held firm near 98.6. The retreat came as geopolitical and trade tensions eased after President Donald Trump softened his stance on Greenland and rolled back tariff threats following a framework understanding with NATO, although details remain unclear and Denmark rejected any talks on sovereignty. Market attention is now on upcoming US weekly jobless claims and delayed PCE inflation data for fresh cues on the economic outlook. The Federal Reserve is widely expected to keep interest rates unchanged next week, while markets continue to price in around 50 basis points of rate cuts later this year. In India, MCX February gold futures fell nearly 1% to Rs 151,640 per 10 grams, retreating from the lifetime high of Rs 158,475 recorded in the previous session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>