<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:17:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concord Control Systems bags Rs 54-cr KAVACH 4.0 order from Indian Railways]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concord-control-systems-bags-rs-54-cr-kavach-40-order-from-indian-railways/1680004</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680004</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract covers the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of onboard KAVACH 4.0 equipment.

The contract covers the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of onboard KAVACH 4.0 equipment. The company confirmed that promoters and group companies have no interest in the awarding entity, and the order does not qualify as a related party transaction. Concord Control Systems is India's leading manufacturer of embedded electronics systems and critical electronic solutions supporting India’s next-generation rail infrastructure. The company is an RDSO-approved OEM and technology leader delivering advanced electrical and electronic systems for Indian Railways. On a consolidated basis, the company had reported 93.48% jump in net profit to Rs 16.02 crore on a 63.92% increase in revenue to Rs 81.55 crore in H1 FY26 over H1 FY25. Shares of Concord Control Systems added 1.58% to end at Rs 2,435 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ConcordControlSystemsLtd_63232532_77868.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[South West Pinnacle bags Rs 307-cr exploration order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/south-west-pinnacle-bags-rs-307-cr-exploration-order/1679998</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679998</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract is slated for execution over four years post-mobilization, with key terms including mobilization of machines, manpower, and resources within 45 days; construction of the approach road by SWPE; and adherence to safety, labor, environmental, and mining engineering standards, while statutory and environmental clearances will be arranged by HMESPL.

The contract is slated for execution over four years post-mobilization, with key terms including mobilization of machines, manpower, and resources within 45 days; construction of the approach road by SWPE; and adherence to safety, labor, environmental, and mining engineering standards, while statutory and environmental clearances will be arranged by HMESPL. SWPEL is an integrated service provider, providing end-to-end drilling & exploration of natural resources, viz., coal, ferrous, non-ferrous & atomic minerals, conventional & non-conventional oil & gas, and groundwater investigation. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 121.6% to Rs 9.22 crore on a 29.1% increase in net sales to Rs 62.67 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of South West Pinnacle Exploration rose 0.14% to end at Rs 183.30 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SouthWestPinnacleExplorationLtd_51702201_71774.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kabra Extrusiontechnik bags order worth Rs 133 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kabra-extrusiontechnik-bags-order-worth-rs-133-crore/1679994</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679994</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract pertains to contract manufacturing and is scheduled to be executed during FY 2026–27.

The contract pertains to contract manufacturing and is scheduled to be executed during FY 2026–27. Due to confidentiality obligations and commercial sensitivity, the name of the customer has not been disclosed. The company clarified that the order has been awarded by a domestic entity. It further stated that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not fall under related party transactions. KEL is a part of the Kolsite group of companies. It manufactures plastic extrusion machinery and mono- and multilayer blown film plants, used in industries such as pipes and packaging. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 4.98 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared to a net profit of Rs 7.04 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Net sales declined 8.9% year-on-year to Rs 110.34 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of Kabra Extrusiontechnik rose 2.40% to end at Rs 256 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KabraExtrusion_60412874996_1227.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aurobindo Pharma arm receives 4 observations after US FDA inspection]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aurobindo-pharma-arm-receives-4-observations-after-us-fda-inspection/1679993</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679993</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The facility (Unit-I), located at Kolthur Village, Shameerpet Mandal, Ranga Reddy, Telangana, was inspected from 16 February to 27 February 2026, and the inspection concluded with four observations.

The facility (Unit-I), located at Kolthur Village, Shameerpet Mandal, Ranga Reddy, Telangana, was inspected from 16 February to 27 February 2026, and the inspection concluded with four observations. The company said it will respond to the US FDA within the stipulated timelines. The company confirmed there is no impact on its financials or operations due to the inspection. Aurobindo Pharma stated its commitment to maintaining high-quality manufacturing standards across all its facilities worldwide and said it will update the stock exchanges if there is any further information. Aurobindo Pharma is principally engaged in the manufacturing and marketing of active pharmaceutical ingredients, generic pharmaceuticals, and related services. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 7.6% to Rs 910.29 crore on a 9% increase in net sales to Rs 8,604.51 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Aurobindo Pharma shed 0.04% to end at Rs 1,221.55 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurobindoPharma_66877283489_4666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITCONS E-Solution secured order worth Rs 3 crore from HAL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itcons-e-solution-secured-order-worth-rs-3-crore-from-hal/1679992</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679992</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves deployment of 43 resources for a period of two years.

The contract involves deployment of 43 resources for a period of two years. It will commence on 3 March 2026 and remain valid till 2 March 2028, unless extended by mutual agreement between the parties. The company clarified that the order has been awarded by a domestic entity and pertains to manpower outsourcing services. It further stated that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity, and the contract does not fall under related party transactions. ITCONS E-Solutions is engaged in the business of recruitment and staffing services. On a full-year basis, the company’s net profit surged 70.2% to Rs 3.25 crore on a 96.4% rise in net sales to Rs 55.98 crore in FY25 over FY24. Shares of ITCONS E-Solution slipped 2.47% to end at Rs 349.95 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITCONSESolutionsLtd_70007426_78414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Artefact Projects secures Rs 4-cr consultancy contract from NHAI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/artefact-projects-secures-rs-4-cr-consultancy-contract-from-nhai/1679991</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679991</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and will be executed over a period of 36 months.

The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and will be executed over a period of 36 months. The total consideration for the contract stands at Rs 3,53,09,279.5. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group or group companies have any interest in the awarding authority. It further stated that the contract does not fall within the ambit of related party transactions. Artefact provides engineering, architectural, and project management services for infrastructure projects, especially highways. Having a global presence through collaboration with renowned international consultants, experienced technical experts, and professionals, together with a dedicated management, Artefact is a leading name in the sector. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 34.67% to Rs 1.67 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1.24 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations declined 8.04% to Rs 6.74 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7.33 crore in Q3 FY25. Shares of Artefact Projects declined 1.05% to end at Rs 60.33 on the BSE. As of February 28, the company’s market capitalisation stood at Rs 43.89 crore on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArtefactProject_28267864_5779.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Camlin Fine Sciences promoter Ashish Dandekar pledges 18 lakh shares]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/camlin-fine-sciences-promoter-ashish-dandekar-pledges-18-lakh-shares/1679989</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679989</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As per the disclosure, the pledge was created on 24 February 2026 in favour of HDFC Bank to facilitate borrowing by the company.

As per the disclosure, the pledge was created on 24 February 2026 in favour of HDFC Bank to facilitate borrowing by the company. Following the transaction, the total number of shares encumbered by Ashish Dandekar stands at 88,00,000 shares, representing 4.58% of the company’s total equity. Prior to this, 70,00,000 shares, or 3.64% of the equity, were already pledged. Ashish Dandekar holds 1,97,78,510 shares in the company, accounting for 10.30% of the total share capital, with about 44.5% of his personal holding currently pledged. As of December 2025, promoters collectively held 48.03% in the company. The latest pledge alone represents 0.94% of the company's total equity. Camlin Fine Sciences is a specialty chemicals company engaged in the research, development, manufacturing and marketing of a diversified portfolio spanning shelf-life solutions, aroma ingredients, performance chemicals, and health and wellness products, catering to multiple industrial and consumer segments. On a consolidated basis, Camlin Fine Sciences reported net loss of Rs 36.23 crore in Q3 December 2025 as against net loss of Rs 4.14 crore in Q3 December 2024. Net sales rose 6.07% YoY to Rs 457.20 crore in Q3 December 2025. Shares of Camlin Fine Sciences surged 6.72% to settle at Rs 148.50 on Friday, 27 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CamlinFine_47161285570_27793.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oriental Rail Infrastructure bags Rs 2-cr order from ICF Chennai]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oriental-rail-infrastructure-bags-rs-2-cr-order-from-icf-chennai/1679987</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679987</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves the manufacturing, supply and installation of 13 sets of “one coach set of seats and berths with hardware.” The order is to be executed by March 29, 2026.

The contract involves the manufacturing, supply and installation of 13 sets of “one coach set of seats and berths with hardware.” The order is to be executed by March 29, 2026. As per the terms of the contract, up to 80% of the supply portion will be paid upon submission of the Inspection Certificate and Provisional Physical Receipt Certificate. The remaining 20% of the supply portion, along with 100% of installation charges, will be paid after receipt and acceptance of stores by the consignee based on the Installation Certificate issued by the competent authority. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group or group companies have any interest in the awarding authority. It also confirmed that the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Oriental Rail Infrastructure is engaged in the manufacturing and supply of several diversified railway products and items for Indian Railways and other related industries. Its products include seat & berths, recorn, compreg board & articles thereof, furniture & parts, coated upholstery fabric, plywood, phenolic resin & hardener, silicon foam, etc. The firm reported a 83.77% growth in consolidated net profit to Rs 13.82 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 7.52 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 10.31% YoY to Rs 168.57 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of Oriental Rail Infrastructure fell 1.68% to end at Rs 129.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OrientalVeneerProductsLtd_6722154754_15746.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PPFAS Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ppfas-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1679979</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679979</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PPFAS Mutual Fund has announced that Ms.

PPFAS Mutual Fund has announced that Ms. Sonal Dave has been appointed as an Independent Director with effect from February 17, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Ms. Sonal Dave Age: 61 years Designation: Independent Director Qualification: B. Com, Chartered Accountant .

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vishal Mega Mart promoter Samayat Services sells 14% stake for Rs 7,635 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vishal-mega-mart-promoter-samayat-services-sells-14-stake-for-rs-7635-crore/1679973</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679973</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Samayat Services LLP, a promoter entity of Vishal Mega Mart, has divested nearly a 14% stake in the supermarket chain through open market transactions, raising Rs 7,635.55 crore on Friday, 27 February 2026.

Samayat Services LLP, a promoter entity of Vishal Mega Mart, has divested nearly a 14% stake in the supermarket chain through open market transactions, raising Rs 7,635.55 crore on Friday, 27 February 2026. According to bulk deal data on the NSE, Samayat Services sold 65.25 crore equity shares in two tranches at prices ranging between Rs 117 and Rs 117.03 per share. The sale represents a 13.96% stake in the Gurugram-based retailer. Following the transaction, the promoter’s holding in Vishal Mega Mart declined to 40.13% from 54.09%. On the buy side, a clutch of large institutional investors absorbed a significant portion of the stake. The Government of Singapore acquired 12.69 crore shares, translating into a 2.72% holding, while HDFC Mutual Fund picked up 9.40 crore shares or a 2.01% stake. The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) purchased 7.33 crore shares, representing a 1.57% stake. Collectively, these investors bought over 29.42 crore shares, or 6.3% equity, at an average price of Rs 117 per share, with the aggregate deal value pegged at Rs 3,443.17 crore. Samayat Services LLP has been gradually trimming its holding in the company since Vishal Mega Mart’s listing in December 2024. In June 2025, it had sold around 90 crore shares, representing a 19.6% stake, for about Rs 10,220 crore. Several large institutional investors, including SBI Mutual Fund and HDFC Mutual Fund, had participated in that earlier transaction. Vishal Mega Mart is a leading retail player. It offers products across three major product categories, i.e., apparel, general merchandise and FMCG, through a pan-India network of 771 Vishal Mega Mart stores as of 31 December 2025 and Vishal Mega Mart mobile application and website. It reported a 19.10% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 312.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 262.72 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 17.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 3,670.41 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of Vishal Mega Mart slumped 7.68% to settle at Rs 117.80 on Friday, 27 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VishalMegaMartLtd_95033477_86391.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quality Power Electrical bags orders worth Rs 34-cr for supply of HVDC reactors]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quality-power-electrical-bags-orders-worth-rs-34-cr-for-supply-of-hvdc-reactors/1679972</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679972</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders have been awarded by a domestic entity.

The orders have been awarded by a domestic entity. However, the name of the awarding entity has not been disclosed due to a non-disclosure agreement (NDA), the company clarified. The contracts pertain to the supply of HVDC reactors and are scheduled to be executed over a period of approximately 18 months. The company further stated that the promoter, promoter group, and group companies have no interest in the entity awarding the orders. It also confirmed that the contracts do not fall under related party transactions. Quality Power Electrical Equipment is engaged in the business of energy transition equipment and power technologies. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 220.69% to Rs 62.76 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 19.57 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25. The counter declined 3.99% to end at Rs 868.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/QualityPowerElectricalEquipmentsLtd_48177673_54766.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1679974</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679974</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 March 2026.

SBI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 March 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager New Fund Manager SBI Nifty Index Fund SBI BSE Sensex Index Fund SBI Nifty Next 50 Index Fund SBI BSE SENSEX ETF SBI Nifty Next 50 ETF SBI Nifty Bank ETF SBI Nifty 50 ETF SBI Nifty 200 Quality 30 ETF SBI Gold Fund Mr. Raviprakash Mr. Viral Chhadva SBI Nifty Midcap 150 Index Fund SBI Nifty Smallcap 250 Index Fund SBI Nifty India Consumption Index Fund SBI Nifty Bank Index Fund SBI Nifty IT Index Fund SBI Nifty IT ETF SBI Nifty Private Bank ETF SBI Nifty Consumption ETF SBI Silver ETF Fund of Fund Mr. Harsh Sethi Mr. Viral Chhadva SBI Gold ETF SBI SILVER ETF Ms. Vandna Soni Mr. Viral Chhadva SBI Equity Minimum Variance SBI BSE SENSEX Next 50 ETF Mr. Raviprakash Sharma Mr. Harsh Sethi Ms. Sukanya Ghosh

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[H.G. Infra Engineering bags LOA from NHAI for Odisha road project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hg-infra-engineering-bags-loa-from-nhai-for-odisha-road-project/1679950</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679950</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package III, stretching from Gobindpur on NH-55 to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza on NH-16.

The project involves the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package III, stretching from Gobindpur on NH-55 to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza on NH-16. The total project length stands at 40.33 km. The project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode. While the estimated project cost is Rs 1,827.33 crore, HGINFRA's bid project cost stands at Rs 1,582.11 crore, excluding applicable GST. The construction period for the project is 910 days. HGINFRA is an infrastructure development company. The company specialises in executing end-to-end Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) services and Hybrid Annuity Model (HAM) projects across transport infrastructure, renewable energy, and Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) including Transmission. On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit fell 18.1% to Rs 94.28 crore on a 12.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,421.16 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of H.G. Infra Engineering fell 2.8% to settle at Rs 541.85 on Friday, 27 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HGInfraEngineeringLtd_52714149365_71631.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta declared preferred bidder for Karnapodikonda bauxite block in Odisha]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-declared-preferred-bidder-for-karnapodikonda-bauxite-block-in-odisha/1679949</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679949</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said it received a 'Declaration of Preferred Bidder' notification from the Directorate of Mines and Geology, Government of Odisha, on 27 February 2026.

In a regulatory filing, the company said it received a 'Declaration of Preferred Bidder' notification from the Directorate of Mines and Geology, Government of Odisha, on 27 February 2026. The tender process was initiated through a Notice Inviting Tender dated 4 December 2025 for grant of a mining lease for the block. After qualifying at the initial bid stage, Vedanta participated in the live e-auction process and emerged as the preferred bidder. According to the tender document, the Karnapodikonda bauxite block is classified at the G2 level of exploration and spans a total area of 532.747 hectares. The company said the acquisition aligns with its strategic objective of backward integration for its aluminium business, strengthening long-term raw material security. Vedanta is a global producer of critical minerals, energy transition metals, power, and technology, with operations across India, South Africa, Namibia, Liberia, the UAE, Saudi Arabia, Korea, Taiwan, and Japan. It is the world’s largest integrated zinc producer, the fourth-largest silver producer, and among the top aluminium producers globally. Vedanta is also India’s only private oil and gas producer and one of the country’s largest private power generators. On a consolidated basis, Vedanta's net profit surged 60.98% to Rs 5,710 crore while revenue from operations jumped 36.95% YoY to Rs 23,369 crore in Q3 December 2025. Shares of Vedanta fell 2.56% to settle at Rs 718.45 on Friday, 27 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>