<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ola Electric slumps as Q3 revenue drops 55% YoY; net loss narrows to Rs 487 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ola-electric-slumps-as-q3-revenue-drops-55-yoy-net-loss-narrows-to-rs-487-crore/1677947</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677947</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Deliveries stood at 32,680 units in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% YoY from 84,029 units and down 37.9% QoQ from 52,666 units.

Deliveries stood at 32,680 units in Q3 FY26, down 61.1% YoY from 84,029 units and down 37.9% QoQ from 52,666 units. Premium deliveries fell 79.3% YoY to 6,065 units and declined 54.8% QoQ. Mass segment deliveries dropped 51.4% YoY and 32.2% QoQ to 26,612 units. However, cells produced rose sharply to 72,418 units, up 90.2% QoQ from 38,080 units. On a consolidated basis, revenue from operations stood at Rs 470 crore, declining 55.0% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and 31.9% QoQ from Rs 690 crore. Automotive and cell sales dropped 53.1% YoY and 35.5% QoQ to Rs 433 crore. Production-linked incentive income declined 69.4% YoY, though increased 94.7% QoQ to Rs 37 crore. Gross profit came in at Rs 161 crore, down 17.0% YoY and 24.4% QoQ. However, gross margin improved to 34.3%, compared with 30.9% in Q2 FY26 and 18.6% in Q3 FY25. Total operating expenses stood at Rs 432 crore, down 33.9% YoY, but up 3.8% QoQ. R&D expenses rose 124.1% YoY and 8.3% QoQ to Rs 65 crore. SG&A expenses declined 38.1% YoY and 4.4% QoQ, while other operating expenses fell 42.2% YoY but increased 5.6% QoQ. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss stood at Rs 323 crore, widening from Rs 258 crore in Q2 FY26 but improving from Rs 494 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA margin was -68.7%, compared with -37.4% in Q2 FY26 and -47.3% a year ago. Net loss for the quarter stood at Rs 487 crore, widening from Rs 418 crore in Q2 FY26 but narrowing compared with Rs 564 crore in Q3 FY25. Cash flow from operations remained negative at Rs 575 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a negative Rs 255 crore in Q2 FY26 and negative Rs 851 crore in Q3 FY25. Free cash flow stood at negative Rs 781 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with negative Rs 405 crore in Q2 FY26 and negative Rs 1,076 crore in Q3 FY25. In the automotive segment, revenue from operations stood at Rs 467 crore, down 55.3% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and lower by 32.1% QoQ from Rs 688 crore. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss stood at Rs 167 crore, improving significantly from a loss of Rs 373 crore in Q3 FY25 but widening from a loss of Rs 102 crore in Q2 FY26. Adjusted EBITDA margin was -35.8%, broadly in line with -35.7% YoY, but weaker than -14.8% in Q2 FY26. In the cell segment, revenue from operations stood at Rs 9 crore, up from Rs 3 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 4 crore in Q2 FY26, reflecting scaling up of cell operations. Adjusted operating EBITDA loss widened to Rs 39 crore, compared with losses of Rs 8 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 27 crore in Q2 FY26. Adjusted EBITDA margin deteriorated sharply to -228.5%, versus -29.6% YoY and -100.0% QoQ. Ola Electric spokesperson said, "Q3 FY26 marks a structural reset for Ola Electric. We chose to fix the fundamentals by restoring service execution, resetting our cost structure, and deepening vertical integration. The result is a leaner operating model with materially lower breakeven and industry-leading gross margins. With service metrics stabilising and our Gigafactory transitioning into commercial scale deployment, we are positioned to enter the next phase of growth with significantly improved operating leverage." Ola Electric Mobility is India's leading electric vehicle (EV) manufacturer. It specialises in the vertical integration of technology and manufacturing for EVs and their components, including battery cells.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlaElectricMobilityLtd_81720871_75559.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crisil jumps after Q4 PAT rises 7.5% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crisil-jumps-after-q4-pat-rises-75-yoy/1677944</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677944</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, the company's income from operations for Q4 2025 was up 18.5% to Rs 1,081.6 crore, compared with Rs 912.9 crore in Q4 2024.

On a consolidated basis, the company's income from operations for Q4 2025 was up 18.5% to Rs 1,081.6 crore, compared with Rs 912.9 crore in Q4 2024. Profit before tax for Q4 2025 was up 10.9% to Rs 326.5 crore, compared with Rs 294.5 crore in Q4 2024. Profit after tax was up 7.5% to Rs 241.5 crore, compared with Rs 224.7 crore in Q4 2024. Crisil's consolidated income from operations in FY 2025, was up 11.9% to Rs 3,649 crore, compared with Rs 3,259.8 crore in FY 2024. Consolidated total income, rose 12.1% to Rs 3,755.6 crore, compared with Rs 3,349.4 crore in FY 2024. Profit before tax was up 12.4% to Rs 1,041 crore, compared with Rs 926.5 crore in FY 2024. Profit after tax was up 12% to Rs 766 crore, compared with Rs 684.1 crore in FY 2024. The above results include impact of new labour codes of Rs 16.8 crore for the fourth quarter and year ended 31 December 2025. Crisil Ratings maintained its leadership in corporate bond ratings. Its revenue grew 14.3% on year in Q4 2025, and 15.7% in FY 2025. Overall, the Ratings segment revenue grew 14.4% in Q4 2025 and 18.4% in FY 2025. The research, analytics and solutions segment revenue grew 20.1% in Q4 2025 and 9.4% in FY 2025. The board has recommended a final dividend of Rs 28 per share (of Re 1 face value), taking the total dividend for the year to Rs 61 per share. Amish Mehta, managing director & CEO, Crisil, "We saw strong revenue and EBITA growth compared with last year, driven by consistent financial delivery and operational resilience across our businesses. While a dynamic macroeconomic backdrop persists, we are committed to delivering sustainable growth through continuous investments in creating new products and solutions, expanding our client footprint, and developing future-ready talent. We focus on creating domain-led GenAI solutions that drive competitiveness by enhancing client experiences and insights and augmenting operational efficiencies. Notably, Crisil is marching towards its 40th year of making markets function better, driven by deep institutional intelligence and rich experience honed by economic cycles, reforms and shocks, and as a steadfast ally in the Viksit Bharat quest." Crisil is a global, insights-driven analytics company. Headquartered in India, Crisil is majority owned by S&P Global. Founded in 1987 as India’s first credit rating agency, its services spans across businesses: Crisil Ratings, Crisil Intelligence, Crisil Coalition Greenwich and Crisil Integral IQ. Crisil’s global workforce operates in the Americas, Asia-Pacific, Europe, Australia and the Middle East.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CRISIL_25806077903_3265.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tenneco Clean Air drops after Q3 PAT slips 5% YoY to Rs 119 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tenneco-clean-air-drops-after-q3-pat-slips-5-yoy-to-rs-119-cr/1677943</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677943</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 16.07% YoY to Rs 191.76 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional item and tax increased 16.07% YoY to Rs 191.76 crore during the quarter. Exceptional items of Rs 271.68 crore were linked to labour code charges. EBITDA climbed 24.8% YoY to Rs 222.5 crore during the quarter, supported by operating leverage, commercial actions, and effective cost management. Value added revenue (VAR) rose 14.7% to Rs 1,194.1 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by increased volumes and new programs. Segment-wise, revenue from Clean Air & Powertrain Solutions increased 5.4% YoY to Rs 564.4 crore while revenue from advanced ride technologies jumped 24.5% YoY to Rs 629.7 crore in Q3 FY26. In Q3 FY26, the company’s DaVinci DCx advanced suspension system was selected by a leading Indian OEM for its new flagship SUV platform. The program, with an estimated annual value of around Rs 220 crore, reinforces the company’s ability to deliver superior ride quality through mechanical innovation, offering an affordable, market-ready solution without reliance on advanced electronics or software. Additionally, the company secured a strategic Clean Air program from a global commercial vehicle OEM for a modular inline BSVI aftertreatment system, carrying an annual revenue potential of approximately Rs 115 crore. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the proposal for capacity expansion by setting up a new factory at Kharkhoda, Haryana. At present, the company has installed capacity of 2.79 million cold end products (mufflers and exhaust pipes) and 1.97 million hot end products (catalytic converters) and the proposed capacity addition will add approximately 130,000 - cold end products and around 256,000 - hot end products. Arvind Chandra, whole-time director and CEO, Tenneco India, said: “The quarter demonstrated sustained execution across our business. We delivered strong business growth, resilient margins, and meaningful progress across Clean Air, Powertrain, and Advanced Ride Technologies. Our Clean Air strategic program win demonstrates our ability to translate the voice of the customer into high-velocity execution, enabled by resident engineering support and a disciplined focus on first- time-right validation. Supporting the Clean Air growth trajectory, the Board has approved to develop a greenfield plant in North India (Kharkhoda, Haryana) to strengthen proximity to our northern customer base and support awarded programs across Light Vehicle, Off-Highway and Tractor segments. The project envisages around Rs 71 crore capex with estimated start of production in Q3 FY27, further enhancing Tenneco’s operational footprint and customer responsiveness. In Exports, our order book remains very strong, reflecting a higher mix versus domestic business and supporting better margins. Recent tariff and duty reductions announced by the U.S. and EU are expected to further strengthen these tailwinds and accelerate export growth. Notably, our current order book already covers 100% of projected FY2028 revenue, underpinning a double-digit CAGR growth over the next three years.” Tenneco Clean Air India is part of the Tenneco Group, a US-headquartered, global Tier-1 automotive component supplier. The company manufacture and supply critical, highly engineered, and technology- intensive clean air, powertrain, and suspension solutions tailored to the needs of Indian OEMs and the export market.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TennecoCleanAirIndiaLtd_96264302_83464.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikran Engg slips after Q3 PAT tumbles 38% YoY to Rs 21 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikran-engg-slips-after-q3-pat-tumbles-38-yoy-to-rs-21-cr/1677942</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677942</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) fell 42.9% YoY to Rs 25.92 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) fell 42.9% YoY to Rs 25.92 crore in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, total expenses increased 11.19% to Rs 245.83 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 221.09 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 69.78 crore (down 50.92% YoY), project-related expenses were at Rs 121.34 crore (up 293.96% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 20.92 crore (up 7.67% YoY), and finance cost was at Rs 13.06 crore (down 35.76% YoY) during the period under review. The company’s consolidated order book surged 146% YoY to over Rs 4,987 crore as of 31 December 2025, from Rs 2,027 crore a year ago, providing strong revenue visibility for the next two years. The company has also incorporated a Special Purpose Vehicle (SPV), Vikran MP Solar. Rakesh Markhedkar, chairman & managing director of Vikran Engineering, said, “FY26 marks a pivotal year for Vikran Engineering as we significantly strengthened our presence in the Solar EPC segment. The large-format solar orders secured during the year have materially enhanced our revenue visibility, with our consolidated order book now exceeding Rs 4,700 crore as of 13th February 2026. While margins during the period reflect execution ramp-up and project mix dynamics, we expect operating leverage benefits to play out as solar projects move into advanced execution phases. With a strong pipeline across Power T&D, Solar, and Water, and a clear focus on disciplined bidding and risk management, we are positioning Vikran Engineering for scalable and sustainable growth. We are also actively evaluating opportunities in select international markets, particularly in Africa and the Middle East, to diversify our growth trajectory.” Vikran Engineering provides end-to-end services from conceptualization, design, supply, installation, testing, and commissioning on a turnkey basis and has a presence across multiple sectors, including power, water, and railway infrastructure.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VikranEngineeringLtd_15725401_76742.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GK Energy hits the roof as Q3 PAT jumps 58% YoY to Rs 59 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gk-energy-hits-the-roof-as-q3-pat-jumps-58-yoy-to-rs-59-cr/1677941</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677941</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 83.51 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 67.8% YoY growth from Rs 49.77 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 83.51 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 67.8% YoY growth from Rs 49.77 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 39.61% YoY to Rs 380 crore during the quarter. Employee benefits expense rose 42.35% YoY to Rs 7.16 crore during the period under review. GK Energy is engaged in providing engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) services for solar-powered agricultural water pump systems under Component B of the PM-KUSUM scheme.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GKEnergyLtd_67239751_94284.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Manulife Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-manulife-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1677946</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677946</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra Manulife Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 16 February 2026.

Mahindra Manulife Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 16 February 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) Mahindra Manulife ELSS Tax Saver Fund Ms. Fatema Pacha 1. Ms. Fatema Pacha 2. Mr. Neelesh Dhamnaskar Mahindra Manulife Flexi Cap Fund Ms. Fatema Pacha 1. Ms. Fatema Pacha 2. Mr. Neelesh Dhamnaskar Mahindra Manulife Large & Mid Cap Fund Ms. Kirti Dalvi 1. Mr. Neelesh Dhamnaskar 2. Ms. Kirti Dalvi Mahindra Manulife Mid Cap Fund 1. Ms. Kirti Dalvi 2. Mr. Krishna Sanghavi 1. Ms. Kirti Dalvi 2. Mr. Neelesh Dhamnaskar 3. Mr. Krishna Sanghavi Mahindra Manulife Small Cap Fund 1. Mr. Vishal Jajoo 2. Mr. Krishna Sanghavi 1. Mr. Vishal Jajoo 2. Mr. Neelesh Dhamnaskar 3. Mr. Krishna Sanghavi Mahindra Manulife Balanced Advantage Fund 1. Ms. Fatema Pacha (Equity portion) 2. Mr. Rahul Pal (Debt portion) 3. Mr. Amit Garg (Debt Portion) 1. Mr. Neelesh Dhamnaskar (Equity portion) 2. Ms. Fatema Pacha (Equity portion) 3. Mr. Rahul Pal (Debt portion) 4. Mr. Amit Garg (Debt portion)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR edges higher in opening trades]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-edges-higher-in-opening-trades/1677937</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677937</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee edged higher in opening trades on Monday amid sustained weakness in dollar overseas and resume of foreign inflows in to Indian markets.

The Indian rupee edged higher in opening trades on Monday amid sustained weakness in dollar overseas and resume of foreign inflows in to Indian markets. INR opened at Rs 90.63 per dollar and steadied around the levels so far during the day. Rupee consolidated in a narrow range and settled for the day 5 paise lower at 90.66 against the US dollar on Friday. Indian shares open on a cautious note Monday even as tame U.S. inflation data underpinned hopes for interest rate cuts. Oil price movements, foreign fund flows, the release of the U.S. Federal Reserve meeting minutes and RBI MPC meeting minutes will be in focus as the week progresses. Asian markets were mostly lower in thin trade this morning, with China, South Korea and Taiwan closed for Lunar New Year holidays. The U.S. markets will also remain shut today for Presidents' Day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge higher in early trade; breadth negative]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-negative/1677933</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677933</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the early trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the early trade. The Nifty traded a tad above the 25,500 level. Realty, PSU bank, and media shares declined, while pharma and IT stocks advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 79.38 points or 0.10% to 82,706.14. The Nifty 50 index rose 31.45 points or 0.12% to 25,503.35. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.02% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.22%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,502 shares rose and 1,832 shares fell. A total of 180 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 7,395.41 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,553.96 crore in the Indian equity market on 13 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: GK Energy rose 4.95% after the company reported a 57.74% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 58.83 crore on a 43.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 460.20 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Vikran Engineering declined 4.39% after the company reported a 37.9% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 20.91 crore on a 0.5% rise in net sales to Rs 266.46 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Shakti Pumps India tumbled 9.05% after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 69.53% to Rs 31.70 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 104.05 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.18% to 6.665 compared with the previous session close of 6.677. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6500 compared with its close of 90.6650 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.71% to Rs 154,794. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.03% to 96.95. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.22% to 4.043. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement shed 3 cents or 0.04% to $67.72 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian indices traded lower on Monday as several major financial centres were shut for holidays, leading to thin trading activity. Weak economic data from Japan also dampened investor sentiment. Markets in China, South Korea, Taiwan, and the United States were closed, keeping activity in currencies, commodities, and bond markets largely subdued. Japan reported that its economy grew just 0.1% on an annualized basis in the December quarter, much lower than expectations, mainly due to lower government spending. The weak data highlights the challenges facing Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and may strengthen the case for additional government spending to support growth. Wall Street markets were mostly steady on Friday after January inflation data came in largely in line with expectations. The S&P 500 ended flat at 6,836.17 points. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.2%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average edged up 0.1% to 49,500.93 points. Data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that consumer prices rose 0.2% in January compared to the previous month and increased 2.4% compared to a year earlier. The inflation numbers offered only limited support to stocks, as hopes of lower interest rates were offset by ongoing concerns about the impact of artificial intelligence on businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indus Towers Ltd Surges 0.57%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indus-towers-ltd-surges-057/1677930</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677930</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indus Towers Ltd gained 0.57% today to trade at Rs 469.15.

Indus Towers Ltd gained 0.57% today to trade at Rs 469.15. The BSE Teck index is up 0.3% to quote at 16639.71. The index is down 11.13 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Wipro Ltd increased 0.49% and HCL Technologies Ltd added 0.45% on the day. The BSE Teck index went down 11.85 % over last one year compared to the 8.61% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Indus Towers Ltd has added 8.14% over last one month compared to 11.13% fall in BSE Teck index and 1.3% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 6256 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 5.79 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 475 on 12 Feb 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 312.6 on 03 Sep 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/INDUSTOWER_43350270_40279.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Titagarh Rail Systems slides as Q3 PAT drops 23% YoY to Rs 48 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/titagarh-rail-systems-slides-as-q3-pat-drops-23-yoy-to-rs-48-cr/1677928</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677928</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax from continuing operations stood at Rs 65.15 crore in Q3 FY26, down 26.40% year on year. Total expenses fell 7.13% to Rs 770.34 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. During the quarter, cost of raw materials & components consumed stood at Rs 643.33 crore, down 7.83% YoY, while employee benefits expense was at Rs 30.61 crore, up 40.41% YoY. On segmental front, revenue from freight rail systems stood at Rs 665.70 crore (down 21.93% YoY) and revenue from passenger rail systems stood at Rs 166.36 crore (up 236.82% YoY), during the quarter. Titagarh Rail Systems is mainly engaged in the manufacturing and selling of Freight Wagons, Passenger Coaches, Metro Trains, Train Electricals, Steel Castings, Specialised Equipments & Bridges, Ships, etc. The Company caters to both domestic and export market.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TitagarhWagons_2675196128_19939.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps tanks as Q3 PAT slides 70% YoY to Rs 97 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shakti-pumps-tanks-as-q3-pat-slides-70-yoy-to-rs-97-cr/1677924</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677924</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax decreased 70.49% year on year (YoY) to Rs 41.76 crore in the quarter ended December 2025. EBITDA stood at Rs 59 crore in December 2025 quarter, down 61.78%, compared with Rs 154.4 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin declined to 10.7% in Q3 FY26 as against 23.8% in Q3 FY25. Dinesh Patidar, Chairman, Shakti Pumps (India), said, “The company’s Q3FY26 performance was affected by a calibrated slowdown in execution, particularly in Maharashtra, aimed at addressing elevated receivables and strengthening the balance sheet. Orders worth approximately Rs 200 crore were temporarily paused to stabilise collections, which led to lower revenue recognition sequentially and YoY, as well as pressure on EBITDA margins. Margins were further impacted by a 4% decline in realisations on Magel Tyala orders, sustained 2% increase in raw material costs (copper, steel, solar panels), higher employee costs, and consumption of elevated-cost inventory from Q2FY26. Manpower expenses included a one-time Rs 4.4 crore impact due to the new labour code and investments in emerging segments expected to contribute from the next financial year. Export revenues continued to perform well and are expected to grow steadily. Trade receivables remained broadly stable, reflecting improved collections and effective working capital management. The company maintains a healthy order book of Rs 2,100 crore (inclusive of GST), diversified across states, with Maharashtra and Karnataka as key contributors. Payments from Maharashtra have improved following fund releases from the Asian Infrastructure Investment Bank (AIIB) and the state government, enabling resumption of execution. Execution in Karnataka will be aligned with payment timelines. Shakti Pumps expects Q4FY26 to be its highest revenue quarter ever, although some revenue may spill into subsequent quarters. While margins are likely to remain under pressure due to lower realisations and cost inflation, the company remains focused on balance sheet consolidation, disciplined execution, and long-term sustainable growth.” Shakti Pumps (India) is engaged in manufacturing and sale of Pumps Motors, VFD, Inverters & their spare parts. The core products of the Company are engineered pumps, industrial pumps, and solar pumps etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShaktiPumps_14702424257_6580.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty signals a weak start ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-signals-a-weak-start/1677916</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677916</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 109 points, suggesting a weak start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 109 points, suggesting a weak start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 7,395.41 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,553.96 crore in the Indian equity market on 13 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 18129.92 crore so far in February (till 13 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian indices traded lower on Monday as several major financial centres were shut for holidays, leading to thin trading activity. Weak economic data from Japan also dampened investor sentiment. Markets in China, South Korea, Taiwan and the United States were closed, keeping activity in currencies, commodities and bond markets largely subdued. Japan reported that its economy grew just 0.1% on an annualised basis in the December quarter, much lower than expectations, mainly due to lower government spending. The weak data highlights the challenges facing Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and may strengthen the case for additional government spending to support growth. Wall Street markets were mostly steady on Friday after January inflation data came in largely in line with expectations. The S&P 500 ended flat at 6,836.17 points. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.2%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average edged up 0.1% to 49,500.93 points. Data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that consumer prices rose 0.2% in January compared to the previous month, and increased 2.4% compared to a year earlier. The inflation numbers offered only limited support to stocks, as hopes of lower interest rates were offset by ongoing concerns about the impact of artificial intelligence on businesses. Domestic Market: Benchmark indices closed sharply lower on Friday, 13 February 2026, as widespread selling pressure dominated the session. Indices traded with a negative bias throughout the day, with the lack of fresh domestic catalysts keeping sentiment subdued. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,048.16 points or 1.25% to 82,626.76. The Nifty 50 index tanked 336.10 points or 1.30% to 25,471.10.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves down by $6.7 billion to $717.6 billion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-down-by-67-billion-to-7176-billion/1677915</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677915</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s foreign exchange reserves fell to $717.6 billion as on February 6, 2026, dropping by $6.71 billion, data from the Reserve Bank of India showed.

India’s foreign exchange reserves fell to $717.6 billion as on February 6, 2026, dropping by $6.71 billion, data from the Reserve Bank of India showed. Meanwhile, data showed a dip in foreign currency assets (FCAs) which declined by $7.66 billion to $570.05 billion during the week. Gold holdings also recorded a sharp drop by $14.2 billion to $123.47 billion. Meanwhile, Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) decreased by $132 million to $18.82 billion. India’s reserve tranche position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) edged down by $32 million to $4.71 billion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-2891849__340_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: GK Energy, Vikran Engineering, Shakti Pumps, Deep Industries, RailTel Corp]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-gk-energy-vikran-engineering-shakti-pumps-deep-industries-railtel-corp/1677913</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677913</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&O trading on 16 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&O trading on 16 February 2026. New listing: In the mainboard IPO space, Fractal Analytics and Aye Finance is set to make its market debut today. Stocks to Watch: GK Energy reported a 57.74% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 58.83 crore on a 43.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 460.20 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Vikran Engineering reported a 37.9% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 20.91 crore on a 0.5% rise in net sales to Rs 266.46 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Shakti Pumps India’s consolidated net profit declined 69.53% to Rs 31.70 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 104.05 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Deep Industries said that it has secured a domestic contract from Oil India for the hiring of a 1000 HP mobile drilling rig package in Assam and Arunachal Pradesh. RailTel Corporation of India has secured a work order worth Rs 92.91 crore from the Directorate of Education, Government of National Capital Territory of Delhi (GNCTD). Titagarh Rail Systems’ consolidated net profit tanked 23.48% to Rs 48.03 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.77 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Crisil's consolidated total income for Q4 2025, rose 17.5% to Rs 1,108.7 crore, compared with Rs 943.2 crore in Q4 2024. On a consolidated basis, the company's income from operations for Q4 2025 was up 18.5% to Rs 1,081.6 crore, compared with Rs 912.9 crore in Q4 2024. Profit after tax was up 7.5% to Rs 241.5 crore, compared with Rs 224.7 crore in Q4 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashoka Buildcon bags $45.28 Mln Intl road project in West Africa]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashoka-buildcon-bags-4528-mln-intl-road-project-in-west-africa/1677912</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1677912</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has been awarded the project from Ministry of Public Works, Liberia, for the upgradation of road stretches from Nrowkia (Sasstown Junction) to Barclayville, Nrowkia (Sasstown Junction) to Sasstown, and part of the Nrowkia (Sasstown Junction) to Nipleppo road in the Liberia.

The company has been awarded the project from Ministry of Public Works, Liberia, for the upgradation of road stretches from Nrowkia (Sasstown Junction) to Barclayville, Nrowkia (Sasstown Junction) to Sasstown, and part of the Nrowkia (Sasstown Junction) to Nipleppo road in the Liberia. The said project is valued at $ 45,276,621.07. The construction work is scheduled to be completed within a period of 24 months. Ashoka Buildcon is engaged in the construction & maintenance of roads and supporting services to land support and operation of toll roads. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 222.59% to Rs to Rs 2,111.41 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 654.50 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 23.47% YoY to Rs 1,827.33 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter declined 4.26% to settle at Rs 151.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokaBuildcon_9945804621_25513.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>