<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:31:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[M&M production jumps 25% YoY in December’25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mm-production-jumps-25-yoy-in-december25/1664282</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664282</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The auto major's total sales stood at 85,501 units in December 2025, registering a growth of 25.41% on a YoY basis while exports fell 9.33% YoY to 3,063 units in December 2025.

The auto major's total sales stood at 85,501 units in December 2025, registering a growth of 25.41% on a YoY basis while exports fell 9.33% YoY to 3,063 units in December 2025. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) Group enjoys a leadership position in farm equipment, utility vehicles, information technology, and financial services in India. It is the world's largest tractor company by volume. It has a strong presence in renewable energy, agriculture, logistics, hospitality and real estate. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit surged 17.7% to Rs 4,520.52 crore on a 21.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 33,421.60 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25, reflecting broad-based growth across Auto and Farm segments. The scrip declined 1.84% to Rs 3,607.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NITCO rises after recording 85% sequential growth in January sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nitco-rises-after-recording-85-sequential-growth-in-january-sales/1664283</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664283</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The robust performance was supported by multiple growth drivers, including higher customer demand, strengthening of the product portfolio, and sustained emphasis on operational efficiencies.

The robust performance was supported by multiple growth drivers, including higher customer demand, strengthening of the product portfolio, and sustained emphasis on operational efficiencies. Vivek Talwar, chairman & managing director of company, said: “Achieving 85% growth in sales reflects the strength of our business strategy, the dedication of our teams, and the trust our customers placed in us. We remain focused on sustainable growth while continuing to invest in innovation, capacity expansion, and customer experience." Looking ahead, NITCO stated that it remains optimistic about its growth prospects and will continue to focus on strengthening its market position while maintaining financial discipline. NITCO is engaged in providing floor and wall solutions with a portfolio comprising a comprehensive range of tiles, marbles and mosaic. The company had reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 1.00 crore in the quarter ended September 2025 as against net loss of Rs 34.60 crore during the previous quarter ended September 2024. Sales increased by 62.21% YoY to Rs 106.78 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Nitco_97046573318_13683.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/motilal-oswal-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1664280</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664280</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 12 January 2026.

Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 12 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Proposed Motilal Oswal Balanced Advantage Fund Mr. Niket Shah Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar Mr. Niket Shah Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Sandeep Jain Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar Motilal Oswal Multi Cap Fund Mr. Niket Shah Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar Mr. Niket Shah Mr. Ajay Khandelwal Mr. Atul Mehra Mr. Sandeep Jain Mr. Rakesh Shetty Mr. Swapnil Mayekar

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades slides below 25,550 mark; realty shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-slides-below-25550-mark-realty-shares-tumble/1664279</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664279</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with significant losses in the mid-morning trade, pressured by escalating geopolitical tensions and renewed concerns over potential U.S.

The key equity indices traded with significant losses in the mid-morning trade, pressured by escalating geopolitical tensions and renewed concerns over potential U.S. tariff hikes. Investor sentiment remained cautious as the Q3 earnings season kicked off, with market participants closely tracking corporate performance and outlook amid global uncertainties. The Nifty traded below the 25,550 mark, while realty shares extended losses for the fifth consecutive trading session. At 11:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, fell 591.38 points or 0.71% to 82,984.86. The Nifty 50 index lost 181.15 points or 0.71% to 25,502.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tumbled 1.62% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 1.93%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 892 shares rose and 3,091 shares fell. A total of 226 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 6.38% to 11.62. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 5,50,11,06,000 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:20 IST on Monday (12 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 15.86 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index dropped 2.10% to 855.65. The index tumbled 6.73% in the past five consecutive trading sessions. SignatureGlobal India (down 6.33%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 3.39%), DLF (down 2.95%), Godrej Properties (down 2.94%), Oberoi Realty (down 2.31%), Anant Raj (down 2.10%), Phoenix Mills (down 1.93%) and Sobha (down 0.98%) declined. On the other hand, Brigade Enterprises (up 0.69%) and Lodha Developers (up 0.40%) edged higher. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharat Heavy Electricals fell 5.75% amid market concerns over reports suggesting that Chinese companies may be allowed to bid for select government contracts. Avenue Supermarts (Dmart) slipped 1%. The company consolidated net profit rallied 18.26% to Rs 855.92 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 723.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Shakti Pumps India rallied 4.11% after the company received letter of award (LoA) for setting up 16,780 stand‐alone off‐grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems (SPWPS) pumps in Karnataka. Global Markets: Asia market rose on Monday following Wall Street gains from last week after a U.S. job report showed that unemployment rate fell, signaling resilience in the labor market. Japanese markets were closed for a holiday. Investors will be keeping an eye on oil prices as Iran entered a third week of protests, which have reportedly seen more than 500 people killed. President Donald Trump is weighing options for intervention in Iran, media reports said. On Sunday, Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s coalition partner, Hirofumi Yoshimura, said that she may call an early general election. His comments come after domestic media reported that Takaichi was considering a snap election in February, citing government sources. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 rose to new highs on Friday, notching a weekly gain, following the release of the latest jobs report. The broad market index closed up 0.65% to 6,966.28, a fresh record close. It also notched a new all-time intraday high in the session. The Nasdaq Composite gained 0.81% to 23,671.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 237.96 points, or 0.48%, to end at 49,504.07, scoring a new closing record as well. The December jobs report showed nonfarm payrolls increasing by 50,000 last month, less than the 73,000 estimate that was widely reported in the media. That data, though slightly weaker than expected, showed a U.S. economy that’s still trudging along, with investors anticipating that growth will ramp up. The unemployment rate inched down to 4.4%, while widely circulated media reports had provided a forecast of 4.5%. Traders took that as a sign that improvement in the economy would happen soon.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tanfac Industries gains on inking seven-year supply pact with Japanese customer worth Rs 2,362-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tanfac-industries-gains-on-inking-seven-year-supply-pact-with-japanese-customer-worth-rs-2362-cr/1664275</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664275</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The aggregate contract value over the seven-year period is approximately Rs 2,362 crore.

The aggregate contract value over the seven-year period is approximately Rs 2,362 crore. The agreement, effective from 1 January 2027, is expected to provide long-term revenue visibility backed by committed volumes, strengthening the company’s domestic and export portfolio, enhancing earnings predictability, and reinforcing its position as a reliable global supplier of fluorinated chemicals. Tanfac Industries clarified that the promoter, promoter group, or group companies have no interest in the entity awarding the contract. Further, the order does not fall under related-party transactions and has been executed at arm’s length. Commenting on the contract, Mr Afzal Malkani, MD, said: “This contract represents a significant step in deepening our engagement with global customers and reflects the confidence placed in our manufacturing capabilities and quality standards. The long-term structure provides revenue stability, representing 37.5% of our recently announced fluorinated chemical plant capacity, and aligns with our strategy of expanding the value-added downstream fluorinated chemicals portfolio and building durable relationships with global customers.” Tanfac Industries is a joint sector company promoted by Anupam Rasayan India and Tamil Nadu Industrial Development Corporation (TIDCO) and s engaged in the manufacture of Anhydrous Hydrofluoric Acid, Sulphuric Acid, Potassium Fluoride, Potassium Bifluoride, etc. The company’s standalone net profit declined 11% to Rs 17.18 crore despite a 51.3% jump in net sales to Rs 168.69 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TanfacInds_95252622_548.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen hovers at year lows as markets eye BOJ and politics]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-hovers-at-year-lows-as-markets-eye-boj-and-politics/1664272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664272</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen hovered above 158 per dollar, staying near one-year lows as thin holiday trading limited volatility.

The Japanese yen hovered above 158 per dollar, staying near one-year lows as thin holiday trading limited volatility. Political uncertainty intensified after talk of a possible snap election in February, while mixed economic data continued to blur the Bank of Japan’s rate-hike trajectory. Although Governor Kazuo Ueda reaffirmed a readiness to raise rates if conditions align with forecasts, markets remain cautious ahead of key economic releases this week. Meanwhile, the dollar softened, with the dollar index slipping to around 98.6 after news of a criminal investigation into Fed Chair Jerome Powell raised concerns over central bank independence.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index net speculative shorts post further decline ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-net-speculative-shorts-post-further-decline/1664271</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664271</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index speculative shorts have come off their record level for more than a decade, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

US dollar index speculative shorts have come off their record level for more than a decade, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of US dollar index futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of -3831 contracts in the data reported through January 06, 2025, showing a further decrease of 129 net short positions compared to the previous week and to a 5-month low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Metropolis Healthcare Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-metropolis-healthcare-ltd-counter/1664268</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664268</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Can Fin Homes Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, Linde India Ltd, Chalet Hotels Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 12 January 2026.

Can Fin Homes Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, Linde India Ltd, Chalet Hotels Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 12 January 2026. Metropolis Healthcare Ltd recorded volume of 1.16 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 36.96 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3127 shares. The stock lost 2.40% to Rs.1,878.55. Volumes stood at 1635 shares in the last session. Can Fin Homes Ltd recorded volume of 2.02 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 17.64 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 11451 shares. The stock lost 1.17% to Rs.879.25. Volumes stood at 13022 shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd clocked volume of 8.25 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 13.5 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 61091 shares. The stock lost 11.20% to Rs.370.05. Volumes stood at 2.57 lakh shares in the last session. Linde India Ltd saw volume of 7313 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.85 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 826 shares. The stock increased 4.48% to Rs.6,175.00. Volumes stood at 1283 shares in the last session. Chalet Hotels Ltd recorded volume of 3.02 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.37 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 36095 shares. The stock lost 1.72% to Rs.857.55. Volumes stood at 1.03 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MetropolisHealthcareLtd_18318340_65221.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Domestic fish output up more than 100% over last decade]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/domestic-fish-output-up-more-than-100-over-last-decade/1664269</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664269</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Fisheries, Animal Husbandry & Dairying stated that domestic Fish production has increased to 197.75 lakh tonnes in FY 2024-25 from 95.79 lakh tonnes fish production in FY 2013-14 increasing a significant 106%.

Ministry of Fisheries, Animal Husbandry & Dairying stated that domestic Fish production has increased to 197.75 lakh tonnes in FY 2024-25 from 95.79 lakh tonnes fish production in FY 2013-14 increasing a significant 106%. Average aquaculture productivity has increased to 4.77 tonnes per hectare. Indian seafood exports have witnessed an impressive growth as we exported 16.98 Lakh tons of seafood worth Rs Rs 62,408 crore during 2023-24. Under various schemes and programs implemented since 2014-15 by the Department of Fisheries, GoI, 74.66 lakh employment opportunities (both direct and indirect) have been generated.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-growth-1-1057028_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ways and Means Advances limit for Delhi govt fixed at Rs 890 cr: RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ways-and-means-advances-limit-for-delhi-govt-fixed-at-rs-890-cr-rbi/1664270</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664270</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank on Friday fixed the Ways and Means Advances (WMA) limit for the Delhi government at Rs 890 crore to help it meet any temporary mismatch in receipts and payments.

The Reserve Bank on Friday fixed the Ways and Means Advances (WMA) limit for the Delhi government at Rs 890 crore to help it meet any temporary mismatch in receipts and payments. Earlier this week, the central bank entered into an agreement with the Government of the National Capital Territory of Delhi (GNCTD) to conduct the city government's general banking business, effective from Friday, January 09, 2026. "The WMA limit for GNCTD has been fixed at Rs 890 crore, effective from January 09, 2026," the Reserve Bank of India said in a statement.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops 353 pts; media shares decline for 3rd day ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-353-pts-media-shares-decline-for-3rd-day/1664265</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664265</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in the morning trade, pressured by escalating geopolitical tensions and renewed concerns over potential U.S.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in the morning trade, pressured by escalating geopolitical tensions and renewed concerns over potential U.S. tariff hikes. Investor sentiment remained cautious as the Q3 earnings season kicked off, with market participants closely tracking corporate performance and outlook amid global uncertainties. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level, while media shares extended losses for a third consecutive trading session. At 10:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 352.53 points or 0.43% to 83,216.75. The Nifty 50 index added 94.40 points or 0.37% to 25,589.35. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.71% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 1%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,054 shares rose and 2,767 shares fell. A total of 225 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 6.77% to 11.67. Result Today: Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.46%), HCL Technologies (down 0.42%), Anand Rathi Wealth (down 0.89%), GTPL Hathway (down 0.41%), Gujarat Hotels (down 2.67%), Lotus Chocolate Company (down 2.30%), Maharashtra Scooters (down 5.24%), OK Play India (up 1.30%) and Tierra Agrotech (down 1.16%) will release their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 1.59% to 1,402.70. The index dropped 3.76% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Tips Music (down 1.29%), Sun TV Network (down 1.09%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 1.07%), Nazara Technologies (down 0.97%), Saregama India (down 0.42%) and PVR Inox (down 0.40%) declined. On the other hand, Prime Focus (up 0.56%) and Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 0.10%) edged higher. Stocks in Spotlight: Saatvik Green Energy declined 1.73%. The company’s material subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries, secured an order worth Rs 13.8 crore from a renowned independent power producer/EPC player for the supply of solar PV modules. Signatureglobal (India) dropped 5.59% after the company reported a 27% decline in pre-sales to Rs 20,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with 27,700 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BHEL slides on reports of Chinese firms entering power equipment bids]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bhel-slides-on-reports-of-chinese-firms-entering-power-equipment-bids/1664262</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664262</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[There has been no official notification from the government on easing restrictions for Chinese manufacturers so far.

There has been no official notification from the government on easing restrictions for Chinese manufacturers so far. However, media reports indicated that in the transmission and high-voltage equipment segment, a Chinese manufacturer may be permitted to participate in bidding processes starting FY27. According to the reports, Chinese power equipment maker TBEA has been approved to bid in certain high-voltage reactor categories, including power transmission projects, from the financial year beginning 2027. The reports added that restrictions have not been fully lifted. Any potential participation would be limited to future bids, with no immediate risk of a surge in imports. Capacity constraints in the transmission space have pushed up pricing sharply in recent years, and the entry of additional players could cap further upside. Stocks across the high-voltage and extra-high-voltage segment also saw pressure. Names such as Hitachi Energy India (-5.43%), GE Vernova T&D India (-3.12%), Transformers and Rectifiers India (-2.72%) and CG Power and Industrial Solutions (-0.83%) declined. Market participants expect valuations in the capital goods space to adjust to rising competition. However, the near-term impact on earnings is seen as limited, as domestic capacities remain constrained and pricing discipline is unlikely to weaken sharply in the immediate term. BHEL is an integrated power plant equipment manufacturer catering to sectors such as power, transmission, transportation, renewable energy, oil and gas and defence. The company reported a 253.17% YoY jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 374.89 crore in Q2 FY26, while revenue rose 14.06% to Rs 7,511.80 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BHEL_16865551712_2306.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Avenue Supermarts gains as Q3 PAT jumps 18% YoY to Rs 856 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avenue-supermarts-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-18-yoy-to-rs-856-cr/1664261</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664261</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 13.32% to Rs 18,100.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15,972.55 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operations rose 13.32% to Rs 18,100.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15,972.55 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax (PBT) rose 18.10% year on year to Rs 1,175.19 crore in Q3 FY26. Earnings before Interest, Tax, Depreciation, and Amortization (EBITDA) for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 1,463 crore, up from Rs 1,217 crore in the same quarter last year, marking a 20% year-on-year increase. The EBITDA margin improved to 8.1% in Q3 FY26 from 7.6% in Q3 FY25, reflecting better operational efficiencies. D-Mart follows Everyday low cost - Everyday low price (EDLC-EDLP) strategy which aims at procuring goods at competitive prices, using operational and distribution efficiency and thereby delivering value for money to customers by selling at competitive prices. The company opened 10 new stores during the quarter, taking the total store count to 442 as of 31 December 2025. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit jumped 17.63% to Rs 923.05 crore on 13.15% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 17,612.62 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Earnings before Interest, Tax, Depreciation, and Amortization (EBITDA) for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 1,481 crore, up from Rs 1,235 crore in the corresponding quarter of last year. The EBITDA margin improved to 8.4% in Q3FY26 from 7.9% in Q3FY25, reflecting stronger operational performance. Anshul Asawa, CEO-Designate of Avenue Supermarts, said: “Our revenue for the quarter grew by 13.2%, while profit after tax (PAT) increased 17.6% over the previous year. Two years and older DMart stores delivered a 5.6% growth in Q3FY26 compared to Q3FY25. Revenue growth was partially impacted by deflation in staples.” The board of Avenue Supermarts based on the recommendation of the nomination and remuneration committee, approved the appointment of Anshul Asawa, currently CEO-Designate, as the chief executive officer and key managerial personnel of the company effective 1st February 2026. Additionally, he will assume the role of managing director (MD) for a term of three years from 1st April 2026, subject to shareholder approval. Avenue Supermarts is a Mumbai-based company, which owns and operates D-Mart stores. D-Mart is a national supermarket chain that offers customers a range of home and personal products under one roof. It offers a wide range of products with a focus on Foods, Non-Foods (FMCG) and General Merchandise & Apparel product categories.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AvenueSupermartsLtd_68548819828_40942.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps jumps after bagging order worth Rs 654-cr from KREDL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shakti-pumps-jumps-after-bagging-order-worth-rs-654-cr-from-kredl/1664260</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664260</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order was awarded by the Karnataka Renewable Energy Development (KREDL) under component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme.

The order was awarded by the Karnataka Renewable Energy Development (KREDL) under component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme. The scope of work includes the design, manufacture, supply, transport, installation, testing and commissioning of the stand-alone off-grid DC SPWS. The contract is valued at Rs 654.03 crore and is expected to be executed on or before 31st March 2026. Shakti Pumps (India) manufactures solar pumps, energy-efficient stainless-steel submersible pumps, pressure booster pumps, pump motors, and other products. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 10.56% to Rs 90.71 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 101.42 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5% YoY to Rs 666.35 crore in Q2 Sept 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShaktiPumps_14702424257_6580.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Phoenix Mills records 20% YoY growth in retail consumption in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/phoenix-mills-records-20-yoy-growth-in-retail-consumption-in-q3/1664259</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664259</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company further said that during the period under review, office leasing momentum translated into visible occupancy improvement, hospitality performance was supported by high occupancies and ARR-driven growth, and residential sales maintaed steady momentum year-to-date.

The company further said that during the period under review, office leasing momentum translated into visible occupancy improvement, hospitality performance was supported by high occupancies and ARR-driven growth, and residential sales maintaed steady momentum year-to-date. In the Retail business, portfolio consumption stood at Rs 4,787 crore in Q3 FY26 (up 20% YoY) and Rs. 12,122 crore in 9M FY26 (up 15% YoY), reflecting broad-based demand across the portfolio during the festive quarter and year-to-date. Consumption growth in Q3 FY26 remained strong, reflecting demand resilience, even as select assets continue to undergo planned revamp and premiumisation initiatives to strengthen portfolio performance over the medium term. In the Commercial Offices segment, leasing activity remained strong through 9M FY26, with gross leasing of 1.20 million square feet, reflecting sustained tenant demand across the portfolio. The leased occupancy in the operational assets at Mumbai and Vimannagar in Pune improved to 77% as at December 2025, from 67% as at March 2025. The leased occupancy across new developments in Pune, Bengaluru and Chennai is at 41%, with advanced-stage leasing discussions providing strong visibility on further ramp-up. PML’s hotel portfolio delivered steady performance in Q3 and 9M FY26, supported by strong occupancies and average room rate (ARR)-driven revenue per available room (RevPAR) growth, led by The St. Regis, Mumbai. The company further said that residential sales and collections remained robust, supported by steady execution and monetisation of premium residential inventory. Gross residential sales of Rs. 140 crore in Q3 FY26 (up 141.4% YoY) and Rs. 412 crore during 9M FY26 (up 205.2% YoY). The Phoenix Mills is India’s leading owner, operator and developer of retail-led mixed-use destinations. The group’s developments are spread across retail, hospitality, commercial offices, and residential asset classes. The company's consolidated net profit increased by 39.38% to Rs 303.99 crore on a 21.51% rise in revenue to Rs 1,115.43 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared to Q2 FY25. The scrip fell 1.13% to currently trade at Rs 1885.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PhoenixMills_41300937830_6418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manappuram Finance jumps on rubbishing report on Bain deal delay; says RBI approvals in place]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/manappuram-finance-jumps-on-rubbishing-report-on-bain-deal-delay-says-rbi-approvals-in-place/1664258</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664258</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company termed the report factually incorrect and speculative.

The company termed the report factually incorrect and speculative. In a clarification to the exchanges on 9 January 2026, Manappuram Finance said it has been making regular disclosures on the proposed investment by BC Asia Investments XIV and BC Asia Investments XXV. The transaction involves the acquisition of joint control along with the existing promoters. The company said it has already received approval from the Reserve Bank of India for change in management at Manappuram Finance. Similar approvals have also been obtained for its subsidiaries Asirvad Micro Finance and Manappuram Home Finance. These approvals were disclosed earlier through regulatory filings dated 17 September 2025 and 27 August 2025, respectively. Manappuram Finance said the change of control application for the proposed transaction is under review. Required filings and responses to clarifications sought by the RBI have already been submitted. Final regulatory approval is pending. Manappuram Finance is a leading non-banking financial institution and the 2nd largest financier in the gold loan segment in India. It offers a wide range of products including gold loans, microfinance, housing finance, vehicle loans, and SME financing. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 61.5% to Rs 219.88 crore on 13.3% fall in total income to Rs 2,285.36 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManappuramFin_40714085963_6083.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Man Industries gains on bagging Rs 550-crore pipe supply orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/man-industries-gains-on-bagging-rs-550-crore-pipe-supply-orders/1664256</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664256</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders are scheduled to be executed within six months, which should support near-term revenue visibility.

The orders are scheduled to be executed within six months, which should support near-term revenue visibility. The contracts have been awarded by both domestic and overseas customers, reflecting continued demand across key end markets. The company clarified that the orders do not involve any related-party transactions, with no promoter or promoter group interest in the awarding entities, and have been awarded at arm’s length. MAN Industries (India) is the flagship company of the MAN Group. The company is one of the largest manufacturers and exporters of large diameter carbon steel line pipes in India, with capabilities in LSAW (longitudinal submerged arc welded), HSAW (helical submerged arc welded), and ERW (electric resistance welded) pipe technologies, as well as advanced pipe coating solutions. The company's consolidated net profit rose 16.07% to Rs 36.98 crore on a 3.46% increase in revenue to Rs 834.09 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManInds_64315062574_1369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers drift lower in early trade; VIX surges 8.07%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-drift-lower-in-early-trade-vix-surges-807/1664250</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664250</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with modest losses in early trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with modest losses in early trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. Barring the Nifty Metal index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the red, with the Media, Realty and Healthcare indices gaining the most. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 434.67 points or 0.52% to 83,141.57. The Nifty 50 index fell 130.95 points or 0.50% to 25,552.35. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tumbled 1.38% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index plunged 1.96%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 812 shares rose and 2,456 shares fell. A total of 207 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 8.07% to 11.81. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,769.31 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,595.84 crore in the Indian equity market on 08 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Globus Spirits rose 1.91% after the company’s standalone net profit skyrocketed over fifteen times to Rs 31.42 crore on a 19.1% increase in revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) to Rs 716.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) advanced 2.93% after the company’s consolidated net profit rallied 15.42% to Rs 1,381.36 crore on 26.80% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 6,135.08 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tejas Networks tumbled 7.15% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 196.55 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 165.67 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company’s total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.18% to 6.624 compared with previous session close of 6.636. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2250 compared with its close of 90.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement gained 1.32% to Rs 1,40,635. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.13% to 98.76. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.14% to 4.178. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 14 cents or 0.22% to $63.48 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market rose on Monday following Wall Street gains from last week after a U.S. job report showed that unemployment rate fell, signaling resilience in the labor market. Japanese markets were closed for a holiday. Investors will be keeping an eye on oil prices as Iran entered a third week of protests, which have reportedly seen more than 500 people killed. President Donald Trump is weighing options for intervention in Iran, media reports said. On Sunday, Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s coalition partner, Hirofumi Yoshimura, said that she may call an early general election. His comments come after domestic media reported that Takaichi was considering a snap election in February, citing government sources. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 rose to new highs on Friday, notching a weekly gain, following the release of the latest jobs report. The broad market index closed up 0.65% to 6,966.28, a fresh record close. It also notched a new all-time intraday high in the session. The Nasdaq Composite gained 0.81% to 23,671.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 237.96 points, or 0.48%, to end at 49,504.07, scoring a new closing record as well. The December jobs report showed nonfarm payrolls increasing by 50,000 last month, less than the 73,000 estimate that was widely reported in the media. That data, though slightly weaker than expected, showed a U.S. economy that’s still trudging along, with investors anticipating that growth will ramp up. The unemployment rate inched down to 4.4%, while widely circulated media reports had provided a forecast of 4.5%. Traders took that as a sign that improvement in the economy would happen soon.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Signatureglobal (India) slips as softer mrkt dents pre-sales outlook]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/signatureglobal-india-slips-as-softer-mrkt-dents-pre-sales-outlook/1664249</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664249</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ina regulatory filing on 11 January 2026, the real estate developer reported a 27% decline in pre-sales to Rs 20,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with 27,700 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Ina regulatory filing on 11 January 2026, the real estate developer reported a 27% decline in pre-sales to Rs 20,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with 27,700 crore posted in Q3 FY25. pre-sales for the nine months ended 31st December 2025, stood at Rs 66,800 crore in 9M FY26 compared with Rs 86,700 crore in 9M FY25. The company said that the overall market environment has turned softer and that has impacted sales momentum. It added that it will not be able to meet its earlier pre-sales guidance of Rs 12,700 crore in FY26, which looked comfortable a few months back. However, the company aims to maintain sales at the same levels as last year. Launches continue to remain on track. Pre-sales stood at Rs 10,290 crore in FY25. Collections climbed to Rs 12,300 crore in Q3 FY26 and Rs 30,900 crore for the nine-month period. Net debt stood at Rs 10,200 crore at the end of 9M FY26, compared with Rs 8,800crore at the end of FY25. Average sales realization improved to Rs 15,182 per sq.ft in Q3 FY26 and Rs 3090 crore for the nine-month period, driven by higher sales in premium markets and price increases across key regions. Pradeep Kumar Aggarwal, chairman and whole-time director, said, “We delivered a healthy performance during the first nine months of FY26, driven by sustained demand across our focused micro-markets. The launch of our wellness-centric premium project, Sarvam at DXP Estate on Dwarka Expressway, witnessed encouraging customer response, reflecting evolving buyer preferences. Strong collections, improving realizations and disciplined balance sheet management underline execution strength. Looking ahead, current momentum and planned launches keep us broadly aligned with our guidance and support our longer-term growth plans.” Signature Global is a publicly held real estate development company in India. It was established in 2014 and is headquartered in Gurgaon, Delhi. It operates in the residential and commercial sectors and has developed projects in the Delhi-NCR region. The company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 46.86 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with net profit of Rs 4.11 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales declined 54.8% YoY to Rs 338.49 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SignatureGlobalIndiaLtd_61604572_77225.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks slumps on reporting dismal Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-slumps-on-reporting-dismal-q3-performance/1664246</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664246</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year.

The company’s total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Pre-tax loss for the quarter stood at Rs 302.87 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to a profit before tax of Rs 211.27 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s inventory stood at Rs 2,363 crore in Q3 FY26, largely unchanged from Rs 2,383 crore in the previous quarter. Management said the inventory will be converted into finished goods and shipped over the coming months. Trade receivables declined to Rs 3,284 crore at the end of Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,026 crore in Q2, reflecting improved collections. The company reported a cash balance of Rs 537 crore at the end of the quarter. Net debt reduced to Rs 3,349 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 3,738 crore in the preceding quarter, primarily due to lower working capital requirements, partially offset by capital expenditure. Gross debt stood at Rs 885 crore, with cash and cash equivalents of Rs 537 crore. During the quarter, the company strengthened its order wins by securing additional packages under Bharatnet Phase-III, where it remains a key supplier of IP/MPLS routers, having won 7 of the 12 packages announced so far. It was also selected as the 5G RAN supplier for a section of the Delhi–Mumbai railway corridor under a Kavach pilot project. Further, the company received expansion orders for DWDM and GPON OLT equipment from leading private telecom operators in India, and won a DWDM backbone buildout order from a broadband ISP in Africa, along with a network transformation deal for its MPLS-TP products for a power sector customer in Southeast Asia. The company said its long-term outlook remains positive, supported by strong structural drivers and rapid technology transitions across the telecom and networking landscape. Growing adoption of AI applications is driving a sharp increase in data traffic, while continued expansion of 4G networks and fresh 5G deployments in emerging markets are creating sustained demand. Investments in AI data centres are also translating into significant connectivity requirements. The company is seeing increasing traction for its new products across India and international markets, with wireless solutions beginning to lead international engagements in regions such as Europe, Latin America and Africa. At the same time, adoption of its wireline products is rising among private telecom operators in India. The company is also scaling up its international wireless engagements through strategic partnerships with NEC and Rakuten, while recent strategic wins for its optical products in Europe, Africa and Asia are providing momentum for further international expansion. Arnob Roy, COO of Tejas Networks said, “In Q3 FY26, our revenue was driven largely by sale of Wireline products to India Pvt and International customers. During the quarter we engaged in multiple field trials for our Wireless products in India and International markets; commercial negotiations are expected to close in the coming months.” Sumit Dhingra, CFO said, “In Q3 FY26 we had a revenue of Rs 307 crore, a QoQ growth of 17%. We ended the quarter with an order book of Rs 1,329 crore. Our net debt was 3,349 crore compared to 3,738 crore in Q2 FY26 mainly due to lower working capital, partly offset by capex; gross debt of 3,885 crore and cash of 537 crore.” Tejas Networks designs and manufactures wireline and wireless networking products, with a focus on technology, innovation, and R&D. TNL carrier-class products are used by telecom service providers, utilities, governments, and defense networks in 75+ countries. Tejas Networks is a part of the Tata Group, with Panatone Finvest (a subsidiary of Tata Sons) being the majority shareholder.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>