<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:59:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stanley Lifestyles Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stanley-lifestyles-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1674462</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674462</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nagreeka Capital & Infrastructure Ltd, Signpost India Ltd, Dynemic Products Ltd and Zodiac Energy Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 10 February 2026.

Nagreeka Capital & Infrastructure Ltd, Signpost India Ltd, Dynemic Products Ltd and Zodiac Energy Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 10 February 2026. Stanley Lifestyles Ltd spiked 16.92% to Rs 210.05 at 10-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.19 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4425 shares in the past one month. Nagreeka Capital & Infrastructure Ltd soared 16.24% to Rs 33.85. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 19431 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2961 shares in the past one month. Signpost India Ltd surged 16.18% to Rs 244.8. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 31690 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 20641 shares in the past one month. Dynemic Products Ltd advanced 15.41% to Rs 253.9. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 5926 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 440 shares in the past one month. Zodiac Energy Ltd gained 15.18% to Rs 306.9. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 13951 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1552 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StanleyLifestylesLtd_44639153_36078.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NITY Aayog says achieving net-zero by 2070 will require cumulative investments of about $22.7 trillion under current policy scenario]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nity-aayog-says-achieving-net-zero-by-2070-will-require-cumulative-investments-of-about-227-trillion-under-current-policy-scenario/1674463</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674463</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s ambitious target to reach net-zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2070 can be achieved without impacting its economic growth or its goal of becoming a developed nation by 2047, but will require an unprecedented restructuring of the country’s energy system, industrial base and financing architecture, according to a comprehensive new scenarios study released by NITI Aayog.

India’s ambitious target to reach net-zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2070 can be achieved without impacting its economic growth or its goal of becoming a developed nation by 2047, but will require an unprecedented restructuring of the country’s energy system, industrial base and financing architecture, according to a comprehensive new scenarios study released by NITI Aayog. The study, Scenarios Towards Viksit Bharat and Net Zero, presents one of the most detailed modelling exercises undertaken so far on India’s low-carbon transition. This entails work of ten inter-ministerial working groups covering power, transport, industry, buildings, agriculture, finance, critical minerals and social impacts. The study maps how India could nearly eightfold its GDP, from about $4.2 trillion in 2025 to around $30 trillion by 2047, while steadily reducing emissions in line with its international climate commitments. Suman Bery, Vice Chairperson, NITI Aayog, has stated that as one the world’s largest economies by 2070, India must be concerned for the welfare of its own citizens, and for the world that they will inhabit in the coming decades. Accordingly, the goal of Net Zero by 2070 provides guidance to Indian actors about a world beyond Viksit Bharat 2047. India’s own pathways will be influential for those to follow, particularly from the global south. The study noted that achieving net-zero emissions by 2070 will require cumulative investments of about $22.7 trillion, nearly $8 trillion more than under the current policy scenario.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/wind-turbine-1804055__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index slips to one-week low under 97 mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-slips-to-one-week-low-under-97-mark/1674451</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674451</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index slipped under 97 mark on Tuesday to a one-week low amid concerns that foreign demand for dollar-denominated assets may weaken, after reports that Chinese regulators urged financial institutions to curb US Treasury holdings to reduce concentration risks and exposure to uncertain US economic policies.

The dollar index slipped under 97 mark on Tuesday to a one-week low amid concerns that foreign demand for dollar-denominated assets may weaken, after reports that Chinese regulators urged financial institutions to curb US Treasury holdings to reduce concentration risks and exposure to uncertain US economic policies. Meanwhile, renewed concerns of Fed’s independence was triggered after Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent last week refused to rule out the possibility of a criminal investigation of Kevin Warsh, President Donald Trump’s nominee for Federal Reserve chair, if Warsh ends up refusing to cut interest rates. Federal Reserve Board Governor Stephan Miran said yesterday the Fed should remain fully independent of political influence, before tempering his remarks by noting that complete, 100% independence is “impossible.” The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 96.78. January US employment report and upcoming CPI data due later in the week will be closely watched to understand the timing of potential Federal Reserve easing.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Signpost India gallops after Q3 PAT soars 215.3% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/signpost-india-gallops-after-q3-pat-soars-2153-yoy/1674452</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674452</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net sales rose 26.85% YoY to Rs 142.34 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 112.21 crore in the year-ago quarter.

On a consolidated basis, net sales rose 26.85% YoY to Rs 142.34 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 112.21 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a sequential basis, revenue increased 6.21% from Rs 134.02 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit after tax jumped sharply to Rs 18.13 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 215.3% YoY increase over Rs 5.75 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, PAT grew 15.77% from Rs 15.66 crore in the previous quarter. Profit before tax stood at Rs 25 crore, soaring from Rs 7.5 crore a year ago, translating into a 233.33% YoY increase. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PBT rose 10.72% from Rs 22.58 crore. Total expenditure increased 11.34% YoY to Rs 104.47 crore in Q3 FY26, while rising 4.90% sequentially from Rs 99.59 crore in Q2 FY26. Employee expenses climbed 9.83% YoY to Rs 12.63 crore, while interest costs rose 42.63% YoY to Rs 3.58 crore. Depreciation increased 4.49% YoY to Rs 10.48 crore. Signpost India is engaged in business of advertising in general and outdoor advertising in various ways and manner including indoor outdoor, newspapers, souvenirs, hoardings, buses, railways, bus shelters, airport etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SignpostIndiaLtd_66037594_69820.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India raises collateral-free MSME loan limit to Rs 20 lakh ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/reserve-bank-of-india-raises-collateral-free-msme-loan-limit-to-rs-20-lakh/1674439</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674439</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has revised its lending norms for the micro, small and medium enterprises (MSME) sector, raising the ceiling for collateral-free loans to micro and small enterprises (MSEs) to Rs 20 lakh.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has revised its lending norms for the micro, small and medium enterprises (MSME) sector, raising the ceiling for collateral-free loans to micro and small enterprises (MSEs) to Rs 20 lakh. Under the amended directions, banks have been instructed not to insist on collateral security for loans of up to Rs 20 lakh extended to MSE units. Lenders have also been advised to provide collateral-free loans up to the same limit to all beneficiaries covered under the Prime Minister Employment Generation Programme (PMEGP), which is implemented by the Khadi and Village Industries Commission (KVIC). Banks may further relax collateral requirements for loans up to Rs 25 lakh for MSEs with a satisfactory repayment history and sound financial position, subject to their internal credit policies. In such cases, lenders may avail coverage under the Credit Guarantee Scheme, wherever applicable. The central bank noted that voluntary pledging of gold or silver by borrowers for loans sanctioned within the collateral-free limit will not be treated as a breach of the directive. The changes have been incorporated into the Master Direction on Lending to the MSME Sector, which was last updated in July 2025. The RBI said the revised framework is intended to strengthen last-mile credit delivery to micro and small enterprises, which often struggle to furnish collateral due to limited asset ownership. RBI noted that amended directions also bring MSME lending norms in line with certain regulatory changes notified separately by the central bank. The RBI stated further that the measures form part of its broader effort to improve the flow of institutional finance to the MSME sector, a key contributor to employment generation and overall economic growth.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/budget-planning-and-allocating-money-concept-picture-id5081_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ISGEC Heavy Engineering  Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/isgec-heavy-engineering-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1674408</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674408</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Praj Industries Ltd, Jyoti Structures Ltd, Sterlite Technologies Ltd and Vesuvius India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 10 February 2026.

Praj Industries Ltd, Jyoti Structures Ltd, Sterlite Technologies Ltd and Vesuvius India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 10 February 2026. ISGEC Heavy Engineering Ltd spiked 19.99% to Rs 946.1 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8032 shares in the past one month. Praj Industries Ltd soared 11.28% to Rs 328.9. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 4.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 43314 shares in the past one month. Jyoti Structures Ltd surged 9.68% to Rs 11.1. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 5.3 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.45 lakh shares in the past one month. Sterlite Technologies Ltd rose 9.35% to Rs 156.2. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 23.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.57 lakh shares in the past one month. Vesuvius India Ltd jumped 7.53% to Rs 529.5. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 14749 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2714 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ISGECHeavy_59632489866_2167.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Equity MF inflows slide 14% on month, Gold ETF inflows see sharp bounce]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/equity-mf-inflows-slide-14-on-month-gold-etf-inflows-see-sharp-bounce/1674410</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674410</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Latest monthly data released by the Association of Mutual Funds in India (AMFI), has revealed that actively managed equity mutual funds recorded a Rs 24,028.59 crore inflow during January, sliding by 14% compared to the inflow of Rs 28,054.06 crore recorded in December.

Latest monthly data released by the Association of Mutual Funds in India (AMFI), has revealed that actively managed equity mutual funds recorded a Rs 24,028.59 crore inflow during January, sliding by 14% compared to the inflow of Rs 28,054.06 crore recorded in December. On net basis, overall mutual fund industry marked a strong inflow of Rs 1.56 lakh crore, as compared to an outflow of Rs 66,591 crore the previous month.The total mutual fund AUM rose to Rs 81.01 lakh crore in January from Rs 80.23 lakh crore in December. The monthly SIP flows held flat at Rs 31,002 crore. Large-cap funds saw an inflow of Rs 2,004.98 crore, against Rs 1,567 crore in December. The mid-cap category saw an inflow of Rs 3,185.47 crore, while the net flows into the category in the preceding month were Rs 4,176 crore. The small-cap funds recorded a net inflow of Rs 2,942.11 crore, while the net inflows stood at Rs 3,824 crore in December. Debt funds recorded an inflow of Rs 74,827.13 crore in the month of January, against an outflow of Rs 1.32 lakh crore in December. Overnight funds recorded an inflow of Rs 46,280 crore against an inflow of Rs 254.25 crore last month. Liquid funds also saw an inflow of Rs 30,681.55 crore, compared to an outflow of Rs 47,307.95 crore in December. Hybrid schemes saw inflows worth Rs 17,356.02 crore, against the Rs 10,755.57 crore inflow recorded in the preceding month. Gold ETFs saw inflows of Rs 24,039.96 crore amid soaring prices, rising sharply from Rs 11,647 crore during December.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/concept-money-tree-on-grass-picture-id462171033_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gravita India rises after inking deal to acquire Rasthriya Metal Industries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gravita-india-rises-after-inking-deal-to-acquire-rasthriya-metal-industries/1674409</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674409</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The proposed acquisition involves the purchase of shares from the existing shareholders of RMIL, which upon completion will result in RMIL becoming a subsidiary of Gravita.

The proposed acquisition involves the purchase of shares from the existing shareholders of RMIL, which upon completion will result in RMIL becoming a subsidiary of Gravita. RMIL is one of the most reputed manufacturers of copper & copper alloy products (strips, coils etc.) with nearly 40% exports to UAE, USA, Thailand, Sri Lanka, Kenya, Indonesia, Oman, and Saudi Arabia etc. RMIL has an integrated manufacturing facility in Sarigram, Gujarat across 58,287 square meters of land with a production capacity of 31,200 MTPA. Further, RMIL is having a turnover of Rs 910 crore and EBITDA of Rs 60 crore for the year ended 31 March 2025. The purchase consideration for the proposed acquisition of 100% equity stake is approximately Rs 565 crore. The transaction is expected to be completed on or before 31 March 2026, subject to completion of due diligence, execution of definitive documentation, receipt of necessary regulatory and other approvals, and satisfaction of customary closing conditions. "Signing of this binding term sheet will create an opportunity for expansion of group into the new vertical of Copper, increase the share of non-Lead business, provide further opportunities for backward integration, and create strong operating synergies with our existing plants across procurement, logistics and sales,” the company said in a statement. Gravita India is a manufacturer of lead, lead alloys & lead products, aluminum alloys & plastic granules, and offers turnkey solutions for the recycling industry and consultancy. The company's consolidated net profit jumped 25.33% to Rs 97.67 crore on 2.07% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,017.07 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GravitaIndia_26101386162_35607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gross NPAs of Scheduled Commercial Banks slide to historic low of 2.15%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gross-npas-of-scheduled-commercial-banks-slide-to-historic-low-of-215/1674406</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674406</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Finance has stated that the gross NPA ratio i.e.

Ministry of Finance has stated that the gross NPA ratio i.e. gross NPAs as a percentage of gross loans and advances of Scheduled Commercial Banks (SCBs), for domestic operations, has been continuously declining during the last eight financial years, and were at a historic low of 2.15% as at the end of September, 2025 (provisional data), which is lower than 2010-11 level. This continuous decline in gross NPAs of SCBs, including PSBs, has led to reduced provisioning by them, which in turn has improved their profitability thereby causing positive impact on the business growth. It also indicates that the asset quality as well as underwriting has improved in PSBs supported by a strong balance sheet and sustained profitability.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Texmaco Rail slides after Q3 PAT drops 45% YoY to Rs 42 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/texmaco-rail-slides-after-q3-pat-drops-45-yoy-to-rs-42-cr/1674402</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674402</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 21.45% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,041.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations fell 21.45% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,041.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax from continuing operations fell 36.72% to Rs 63.05 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 99.64 crore in Q3 FY25. On the expenses front, the company’s total expenses amounted to Rs 996.09 crore (down 19.74% YoY), employee expenses stood at Rs 45.03 crore (up 2.15% YoY) and other expenses were Rs 39.43 crore (down 14.81% YoY). During the quarter, Texmaco continued to deepen its engagement with Indian Railways, advancing its growth strategy by securing multiple orders across rail electrification, freight mobility, and metro rail infrastructure. Alongside, the company is actively exploring future-ready product segments, including export-led foundry expansion, infrastructure business growth, new rolling stock markets, wheelsets under the building-block model, metro and EMU coaches, fabricated bogies, propulsion systems, MSDAC, Kavach, ELS, as well as diversification into iron pellet trading and GCC expansion. The operating environment for the rail sector remains supportive. The Union Budget 2026–27 allocated a record Rs 2.93 lakh crore to Indian Railways, with a strong focus on electrification, freight capacity enhancement, safety infrastructure, and high-speed rail corridors. These priorities are expected to drive sustained public investment across network expansion, high-density routes, and traction and maintenance upgrades, closely aligning with Texmaco’s long-term growth roadmap. On the ESG front, Texmaco reaffirmed its commitment to sustainability. During the year, the company commissioned a 10 MW solar power plant at its Urla Foundry in Raipur, significantly reducing its carbon footprint. At the Belgharia Foundry in Kolkata, one high-tension furnace was converted from LDO to LPG, further lowering emissions. Reflecting improved governance and operational practices, CRISIL upgraded Texmaco’s ESG rating to 51 from 50, placing it in the ‘Adequate’ risk category, while ESG Risk Assessments & Insights assigned an ESG score of 43. Indrajit Mookerjee, Vice Chairman & Executive Director, said, “During Q3 FY26, Texmaco reported revenue of Rs 1,042 crore, EBITDA of Rs 102 crore with a margin of 9.6%, and PAT of Rs 42 crore. He noted that while revenues were impacted by transient supply-side constraints and export headwinds, operational discipline and cost control supported margin stability, adding that the company’s three-pillar growth strategy positions it for sustainable and scalable value creation as sector conditions normalise.” Sudipta Mukherjee, managing director, said, “Operational momentum remained steady during the quarter, with deliveries of over 2,000 freight cars and continued progress across rail electrification and infrastructure projects. He added that the company remains focused on disciplined execution, selective bidding, and expanding its addressable market through mobility and technology-led initiatives, supported by a strong policy and investment environment.” Texmaco Rail & Engineering (TEXMACO) is a listed company and part of the Adventz Group. Texmaco is a key player in the railway and infrastructure sector. It operates across three business segments: Freight Cars, Rail Infrastructure & Green Energy, and Infrastructure – Electrical.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TexmacoRail_96355740994_27419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 327 pts; auto shares in demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-327-pts-auto-shares-in-demand/1674400</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674400</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from returning foreign portfolio investors (FPIs).

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from returning foreign portfolio investors (FPIs). The Nifty traded tad above the 25,950 mark. Auto shares extended gains for the second consecutive trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 327.43 points or 0.39% to 84,393.18. The Nifty 50 index rose 91.30 points or 0.35% to 25,958.60. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.19% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.65%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,592 shares rose and 1,324 shares fell. A total of 192 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Fractal Analytics received bids for 21,86,224 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.12 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. Aye Finance received bids for 63,82,668 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.14 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index rose 1.28% to 28,148.55. The index added 2.29% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Tube Investments of India (up 2.97%), Bajaj Auto (up 1.92%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 1.76%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 1.72%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.6%), Uno Minda (up 1.37%), Eicher Motors (up 1.31%), Bharat Forge (up 1.19%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 0.7%) and Hero MotoCorp (up 0.53%) jumped. Stocks in Spotlight: Route Mobile jumped 5.53% after its consolidated net profit jumped 18.45% to Rs 97.70 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 82.48 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations declined 6.48% to Rs 1,107.06 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,183.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Ceigall India surged 4.70% after the company announced the receipt of a letter of award (LOA) from Rewa Ultra Mega Solar (RUMSL) for the development of Unit 1 (220 MW) at Morena Solar Park, Madhya Pradesh. Global Markets: Asian markets traded higher on Tuesday as Japan’s Nikkei 225 continued its post-election rally and reached new highs. The Japanese market continues to ride the "Takaichi trade” in the wake of Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s landslide victory in the Lower House. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 rose on Monday, boosted by technology stocks, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average reached new heights as investors awaited critical economic data and another batch of earnings reports. The broad-based index advanced for a second straight day, rising 0.47% and ending at 6,964.82. The blue-chip Dow eked out a 20.20-point gain, or 0.04%, and settled at 50,135.87. The Nasdaq Composite jumped 0.9%, closing at 23,238.67. Investors will also be watching for the delayed January jobs report from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, which is due out Wednesday. The release was initially scheduled for last Friday but was postponed due to the partial government shutdown. It also comes after ADP reported last week that private payrolls increased by a mere 22,000 in January. The January consumer price index reading—which was also delayed by the shutdown—is due out Friday, with the consensus looking for a 2.5% annual rate.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ISGEC Heavy Engineering hits the roof after blockbuster Q3 show]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/isgec-heavy-engineering-hits-the-roof-after-blockbuster-q3-show/1674381</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674381</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit came in at Rs 69.78 crore in Q3 FY26, soaring 247.7% YoY from Rs 20.07 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit came in at Rs 69.78 crore in Q3 FY26, soaring 247.7% YoY from Rs 20.07 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 58.77% from Rs 43.95 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 1,738.56 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.26% YoY compared with Rs 1,495.39 crore in Q3 FY25. On a QoQ basis, revenue increased 2.81% from Rs 1,691.09 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 122.68 crore in Q3 FY26, up a sharp 135.7% YoY from Rs 52.04 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, PBT rose 30.21% from Rs 94.22 crore in Q2 FY26. Total expenditure for the quarter increased to Rs 1,589.10 crore, up 13.59% YoY. Raw material consumption rose 7.17% YoY to Rs 611.74 crore, while employee expenses climbed 17.72% YoY to Rs 169.38 crore. Interest cost surged 98.57% on a YoY basis to Rs 16.72 crore, while depreciation declined 30.84% YoY to Rs 27.85 crore. Alongside the strong earnings print, the company also announced a significant capacity expansion roadmap. The board approved capital expenditure of Rs 22.6 crore to set up a new machining shop for the iron foundry division. It also cleared an investment of Rs 218 crore towards expansion of the machine building division. In addition, the proposed investment for the process skids and modules facility at SEZ Dahej was enhanced to Rs 110 crore from Rs 87 crore earlier. ISGEC Heavy Engineering is a global leader in manufacturing, industrial projects, and sugar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ISGECHeavy_59632489866_2167.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Pfizer Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-pfizer-ltd-counter/1674339</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674339</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bata India Ltd, Jyothy Labs Ltd, Tata Steel Ltd, Navin Fluorine International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 10 February 2026.

Bata India Ltd, Jyothy Labs Ltd, Tata Steel Ltd, Navin Fluorine International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 10 February 2026. Pfizer Ltd witnessed volume of 44834 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 69.86 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 642 shares. The stock increased 9.07% to Rs.5,192.15. Volumes stood at 1358 shares in the last session. Bata India Ltd registered volume of 1.09 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 14.29 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7653 shares. The stock rose 4.58% to Rs.924.85. Volumes stood at 6711 shares in the last session. Jyothy Labs Ltd saw volume of 2.27 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.35 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 24272 shares. The stock increased 0.08% to Rs.250.30. Volumes stood at 78255 shares in the last session. Tata Steel Ltd witnessed volume of 181.87 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7.48 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 24.31 lakh shares. The stock increased 2.97% to Rs.208.10. Volumes stood at 49.07 lakh shares in the last session. Navin Fluorine International Ltd saw volume of 73254 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 10465 shares. The stock dropped 0.04% to Rs.6,599.80. Volumes stood at 20319 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Pfizer_34853668517_434.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aurionpro Solutions jumps after expanding transaction banking engagement with DTB]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aurionpro-solutions-jumps-after-expanding-transaction-banking-engagement-with-dtb/1674337</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674337</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aurionpro said the upgraded engagement will support DTB's corporate transaction banking operations across Kenya, Uganda, and Tanzania.

Aurionpro said the upgraded engagement will support DTB's corporate transaction banking operations across Kenya, Uganda, and Tanzania. The bank aims to modernise platforms, improve operational efficiency, and manage rising transaction volumes as it expands regionally. As part of the upgrade, Aurionpro will deploy its iCashpro transaction banking platform, offering a unified digital interface covering payments, trade services, virtual accounts, and real-time reporting. The platform is aimed at enabling standardisation of processes, improved straight-through processing, and better visibility and control across markets. The company said the expanded engagement aligns with DTB’s focus on scaling its corporate banking footprint in Africa. It added that the initiative is aimed at maintaining consistent service levels and security standards across geographies. Aurionpro Solutions is a global enterprise technology leader pioneering intuitive-tech through deep-tech IPs and scalable products. With a strong presence across banking, payments, mobility, insurance, transit, data centers, and government sectors, Aurionpro is setting new benchmarks for AI innovation and impact. Its B2E (Business-to-Ecosystem) approach empowers entire ecosystems – driving growth, transformation, and scale across interconnected value chains. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Aurionpro Solutions declined 8% to Rs 44 crore while revenue rose 21% to Rs 371 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurionproSol_26787240482_8040.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty above 25,950; media shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-above-25950-media-shares-advance/1674335</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674335</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from returning foreign portfolio investors (FPIs).

The domestic equity indices traded with modest gains in the morning trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from returning foreign portfolio investors (FPIs). The Nifty traded above the 25,950 mark. Media shares extended gains for the second consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 318.22 points or 0.38% to 84,383.97. The Nifty 50 index rose 96.55 points or 0.37% to 25,963.85. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.22% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.61%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,585 shares rose and 1,168 shares fell. A total of 184 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Titan Company (up 0.83%), Eicher Motors (up 0.91%), Grasim Industries (up 0.60%), Apollo Hospitals Enterprise (up 0.07%), Britannia Industries (up 0.48%), Oil India (down 0.35%), Afcons Infrastructure (up 1.06%), Dilip Buildcon (up 0.23%), Edelweiss Financial Services (up 1.93%), Escorts Kubota (up 1.36%), Jubilant FoodWorks (up 1.26%), Karnataka Bank (up 0.07%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 1.97%), Torrent Power (up 1.72%), TVS Supply Chain Solutions (up 0.96%), United Breweries (up 0.96%), Wakefit Innovations (down 0.75%), and Wockhardt (down 0.86%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index advanced 1.86% to 1,478.50. The index rose 6.31% in the two consecutive trading sessions. D B Corp (up 3.73%), Sun TV Network (up 2.94%), Network 18 Media & Investments (up 2.65%), Nazara Technologies (up 2.46%), Prime Focus (up 2.04%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 1.4%), Saregama India (up 1.28%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (up 1.27%), and PVR Inox (up 1.25%) rose. Stocks in Spotlight: BSE surged 5.12% after the exchange reported a 174.0% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 601.81 crore on a 62.0% increase in net sales to Rs 1,244.10 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Bata India rallied 5.07% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 12.62% to Rs 66.10 crore on a 2.81% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 944.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Route Mobile gains as Q3 PAT spurts 18% YoY to Rs 98 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/route-mobile-gains-as-q3-pat-spurts-18-yoy-to-rs-98-cr/1674333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674333</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations declined 6.48% to Rs 1,107.06 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,183.79 crore in Q3 FY25.

However, revenue from operations declined 6.48% to Rs 1,107.06 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,183.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax jumped 26.42% to Rs 135.21 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 106.95 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses fell 9.28% to Rs 984.72 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,085.47 crore posted in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 73.74 crore (up 2.91% YoY), and finance costs stood at Rs 1.42 crore (down 84.66% YoY) during the quarter under review. Seckin Arikan, Chairman of the Board, Route Mobile and CEO, Proximus Global, commented, “Our performance this quarter reflects solid profitable growth. Despite a transitional period in parts of the portfolio, disciplined execution drove solid margin expansion thanks to strong seasonal contributions across regions. I would like to congratulate Mr. Agnihotri on his appointment as CEO and am confident his industry experience will drive our continued growth. I also extend sincere thanks to Mr. Gupta for his leadership in shaping Route Mobile’s success and look forward to benefiting from his continued expertise as Managing Director and Advisor to the Board. As we advance our strategy, we remain committed to building a scalable, differentiated business supported by a solid pipeline and the strengths of Proximus Global.” Rajdipkumar Gupta, MD, Route Mobile, added, “Q3 25-26 saw slightly downward revenue as we managed a transitional period in certain segments of our business. More importantly, our gross margins have strengthened considerably, driven by new customer additions in higher-margin segments, demonstrating the effectiveness of our portfolio optimization strategy. I am grateful to our teams across geographies for their dedication and agility in executing this strategic shift while delivering consistent service quality to our customers.” The Board of Route Mobile has approved the redesignation of Rajdipkumar Gupta as managing director, effective 9 February 2026, as he steps down from the role of CEO. Gupta will continue as a Key Managerial Personnel, with all other terms of his appointment unchanged. Simultaneously, Tushar Agnihotri has been appointed as chief executive officer and key managerial personnel, effective 9 February 2026. Previously Executive Vice President – India & APAC, Agnihotri will oversee overall operations and drive strategic initiatives, working closely with Mr. Gupta to accelerate growth and profitability. The company’s board has approved a third interim dividend of Rs 3 per equity share of Rs 10 each for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for eligibility is February 13, 2026, and the dividend will be paid to shareholders on the approved payment date. Route Mobile ("RML") is a cloud communications platform service provider, catering to enterprises, over-the-top (OTT) players, and mobile network operators (MNO). RML's portfolio comprises solutions in messaging, voice, email, SMS filtering, analytics, and monetization. RML has a diverse enterprise client base across a broad range of industries, including social media companies, banks and financial institutions, e-commerce entities, and travel aggregators. RML is headquartered in Mumbai, India, with a global presence in the Asia Pacific, the Middle East, Africa, Europe, and North America.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RouteMobileLtd_13116451_72028.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ceigall India spurts after bagging Rs 1,700 crore solar project in Madhya Pradesh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ceigall-india-spurts-after-bagging-rs-1700-crore-solar-project-in-madhya-pradesh/1674334</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674334</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project, awarded on a tariff-based competitive bidding mechanism, comprises a 220 MW solar power project integrated with a battery energy storage system (BESS).

The project, awarded on a tariff-based competitive bidding mechanism, comprises a 220 MW solar power project integrated with a battery energy storage system (BESS). The tariff quoted for the project is ₹2.70 per kWh, with an approximate project value of Rs 1,700 crore. The construction period for the project is 24 months, followed by an operational period of 25 years. The Morena Solar Park is a key renewable energy initiative in Madhya Pradesh and is designed to enhance grid stability through integrated storage solutions. The addition of BESS alongside solar generation will enable efficient peak power management and improved dispatch reliability. The company stated that this order would further strengthens its growing order book and mark a strategic expansion into large-scale renewable energy infrastructure. Ramneek Sehgal, Chairman & Managing Director, Ceigall India Limited, said: "We are pleased to secure the 220 MW Solar and BESS project at Morena Solar Park from Rewa Ultra Mega Solar Limited. This project strengthens our presence in the clean energy segment, and we are committed to executing it efficiently while supporting India’s energy transition and decarbonisation objectives." Ceigall India has also announced its earnings for the quarter ended on 31 December 2025. The company has reported 1.2% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 74.11 crore on a 19.3% increase in net revenue to Rs 991.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. While EBITDA improved by 12.7% to Rs 139.1 crore, EBITDA margin declined by 90 basis points YoY to 14.0% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 97.05 crore, up by 2.7% from Rs 94.53 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Ceigall India is an infrastructure engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) company undertaking specialized structural works such as elevated roads, flyovers, bridges, railway overbridges, tunnels, highways, expressways, and runways. The principal business operations are broadly divided into EPC projects and hybrid annuity model (HAM) projects.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CeigallIndiaLtd_68678209_85110.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE zooms after recording PAT of Rs 601 crore in Q3; EBITDA margin expands to 59% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-zooms-after-recording-pat-of-rs-601-crore-in-q3-ebitda-margin-expands-to-59/1674331</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674331</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In the trading segment, Cash Market volumes stood at Rs 7,645 crore in Q3 FY26, while Index Derivatives achieved a record average daily premium turnover of Rs 19,459 crore—driven by continued growth in Sensex Index Options.

In the trading segment, Cash Market volumes stood at Rs 7,645 crore in Q3 FY26, while Index Derivatives achieved a record average daily premium turnover of Rs 19,459 crore—driven by continued growth in Sensex Index Options. BSE StAR MF recorded 14% year-on-year growth in revenues to Rs 72.5 crore and total transactions increased by 21% to 21.7 crore. The platform also processed a record 7.97 crore transactions in January 2026. ICCL, BSE’s clearing subsidiary, reported strong performance with Equity Settled Turnover of Rs 8.14 lakh crore and Equity Derivatives Premium Turnover of Rs 12.57 lakh crore, settling 364 crore derivatives contracts in Q3 FY26. Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 511.96 crore, down 3.9% YoY. Consolidated operating EBITDA rose by 211% year on year to Rs 732 crore, with margins expanding sharply to 59% in Q3 FY26 from 31% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 795.33 crore, up by 176.2% from Rs 287.97 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The MD & CEO, BSE, said: “BSE’s strong Q3 performance is a testament to the strength of our platforms and the confidence the marketplaces in BSE. With record SME listings, growing index derivatives activity and continued success of StAR MF, we are accelerating innovation across all our businesses." BSE is Asia’s oldest exchange and the world’s largest exchange in terms of the number of listed companies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BSELtd_11315994_21236.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends downside: Positive cues from equities likely to limit losses]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-downside-positive-cues-from-equities-likely-to-limit-losses/1674326</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674326</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.77 against the US dollar in early trade on Tuesday as the currency market continues to price in caution following the India-US interim trade framework.

The Indian rupee depreciated 11 paise to 90.77 against the US dollar in early trade on Tuesday as the currency market continues to price in caution following the India-US interim trade framework. At the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 90.63 against the US dollar, then lost some ground to touch 90.77, registering a loss of 11 paise over its previous close. Yesterday, rupee witnessed a volatile trading session and settled for the day on a slightly lower note, down 1 paisa at 90.66 against the US dollar. Indian shares edged higher in opening trades on Tuesday, tracking firm cues from global markets. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.6 percent and 0.7 percent, respectively on Monday after the United States and India unveiled an interim framework designed to reduce tariffs, redefine energy partnerships, and enhance economic collaboration. Foreign institutional investors bought shares worth Rs 2,255 crore on a net basis Monday, while domestic institutional investors bought shares to the extent of Rs 4 crore, according to provisional exchange data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bata India spurts after Q3 PAT jumps 13% YoY to Rs 66 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bata-india-spurts-after-q3-pat-jumps-13-yoy-to-rs-66-cr/1674315</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674315</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before Tax grew by 14.96% to Rs 88.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 77.30 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before Tax grew by 14.96% to Rs 88.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 77.30 crore in Q3 FY25. The results for the quarter also include a one-time exceptional expenditure of Rs 6.66 crore recognized under the new Labour Code. Total expenses jumped 3.30% to Rs 868.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 841.10 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses were at Rs 111.41 crore (up 7.72% YoY), while the cost of material consumed stood at Rs 48.84 crore (down 27.59% YoY) during the period under review. Speaking on Bata India’s Q3 FY26 performance, MD and CEO Gunjan Shah, said, “the improvement in demand post-GST 2.0 rollout continued during the quarter, supported by a few green shoots, resulting in strong EBITDA performance driven by sales and margin growth. All channels delivered growth with solid gross margin management, reflecting disciplined execution of key strategic levers. Premium products, particularly brands like Hush Puppies and Power, showed robust growth, while fresh sales contribution rose quarter-on-quarter. The company added 27 franchise stores, and the Zero Base Merchandising (ZBM) project was scaled to 400+ stores, improving consumer experience and revenue per square foot. Inventory efficiencies in both quantity and quality continued, with gross inventory reduction of 11%. Shah noted that initiatives in decluttering, inventory freshness, and cost optimization helped drive operating margin leverage, and continued marketing investments, along with a focus on strategic levers — product, channels, and inventory — keep the company optimistic for the future under GST 2.0.” Bata India is the largest retailer and manufacturer of footwear in the country. The company is engaged in the business of manufacturing and trading footwear and accessories through their retail and wholesale network. Their products include leather footwear, rubber/canvas footwear, and plastic footwear.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BataIndia_31276004590_60.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>