<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:57:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Power India Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-power-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1675767</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675767</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd, Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd, Borosil Scientific Ltd and Apex Frozen Foods Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 February 2026.

JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd, Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd, Borosil Scientific Ltd and Apex Frozen Foods Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 February 2026. GE Power India Ltd spiked 20.00% to Rs 399.95 at 11:59 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.71 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10058 shares in the past one month. JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd surged 19.63% to Rs 29.74. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 2 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1089 shares in the past one month. Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd soared 17.32% to Rs 319. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1872 shares in the past one month. Borosil Scientific Ltd rose 16.17% to Rs 122.85. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 3.78 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2742 shares in the past one month. Apex Frozen Foods Ltd gained 15.83% to Rs 431.35. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 4.81 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 97157 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GEPower_62970729410_20944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Avanti Feeds Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avanti-feeds-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1675756</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675756</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ratnamani Metals & Tubes Ltd, Garware Technical Fibres Ltd, Godrej Agrovet Ltd and Sharda Cropchem Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 February 2026.

Ratnamani Metals & Tubes Ltd, Garware Technical Fibres Ltd, Godrej Agrovet Ltd and Sharda Cropchem Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 February 2026. Avanti Feeds Ltd soared 13.57% to Rs 1355.05 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 5.12 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.5 lakh shares in the past one month. Ratnamani Metals & Tubes Ltd surged 12.31% to Rs 2223.15. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 14068 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1218 shares in the past one month. Garware Technical Fibres Ltd spiked 9.95% to Rs 758. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 55289 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5529 shares in the past one month. Godrej Agrovet Ltd jumped 9.50% to Rs 646.15. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.6 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17259 shares in the past one month. Sharda Cropchem Ltd rose 7.98% to Rs 1235.95. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 32403 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 65476 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AvantiFeeds_50148690699_3852.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Garuda Construction Q3 PAT spurts 156% YoY to Rs 33 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/garuda-construction-q3-pat-spurts-156-yoy-to-rs-33-cr/1675755</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675755</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 43.67 crore, up by 153.9% from Rs 17.20 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 43.67 crore, up by 153.9% from Rs 17.20 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 96.53 crore, up 112.53% YoY. Garuda Construction and Engineering specializes in turnkey EPC solutions and has expertise in residential, commercial, infrastructure, and renewable energy projects. The scrip rose 0.52% to currently trade at Rs 204.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GarudaConstructionandEngineeringLtd_41144652_92781.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Unilever Q3 PAT skyrockets 121% YoY to Rs 6,603 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-unilever-q3-pat-skyrockets-121-yoy-to-rs-6603-cr/1675749</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675749</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The PAT was primarily driven by a one-off positive impact from the Ice Cream demerger, accounted for in accordance with the approved scheme of demerger and applicable accounting standards.

The PAT was primarily driven by a one-off positive impact from the Ice Cream demerger, accounted for in accordance with the approved scheme of demerger and applicable accounting standards. Profit before tax (PBT) declined 27.62% YoY to Rs 2,919 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. EBITDA rose 3% to Rs 3,788 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,689 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin fell 70 bps to 23.3% in Q3 FY26 as against 24% in Q3 FY25. The company reported a consolidated 5% underlying sales growth (USG), driven by a 4% increase in underlying volume growth (UVG). Revenue from the Home Care division stood at Rs 5,887 crore in Q3 FY26, up 2.57% year-on-year. The division reported 3% Underlying Sales Growth (USG) supported by mid-single digit Underlying Volume Growth (UVG). The category continued to experience negative price impact due to pricing actions taken during the year. Fabric Wash delivered mid-single digit UVG, while the Liquids portfolio accelerated its growth with double-digit gains. Household Care strengthened its double-digit UVG trend, led by Vim Liquid. During the quarter, market-development efforts were intensified to drive penetration and consumer upgradation to premium powders, with a focused push on the Rs 99 Surf Excel Easy Wash pack. Revenue from the Beauty & Wellbeing division stood at Rs 3,930 crore in Q3 FY26, up 10.51% year-on-year. The division delivered 6% Underlying Sales Growth (USG) with low-single digit Underlying Volume Growth (UVG). Hair Care reported volume-led double-digit growth, strengthening its leadership position, driven by outperformance in premium brands Dove and TRESemmé. Skin Care and Colour Cosmetics performed strongly in light moisturisers and the winter portfolio, offset by a subdued non-winter performance. The category maintained double-digit growth momentum in Channels of the Future, continuing to gain market share. Health & Wellbeing recorded another quarter of robust high double-digit growth. During the quarter, the company launched TRESemmé Hydra Matrix, powered by category-defining hydration technology, and Minimalist expanded its skin and face portfolio with science-backed toners and serums for barrier support and advanced anti-ageing results. Revenue from the Personal Care division stood at Rs 2,370 crore in Q3 FY26, up 5.66% year-on-year. The division grew 6% overall, with Skin Cleansing delivering mid-single digit growth, driven by strong double-digit gains in Pears and Dove. The Bodywash portfolio continued to outperform, further strengthening its market leadership. Oral Care posted double-digit growth, led by the outperformance of Closeup. During the quarter, the freshness portfolio in Oral Care was further expanded with the launch of Closeup Intense Cool, whose zinc and cooling beads formula provides consumers with an instant burst of intense cooling and long-lasting freshness. The Foods division delivered 6% Underlying Sales Growth (USG), led by high-single digit Underlying Volume Growth (UVG). Tea reported mid-single digit UVG, while revenue grew at a low-single digit pace, reflecting the impact of price reductions in a deflationary commodity environment. Coffee maintained strong double-digit growth, supported by both price and volume. Lifestyle Nutrition grew in high-single digits, driven by Boost and Horlicks. Packaged Foods also reported high-single digit growth, led by volumes, with broad-based performance across Ketchup, Mayonnaise, Soups, and Unilever Foods Solutions. During the quarter, the Kissan masterbrand was extended into new demand spaces with the introduction of the Great Indian Chutneys range, inspired by flavors from across India. Horlicks’ desirability was further enhanced with the launch of Horlicks Superfoods, enriched with superfood ingredients and powered by Nutrimax technology for superior nutrient absorption, along with a zero added sugar variant. Priya Nair, CEO and MD, commented: “During the quarter, demand trends reflected early signs of recovery, underpinned by supportive policy measures. Against this backdrop, we delivered a competitive performance, with 6% Revenue Growth and 4% Underlying Volume Growth. We continued to build desirability at scale with our brands, accelerate market development in high-growth demand spaces and strengthen our capabilities to scale Channels of the Future with a dedicated organisation for Quick commerce. As market leaders in FMCG, our commitment to build modern brands, lead category creation and invest disproportionately to build future moats, places us in good stead to deliver sustained volume-led growth and create long-term shareholder value.” Hindustan Unilever is in the FMCG business comprising primarily of Home Care, Beauty & Personal Care and Foods & Refreshment segments. The Company has manufacturing facilities across the country and sells primarily in India. Shares of Hindustan Unilever slipped 3.21% to currently trade at Rs 2,383.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindUnilever_85453091314_255.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty slips below 25,850 mark; realty shares witness profit booking]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-slips-below-25850-mark-realty-shares-witness-profit-booking/1675748</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675748</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with substantial losses in mid-morning trade weighed down by profit booking.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with substantial losses in mid-morning trade weighed down by profit booking. Sentiment remained cautious due to the expiry of BSE derivatives contracts and FII selling, prompting a shift toward a risk-off approach. The Nifty traded below the 25,850 mark. Investors also awaited for the Q3 results from Indian Hotel Company, Hindustan Aeronautics, ONGC and Coal India, due later today. Realty shares tumbled after rallying for four consecutive trading sessions. At 11:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 427.92 points or 0.51% to 83,805.72. The Nifty 50 index fell 121.55 points or 0.47% to 25,832.30. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.71% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.89%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,557 shares rose and 2,290 shares fell. A total of 234 shares were unchanged. Direct Tax Collection : The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index dropped 1.10% to 28,986.55. The index jumped 4.28% in the past four consecutive trading sessions. Anant Raj (down 2.26%), Brigade Enterprises (down 1.78%), DLF (down 1.59%), Sobha (down 1.58%) and Godrej Properties (down 1.38%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 1.23%), Oberoi Realty (down 0.83%), Lodha Developers (down 0.78%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.14%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Apex Frozen Foods zoomed 15.96% after the company reported a net profit of Rs 10.09 crore in Q3 FY26 as against a net loss of Rs 0.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales for the period under review added up to Rs 264.29 crore, up 14.5% YoY. Zydus Lifesciences rose 1.61% after the company announced a settlement agreement with Astellas Pharma Inc. in relation to Myrbetriq (generic name: Mirabegron) in the United States. Mazda zoomed 9.32% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 17.52% to Rs 8.72 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 7.42 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 1.30% to Rs 47.39 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 46.78 crore in the same quarter last year. Global markets: Most Asian market advanced on Thursday, buoyed by Japan’s post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Japanese stocks extending its post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Media reports noted that Takaichi’s snap-election landslide gives her an unusually strong, multi-year mandate to execute policy, which they view as broadly supportive for Japan’s markets and corporate sector. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day win streak after a better-than-expected January jobs report. The blue-chip index lost 66.74 points, or 0.13%, and closed at 50,121.40. The S&P 500 was nearly flat at 6,941.47. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 0.16% to end at 23,066.47. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000. Strong labor market has reduced the odds for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The jobs report follows weaker-than-expected consumer data released on Tuesday. That report showed that consumer spending in December was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain expected from economists polled by Dow Jones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DXY stays pressured under 97 mark despite stronger than expected US nonfarm payrolls]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dxy-stays-pressured-under-97-mark-despite-stronger-than-expected-us-nonfarm-payrolls/1675747</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675747</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar index stays pressurized under 97 mark on Thursday despite improved US economic data which provides some relief to concerns about the state of the US labor market.

The US dollar index stays pressurized under 97 mark on Thursday despite improved US economic data which provides some relief to concerns about the state of the US labor market. Data released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics on Wednesday showed that the US economy added 130,000 jobs in January, above the market consensus of 70,000. The Unemployment Rate edged lower to 4.3% in January versus 4.4% prior, better than the forecast of 4.4%. Meanwhile, Fed’s Hammack said that the unemployment rate is stabilizing, following the upbeat January Nonfarm Payrolls (NFP) report. Meanwhile, Kansas City Fed President Jeff Schmid stated that the central bank needs to keep rates at restrictive levels to continue putting downward pressure on inflation and added he’s not seeing many indications of restraint in the economic data. Investors now shift attention to the release of the latest US consumer inflation figures on Friday, which could offer more cues about the Fed's rate-cut path. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 96.88, up 0.16% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Commerce Minister urges exporters to take full advantage of Free Trade Agreements signed with developed countries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/commerce-minister-urges-exporters-to-take-full-advantage-of-free-trade-agreements-signed-with-developed-countries/1675739</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675739</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal has urged exporters and industry bodies to take full advantage of the series of Free Trade Agreements signed with developed countries maximise job creation and boost exports of goods and services.

Union Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal has urged exporters and industry bodies to take full advantage of the series of Free Trade Agreements signed with developed countries maximise job creation and boost exports of goods and services. The minister met 35 Export Promotion Councils (EPCs) and key Industry Associations representing India’s major export sectors. Industry leaders and association office bearers appreciated the government’s trade-promotion initiatives during their interaction with the minister. Goyal noted that the government had signed Free Trade Agreements with developed countries to help India’s farmers, workers, professionals, artisans and MSMEs take advantage of the global market with preferential access. With these trade agreements, India’s traditional medicines and yoga will also get global opportunities, while the interest of India’s agriculture and dairy sectors have been protected. He further stated that industry must now intensify its efforts to penetrate new markets, upgrade quality and become more competitive to take maximum advantage of trade agreements.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/coworker-carrying-cardboard-box-in-warehouse-picture-id5207_commodities.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Australian dollar hits three-year high against US dollar as RBA rate hike talk dominates sentiments]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/australian-dollar-hits-three-year-high-against-us-dollar-as-rba-rate-hike-talk-dominates-sentiments/1675735</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675735</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Australian dollar has been rising recently and is consolidating near a three-year high as market eye Reserve Bank of Australia monetary tightening action.

The Australian dollar has been rising recently and is consolidating near a three-year high as market eye Reserve Bank of Australia monetary tightening action. AUD/USD climbed to 0.7125 today and currently trades at 0.7119, down marginally on the day. US dollar index is lax in global markets while key commodity prices generally stay elevated. Rising commodities tend to support the AUD given Australia’s heavy dependence on exports of a number of minerals and metals. Reserve Bank of Australia bank will raise rates again if inflation becomes entrenched, Michele Bullock, the central bank governor said today. The RBA delivered the first rate rise in two years last week. The RBA Deputy Governor Andrew Hauser also delivered a hawkish set of comments yesterday as he highlighted resurgent domestic demand.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Indegene Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-indegene-ltd-counter/1675734</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675734</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[APL Apollo Tubes Ltd, Elgi Equipments Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd, AAVAS Financiers Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 12 February 2026.

APL Apollo Tubes Ltd, Elgi Equipments Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd, AAVAS Financiers Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 12 February 2026. Indegene Ltd registered volume of 5.38 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 38.48 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 13975 shares. The stock slipped 0.45% to Rs.471.05. Volumes stood at 10855 shares in the last session. APL Apollo Tubes Ltd witnessed volume of 14.11 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 18.13 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 77831 shares. The stock dropped 0.04% to Rs.2,279.70. Volumes stood at 80089 shares in the last session. Elgi Equipments Ltd notched up volume of 7.69 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 14.42 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 53332 shares. The stock rose 4.03% to Rs.516.50. Volumes stood at 18752 shares in the last session. Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd clocked volume of 1.87 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.43 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 19797 shares. The stock gained 5.25% to Rs.1,392.10. Volumes stood at 48933 shares in the last session. AAVAS Financiers Ltd clocked volume of 99417 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.94 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 11115 shares. The stock gained 0.79% to Rs.1,318.60. Volumes stood at 7842 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndegeneLtd_69609587_43575.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Apex Frozen Foods spurts after registering PAT of Rs 10 crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apex-frozen-foods-spurts-after-registering-pat-of-rs-10-crore-in-q3/1675733</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675733</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales for the period under review added up to Rs 264.29 crore, up 14.5% YoY.

Net sales for the period under review added up to Rs 264.29 crore, up 14.5% YoY. PBIDT improved by 175.2% to Rs 17.31 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6.29 crore in Q3 FY25. The company has posted a pre-tax profit of Rs 13.35 crore in Q3 FY6 as against a pre-tax loss of Rs 0.21 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Apex Frozen Foods (AFFL) is engaged in the business of processing and exporting seafood.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ApexFrozenFoodsLtd_2930397471_70330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aye Finance IPO ends with 97% subscription; QIB demand supports issue ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aye-finance-ipo-ends-with-97-subscription-qib-demand-supports-issue/1675732</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675732</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Aye Finance received bids for 4,42,21,288 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer.

The initial public offer (IPO) of Aye Finance received bids for 4,42,21,288 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.97 times. The Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 1.50 times, the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 0.77 times and the Non-Institutional Investors category was subscribed 0.05 times. The issue opened for bidding on Monday (9 February 2026) and it closed on Wednesday (11 February 2026). The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. The issue also consists of offer for sale (OFS) of Rs 300 crore through issuance of 2.33-2.46 crore equity shares. The OFS from investor selling shareholders was Rs 30 crore from Alpha Wave India I LP, Rs 139.763 crore from MAJ Invest Financial Inclusion Fund II K/S, Rs 82.5 crore from CapitalG L P, Rs 30 crore from LGT Capital Invest Mauritius PCC with Cell E/VP and Rs 17.737 crore from Vikram Jetley. The company proposed to utilize the net proceeds from the fresh issue towards augmenting the capital base to meet future capital requirements. Ahead of the IPO, Aye Finance Labs on 8 February 2026, the company raised Rs 454.49 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 3. 52 crore shares at Rs 129 each to 19 anchor investors. Aye Finance incorporated in 1993 is Delhi based non-banking financial company – middle layer (NBFC-ML) focused on providing loans to micro scale micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMEs) across India. It offers a range of small ticket business loans with average ticket size on disbursement at Rs 1.8 lakh for working capital and business expansion needs, against hypothecation of working assets or against security of property to customers across manufacturing, trading, service and allied agriculture sectors. Gross NPA ratio has increased from 2.49% at end March 2023 to 4.21% at end March 2025 and 4.85% end September 2025. The capital adequacy ratio was 32.27%, with Tier I capital comprising 32.27% and Tier II capital comprising Nil at end September 2025. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 64.6 crore and income from operations of Rs 733.83 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zydus Lifesciences gains on settlement with Astellas over Myrbetriq]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zydus-lifesciences-gains-on-settlement-with-astellas-over-myrbetriq/1675729</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675729</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company, along with its wholly owned subsidiary Zydus Pharmaceuticals USA, has entered into a settlement that concludes all ongoing patent litigations with Astellas concerning Myrbetriq and Mirabegron.

The company, along with its wholly owned subsidiary Zydus Pharmaceuticals USA, has entered into a settlement that concludes all ongoing patent litigations with Astellas concerning Myrbetriq and Mirabegron. Under the terms of the agreement, Zydus will pay Astellas an aggregate amount of $120 million. In addition, the company will pay a prepaid per-unit licensing fee on sales of its generic Mirabegron in the US from the date of the settlement until September 2027. Other terms of the agreement remain confidential. The settlement enables Zydus to continue marketing its generic Mirabegron product in the US market. In April 2025, Zydus had informed exchanges that the United States District Court for the District of Delaware had ruled in favour of Astellas on the validity of US Patent No. 10,842,780 related to a sustained-release formulation of mirabegron marketed as Myrbetriq. The court order had upheld the patent’s validity, while issues relating to alleged infringement and damages were scheduled to be litigated at a consolidated jury trial in 2026. Zydus Lifesciences is a global life sciences company with operations across pharmaceuticals, consumer wellness, and medical technology. On a consolidated basis, its net profit rose 1.82% to Rs 1042.10 crore while net sales rose 32.34% to Rs 6780.40 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CadilaHealth_93490673476_20883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/motilal-oswal-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1675722</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675722</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 12 February 2026.

Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 12 February 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund management Structure Revised Fund management Structure Motilal Oswal Quant Fund Ajay Khandelwal Ajay Khandelwal Ankit Agarwal Motilal Oswal Business Cycle Fund Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma Atul Mehra Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma Motilal Oswal Multi Cap Fund Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Sandeep Jain Atul Mehra Sandeep Jain Motilal Oswal Balanced Advantage Fund Ajay Khandelwal Atul Mehra Sandeep Jain Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma Atul Mehra Sandeep Jain Ankit Agarwal Varun Sharma

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mazda spurts as Q3 PAT climbs 18% YoY to Rs 9 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mazda-spurts-as-q3-pat-climbs-18-yoy-to-rs-9-cr/1675720</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675720</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 1.30% to Rs 47.39 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 46.78 crore in the same quarter last year.

Revenue from operations rose 1.30% to Rs 47.39 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 46.78 crore in the same quarter last year. Profit from operations before tax stood at Rs 11.29 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.39%, compared with Rs 9.70 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. The company's revenue from engineering division rose 2.52% YoY to Rs 40.14 crore in Q3 FY26, while revenue from food division decreased 4.98% YoY to Rs 7.24 crore. Mazda is engaged in the business of manufacturing Engineering goods like Vacuum Products, Evaporators, Pollution Control Equipments and Manufacturing of Food Products like Food colour, Various Fruit Jams & Fruit mix Powders etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Mazda_56183286306_2838.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade in negative terrain; IT shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-in-negative-terrain-it-shares-decline/1675716</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675716</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses in morning trade weighed down by profit booking.

The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses in morning trade weighed down by profit booking. Sentiment remained cautious due to the expiry of BSE derivatives contracts and FII selling, prompting a shift toward a risk-off stance. Investors also awaited for the Q3 results from Indian Hotel Company, Hindustan Aeronautics, ONGC and Coal India, due later today. The Nifty traded below the 25,900 mark. IT stocks witnessed selling pressure for the second consecutive session after stronger-than-expected US jobs data further dampened hopes of a Fed rate cut. Sentiment was also weighed down by concerns over AI-led disruptions. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 304.29 points or 0.36% to 83,929.15. The Nifty 50 index fell 89.05 points or 0.34% to 25,866.35. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.59% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.63%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,597 shares rose and 2,047 shares fell. A total of 227 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Hindustan Unilever(up 0.32%), Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (up 0.69%), Coal India(down 0.01%), Lupin(up 0.26%), Indian Hotels Company(down 0.71%), Hindalco Industries(down 0.64%), Honasa Consumer(up 1.06%), Abbott India(down 0.65%), Bajaj Hindusthan Sugar(down 0.70%), Bharat Forge(down 0.60%), Biocon(up 1.89%), CRISIL(down 1.58%), Endurance Technologies(down 1.09%), Hindustan Aeronautics(down 0.71%), Indraprastha Gas(down 3.69%), Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation(down 0.20%), Muthoot Finance(up 0.46%), Natco Pharma(up 0.79%), Petronet LNG(down 0.69%), Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers(down 0.63%), SpiceJet(up 0.19%) and Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services (down 0.91%) will release their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index dropped 3.96% to 33,704. The index declined 5.65% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Coforge (down 5.04%), Infosys (down 4.72%), Mphasis (down 4.42%), LTIMindtree (down 4.36%) and Tech Mahindra (down 4.24%), Wipro (down 4.23%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 3.96%), Persistent Systems (down 3.96%), HCL Technologies (down 3.62%) and Oracle Financial Services Software (down 3.21%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: SJVN rallied 3.14% after the company reported a 50.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 224.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 149.03 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations surged 61.2% year-on-year to Rs 1,081.97 crore during the quarter under review, up from Rs 670.99 crore in the corresponding period last year. Elgi Equipments rose 2.72% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 95.2 crore in Q3 FY26, up 18.1% from Rs 80.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 18.4% year-on-year to Rs 1,003 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 848 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Fractal Analytics IPO ends with 2.66 times subscription]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fractal-analytics-ipo-ends-with-266-times-subscription/1675712</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675712</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Fractal Analytics received bids for 4,94,79,888 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer.

Fractal Analytics received bids for 4,94,79,888 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 2.66 times. The Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 4.18 times, the Non-Institutional Investors category was subscribed 1.06 times and the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 1.03 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. The Rs 2,833.9 crore IPO comprises a fresh issue of 11,372,222 equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,023.5 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 20,115,556 equity shares worth Rs 1,810.4 crore at the upper price band of Rs 900. Fractal will utilize Rs 264.9 crore from the net fresh issue proceeds to invest in its unit, Fractal USA, for repayment of its borrowings; Rs 57.1 crore for the purchase of laptops; Rs 121.1 crore for setting up of new office premises in India; and Rs 355.1 crore for investment in R&D and sales and marketing under Fractal Alpha. The remaining funds will be utilized for general corporate purposes. Fractal Analytics is an enterprise AI company providing end-to-end artificial intelligence solutions to global enterprises to support data-driven decision-making. With over 25 years of experience, the company operates through Fractal.ai and Fractal Alpha, serving clients across CPG and retail, TMT, healthcare and life sciences, and BFSI, with a customer base that includes several leading global corporations. Ahead of the IPO of Fractal Analytics on 6 February 2026, the company raised Rs 474.99 crore from anchor investors by allotting 52.77 lakh shares at Rs 900 each to 22 anchor investors. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 70.90 crore and sales of Rs 1,559 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zaggle Prepaid inks pact with Rebel Foods]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zaggle-prepaid-inks-pact-with-rebel-foods/1675710</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675710</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the agreement, Zaggle will provide its Zaggle Zoyer platform to Rebel Foods for a period of one year.

Under the agreement, Zaggle will provide its Zaggle Zoyer platform to Rebel Foods for a period of one year. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and is in the nature of an agreement. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services (Zaggle) is a leading player in spend management, with a differentiated value proposition and diversified user base. The company operates in the business-to-business-to-customer segment. It is one of the largest numbers of issued prepaid cards in India in partnership with its banking partners. Additionally, the company has a diversified portfolio of software as a service (SaaS) products, including tax and payroll software, and a wide touchpoint reach. The company’s standalone net profit surged 79.1% to Rs 33.24 crore on a 42.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 430.98 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services fell 1.16% to Rs 293.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZagglePrepaidOceanServicesLtd_95613182_78337.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ceigall India rises after subsidiary secures Rs 2,160 crore NHAI project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ceigall-india-rises-after-subsidiary-secures-rs-2160-crore-nhai-project/1675709</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675709</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company's wholly owned subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects, has received a Letter of Award from the National Highways Authority of India for a highway project in Bihar.

The company's wholly owned subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects, has received a Letter of Award from the National Highways Authority of India for a highway project in Bihar. The project involves four-laning of the Sahebganj-Areraj-Bettiah section of NH-139W in Bihar, with a total length of 78.942 km. The stretch comprises Section 1 from Sahebganj to Areraj covering 38.362 km and Section 2 from Areraj to Bettiah covering 40.580 km. The bid project cost is approximately Rs 2,160 crore, and the project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). The construction period is 730 days, followed by a 15-year operation and maintenance period. The company said the corridor is expected to improve regional connectivity in Bihar and support economic activity in the region. Ceigall India is an infrastructure engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) company engaged in the development of highways, expressways, bridges, flyovers, railway overbridges, tunnels, and runways. The company executes projects under EPC as well as Hybrid Annuity Model (HAM) formats and has a strong track record of timely execution across multiple states in India. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Ceigall India rose 1.24% to Rs 74.11 crore while net sales rose 19.34% to Rs 991.14 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CeigallIndiaLtd_68678209_85110.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IRCON Intl Q3 PAT jumps 16% YoY to Rs 100 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ircon-intl-q3-pat-jumps-16-yoy-to-rs-100-cr/1675708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675708</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations declined 18.89% to Rs 2,119.04 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 2,612.86 crore in the same quarter last year.

However, revenue from operations declined 18.89% to Rs 2,119.04 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 2,612.86 crore in the same quarter last year. Profit from operations before tax stood at Rs 134.69 crore in Q3 FY26, up 2.17%, compared with Rs 131.82 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. EBITDA were at Rs 269.3 crore in Q3 FY26, up 23.36% as compared with Rs 218.3 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s EBITDA margin stood at 12.2% in Q3 FY26. The company's revenue from international customers fell 38.47% YoY to Rs 49.52 crore in Q3 FY26, while revenue from domestic customers decreased 18.27% YoY to Rs 2,069.52 crore. As of 31 December 2025, the total order book stands at Rs 23,801 crore, with the Railways segment accounting for Rs 17,781 crore, Highways contributing Rs 4,297 crore, and other segments making up Rs 1,723 crore. The board of directors has approved an interim dividend of Rs 1.20 per equity share of Rs 2 each for the financial year 2025-26. On its outlook, the company is well-positioned to capitalize on India’s rapidly evolving infrastructure landscape. With robust government support through initiatives like PM Gati Shakti, Bharatmala, Sagarmala, and the Smart Cities Mission, alongside increased CAPEX of Rs 12.20 lakh crore and new high-speed rail and freight corridors proposed in Budget 2026, the company expects strong growth opportunities across railways, roadways, and urban infrastructure projects. Leveraging its existing order book and strategic capabilities, the company is poised to benefit from these developments and strengthen its market presence. Ircon International is a public sector construction company with an emphasis on infrastructure projects, with a specialization in the execution of railway projects on a turnkey basis and otherwise. After commencing business as a railway construction company, it diversified progressively to roads, buildings, electrical substations and distribution, airport construction, commercial complexes, as well as metro rail works. Shares of Ircon International shed 0.93% to Rs 154.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IrconIntl_4733182919_5497.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Power spurts on reporting turnaround Q3 numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-power-spurts-on-reporting-turnaround-q3-numbers/1675707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675707</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income rose by 16.5% year on year (YoY) to Rs 401.25 crore in the third quarter of FY26.

Total income rose by 16.5% year on year (YoY) to Rs 401.25 crore in the third quarter of FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 131.57 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 24.48 crore a year ago. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 27.57 crore during the quarter relating to the impact of newly notified labour codes. The EBITDA margin for the quarter ended (QE) 31 December 2025 is 35%, compared to 9.0% for the quarter ended (QE) 31 December 2024. The order backlog stood at Rs 1,670.6 crore as of 31 December 2025, down 38.3% compared with Rs 2,706.0 crore as of 31 December 2024 for continuing operations, primarily due to the termination of two FGD EP contracts—Jaypee Bina and Nigrie—aggregating Rs 775 crore. Puneet Bhatla, MD, GE Power India, said, “Execution discipline and operational excellence have continued to drive meaningful margin expansion across our core services and upgrade businesses. With a focused portfolio, improving margins, and a healthy order book, we are well positioned for building momentum.” GE Power India is one of the leading players in the Indian power generation equipment market. Hydro and gas businesses are also housed in the company in addition to steam power. The company offers a comprehensive portfolio of power generation solutions with a focus on emissions control and a services portfolio providing sustainable, affordable, and reliable electricity.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GEPower_62970729410_20944.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>