<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:42:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund Change in Minimum SIP Amount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-mutual-fund-change-in-minimum-sip-amount/1669024</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669024</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund has announced that the minimum application amount for the Systematic Investment Plan (“SIP”) under Axis Silver Fund of Fund (“the Scheme”) stands revised, as under: effective from February 09, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Existing Provisions Revised provisions effective from February 09, 2026 Axis Silver Fund of Fund Rs.

Axis Mutual Fund has announced that the minimum application amount for the Systematic Investment Plan (“SIP”) under Axis Silver Fund of Fund (“the Scheme”) stands revised, as under: effective from February 09, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Existing Provisions Revised provisions effective from February 09, 2026 Axis Silver Fund of Fund Rs. 1,000 and 6 in multiples of installments Re. 1/- 6 installments Rs. 100 and in 6 multiples of installments Re. 1/- thereafter. 6 installments

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Silver cools below $108 after explosive 50% January rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/silver-cools-below-108-after-explosive-50-january-rally/1669018</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669018</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Silver futures eased below the $108 per ounce level, declining over 4% as month-end and pre-weekend profit-taking emerged in the aftermath of January’s blistering 50% rally.

Silver futures eased below the $108 per ounce level, declining over 4% as month-end and pre-weekend profit-taking emerged in the aftermath of January’s blistering 50% rally. The pullback reflects tactical position trimming following an overheated advance, rather than a breakdown in the underlying narrative. Structural tailwinds — including persistent geopolitical uncertainty, expectations of lower global interest rates, constrained supply dynamics, and surging industrial consumption — continue to anchor silver’s medium-term outlook. In the domestic market, MCX benchmark silver futures plunged by more than ₹20,000 to trade near ₹3,80,649 per kg, underscoring heightened volatility after an exceptional run-up.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silver-trophy-1310083_silver.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon Life gains as Q3 PAT jumps 37% YoY to Rs 404 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-life-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-37-yoy-to-rs-404-crore/1669021</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669021</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income jumped 29.38% to Rs 780.55 crore in the third quarter of FY26, as against Rs 603.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Total income jumped 29.38% to Rs 780.55 crore in the third quarter of FY26, as against Rs 603.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) rose 36.01% to Rs 532.77 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 391.71 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter the previous year. Total expenses added 17.10% to Rs 247.78 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 211.59 crore in Q3 FY25. As on 31 December 2025, NAM India’s assets under management stood at Rs 8.16 trillion (US$ 90.7 billion). For the quarter ended December 31, 2025, NIMF’s average assets under management stood at Rs 7.01 trillion (US$ 78.0 billion) up 23% YoY. NIMF has one of the largest retail assets in the Industry, at Rs 2.01 trillion (US$ 22.3 billion). Retail assets contributed 28% to NIMF’s AUM vs Industry average of 27%. In Q3 FY26, high networth individual (HNI) AUM at Rs 2.27 trillion (US$ 25.2 billion), up 34% YoY & market share up 109 bps YoY. Sustained market share gain for 16 successive quarters. In Q3 FY26, Corporate AUM stood at Rs 2.84 trillion (US$ 31.6 billion), up 23% YoY, with a market share gain of 6 bps YoY. NIMF’s AUM from ‘Beyond the Top 30 cities’ (B-30) reached Rs 1.41 trillion (US$ 15.7 billion), growing 20% YoY and representing 19.9% of NIMF’s total AUM, compared with 18.4% for the industry. Quarterly systematic flows at NIMF rose 11% YoY to Rs 109.8 billion (US$ 1.2 billion), resulting in an annualized systematic book of Rs 451 billion (US$ 5.0 billion). NIMF continues to be one of the largest ETF players, with AUM of Rs 2.09 trillion (US$ 23.3 billion) and a market share of 20.31%. Nippon India AIF offers Category II and III Alternative Investment Funds, with a total commitment of Rs 89.2 billion (US$ 1.0 billion) across various schemes, marking a 28% YoY increase. Digital purchase transactions rose to 4.32 million in Q3 FY26, up from 4.08 million in Q3 FY25. Digital channel contributed 77% to new purchase transactions in Q3 FY26. Sundeep Sikka, ED & CEO, NAM India, said “We continue to improve our market share with the highest increase in the Industry in 9M FY26. Also, our Equity Net Sales and SIP market share, both remain well above Equity AUM market share. Industry SIP flows touched another all-time high in December-2025. We remain humbled to have the trust of 22.7 mn unique investors i.e. over 1 in every 3 mutual fund investors – highest in the Industry.” Nippon Life India Asset Mgt. is engaged in managing mutual funds including exchange traded funds (ETFs); managed accounts, including portfolio management services, alternative investment funds and pension funds; and offshore funds and advisory mandates.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RelianceNipponLifeAssetManagementLtd_43034021988_12622.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Blue Star records over 39% YoY fall in Q3 PAT; order book stands at Rs 6,898.74 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/blue-star-records-over-39-yoy-fall-in-q3-pat-order-book-stands-at-rs-689874-crore/1669023</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669023</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s revenue from operations increased by 4.2% to Rs 2,925.31 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as compared to Rs 2807.36 crore during the same period in the previous year.

The company’s revenue from operations increased by 4.2% to Rs 2,925.31 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as compared to Rs 2807.36 crore during the same period in the previous year. Revenue of segment 1, comprising of Electro-Mechanical Projects, Commercial Air Conditioning Systems, Service and International Business, grew by 8.6% to Rs 1,696.21 crore in Q3 FY26, as compared to Rs 1,562.41 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue for the Unitary Products Segment, comprising Room Air Conditioners and Commercial Refrigeration, was Rs 1,154.22 crore in Q3 FY26, as compared to Rs 1,164.36 crores in Q3 FY25. The Professional Electronics and Industrial Systems segment revenue declined by 7.1% to Rs 74.88 crore in Q3 FY26, as compared to Rs 80.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating profit for Q3 FY26 increased by 5.4% to Rs 220.72 crore as compared to Rs 209.38 crore in Q3FY25. Operating profit margin remained flat at 7.5%. Profit before tax was marginally lower at Rs 164.66 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared to Rs 167.20 crore in Q3 FY25. Carried-forward order book as of 31 December 2025, stood at Rs 6,898.74 crore, as compared to Rs 6,810 crore as of 31 December 2024. Net Borrowings were at Rs 352 crore as on 31 December 2025. Vir S. Advani, chairman & managing director, Blue Star, said: "The first three quarters of the current fiscal year were challenging, but the signs of market revival are encouraging. The company expects Q4 FY26 to be a strong quarter for Room ACs, Commercial Air Conditioning and Commercial Refrigeration businesses. In anticipation of robust growth in FY27, the Company is continuing to expand distribution and invest in R&D, manufacturing, digitalisation and the brand, while introducing cost optimisation and productivity improvement measures. We are hopeful that Q4 FY26 will be an encouraging quarter.” Blue Star is an Indian multinational home appliances company. It specializes in air conditioning, commercial refrigeration, and MEP (mechanical, electrical, plumbing, and firefighting). The scrip advanced 3.04% to currently trade at Rs 1783.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BlueStar_62229394829_82.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vardhman Textiles Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vardhman-textiles-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1669009</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669009</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Idea Ltd, Raymond Lifestyle Ltd, MTAR Technologies Ltd and 63 Moons Technologies Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 30 January 2026.

Vodafone Idea Ltd, Raymond Lifestyle Ltd, MTAR Technologies Ltd and 63 Moons Technologies Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 30 January 2026. Vardhman Textiles Ltd soared 12.93% to Rs 466.9 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 82155 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7187 shares in the past one month. Vodafone Idea Ltd surged 11.64% to Rs 11.22. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1160.09 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 752.51 lakh shares in the past one month. Raymond Lifestyle Ltd spiked 11.13% to Rs 1025.3. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.42 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5497 shares in the past one month. MTAR Technologies Ltd jumped 9.41% to Rs 2998.8. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 39862 shares in the past one month. 63 Moons Technologies Ltd gained 9.30% to Rs 672.55. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 16263 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7754 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VardhmanTextile_60310538344_932.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India set to cut weight of food and beverages in consumer price index to 36.75% in new series]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-set-to-cut-weight-of-food-and-beverages-in-consumer-price-index-to-3675-in-new-series/1669007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669007</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India is set to cut the weight of food and beverages in its consumer price index (CPI) to 36.75% in a new inflation series.

India is set to cut the weight of food and beverages in its consumer price index (CPI) to 36.75% in a new inflation series. This is much below the 45.86% weight in the current series with 2012 as the base year. The weight of food, without beverages, in the new series will be 34.77%. The statistics ministry has stated that the revamped data series will use 2024 as the base year, while 2025 will be used as ‌an overlapping year ‍between the old and new series so that past data can ‍be converted into the new base statistically. It also noted that the number of major ‌spending groups will be expanded to 12 from six, aligning India's inflation framework with international standards.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/fennel-vegetables-fennel-bulb-food-159357_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Shayona Engineering rings the listing bell softly]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-shayona-engineering-rings-the-listing-bell-softly/1669006</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669006</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 144, matching the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 144, matching the issue price. The stock touched a high of Rs 144 and a low of Rs 137.40, with around 7.02 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Shayona Engineering's IPO was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 January 2026 and it closed on 27 January 2025. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 140 to Rs 144 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 10,32,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for purchase of plant and machinery for the existing line of business, repayment of secured loan availed by company from financial institution, funding of the working capital requirements of company and for general corporate purpose. Shayona Engineering is engaged in the business of precision castings, machining, dies and moulds, industrial automation, heavy fabrication, casting, forging, reverse engineering, and turnkey project machinery. It offers customized solutions for precision castings in special grades, with weights ranging from a few grams to 3 metric tons in a single piece. The company operates from three locations in Vadodara, Gujarat, utilizing sophisticated, cutting-edge technology-based equipment to deliver accurate engineering solutions, along with prompt after-sales services, all under one roof. As of 15 January 2026, the company had 22 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 19.14 crore and net profit of Rs 2.45 crore for the period ended 30 November 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShayonaEngineeringLtd_25286329_94289.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1669005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669005</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced the appointment of Mr.

Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced the appointment of Mr. C. N. Ram as an Independent Director on the Board of Directors of Bandhan AMC Limited (“the AMC”) with effect from January 31, 2026. Name: Mr. C.N. Ram Age: 68 years Designation: Independent Director Qualification: PGDM & B. Tech (Electrical Engineering)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slides 507 pts; consumer durables shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slides-507-pts-consumer-durables-shares-decline/1669003</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669003</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Headline equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in mid-morning trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on February 1.

Headline equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in mid-morning trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on February 1. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments for fresh direction. Investor focus is also on quarterly results due later today from key companies such as Bajaj Auto, NTPC, Power Grid Corporation of India, Nestlé India, and Ambuja Cements. Reflecting the subdued sentiment, the Nifty slipped below the 25,300 level during morning trade. IT shares extended losses for the second consecutive trading session. At 11:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 506.85 points or 0.61% to 82,059.52. The Nifty 50 index fell 161.40 points or 0.65% to 25,257.50. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index is flat and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.20%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,299 shares rose and 1,562 shares fell. A total of 189 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 4.74% to 14.01. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 1.51% to 37,849.65. The index fell 2.26% in two consecutive trading sessions. Infosys (down 2.32%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 1.63%), MphasiS (down 1.50%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.43%), HCL Technologies (down 1.43%), Wipro (down 1.33%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.90%), LTIMindtree (down 0.83%), Persistent Systems (down 0.62%) and Coforge (down 0.61%), declined. Stocks in Spotlight: ITC rose 0.46%. The company reported 5.6% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 4934.80 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5016.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose by 6.2% year-on-year to Rs 17857.56 crore during the period under review. One 97 Communications slipped 2.41%. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 225 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 208 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations during the period under review increased by 20.02% YoY to Rs 2,194 crore Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump said that he will announce his choice for the next Federal Reserve chair on Friday. Speaking at the premiere of Melania, a film about first lady Melania Trump, he said the five-month search to replace current chair Jerome Powell was nearing its conclusion. The process for selecting Powell’s replacement began in September with an 11-candidate field that included past and current Fed officials, economists, and Wall Street investment professionals. Trump also endorsed a Senate deal to fund the vast majority of the federal government through the remainder of the fiscal year, easing near-term political uncertainty for investors. Senators clinched a deal with just over a day until a partial government shutdown. They agreed to remove funding for the Department of Homeland Security from the package and pass the other five bills, while DHS will be funded by a stopgap. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index slipped 0.13% to close at 6,969.01, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 0.72% to end at 23,685.12. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.11%, or 55.96 points, and settled at 49,071.56.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MTAR Tech jumps on strong earnings, robust order inflows in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mtar-tech-jumps-on-strong-earnings-robust-order-inflows-in-q3-fy26/1669002</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669002</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit jumped 117.3% YoY to Rs 34.7 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 16.0 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit jumped 117.3% YoY to Rs 34.7 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 16.0 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, profit after tax surged 717.2% from Rs 4.2 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations rose 59.3% YoY to Rs 278.0 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 174.5 crore a year ago. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue more than doubled, rising 105.0% QoQ from Rs 135.6 crore in Q2 FY26. Gross profit increased 47.7% YoY to Rs 128.1 crore, while gross margin stood at 46.1%, compared with 49.7% in Q3 FY25 and 51.2% in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 46.1 crore in Q3 FY26, more than doubling from Rs 21.4 crore in the year-ago quarter and rising sharply from Rs 5.7 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA surged 92.5% YoY to Rs 64.0 crore, compared with Rs 33.3 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, EBITDA jumped 276.6% QoQ from Rs 17.0 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA margin improved to 23.0%, from 19.1% a year ago and 12.5% in the previous quarter. On the cost front, cost of materials consumed surged 70.7% YoY to Rs 163.9 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 96.0 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses increased 28.4% YoY to Rs 40.2 crore, compared with Rs 31.3 crore a year ago. Finance costs climbed 22.2% YoY to Rs 7.7 crore, up from Rs 6.3 crore in the year-ago quarter. The company also reported exceptional items of Rs 3.8 crore during the quarter, compared with nil in Q3 FY25, on account of the statutory impact of the new labour codes. On the order book front, MTAR Technologies received fresh orders worth Rs 1,368.8 crore during the quarter, spanning clean energy segments such as civil nuclear power, fuel cells and hydel, along with aerospace and defence and other industrial products. The company’s diversified order book stood at Rs 2,394.9 crore as of 31 December 2025, providing strong revenue visibility. Parvat Srinivas Reddy, managing director & promoter, MTAR Technologies, said, "We recorded our highest-ever quarterly revenue in Q3, driven by strong operational performance. Our robust order book reflects strong industry tailwinds and structural growth in the Clean Energy – Fuel Cells, Civil Nuclear Power and Aerospace sectors. Margins are expected to improve sequentially over the coming quarters, supported by higher operating leverage and a favourable shift in the product mix towards volume-based production." MTAR Technologies is a leading manufacturer engaged in manufacturing and development of mission critical precision engineered systems catering to clean energy – civil nuclear power, fuel cells, hydel & others, aerospace and defence sectors. It has nine strategically based manufacturing units including an export-oriented unit each based in Hyderabad, Telangana.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MTARTechnologies_27377516.911779_34242.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Finserv Mutual Fund Change in Minimum Application Amount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-finserv-mutual-fund-change-in-minimum-application-amount/1669001</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669001</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bajaj Finserv Mutual Fund has announced the revision in the minimum application amount for fresh and additional purchase (lumpsum) in Bajaj Finserv Nifty 50 Index Fund and Bajaj Finserv Nifty Next 50 Index Fund with effect from February 02, 2026 (“Effective Date”), as follows: Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Existing Minimum Amount Revised Minimum Amount Minimum application amount for purchase /switch in During ongoing offer: Fresh Purchase (lumpsum): Rs.

Bajaj Finserv Mutual Fund has announced the revision in the minimum application amount for fresh and additional purchase (lumpsum) in Bajaj Finserv Nifty 50 Index Fund and Bajaj Finserv Nifty Next 50 Index Fund with effect from February 02, 2026 (“Effective Date”), as follows: Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Existing Minimum Amount Revised Minimum Amount Minimum application amount for purchase /switch in During ongoing offer: Fresh Purchase (lumpsum): Rs. 500/- and in multiples of Re. 1/- thereafter Minimum amount for switch-in: Rs. 500 and in multiples of Re. 1. During ongoing offer: Fresh Purchase (lumpsum): Rs. 5,000/- and in multiples of Re. 1/- thereafter Minimum amount for switch-in: Rs. 5,000 and in multiples of Re. 1. Minimum Additional Purchase Amount On Ongoing basis Rs. 100/- and in multiples of Re. 1/- thereafter. During ongoing offer: Fresh Purchase (lumpsum): Rs. 5,000/- and in multiples of Re. 1/- thereafter On Ongoing basis Rs. 1,000/- and in multiples of Re. 1/- thereafter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TD Power Systems gains as Q3 PAT climbs 25% YoY to Rs 56 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/td-power-systems-gains-as-q3-pat-climbs-25-yoy-to-rs-56-cr/1669000</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669000</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 78.20 crore in Q3 FY26, up 31.3% from the Rs 59.55 crore reported in the same period a year ago.

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 78.20 crore in Q3 FY26, up 31.3% from the Rs 59.55 crore reported in the same period a year ago. EBITDA increased by 33% YoY to Rs 82.60 crore during the period under review. The EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 stood at 18.6%, compared to 17.6% in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 25.2% to Rs 368.62 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 294.42 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 304.27 crore (up 14.99% YoY), finance cost was at Rs 0.52 crore (up 44.44% YoY), and employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 43.24 crore (up 33.54% YoY) during the period under review. The company reiterated its FY26 topline guidance of Rs 1,800 crore and revised FY27 revenue guidance to Rs 2,200 crore. Export orders remain the primary growth driver, supported by a diversified product portfolio and a strong base of around 45 global OEMs. Management expects export-led momentum to continue through FY27–FY28, with production and sales ramp-up from the third plant beginning in Q4 FY26 onwards. TD Power Systems (TDPS) is engaged in manufacturing AC generators and electric motors for various applications, which are specifically designed and tailor-made to suit the needs of the customers based on their requirements and specifications.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TDPowerSys_46187686965_34673.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ASSOCHAM notes that Economic Survey 2025-26 provides a robust analytical backdrop for forthcoming Union Budget ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/assocham-notes-that-economic-survey-2025-26-provides-a-robust-analytical-backdrop-for-forthcoming-union-budget/1668995</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668995</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Associated Chambers of Commerce & Industry of India (ASSOCHAM) has noted that the Economic Survey 2025-26 provides a robust analytical backdrop for the forthcoming Union Budget 2026-27 and expressed hope that the Budget will further institutionalise these reform priorities to support investment, competitiveness and job creation.

Associated Chambers of Commerce & Industry of India (ASSOCHAM) has noted that the Economic Survey 2025-26 provides a robust analytical backdrop for the forthcoming Union Budget 2026-27 and expressed hope that the Budget will further institutionalise these reform priorities to support investment, competitiveness and job creation. Besides, recent agreements with the European Union, UK and EFTA are expected to strengthen India’s merchandise and services exports, while supporting higher investment flows and deeper integration with global markets. Some of the welcome observations of the Economic Survey include India’s real GDP growth in FY25 which is expected to be around 7.4 per cent, moderation of the fiscal deficit to 4.8 per cent of GDP from its pandemic-era highs of 9.2 per cent and steady job creation along with an expanding workforce. ASSOCHAM believes that the Survey rightly links the translation of growth into quality employment with productivity gains, enterprise scaling and a reduction in operational frictions, particularly for MSMEs and manufacturing-led activities. The Chamber noted the Survey’s emphasis on strengthening manufacturing competitiveness, deepening integration into global value chains and reducing domestic cost disadvantages as essential for improving export resilience and supporting external sector stability. The Survey highlights the central role of public capital expenditure in sustaining growth momentum, alongside a revival in private investment. Gross fixed capital formation remained robust at 30 per cent of GDP, supported by infrastructure expansion and improved logistics. It also revises India’s potential growth rate upward in the range of 6.8 per cent to 7.2 per cent for FY27, reflecting gains from sustained public investment and structural reforms undertaken in recent years.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/growth-951606__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Aurobindo Pharma Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-aurobindo-pharma-ltd-counter/1668983</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668983</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ramkrishna Forgings Ltd, Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts Ltd, Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd, Craftsman Automation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 30 January 2026.

Ramkrishna Forgings Ltd, Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts Ltd, Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd, Craftsman Automation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 30 January 2026. Aurobindo Pharma Ltd clocked volume of 5.81 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 53.98 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10754 shares. The stock gained 2.13% to Rs.1,175.00. Volumes stood at 13339 shares in the last session. Ramkrishna Forgings Ltd notched up volume of 4.2 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 28.34 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 14831 shares. The stock rose 2.07% to Rs.518.10. Volumes stood at 6978 shares in the last session. Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts Ltd witnessed volume of 14.11 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 27.8 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 50757 shares. The stock increased 1.29% to Rs.406.75. Volumes stood at 3.08 lakh shares in the last session. Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd registered volume of 2.13 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.06 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 23486 shares. The stock rose 1.79% to Rs.1,774.30. Volumes stood at 9677 shares in the last session. Craftsman Automation Ltd registered volume of 21129 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.13 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2598 shares. The stock rose 0.55% to Rs.7,348.45. Volumes stood at 2893 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurobindoPharma_66877283489_4666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s space economy grows to an estimated $8.4 billion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-space-economy-grows-to-an-estimated-84-billion/1668970</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668970</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s space economy has grown to an estimated $8.4 billion, with 399 start-ups now operating across launch vehicles, satellites, propulsion systems and space-grade electronics, Union Minister of State (Independent Charge) for Science and Technology and Space, Dr.

India’s space economy has grown to an estimated $8.4 billion, with 399 start-ups now operating across launch vehicles, satellites, propulsion systems and space-grade electronics, Union Minister of State (Independent Charge) for Science and Technology and Space, Dr. Jitendra Singh has noted. Singh told parliament that the expansion followed key policy decisions taken after 2019 to open the space sector to private participation. A major institutional change, he said, was the establishment of the Indian National Space Promotion and Authorisation Centre (IN-SPACe), which functions as a single-window interface between private industry and government agencies, including the Indian Space Research Organisation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[One 97 Communications reports turnaround Q3 numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/one-97-communications-reports-turnaround-q3-numbers/1668969</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668969</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations during the period under review increased by 20.02% YoY to Rs 2,194 crore, driven by industry-leading customer monetization.

Revenue from operations during the period under review increased by 20.02% YoY to Rs 2,194 crore, driven by industry-leading customer monetization. The growth was led by higher payments GMV, increased merchant subscriptions, and stronger revenue from the distribution of financial services. In Q3 FY26, contribution profit stood at Rs 1,249 crore, up 30% year-on-year. Contribution margin improved to 57%, driven by higher payment processing margins and an increased share of distribution of financial services revenue. EBITDA in Q3 FY26 was Rs 156 crore, with an EBITDA margin of 7%, marking a Rs 379 crore year-on-year improvement, despite higher promotional expenses for consumer growth and the full impact of the new labour code. Paytm UPI continued to gain market share for the third consecutive quarter. Its consumer UPI GMV grew 35% in the last nine months versus industry GMV growth of 16%, the company said. Paytm said there was an ‘insignificant’ impact on revenue from industry stoppage of rent payments through credit card (PA PG guidelines, September 2025) and the Real Money Gaming (RMG) Act, August 2025, as the company had taken proactive compliance measures over the past few years. Payments services revenue (including other operating revenue) grew 21% YoY to Rs 1,284 crore. Net payment revenue increased by 25% YoY to Rs 613 crore, due to improved payment processing margin and an increase in merchant subscriptions, which grew by 27 lakh YoY to reach 1.44 crore. Payments GMV grew 24% YoY to Rs 6.2 lakh crore, the company said. In Q3 FY 2026, distribution of financial services revenue grew 34% YoY to Rs 672 crore, driven by continued growth in distribution of merchant loans and wealth products. This is despite lower volumes under the Default Loss Guarantee (DLG) program, which leads to lower revenue and lower other direct costs, the company said. Cash balance stood at Rs 12,882 crore as of the quarter ending December 2025. During the quarter, the offline merchant business was transferred to Payments Services, a wholly owned subsidiary of the company, in line with regulatory guidelines. Payments Services received final approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to operate as an Online Payment Aggregator. Further, the RBI authorised PPSL to operate as a Payment Aggregator for offline and cross-border payments, it said. The company said, Vijay Shekhar Sharma, Chairman, MD & CEO, has been additionally appointed as managing director (MD) (designated MD & CEO) of PPSL for 5 years, with effect from 29 January 2026. Paytm is India's leading mobile payments and financial services distribution company. Shares of One 97 Communications slipped 2.03% to Rs 1,145 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/One97-Communications-Ltd_42949010_40147.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JM Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jm-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1668993</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668993</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[JM Mutual Fund has announced the designation of Ms.

JM Mutual Fund has announced the designation of Ms. Mugdha Ghag as Key Personnel of JM Financial Asset Management Limited (“the AMC”) with effect from January 29, 2026. The relevant details shall be incorporated in the SAI under “Information on Key Personnel”. Details of Ms. Mugdha Ghag Age: 14 years Designation: Head –Marketing & Branding Qualification: Advanced Program for Marketing Professionals from IIM Calcutta, Post Graduate Diploma in Business Economics from Wigan & Leigh College and B.Sc. Biotechnology from K C College

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,300 level; metal shares under pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25300-level-metal-shares-under-pressure/1668931</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668931</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Frontline equity benchmarks trimmed some losses and traded with modest declines in morning trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on February 1.

Frontline equity benchmarks trimmed some losses and traded with modest declines in morning trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on February 1. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments for fresh direction. Investor focus is also on quarterly results due later today from key companies such as Bajaj Auto, NTPC, Power Grid Corporation of India, Nestlé India, and Ambuja Cements. Reflecting the subdued sentiment, the Nifty slipped below the 25,300 level during morning trade. Metal shares dropped after advancing in the past three consecutive trading sessions. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 380.57 points or 0.45% to 82,185.80. The Nifty 50 index fell 126 points or 0.50% to 25,292.90. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index is flat and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.20%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,012 shares rose and 1,667 shares fell. A total of 189 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Bajaj Auto (down 0.61%), NTPC (down 0.53%), Power Grid Corporation of India (down 0.06%), Nestle India (up 1.43%), Bank of Baroda (up 0.03%), Meesho (up 2.05%), Ajanta Pharma (up 2.53%), Ambuja Cements (down 0.76%), Ashoka Buildcon (up 1.07%), Aster DM Healthcare (up 0.68%), Antony Waste Handling Cell (up 6.08%), Brigade Enterprises (up 1.10%), Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company (up 0.65%), Exide Industries (up 0.70%), Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (down 0.61%), Jindal Steel (down 2.85%), KEC International (up 2.69%), Dr Lal PathLabs (up 0.32%), LIC Housing Finance (up 0.91%), National Aluminium Company (down 7.69%), New India Assurance Company (up 1.33%), Steel Authority of India (down 4.26%) and Welspun Corp (up 1.61%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index dropped 4.18% to 11,955.90. The index rallied 8.71% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Stocks in Spotlight: Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) rose 0.35%. The company said that it has secured a domestic contract from Pawan Hans for the supply of 10 Dhruv NG helicopters, along with associated spares and accessories. Colgate-Palmolive (India) shed 0.90%. The company reported a marginal 0.3% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 323.9 crore, while revenue from operations rose 1.4% to Rs 1,472.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dabur India rose 1.52% after the company reported a 7.3% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 553.61 crore on a 6.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3,558.65 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITC gains after recording PAT of Rs 4935 crore in Q3; board OKs dividend of Rs 6.50/share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itc-gains-after-recording-pat-of-rs-4935-crore-in-q3-board-oks-dividend-of-rs-650share/1668952</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668952</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales rose by 6.2% year-on-year to Rs 17857.56 crore during the period under review.

Net sales rose by 6.2% year-on-year to Rs 17857.56 crore during the period under review. The company’s FMCG – Others business has reported 11.1% YoY growth in revenue to Rs 6,019.69 crore in Q3 FY26. The revenue from Cigarettes rose by 8% YoY to Rs 8,790.76 crore in the third quarter. The Agri Business segment revenue increased by 9.7% YoY to Rs 3,560.27 crore. Paperboards, Paper and Packaging segmental revenue for Q3 FY25 was Rs 2202.41 crore, up 3.1% YoY. PBIDT declined by 7.7% to Rs 7,069.24 crore in Q3 FY25 from Rs 7,659.85 crore in Q3 FY24. Profit before tax in Q3 FY25 stood at Rs 6685.05 crore, down by 8.3% from Rs 7290.46 crore in Q3 FY24. Tax outgo for the period under review was Rs 941.16 crore, down 37.3% YoY. On a consolidated basis, the company’s net profit declined 0.1% to Rs 4931.19 crore despite a 7.2% increase in net sales to Rs 19,918.24 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The company’s board recommends interim dividend of Rs 6.50 per share for the financial year ending 31 March 2026. ITC is a diversified conglomerate with businesses spanning fast-moving consumer goods, hotels, paperboards and packaging, agribusiness and information technology.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITC_29088800077_301.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1668927</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668927</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced the appointment of Mr.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced the appointment of Mr. Amit Ganatra as Senior Member – Investment (Equity) of HDFC Asset Management Company Limited (“HDFC AMC”) with effect from January 28, 2026. He has been designated as a Key Personnel of HDFC AMC. Details of Mr. Amit Ganatra Age: 45 years Designation: Senior Fund Manager – Equities Qualification: • Chartered Accountant (ICAI), • CFA (CFA Institute, USA) • M.Com

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>