<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:29:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold and silver pause near $5,108 and $117.7 after historic rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-and-silver-pause-near-5108-and-1177-after-historic-rally/1667693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667693</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices traded marginally lower in early Tuesday electronic trade after surging to an all-time high above $5,107.9 in the previous session, as the market paused following an intense safe-haven rally driven by escalating geopolitical tensions.

Gold prices traded marginally lower in early Tuesday electronic trade after surging to an all-time high above $5,107.9 in the previous session, as the market paused following an intense safe-haven rally driven by escalating geopolitical tensions. Silver futures witnessed a sharper pullback, sliding nearly 4% after scaling fresh lifetime highs of $117.7 per ounce, reflecting profit-taking after a rapid advance fueled by trade uncertainties, investor flight from sovereign bonds and currencies, and heightened demand for defensive assets. Sentiment was further influenced by renewed trade frictions after US President Donald Trump threatened higher tariffs on autos, lumber, and pharmaceutical imports from South Korea, while lifting duties on other goods to 25% amid stalled negotiations. Investor focus has now shifted to the US Federal Reserve’s two-day policy meeting beginning today, where interest rates are expected to remain unchanged but Chair Jerome Powell’s guidance will be closely scrutinized amid mounting pressure from the White House to ease monetary policy. In domestic markets, MCX March silver futures surged nearly 10% to a record Rs 364,821 per kg, while MCX February gold futures climbed almost 2% to a fresh all-time high of Rs 159,820 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Asian Paints slides as Q3 PAT decline 5% YoY to Rs 1,060 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/asian-paints-slides-as-q3-pat-decline-5-yoy-to-rs-1060-cr/1667689</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667689</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26.

However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax increased by 8.5% to Rs 1,646.7 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,518.2 Crore in Q3 FY25. PBDIT (Profit before depreciation, interest, tax, other income, and exceptional items) (before share in profit of associates) increased 8.8% to Rs 1,781.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,636.7 crore in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, PBDIT margin as % to Net Sales increased to 20.1%, up from 19.2% posted in the same quarter last year. The Decorative Business in India delivered strong volume growth of 7.9% despite a shorter festive period and an extended monsoon, while value growth stood at 2.8%. Although demand remained subdued, a series of internal initiatives helped drive resilient performance. Net sales from the International Business rose 6.3% year-on-year to Rs 869.6 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by strong performance in Sri Lanka, the UAE, and Ethiopia. Within the industrial business segment, revenue from APPPG increased 16.5% year-on-year to Rs 334.7 crore in Q3 FY26, while PPGAP sales rose 16.9% year-on-year to Rs 713.3 crore in Q3 FY26. Within the Home Décor segment, net sales from the Bath Fittings business declined 4.1% year-on-year to Rs 84 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 87.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Kitchen business net sales increased 2.6% year-on-year to Rs 105.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 102.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Meanwhile, net sales at White Teak rose 12.4% year-on-year to Rs 29.2 crore, while Weatherseal posted a sharp 58.6% year-on-year increase to Rs 18.7 crore in Q3 FY26. Amit Syngle, managing director & CEO of Asian Paints, said, “We had a third consecutive quarter of good volume growth with our India Decorative Business delivering a robust 7.9% volume growth in the quarter. The overall coatings business registered a 4.4% revenue growth for the quarter with Decorative business revenue growth of 2.8%. This performance for the quarter reflects the sustained momentum delivered through persistent actions across our identified growth initiatives even as the broader market faced persistent competitive intensity and subdued demand conditions. We have intensified our brand building efforts, launched a robust wave of retailing initiatives and introduced a wide range of innovative product and service propositions. Our disciplined cost management, backward integration efforts and enhanced operational efficiencies enabled us to fuel these brand investments while simultaneously improving our operating margins. Our industrial coatings segment registered good double-digit growth, boosting our overall coatings performance. In the same league, our international business achieved a 6.3% revenue increase led by steady performance in key markets of UAE, Sri Lanka and Ethiopia. As the external environment remains dynamic, we continue to drive differentiated strategies, harness our structural strengths, and embrace technology to sustain momentum, respond with agility, creating long term value for all stakeholders.” Asian Paints, established in 1942, is the largest listed company in India's decorative paints segment. It ranked among the top eight decorative coatings companies in the world. It is engaged in the business of manufacturing, selling, and distributing paints, coatings, and products related to home décor and bath fittings and providing related services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AsianPaints_3886867460_34.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex Nifty trade with minor cuts; auto shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-minor-cuts-auto-shares-decline/1667688</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667688</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded near flat line in mid-afternoon trade.

The key equity barometers traded near flat line in mid-afternoon trade. The movement came after India and the European Union clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA) following 18 years of stalled negotiations. The Nifty traded below the 25,100 level. Auto shares declined for three consecutive trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 118.09 points or 0.14% to 81,419.61. The Nifty 50 index fell 3.90 points or 0.02% to 25,043.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.41% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.54%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,556 shares rose and 2,673 shares fell. A total of 188 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.29% to 14.19. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union have signed the “mother of all deals”, PM Modi said on Tuesday. Prime Minister Narendra Modi lauded the signing of the free trade agreement between India and the European Union and said that the deal represented “25 per cent of the global GDP and 1/3rd of global trade”. The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Automobile tariffs will fall sharply, with duties on cars gradually reduced from 110% to as low as 10%, and car parts tariffs fully eliminated within five to ten years. Agri-food tariffs will drop significantly, including wine tariffs cut from 150% to 75% initially and as low as 20% later, and olive oil tariffs reduced from 45% to zero over five years. The pact includes strong sustainability and climate commitments, alongside plans for an EU–India climate cooperation platform and up to €500 million in EU support for India’s green transition. On tariffs overall, Sefcovic said the aim is 97–99% partial or full tariff liberalisation, which could generate savings of around €4 billion a year and help double bilateral trade within five years. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index fell 2.05% to 26,255.65. The index dropped 3.15% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Mahindra & Mahindra (down 4.32%), Tube Investments of India (down 2%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 1.87%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 1.85%), Exide Industries (down 1.65%), Ashok Leyland (down 1.41%), Uno Minda (down 1.29%), Hero MotoCorp (down 1.12%), Bosch (down 0.47%) and TVS Motor Company (down 0.34%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was advanced 0.47% to 6.695 as compared with the previous close of 6.664. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6875 compared with its close of 91.9050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement advanced 1.71% to Rs 1,58,710. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.22% to 97.25. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.26% to 4.240. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 34 cents or 0.52% to $65.25 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Marine Electricals (India) surged 6.38% after the company announced that it has received orders worth Rs 284.39 crore from multiple clients. The company has secured an order from Digital Edge DC (India) for the supply of power distribution systems for the BOM-2 Data Center Project. The order is to be executed over a period of 6–8 months. Marine Electricals has also received an order from Crescon Projects & Services for the supply of power distribution systems for the LBOM-12 Data Center Project, with deliveries expected to be completed within 1–2 months. In addition, the company bagged an order from SHM Shipcare for the supply of power distribution systems, which is to be executed over a period of 4–5 months. Kirloskar Pneumatic Company rallied 3.19% after the company was provisionally selected by the Government of India in the latest round of the Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for white goods. According to an official release dated January 23, the PLI scheme for white goods, covering air conditioners and LED lights, is expected to attract investments of Rs 11,198 crore from 85 companies over the scheme period. In the fourth round, five applicants were provisionally selected with a combined committed investment of Rs 863 crore, while eight other applications were referred to a committee of experts for further evalu

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IFB Industries Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ifb-industries-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1667687</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667687</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shiva Texyarn Ltd, Digicontent Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 January 2026.

Shiva Texyarn Ltd, Digicontent Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 January 2026. IFB Industries Ltd lost 16.54% to Rs 1128.5 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 43924 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1332 shares in the past one month. Shiva Texyarn Ltd crashed 12.98% to Rs 164.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1057 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 221 shares in the past one month. Digicontent Ltd tumbled 12.81% to Rs 27.03. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 13018 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1442 shares in the past one month. Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd fell 11.64% to Rs 48.11. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 184 shares in the past one month. Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd dropped 11.35% to Rs 109. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1925 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2043 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IFBInds_5044625029_281.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Aegis Vopak Terminals Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-aegis-vopak-terminals-ltd-counter/1667673</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667673</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBFC Finance Ltd, JSW Energy Ltd, Karur Vysya Bank Ltd, OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 27 January 2026.

SBFC Finance Ltd, JSW Energy Ltd, Karur Vysya Bank Ltd, OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 27 January 2026. Aegis Vopak Terminals Ltd clocked volume of 82.69 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.7 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5.27 lakh shares. The stock gained 9.72% to Rs.220.78. Volumes stood at 3.05 lakh shares in the last session. SBFC Finance Ltd registered volume of 298.64 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 13.72 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 21.77 lakh shares. The stock slipped 11.73% to Rs.89.91. Volumes stood at 7.85 lakh shares in the last session. JSW Energy Ltd registered volume of 189.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.73 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 14.89 lakh shares. The stock slipped 9.50% to Rs.432.25. Volumes stood at 17.59 lakh shares in the last session. Karur Vysya Bank Ltd registered volume of 402.17 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.67 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 34.47 lakh shares. The stock rose 11.30% to Rs.295.50. Volumes stood at 85.57 lakh shares in the last session. OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd clocked volume of 23.23 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.92 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.34 lakh shares. The stock lost 18.58% to Rs.1,166.30. Volumes stood at 7.28 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisVopakTerminalsLtd_23442647_74261.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,100 level; European markets advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25100-level-european-markets-advance/1667655</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667655</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in afternoon trade, buoyed by news that India and the European Union had clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA) after 18 years of stalled negotiations.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in afternoon trade, buoyed by news that India and the European Union had clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA) after 18 years of stalled negotiations. Investor focus remained on key quarterly earnings from Asian Paints, Vodafone Idea, and Motilal Oswal Financial Services, while traders also monitored movements in the rupee and global geopolitical developments. The Nifty traded above 25,100 level. Metal, oil & gas and FMCG shares advanced, while media, consumer durables and auto shares declined. At 13:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex added 122.25 points or 0.16% to 81,649.34. The Nifty 50 index rose 59.90 points or 0.22% to 25,103.25. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 1.56% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 2.19%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,677 shares rose and 2,484 shares fell. A total of 190 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.64% to 15.14. Gainers & Losers: Adani Enterprises (up 4.85%), Axis Bank (up 4.40%), Grasim Industries (up 3.19%), Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (up 3.13%) and JSW Steel (up 2.71%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Mahindra & Mahindra (down 4.04%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (down 3.15%), Eternal (down 2.65%), Max Healthcare Institute (down 2.06%) and Maruti Suzuki India (down 1.68%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Axis Bank jumped 4.27% after the bank reported a 2.94% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 6,489.57 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 6,303.77 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union have signed the “mother of all deals”, PM Modi said on Tuesday. Prime Minister Narendra Modi lauded the signing of the free trade agreement between India and the European Union and said that the deal represented “25 per cent of the global GDP and 1/3rd of global trade”. On tariffs overall, Sefcovic said the aim is 97–99% partial or full tariff liberalisation, which could generate savings of around €4 billion a year and help double bilateral trade within five years. The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Stocks in Spotlight: Indusind Bank slipped 1.04% after the bank reported 88.5% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 161.16 crore on 13.67% fall in total income to Rs 13,079.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shriram Finance lost 1.12% after the NBFC’s standalone net profit declined 29.36% to Rs 2,521.67 crore on a 13.88% increase in total income to Rs 12,191.58 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ultratech Cement advanced 2.66% after the company reported a 26.92% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,725.40 crore on 22.78% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 21,829.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) added 1.47% after the company reported a 62.29% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 7,545.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 4,649.20 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter. DCB Bank surged 7.82% after the bank reported 22% jump in net profit to Rs 185 crore on a 16% increase in total income to Rs 846 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Godrej Consumer Products tumbled 5.64% after the company's consolidated net profit remained flat at Rs 497.91 crore in Q3 FY26, even as net sales increased 8.8% year-on-year to Rs 4,079.47 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets traded higher on Tuesday, helped by a trade deal between the European Union and India, as investors await more quarterly earnings and a Federal Reserve rate decision. Asian shares advanced despite concerns regarding tariffs resurfaced post US President Donald Trump threatening to increase levies on South Korean goods. Trump said on Truth Social that South Korea's legislature has not approved Seoul’s trade deal with Washington, and that tariffs on the country will climb to 25%, from 15%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index advanced 0.50%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 0.64%. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.43%, supported by jumps of about 3%, 2% and 1% in Apple, Meta Platforms and Microsoft, respectively, ahead of their earnings reports later in the week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s energy sector offers investment opportunities worth 500 billion dollars: PM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-energy-sector-offers-investment-opportunities-worth-500-billion-dollars-pm/1667654</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667654</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Tuesday invited global investors to participate in India's growing energy sector, which offers a USD 500 billion investment opportunity, and stressed that the country will soon become the world's largest refining hub.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Tuesday invited global investors to participate in India's growing energy sector, which offers a USD 500 billion investment opportunity, and stressed that the country will soon become the world's largest refining hub. Addressing the India Energy Week 2026, he urged investors to invest in sectors like refining, LNG value chain infrastructure, city gas distribution, and oil & gas exploration. Modi highlighted that India has significantly opened up its exploration sector and referred to the deep-sea exploration initiative known as the Samudra Manthan Mission. He stated that by the end of this decade, India aims to raise investments in the oil and gas sector to 100 billion dollars, with a target of expanding the scope of exploration to one million square kilometers. The Prime Minister noted that more than 170 blocks have already been awarded, and the Andaman and Nicobar basin is emerging as the next hydrocarbon hope. He further remarked that India possesses a very large refining capacity and currently ranks second in the world in this regard. The Prime Minister said the nation is targeting USD 100 billion investments in the oil and gas sector by 2030, and the oil refining capacity will be expanded from 260 million tonnes per annum to 300 MTPA. The Prime Minister underlined that India’s energy sector lies at the center of the nation’s aspirations, offering investment opportunities worth 500 billion dollars.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/golden-sunset-in-crude-oil-refinery-with-pipeline-system-pi_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Motor Company Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-motor-company-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1667644</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667644</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TVS Motor Company Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

TVS Motor Company Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3533.5, down 0.46% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.2% on the day, quoting at 25098.05. The Sensex is at 81588.28, up 0.06%.TVS Motor Company Ltd has eased around 1.14% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which TVS Motor Company Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.1% in last one month and is currently quoting at 26804.55, down 1.28% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 5.71 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.89 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3525.4, down 0.26% on the day. TVS Motor Company Ltd jumped 51.28% in last one year as compared to a 9.33% rally in NIFTY and a 18.85% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 53.44 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSMotorCo_68147319859_8029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1667645</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667645</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Hero MotoCorp Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5350.5, down 0.62% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.2% on the day, quoting at 25098.05. The Sensex is at 81588.28, up 0.06%.Hero MotoCorp Ltd has eased around 3.87% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Hero MotoCorp Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.1% in last one month and is currently quoting at 26804.55, down 1.28% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.62 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.37 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5348, down 0.62% on the day. Hero MotoCorp Ltd jumped 32.89% in last one year as compared to a 9.33% rally in NIFTY and a 18.85% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 22.46 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki India Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1667646</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667646</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 15212, down 1.66% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.2% on the day, quoting at 25098.05. The Sensex is at 81588.28, up 0.06%.Maruti Suzuki India Ltd has lost around 8.04% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 4.1% in last one month and is currently quoting at 26804.55, down 1.28% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.51 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.63 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 15225, down 1.59% on the day. Maruti Suzuki India Ltd jumped 25.47% in last one year as compared to a 9.33% rally in NIFTY and a 18.85% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 34.15 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Marine Electricals rises after bagging Rs 284-cr orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/marine-electricals-rises-after-bagging-rs-284-cr-orders/1667653</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667653</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has secured an order from Digital Edge DC (India) for the supply of power distribution systems for the BOM-2 Data Center Project.

The company has secured an order from Digital Edge DC (India) for the supply of power distribution systems for the BOM-2 Data Center Project. The order is to be executed over a period of 6–8 months. Marine Electricals has also received an order from Crescon Projects & Services for the supply of power distribution systems for the LBOM-12 Data Center Project, with deliveries expected to be completed within 1–2 months. In addition, the company bagged an order from SHM Shipcare for the supply of power distribution systems, which is to be executed over a period of 4–5 months. Marine Electricals (India) is engaged in the manufacturing and sale of all types of marine and industrial electrical & electronic components like switchgears, control gears, etc., and is also engaged in the renewable energy sector, specifically solar. It also provides services like designing and fabricating for all types of electrical & electronic installations in India and abroad and undertakes annual maintenance contracts. On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit of Marine Electricals (India) rose 29.64% to Rs 16.49 crore, while net sales rose 20.72% to Rs 222.25 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarineElectricalsIndiaLtd_21789970758_38996.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India and EU conclude landmark Free Trade Agreement]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-and-eu-conclude-landmark-free-trade-agreement/1667641</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667641</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Tuesday announced that India and the EU have reached a free trade agreement (FTA), saying it accounts for 25 per cent of global GDP and one-third of global trade.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Tuesday announced that India and the EU have reached a free trade agreement (FTA), saying it accounts for 25 per cent of global GDP and one-third of global trade. India and Europe have concluded the "mother of all" trade deals, European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen said as Prime Minister Narendra Modi and the top EU leadership held summit talks to elevate the two-way ties to jointly navigate geopolitical turbulence and trade disruptions. Meanwhile, European Commission President, Ursula von der Leyen, said: “The EU and India make history today, deepening the partnership between the world's biggest democracies. We have created a free trade zone of 2 billion people, with both sides set to gain economically. We have sent a signal to the world that rules-based cooperation still delivers great outcomes. And, best of all, this is only the start - we will build on this success, and grow our relationship to be even stronger.”

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kirloskar Pneumatic Company jumps on PLI white goods selection, strong Q3 show]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kirloskar-pneumatic-company-jumps-on-pli-white-goods-selection-strong-q3-show/1667642</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667642</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The provisional selection positions the company to benefit from government incentives aimed at boosting domestic manufacturing of white goods.

The provisional selection positions the company to benefit from government incentives aimed at boosting domestic manufacturing of white goods. Under the PLI framework, eligible companies receive incentives linked to incremental sales and committed investments, supporting capacity expansion and localisation. According to an official release dated January 23, the PLI scheme for white goods, covering air conditioners and LED lights, is expected to attract investments of Rs 11,198 crore from 85 companies over the scheme period. In the fourth round, five applicants were provisionally selected with a combined committed investment of Rs 863 crore, while eight other applications were referred to a committee of experts for further evaluation. Kirloskar Pneumatic has committed an investment of Rs 320 crore to manufacture key components such as compressors, motors, heat exchangers and sheet metal parts. Companies selected in this round are expected to generate total production worth Rs 8,337.24 crore and create 1,799 additional direct jobs by FY28. Overall, the 85 companies approved under the scheme are projected to deliver cumulative production of around Rs 1.90 lakh crore. The initiative aims to significantly raise domestic value addition from the current 20-25% to 75-80% and strengthen India’s position in global supply chains for air conditioners and LED lighting products. The PLI scheme for white goods was approved in April 2021 with a total outlay of Rs 6,238 crore and is being implemented from FY22 to FY29. It offers incentives ranging from 6% to 4% on incremental sales over a five-year period, following a base year and gestation phase, to encourage large-scale domestic manufacturing of critical components. Separately, Kirloskar Pneumatic Company reported a solid performance for the quarter ended December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit came in at Rs 42.2 crore, up 15.9% YoY from Rs 36.4 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. However, profit declined 3% QoQ from Rs 43.5 crore reported in the September quarter. Net sales rose 18.8% YoY to Rs 406.9 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 342.6 crore in the year-ago period. On a sequential basis, revenue increased 5.3% QoQ from Rs 386.4 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 58.9 crore, marking a 20.7% YoY increase over Rs 48.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, PBT edged up 2.6% QoQ from Rs 57.4 crore in Q2 FY26. The company's board declared an interim dividend of Rs 3.50 per equity share of Rs 2 each for the Financial Year 2025-26. Order book stood around Rs 1,939 crore as on 1 January 2026, which is 19% higher than at the beginning of year. (Rs 1,624 crore as on 1 April 2025). Kirloskar Pneumatic Company is a diversified company offering a comprehensive range of products, including air, refrigeration, and gas compressors and systems, vapour absorption chillers, and industrial gearboxes.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KirlPneumatic_91477874_318.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Cables jumps after PAT rises 42% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dynamic-cables-jumps-after-pat-rises-42-yoy-in-q3/1667643</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667643</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 270.59 crore, up 16% YoY.

Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 270.59 crore, up 16% YoY. Profit before tax stood at Rs 30.04 crore in Q3 FY26, up by 43% from Rs 21.03 crore registered in Q3 FY25. Dynamic Cables is manufacturer of power infra cables that includes LV, HV, MV, power control & instrumentation cables, and signaling cables. It supplies cables to government discoms, private distribution companies, private EPC contractors, industrial and export clients.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DynamicCablesLtd_63561603370_37752.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro speculative net longs fall further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-speculative-net-longs-fall-further/1667640</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667640</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market fell further, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market fell further, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Euro futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net long position of 111695 contracts in the data reported through January 20, 2026. This was a weekly reduction of 20961 net long contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[APL Apollo Tubes Ltd soars 3.27%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apl-apollo-tubes-ltd-soars-327-up-for-third-straight-session/1667639</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667639</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[APL Apollo Tubes Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

APL Apollo Tubes Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2065.6, up 3.27% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.04% on the day, quoting at 25058.5. The Sensex is at 81541.25, up 0%. APL Apollo Tubes Ltd has gained around 9.37% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which APL Apollo Tubes Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 8.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11477.8, up 2.24% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 15.65 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.41 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2060.8, up 3.02% on the day. APL Apollo Tubes Ltd is up 38.74% in last one year as compared to a 9.15% jump in NIFTY and a 43.86% jump in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 112.73 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/APLApollo_78059449708_12334.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index net speculators add net short position]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-net-speculators-add-net-short-position/1667636</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667636</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index speculators further added net short position, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

US dollar index speculators further added net short position, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of US dollar index futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 6418 contracts in the data reported through January 20, 2026, showing an increase of 2688 net short positions compared to the previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank slips as brokers flag NIM, profitability pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-bank-slips-as-brokers-flag-nim-profitability-pressure/1667632</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667632</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Despite the near-term concerns, the foreign broker has maintained a ‘Buy’ rating on the stock with a target price of Rs 530, implying an upside of about 26% from the price cited in its January 25 report.

Despite the near-term concerns, the foreign broker has maintained a ‘Buy’ rating on the stock with a target price of Rs 530, implying an upside of about 26% from the price cited in its January 25 report. The broker said that bank’s standalone profit for December quarter, excluding one-off costs, rose 6% year-on-year and was ahead of estimates, while loan growth of 16% and deposit growth of 15% were higher than peers including HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank. However, the brokerage added that net interest income growth of 5% lagged peers due to weaker margin performance, leading it to describe the quarter as “on par with peers.” Further, the another foreign broker has retained a ‘Neutral’ rating on the counter and raised its target price to Rs 460, implying an upside of about 9% from the last closing price cited in its January 26 report. The brokerage highlighted that margins stayed flat at 4.54% against its expectation of an improvement, while higher operating expenses led to a miss at the core pre-provision operating profit level. The bank reported a 4.28% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 3,446.14 crore on 4.3% increase in total income to Rs 16,741.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Operating profit before provisions and tax rose 3.84% YoY to Rs 5,379.77 crore during the quarter. Provision (other than tax) and contingencies increased 1.95% YoY to 809.58 crore during the quarter. Net interest income (NII) stood at Rs 7565 crore in Q3 FY26, up 5% compared with Rs 7,196 crore in Q3 FY25. Net Interest Margin (NIM) was 4.54% for Q3FY26 compared with 4.93% for Q3FY25. Operating expenses rose 8% to Rs 5,023 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 4,638 crore in Q3 FY25. Q3FY26. These expenses include an estimated incremental cost of Rs 96 crore arising from the implementation of the new Labour Code. Excluding this impact, operating expenses for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 4,927 crore, reflecting a 6% YoY increase. Credit cost (annualised) stood at 0.63% in Q3 FY26, compared with 0.68% in Q3 FY25. Total deposits at the end of the period grew 15% to Rs 542,638 crore for Q3FY26, from Rs 473,497 crore for Q3FY25. Average total deposits also increased 15% to Rs 526,025 crore for Q3FY26, from Rs 458,614 crore for Q3FY25. Average current deposits grew to Rs 75,596 crore for Q3FY26, up 14% from Rs 66,589 crore for Q3FY25. Net Advances increased 16% to Rs 480,673 crore as at December 31, 2025 from Rs 413,839 crore as at December 31, 2024. Asset quality continued to improve, with gross non-performing assets (GNPA) declining to 1.30% as on December 31, 2025, from 1.50% as on 31st December 2024 and net non-performing assets (NNPA) was 0.31% as on 31st December 2025 compared with 0.41% as of 31st December 2024. As at December 31, 2025, Provision Coverage Ratio stood at 76% as of 31st December 2025. The bank’s capital adequacy ratio under Basel III norms stood at 22.6% as of December 31, 2025, while the CET1 ratio was strong at 21.5%, including unaudited profits. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved a proposal to raise funds by way of issuance of unsecured, redeemable, non-convertible debentures (NCDs), on a private placement basis, for an amount up to Rs 15,000 crore, in one or more tranches / series, during FY 2026-27, subject to the approval of the members of the bank. Kotak Mahindra Bank is the part of the Kotak Group and has diversified operations covering commercial vehicle financing, consumer loans, corporate finance, and asset reconstruction. Through its subsidiaries, the bank is engaged in investment banking, equity broking, securities-based lending, and car finance. As on 31 st December 2025, the bank has a national footprint of 2,218 branches and 2,749 ATMs (incl. cash recyclers) and branches in GIFT City and DIFC (Dubai).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KotakMahBank_47062626511_2330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex spurts 122 pts; oil & gas shares advance; VIX zooms 7.78% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-spurts-122-pts-oil-gas-shares-advance-vix-zooms-778/1667631</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667631</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in early afternoon trade, buoyed by news that India and the European Union had clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA) after 18 years of stalled negotiations.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in early afternoon trade, buoyed by news that India and the European Union had clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA) after 18 years of stalled negotiations. Investor focus remained on key quarterly earnings from Asian Paints, Vodafone Idea, and Motilal Oswal Financial Services, while traders also monitored movements in the rupee and global geopolitical developments. The Nifty traded above 25,100 level. Oil & Gas shares advanced after declining for previous consecutive trading session. At 12:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex added 122.19 points or 0.15% to 81,658.93. The Nifty 50 index rose 66.40 points or 0.27% to 25,113.95. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.23% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.43%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,712 shares rose and 2,385 shares fell. A total of 197 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 7.78% to 15.30. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union have signed the “mother of all deals”, PM Modi said on Tuesday. Prime Minister Narendra Modi lauded the signing of the free trade agreement between India and the European Union and said that the deal represented “25 per cent of the global GDP and 1/3rd of global trade”. On tariffs overall, Sefcovic said the aim is 97–99% partial or full tariff liberalisation, which could generate savings of around €4 billion a year and help double bilateral trade within five years. The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, soared 5.93% to 15.04. The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures were trading at 25,145, at a premium of 31.05 points as compared with the spot at 25,113.95. The Nifty option chain for the 27 January 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 202.7 lakh contracts at the 25,300 strike price. Maximum put OI of 259.6 lakh contracts was seen at 25,000 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index added 0.73% to 11,388.80. The index tanked 1.19% in the previous trading session. Oil India (up 3.28%), Adani Total Gas (up 2.7%), Aegis Logistics (up 1.83%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (up 1.7%), Indian Oil Corporation (up 1.52%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (up 1.21%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (up 1.07%), Reliance Industries (up 0.28%), Petronet LNG (up 0.16%) and Castrol India (up 0.02%) added. On the other hand, Mahanagar Gas (down 3.44%), Gujarat State Petronet (down 1.53%) and GAIL (India) (down 0.81%) edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: Ultratech Cement added 2.54% after the company reported a 26.92% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,725.40 crore on 22.78% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 21,829.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Axis Bank jumped 4.51% after the bank reported a 2.94% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 6,489.57 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 6,303.77 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26. DCB Bank zoomed 7.04% after the bank reported 22% jump in net profit to Rs 185 crore on a 16% increase in total income to Rs 846 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Allcargo Terminals Ltd Partly Paidup leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/allcargo-terminals-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1667621</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667621</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd, Antelopus Selan Energy Ltd, Apex Frozen Foods Ltd and Mercury EV-Tech Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 January 2026.

Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd, Antelopus Selan Energy Ltd, Apex Frozen Foods Ltd and Mercury EV-Tech Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 January 2026. Allcargo Terminals Ltd Partly Paidup soared 17.00% to Rs 11.7 at 11:59 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 16 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2652 shares in the past one month. Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd surged 15.91% to Rs 928. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 67315 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15774 shares in the past one month. Antelopus Selan Energy Ltd spiked 15.44% to Rs 583.85. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 2.37 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 88108 shares in the past one month. Apex Frozen Foods Ltd spurt 14.90% to Rs 302.75. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.75 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 27456 shares in the past one month. Mercury EV-Tech Ltd exploded 13.40% to Rs 41.14. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 11.74 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.98 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>