<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:05:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd Spikes 4.22%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-ltd-spikes-422/1667817</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667817</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd rose 4.22% today to trade at Rs 308.95.

Tejas Networks Ltd rose 4.22% today to trade at Rs 308.95. The BSE Telecommunication index is up 0.55% to quote at 2875.43. The index is down 8.6 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, ADC India Communications Ltd increased 3.28% and ITI Ltd added 2.13% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 6.52 % over last one year compared to the 7.89% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Tejas Networks Ltd has lost 32.21% over last one month compared to 8.6% fall in BSE Telecommunication index and 3.31% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 7554 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 2 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 973.9 on 27 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 294.1 on 27 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Asian Paints Ltd Slides 6.27%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/asian-paints-ltd-slides-627/1667818</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667818</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Asian Paints Ltd fell 6.27% today to trade at Rs 2460.4.

Asian Paints Ltd fell 6.27% today to trade at Rs 2460.4. The BSE Consumer Durables index is down 0.93% to quote at 55656.76. The index is down 6.72 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Berger Paints India Ltd decreased 0.55% and Blue Star Ltd lost 0.42% on the day. The BSE Consumer Durables index went down 1.33 % over last one year compared to the 7.89% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Asian Paints Ltd has lost 11.34% over last one month compared to 6.72% fall in BSE Consumer Durables index and 3.31% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 13610 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 50500 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2985.5 on 04 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 2125 on 04 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AsianPaints_3886867460_34.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nesco slips after Q3 PAT falls 5% YoY to Rs 105 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nesco-slips-after-q3-pat-falls-5-yoy-to-rs-105-crore/1667816</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667816</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 131.85 crore, down 7.04% YoY for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 131.85 crore, down 7.04% YoY for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Total expenses rose 48.29% YoY to Rs 142.58 crore during the quarter. Employee benefits expense was at Rs 12.27 crore (up 46.07% YoY), finance cost stood at Rs 7.76 crore (up 249.55% YoY), while other expenses increased 28.81% YoY to Rs 70.73 crore during the period under review. On the segmental front, revenue from the realty segment rose 7.71% year-on-year to Rs 100.11 crore, while income from the Bombay Exhibition Center increased 1.61% to Rs 68.21 crore. Revenue from the indabrator segment declined 25.33% to Rs 9.17 crore, whereas the foods segment reported a strong 106% growth to Rs 70.43 crore in Q3 FY26. NESCO is mainly engaged in licensing premises in IT park buildings and providing related services, licensing premises for exhibitions and providing services to the organizers, manufacturing machines and capital equipment, and providing hospitality and catering services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NESCO_30338869449_690.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests muted start for equities as investors focus on US Fed meet outcome]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-muted-start-for-equities-as-investors-focus-on-us-fed-meet-outcome/1667803</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667803</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 19.00 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 19.00 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today. Today, the industrial production data for the month of December 2025 would be announced. The industrial production in India grew 6.7% from the previous year in November of 2025, accelerating from the upwardly revised 0.5% increase in the previous month, to mark the sharpest pace of expansion since October of 2023. The US Federal Reserve has will commence its monetary policy meet today and will announce the outcome of this meet tomorrow. The Federal Reserve had reduced the federal funds rate by 25 basis points at the December meeting. It had also announced its plans to begin purchasing shorter-term Treasury securities. This marked the third rate cut of the year 2025, following two 25-basis-point moves in September and October. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,068.49 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 8,999.71 crore in the Indian equity market on 27 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 43,772.88 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets were mixed Wednesday, breaking ranks with Wall Street after the S&P 500 closed at a record high. Meanwhile, Australia saw its headline inflation come in at 3.6% for the last quarter of 2025, its highest level of inflation in six quarters. Overnight in the U.S., the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.91%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average broke ranks, losing 408.99 points, or 0.83%, and settling at 49,003.4. The S&P 500 futures were near the flatline ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision and earnings reports from major tech companies. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks ended modestly higher in a volatile session, supported by improving risk appetite. Sentiment was lifted by optimism around the India-European Union free trade agreement and expectations of a potential easing of US tariff measures related to India’s imports of Russian oil. The rupee rebounded from record lows, providing additional support to domestic equities, while firm global market cues aided sentiment. Investors also took note of remarks at Davos by US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent, who indicated that the additional 25% tariffs on India could be withdrawn amid reduced Indian purchases of Russian oil. Separately, liquidity support from the Reserve Bank of India boosted confidence after the central bank announced measures to inject funds into the banking system. The Nifty closed above the 25,150 level, led by gains in metal and banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 319.78 points or 0.39% to 81,857.48. The Nifty 50 index added 126.75 points or 0.51% to 25,175.40.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Marico, Motilal Oswal, Vishal Mega Mart, Metro Brands, PC Jeweller, Ramkrishna Forgings]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-marico-motilal-oswal-vishal-mega-mart-metro-brands-pc-jeweller-ramkrishna-forgings/1667802</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667802</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Wednesday, 28 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Wednesday, 28 January 2026. Listing In the mainboard segment, Shadowfax Technologies’ IPO will debut on the bourses today. The issue price is set at Rs 124 per share. The issue was subscribed 2.72 times. The IPO was open between 20 and 22 January 2026. The price band was Rs 118 and 124 per share. In the SME segment, BSE SME Digilogic Systems is set to list today. The issue price is set at Rs 104 per share. The issue was subscribed 1.09 times. The issue was open between 20 and 22 January 2026. The price band was Rs 98 to Rs 104 per share. Result Today: Larsen & Toubro, Maruti Suzuki India, Bharat Electronics, SBI Life Insurance Company, ACC, Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services, Aditya Birla Real Estate, ASK Automotive, Balkrishna Industries, CarTrade Tech, CSB Bank, Gland Pharma, ICRA, Lodha Developers, Novartis India, National Securities Depository, Pine Labs, SBI Cards and Payment Services, Star Health and Allied Insurance Company, Sundram Fasteners, Thyrocare Technologies, and TVS Motor Company will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Marico reported a 12.03% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 447 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 399 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 26.59% YoY to Rs 3,537 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Motilal Oswal Financial Services reported a marginal 0.25% YoY rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 566 crore, while revenue from operations increased 5.9% to Rs 2,111.7 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Vishal Mega Mart reported a 19.1% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 312.9 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 262.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 17% YoY to Rs 3,670 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Metro Brands reported consolidated net profit rose 35.7% to Rs 128.4 crore on a 15.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 811.3 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. PC Jeweller reported consolidated net profit jumped 28.5% to Rs 190.1 crore on a 36.9% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 875.4 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dodla Dairy reported consolidated net profit rose 8.1% to Rs 68.7 crore on a 13.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,025 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ramkrishna Forgings reported a 35% YoY decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 13.6 crore, even as revenue from operations rose 2.3% to Rs 1,098.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Rail Vikas Nigam has emerged as the lowest bidder for an order worth Rs 242.5 crore from South Central Railway. The order involves design, supply, erection, testing, and commissioning for OHE upgradation of the existing 1x25 kV system to a 2x25 kV feeding system, along with feeder and earthing works in the Ongole–Gudur section of Vijayawada.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rail Vikas Nigam bags Rs 242-cr OHE upgradation order from South Central Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rail-vikas-nigam-bags-rs-242-cr-ohe-upgradation-order-from-south-central-railway/1667778</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667778</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves upgrading the existing 1×25 kV system to a 2×25 kV AT feeding system, including feeder and earthing works, on the Ongole (OGL)–Gudur (GDR) section of the Vijayawada Division.

The project involves upgrading the existing 1×25 kV system to a 2×25 kV AT feeding system, including feeder and earthing works, on the Ongole (OGL)–Gudur (GDR) section of the Vijayawada Division. The total project length is 154 route kilometres (RKM) / 462 track kilometres (TKM) and has been awarded under Tender No: 2x25KV-OHE-OGL-GDR-15. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is to be executed within 24 months. The order value stands at Rs 242.49 crore, inclusive of applicable taxes. Rail Vikas Nigam added that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity and the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction. Rail Vikas Nigam is in the business of executing all types of railway projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, construction of cable-stayed bridges, institution buildings, etc. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 19.73% to Rs 230.29 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 286.88 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5.22% YoY to Rs 5,122.98 crore in Q2 FY26. The scrip shed 0.45% to end at Rs 323.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>