<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:21:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cupid Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cupid-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662988</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662988</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, Kiri Industries Ltd and SRG Housing Finance Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 January 2026.

Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, Kiri Industries Ltd and SRG Housing Finance Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 January 2026. Cupid Ltd tumbled 19.99% to Rs 419.95 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 39.48 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.97 lakh shares in the past one month. Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd lost 19.99% to Rs 55.14. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 68.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7.75 lakh shares in the past one month. Vivimed Labs Ltd crashed 9.97% to Rs 15.08. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3516 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10126 shares in the past one month. Kiri Industries Ltd dropped 9.86% to Rs 617.1. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 14.83 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.26 lakh shares in the past one month. SRG Housing Finance Ltd slipped 7.54% to Rs 282. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 104 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 348 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cupid_16723626520_5185.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades near record highs; metal shares shine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-near-record-highs-metal-shares-shine/1662987</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662987</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key benchmark indices traded with strong gains in mid-afternoon trade, as the Nifty traded above the 26,300 level.

The key benchmark indices traded with strong gains in mid-afternoon trade, as the Nifty traded above the 26,300 level. Market sentiment remained upbeat, supported by optimism over robust monthly auto sales data and sustained buying interest. Metal stocks continued their rally for a fourth consecutive trading session. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 491.58 points or 0.58% to 85,683.42. The Nifty 50 index gained 163.70 points or 0.63% to 26,310.25. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.86% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.72%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,653 shares rose and 1,466 shares fell. A total of 183 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index added 1.09% to 11,378.75. The index jumped 5.47% for the four consecutive trading sessions. National Aluminium Company (up 3.97%), Hindalco Industries (up 3.06%), Hindustan Copper (up 2.31%), Hindustan Zinc (up 2%), Vedanta (up 1.76%), Welspun Corp (up 0.84%), NMDC (up 0.74%), Adani Enterprises (up 0.58%), Jindal Steel (up 0.54%) and JSW Steel (up 0.4%) surged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.40% to 6.607 as compared with the previous close of 6.581. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2200 compared with its close of 89.9850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.85% to Rs 136,962. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.13% to 98.41. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.31% to 4.163. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 18 cents or 0.30% to $61.03 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Tamilnad Mercantile Bank rose 2.27% after the company’s total advances jumped 16.30% to Rs 50,763 crore as of 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 43,650 crore as of 31 December 2024. Zota Health Care advanced 1.75% after the company announced significant expansion in its Davaindia store network, adding 276 new stores. The company’s COCO segment opened 231 stores in Q3 FY26, taking the total number of COCO stores managed by wholly owned subsidiary Davaindia Health Mart to 1,207 as of 30 September 2025. Rama Steel Tubes rose 0.32%. The company said that it has registered a sales volume of 58,974.55 ton in Q3 FY26, which is higher by 14.1% as compared with the volume of 51,669.01 ton recorded in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Devyani International Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-devyani-international-ltd-counter/1662986</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662986</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IDBI Bank Ltd, SJVN Ltd, Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd, Elecon Engineering Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 02 January 2026.

IDBI Bank Ltd, SJVN Ltd, Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd, Elecon Engineering Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 02 January 2026. Devyani International Ltd recorded volume of 379.95 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.08 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 31.45 lakh shares. The stock gained 2.39% to Rs.150.95. Volumes stood at 15.28 lakh shares in the last session. IDBI Bank Ltd saw volume of 946.69 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.02 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 94.46 lakh shares. The stock increased 10.00% to Rs.114.14. Volumes stood at 69.9 lakh shares in the last session. SJVN Ltd clocked volume of 336.49 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.84 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 34.20 lakh shares. The stock gained 11.61% to Rs.83.42. Volumes stood at 16.02 lakh shares in the last session. Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd recorded volume of 325.76 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.02 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 46.38 lakh shares. The stock gained 9.00% to Rs.335.60. Volumes stood at 239.61 lakh shares in the last session. Elecon Engineering Company Ltd clocked volume of 16.49 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.98 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.36 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.58% to Rs.502.70. Volumes stood at 1.7 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Devyani-International_90569402_24609.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps India bags Rs 24 crore order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shakti-pumps-india-bags-rs-24-crore-order/1662985</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662985</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is to be executed within 90 days.

The project is to be executed within 90 days. Shakti Pumps (India) manufactures solar pumps, energy-efficient stainless-steel submersible pumps, pressure booster pumps, pump motors, and other products. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 10.56% to Rs 90.71 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 101.42 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5% YoY to Rs 666.35 crore in Q2 Sept 2025. Shares of Shakti Pumps India shed 0.04% to Rs 739 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShaktiPumps_14702424257_6580.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sambhv Steel Tubes jumps on record Q3 value-added product volumes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sambhv-steel-tubes-jumps-on-record-q3-value-added-product-volumes/1662983</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662983</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total sales volume increased 34.3% year-on-year (YoY) to 97,472 tonnes in Q3 FY26, compared with 72,559 tonnes in the year-ago quarter.

Total sales volume increased 34.3% year-on-year (YoY) to 97,472 tonnes in Q3 FY26, compared with 72,559 tonnes in the year-ago quarter. Volumes were largely flat sequentially, down 1.3% quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) from 98,768 tonnes in Q2 FY26. Value-added products recorded sharp growth, with volumes rising 63.5% YoY to 90,612 tonnes in Q3 FY26, up from 55,410 tonnes in Q3 FY25. Within this, structural pipes and tubes stood at 57,262 tonnes, up 11.6% YoY, while pre-galvanised coils and pipes surged 2,667.2% to 19,979 tonnes from 722 tonnes a year earlier, while stainless steel coils volumes rose 294.1% YoY to 13,371 tonnes. Intermediate product volumes slumped 60% YoY to 6,860 tonnes, compared with 17,149 tonnes in the corresponding quarter last year. The company said the strong showing in value-added products reflects robust capacity utilisation, especially in the stainless steel segment, and underscores its strategic focus on scaling higher-margin products. Sambhv Steel Tubes is a manufacturer of ERW steel pipes and structural tubes with integrated manufacturing capabilities spanning sponge iron to finished products, including ERW pipes, CRFH pipes, pre-galvanised coils and pipes, GI pipes and steel door frames. The company is among the limited number of domestic producers with backward-integrated stainless steel operations, manufacturing SS blooms and slabs for captive conversion into HR, HRAP and CR coils. Sambhv Steel Tubes operates two manufacturing facilities in Chhattisgarh with installed capacities of 350,000 MTPA for ERW pipes and tubes, 116,000 MTPA for GP coils, 100,000 MTPA for GP pipes and 58,000 MTPA for stainless steel coils, and distributes its products through 43 distributors across 15 states and one union territory, serving over 700 dealers in India. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 468.8% to Rs 30.60 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 5.38 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales jumped 83.4% YoY to Rs 580.17 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SambhvSteelTubesLtd_81933086_94069.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 26,300 level; realty shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-26300-level-realty-shares-rally/1662981</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662981</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline domestic indices traded with substantial gains in the afternoon trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,300 level.

The headline domestic indices traded with substantial gains in the afternoon trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,300 level. Market sentiment remained positive, supported by optimism over strong monthly auto sales data and sustained buying interest. Barring the Nifty FMCG index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the green, with the Realty, Auto and PSU Bank indices gaining the most. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 488.65 points or 0.57% to 85,676.82. The Nifty 50 index climbed 157.40 points or 0.60% to 26,303.95. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 0.82% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.66%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,611 shares rose and 1,429 shares fell. A total of 195 shares were unchanged. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) – a single-figure indicator of sector performance – fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signalling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years. Amid a general lack of pressure on operating capacities, there was only a marginal increase in factory employment during December. Gainers & Losers: Coal India (up 5.91%), NTPC (up 3.18%), Hindalco Industries (up 2.64%), Trent (up 2.58%) and Jio Financial Services (up 2.08%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. ITC (down 3.97%), Nestle India (down 0.92%), Shriram Finance (down 0.87%), Bharti Airtel (down 0.44%) and Dr. Reddy's Laboratories (down 0.41%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Maruti Suzuki India rose 1.57% after the company’s total production rose 34.43% to 211,939 units in December 2025 as against 157,654 units recorded in December 2024. Avantel added 0.29%. The company has received a manufacturing order worth Rs 1.76 crore from Bharat Electronics (BEL). Olectra Greentech jumped 4.16% after the company announced the start of commercial operations at its greenfield EV manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. ACME Solar Holdings added 0.80%. The company announced the incorporation of a wholly owned subsidiary, ACME Greentech Eighteen, to strengthen its presence in the renewable energy segment. Remsons Industries rallied 3.68% after the company has secured a Rs 60-crore order from a leading domestic commercial vehicle (CV) OEM. Punjab & Sind Bank jumped 4.83% after the bank's gross advances increased by 15.25% to Rs 110,488 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 95,870 crore as of 31 December 2024. South Indian Bank advanced 2.82% after the private lender said that its gross advances jumped 11.27% to Rs 96,765 crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 86,966 crore as of 31 December 2024. Hyundai Motor India (HMIL) declined 1.40%. The company has recorded 6.6% year-on-year (YoY) growth in total monthly sales, clocking sales of 58,702 units in December 2025. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Friday, starting the first trading day of the year on a positive note. Asian markets traded higher to start the new year, with Hong Kong and South Korea leading the gains. South Korea’s Kospi index hit a new record on Friday, lifting investor sentiment across the region. Some Asian markets were still closed for the holidays, including Japan and mainland China. Meanwhile, Singapore’s economy expanded 5.7% year-on-year for the fourth quarter, driven mainly by strong manufacturing growth in the three months through December. The latest reading is faster than the revised 4.3% growth in the previous quarter. On Wednesday, Prime Minister Lawrence Wong announced in his New Year message that the country had clocked a stronger-than-expected 4.8% expansion for the full year of 2025. U.S. stock futures were looking up in early Asian hours, with S&P futures up by 0.15% and Nasdaq-100 futures climbing 0.12%. Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 0.16% higher. On Wednesday stateside, the S&P 500 dipped 0.74%, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and the Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 0.63%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tamilnad Mercantile Bank rise as total advances jump 12% YoY in Q3 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-rise-as-total-advances-jump-12-yoy-in-q3/1662979</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662979</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total deposits climbed 12.53% to Rs 56,707 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 50,392 crore as of 31 December 2024.

Total deposits climbed 12.53% to Rs 56,707 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 50,392 crore as of 31 December 2024. As of 31 December 2025, total business stood at Rs 107,470 crore, registering a growth of 14.28% compared with Rs 94,042 crore as of 31 December 2024. CASA increased 14.93% to Rs 15,847 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 13,788 crore as of 31 December 2024. Tamilnad Mercantile Bank (TMB) is one of the renowned old private sector banks, having its headquarters in Thoothukudi (Tamil Nadu). The bank’s standalone net profit rose 4.7% to Rs 317.51 crore on a 3.6% increase in total income to Rs 1,621.46 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TamilnadMercantileBankLtd_18937215_12426.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bosch Ltd soars 7.98%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bosch-ltd-soars-798-up-for-third-straight-session/1662964</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662964</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bosch Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Bosch Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 39025, up 7.98% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Bosch Ltd has added around 6.68% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bosch Ltd is a constituent, has added around 4.29% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28480.55, up 1.23% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.05 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 18420 shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 39315, up 8.23% on the day. Bosch Ltd is up 13.93% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% gain in NIFTY and a 20.1% gain in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 46.93 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Bosch_19930465954_378.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd spurts 1.03%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/exide-industries-ltd-spurts-103/1662965</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662965</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Exide Industries Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 367, up 1.03% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Exide Industries Ltd has dropped around 1.52% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Exide Industries Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 4.29% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28480.55, up 1.23% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.3 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 11.16 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 369.4, up 1.15% on the day. Exide Industries Ltd is down 13.6% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% spurt in NIFTY and a 20.1% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 29.67 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ExideInds_97756038201_111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coal India Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coal-india-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662966</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662966</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Coal India Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Coal India Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 421.7, up 5.31% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Coal India Ltd has gained around 12.38% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Coal India Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35507.65, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 169.41 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 51.22 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 425.1, up 5.64% on the day. Coal India Ltd is up 7.13% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% jump in NIFTY and a 0.52% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 11.61 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoalIndia_84226386779_12019.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Torrent Power Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/torrent-power-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1662967</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662967</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Torrent Power Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Torrent Power Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1391, up 4.82% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Torrent Power Ltd has gained around 6.82% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Torrent Power Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35507.65, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 9 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.84 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1388.3, up 3.89% on the day. Torrent Power Ltd is down 8.09% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% jump in NIFTY and a 0.52% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 23.15 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TorrentPower_38030455678_18488.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NTPC Ltd spurts 3.49%, rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ntpc-ltd-spurts-349-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662968</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662968</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NTPC Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

NTPC Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 348.05, up 3.49% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. NTPC Ltd has added around 7.77% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which NTPC Ltd is a constituent, has added around 2.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35507.65, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 110.29 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 73.73 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 346.75, up 2.89% on the day. NTPC Ltd is up 2.41% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% gain in NIFTY and a 0.52% gain in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 16.37 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NTPC_90569510917_12001.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Power Company Ltd soars 2.37%, rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-power-company-ltd-soars-237-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662969</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662969</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Power Company Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Tata Power Company Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 390.9, up 2.37% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Tata Power Company Ltd has added around 1.89% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Tata Power Company Ltd is a constituent, has added around 2.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35507.65, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 94.23 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 35.78 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 392.85, up 2.2% on the day. Tata Power Company Ltd is down 1.45% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% gain in NIFTY and a 0.52% gain in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 52.16 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataPowerCo_38377109932_554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JSW Energy Ltd soars 2.33%, Gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jsw-energy-ltd-soars-233-gains-for-third-straight-session/1662970</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662970</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[JSW Energy Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

JSW Energy Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 513.7, up 2.33% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. JSW Energy Ltd has added around 9.25% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which JSW Energy Ltd is a constituent, has added around 2.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35507.65, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 39.77 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 36.72 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 514.8, up 1.93% on the day. JSW Energy Ltd is down 19.03% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% gain in NIFTY and a 0.52% gain in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 84.92 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JSWEnergy_53555504993_27323.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd spurts 1.71%, rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-spurts-171-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662971</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662971</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Hitachi Energy India Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 18798, up 1.71% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Hitachi Energy India Ltd has dropped around 13.97% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Hitachi Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 2.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35507.65, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 40927 shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.24 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 18858, up 1.43% on the day. Hitachi Energy India Ltd is up 24.23% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% gain in NIFTY and a 0.52% gain in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 114.85 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HitachiEnergyIndiaLimited_51485438_74646.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-grid-corporation-of-india-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662972</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662972</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 270, up 1.2% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has gained around 0.58% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.78% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35507.65, up 1.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 73.79 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 83.89 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 271.6, up 1.17% on the day. Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd is down 14.57% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% jump in NIFTY and a 0.52% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 16.08 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerGridCorpn_89479008350_5455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[REC Ltd spurts 3.77%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rec-ltd-spurts-377/1662973</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662973</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[REC Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

REC Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 381.55, up 3.77% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. REC Ltd has risen around 8.92% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which REC Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 0.92% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27666.8, up 0.79% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 171.84 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 60.21 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 382.45, up 3.74% on the day. REC Ltd is down 29.09% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% spurt in NIFTY and a 17.48% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 5.65 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RECLtd_11504702_18075.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Finance Corporation Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-finance-corporation-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662974</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662974</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Power Finance Corporation Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Power Finance Corporation Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 375.95, up 3.52% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Power Finance Corporation Ltd has gained around 6.82% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Power Finance Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.92% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27666.8, up 0.79% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 148.99 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 57.43 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 377, up 3.37% on the day. Power Finance Corporation Ltd is down 19.12% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% jump in NIFTY and a 17.48% jump in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 6.57 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerFinCorpn_2130951000_12068.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jio Financial Services Ltd soars 2.05%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jio-financial-services-ltd-soars-205/1662975</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662975</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jio Financial Services Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Jio Financial Services Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 301.75, up 2.05% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. Jio Financial Services Ltd has risen around 0.25% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Jio Financial Services Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 0.92% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27666.8, up 0.79% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 74.78 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 70.69 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 303.65, up 2% on the day. Jio Financial Services Ltd is down 1.85% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% spurt in NIFTY and a 17.48% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 268.73 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JioFinancialServicesLtd_17889422_20712.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1662976</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662976</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2073.8, up 1.64% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.55% on the day, quoting at 26289.4. The Sensex is at 85636.03, up 0.53%. SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd has gained around 5.12% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.92% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27666.8, up 0.79% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.86 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.09 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2080.9, up 1.34% on the day. SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is up 43.25% in last one year as compared to a 9.52% jump in NIFTY and a 17.48% jump in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 83.44 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SBILifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_43034021988_22045.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>