<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures holds near one and half week low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-copper-futures-holds-near-one-and-half-week-low/1678083</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678083</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures held near one and half week low as a break under $6 per pound capped advances.

COMEX Copper futures held near one and half week low as a break under $6 per pound capped advances. Asian markets saw thin moves as China, South Korea and Taiwan markets are closed for Lunar New Year holidays. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index added 0.52%. Japanese NIKKEI 225 index eased 0.24%. European stocks moved up modestly.US stocks saw choppy moves on Friday and recorded modest losses for the week. COMEX Copper futures are currently quoting at $5.78 per pound, down 0.36% on the day. MCX Copper futures are trading at Rs 1201.45 per kg, down 0.67% on the day. The counter rose in afternoon trades but gains have been limited.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee tumbles down further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-tumbles-down-further/1678081</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678081</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.7225 per Dollar on Monday (16 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.6900 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's unemployment rate rises slightly to 5% in Jan-26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-unemployment-rate-rises-slightly-to-5-in-jan-26/1678080</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678080</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Periodic Labour Force Survey (PLFS) data showed that India’s Labour Force Participation Rate (LFPR) shows steady trend.

The Periodic Labour Force Survey (PLFS) data showed that India’s Labour Force Participation Rate (LFPR) shows steady trend. The overall LFPR among persons of age 15 years and above reported as 55.9% in January, 2026. Rural LFPR was 58.7% in January, 2026 compared to 59.0% in December, 2025. Urban LFPR observed as 50.3% in January, 2026, against 50.2% in December, 2025. Female Labour Force Participation Rate (LFPR) in January, 2026 reported as 35.1%. Rural female LFPR was found as 39.7% in January, 2026, while urban female LFPR reached to 25.5% during the month. The overall Worker Population Ratio (WPR) in the age group 15 years and above exhibited a broad stability in January, 2026. Following a gradual increase in rural WPR since June, 2025 (53.3%) to December, 2025 (56.7%), it declined marginally to 56.2% in January, 2026. In rural areas, the male and female WPR stood at 75.7% and 38.0%, respectively, in January, 2026, compared to 76.0% and 38.6% in December, 2025. Urban WPR, on the other hand, remained stable across genders and was recorded as 70.5% for male, 23.0% for female and 46.8% at the person level in January, 2026. Data showed that Unemployment Rate (UR) marked a modest increase. The UR among persons of age 15 years and above rose slightly to 5.0% in January, 2026 from 4.8% in December, 2025. The rural UR edged up from 3.9% to 4.2%, while urban UR increased from 6.7% to 7.0% during December, 2025 to January, 2026. Among male aged 15 years and above, the UR continued to remain stable in January, 2026. In contrast, the female UR in the same age group was comparatively higher in January, 2026 than in December, 2025. However, the female UR remains within the range observed during the period April to December, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures advance towards 124 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-advance-towards-124-mark/1678078</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678078</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USDINR futures edged up to settle at 90.72.

On the NSE, USDINR futures edged up to settle at 90.72. GBPINR and EURINR climbed 0.29% and 0.12% to end at 123.90 and 107.75 respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles flat in range-bound trades]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-flat-in-range-bound-trades/1678077</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678077</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee settled flat at 90.66 (provisional) against the US dollar in a range-bound trade on Monday, as positive momentum in domestic equities was offset by a strong US dollar in the overseas market.

The Indian rupee settled flat at 90.66 (provisional) against the US dollar in a range-bound trade on Monday, as positive momentum in domestic equities was offset by a strong US dollar in the overseas market. Lower crude oil prices supported the local unit, while foreign fund outflows limited its movement. Indian shares rose notably on Monday despite lackluster cues from global markets and continued declines in IT stocks on AI disruption fears. Investors shrugged off official data that showed India's wholesale prices increased more-than-expected in January to the highest level in ten months. Recovering from an early slide, the benchmark BSE Sensex ended the session up 650.39 points, or 0.79 percent, at 83,277.15. The broader NSE Nifty index jumped 211.65 points, or 0.83 percent, to 25,682.75. In the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 90.63 against the US dollar and moved between an intraday high of 90.61 and a low of 90.72 during the session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmark indices rebound sharply; Nifty climbs past 25,650]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmark-indices-rebound-sharply-nifty-climbs-past-25650/1678076</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678076</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Benchmark equity indices finished firmly higher on Monday, buoyed by robust buying in banks and financial counters.

Benchmark equity indices finished firmly higher on Monday, buoyed by robust buying in banks and financial counters. The Nifty reversed its two-day slide and settled above the 25,650 mark after a sharp intraday recovery. The session began on a cautious note amid mixed global signals, with the Nifty slipping to 25,372.70 in early trade. However, strong domestic buying quickly reversed the trend, triggering a steady upmove through the day. Gains gathered momentum in the latter half of the session, lifting the index to an intraday high of 25,697 before it closed near the day’s peak. The S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 650.39 points or 0.79% to 83,277.15. The Nifty 50 index rallied 211.65 points or 0.83% to 25,682.75. The 50-unit index fell 1.86% in the past two sessions. HDFC Bank (up 2.39%), Axis Bank (up 1.93%) and Reliance Industries (up 1.02%) boosted the Nifty higher. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.64% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index shed 0.16%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,747 shares rose and 2,565 shares fell. A total of 201 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 0.28% to 13.33. Economy: India’s wholesale price index (WPI) inflation accelerated to 1.81% in January 2026 from 0.83% in December 2025. The uptick was driven by higher prices in basic metals, other manufacturing, non-food articles, food articles and textiles, among other categories. Food inflation rose to 1.41% in January after remaining flat at 0.00% in the previous month. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.15% to 6.667 compared with the previous session close of 6.677. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6600 compared with its close of 90.6650 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.36% to Rs 155,333. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.08% to 96.91. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.10% to 4.056. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement lost 25 cents or 0.37% to $67.50 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently up by 214 points, signaling a strong opening for US stocks in the next session. The US stock market will remain closed for trading on Monday, February 16, in observance of Presidents' Day. European markets traded higher on Monday, supported by a generally positive earnings season, although holidays in Asia and the U.S. have resulted in subdued activity. Asian indices ended mixed as several major financial centres remained closed for the Lunar New Year holiday, resulting in thin trading activity, while weak economic data from Japan weighed on investor sentiment. Markets in China, South Korea, Taiwan, and the United States were closed, keeping activity in currencies, commodities, and bond markets largely subdued. Japan reported that its economy grew just 0.1% on an annualized basis in the December quarter, much lower than expectations, mainly due to lower government spending. The weak data highlights the challenges facing Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and may strengthen the case for additional government spending to support growth. Wall Street markets were mostly steady on Friday after January inflation data came in largely in line with expectations. The S&P 500 ended flat at 6,836.17 points. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.2%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average edged up 0.1% to 49,500.93 points. Data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that consumer prices rose 0.2% in January compared to the previous month and increased 2.4% compared to a year earlier. The inflation numbers offered only limited support to stocks, as hopes of lower interest rates were offset by ongoing concerns about the impact of artificial intelligence on businesses. New listing: Shares of Fractal Analytics ended at Rs 847.40 on the BSE, a discount of 5.84% compared with the issue price of Rs 900. The scrip was listed at 900, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock has hit a high of 900 and a low of 832.10. On the BSE, over 4.21 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Shares of Aye Finance closed at Rs 128.90 on the BSE, a discount of 0.08% compared with the issue price of Rs 129. The scrip was listed at 129, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock has hit a high of 132.75 and a low of 120.60. On the BSE, 13.16 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Stocks in Spotlight: Shares of Kwality Wall's (India) began trading on the bourses on Monday, marking the standalone listing of the ice cream business following its demerger from Hindustan Unilever. The stock listed at Rs 29.90 on the BSE and at Rs 29.80 on the NSE, below the adjusted reference prices of Rs 38.15 on the BSE and Rs 40.20 on the NSE. It settled at Rs 29.51 on the BSE and Rs 29.20 on the NSE. Precision Wires India soared 15.14% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 98.89% to Rs 37.69 crore on a 36.55% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1336.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. CarTrade Tech surged 5.37% after the company announced the rollout of its multi-agent AI ecosystem, a technology-led initiative aimed at enhancing customer experience and accelerating margin expansion across its platforms. Tenneco Clean Air India declined 2.19% after the company’s consolidated net profit dropped 5.21% to Rs 118.68 crore despite a 14.23% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1285.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. KFin Technologies rallied 3.40% after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 2.02% to Rs 91.99 crore on a 27.88% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 370.87 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Titagarh Rail Systems fell 1.59% after its consolidated net profit tanked 23.48% to Rs 48.03 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.77 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shakti Pumps India slumped 11.83% after its consolidated net profit declined 69.53% to Rs 31.70 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 104.05 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Ola Electric Mobility fell 6.70% after the company’s net loss for the quarter stood at Rs 487 crore, widening from Rs 418 crore in Q2 FY26 but narrowing compared with Rs 564 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 470 crore, declining 55.0% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and 31.9% QoQ from Rs 690 crore. CRISIL rose 3.38% after the company reported a 7.5% increase in profit after tax to Rs 241.5 crore in Q4 2025, compared with Rs 224.7 crore in Q4 2024. Total income for Q4 2025 rose 17.5% to Rs 1,108.7 crore from Rs 943.2 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. GK Energy was locked in a 5% upper circuit after the company reported a 57.74% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 58.83 crore on a 43.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 460.20 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Vikran Engineering declined 10.21% after the company reported a 37.9% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 20.91 crore on a 0.5% rise in net sales to Rs 266.46 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Religare Ent slips after Q3 net loss widens to Rs 45 cr; board OKs demerger plan]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/religare-ent-slips-after-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-45-cr-board-oks-demerger-plan/1678075</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678075</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 23.25% YoY to Rs 2056.38 crore during the quarter.

Revenue from operations jumped 23.25% YoY to Rs 2056.38 crore during the quarter. The company reported pre-tax loss of Rs 103.09 crore in Q3 FY26 comapred with pre-tax loss of Rs 78.90 crore in corresponding quarter last year. Meanwhile, the board of Religare Enterprises (REL) and its wholly owned subsidiary, Religare Finvest (RFL), have approved the separation of the financial services and insurance businesses into two independently listed entities. The financial services business — including lending, broking, investment activities, and related ancillary and support services — will be transferred to RFL on a going concern basis. As consideration for the demerger, RFL will issue fully paid-up equity shares to REL shareholders on a 1:1 basis. Post-demerger, RFL's shareholding pattern will mirror REL's pre-demerger shareholding. Under the proposed scheme of arrangement, REL will retain its stake in Care Health Insurance Limited (CHIL) which will continue as an insurance-focused entity. The rationale for the demerger is to segregate the financial services and insurance verticals into focused, standalone entities. The move is aimed at attracting different investor profiles suited to each sector, enabling sharper performance tracking and reward alignment for employees, support the retention of sector-specific talent and resources, unlock shareholder value, and facilitate the pursuit of distinct growth opportunities. The company aims to complete the process and list RFL in Q1 of FY28. Pratul Gupta, chief financial officer, Religare Enterprises said, "We are simplifying our corporate structure to create two focused, well-capitalised and agile entities with distinct mandates. Each entity will benefit from improved capital allocation efficiency, enhanced transparency for investors, and the ability to optimize its capital structure based on its business characteristics and growth requirements. This transaction is expected to broaden our combined investor base, reduce complexity, and create two well-capitalised platforms ready to pursue their strategic ambitions independently. We are confident that this transformation will establish both entities as leaders in their respective domains, each with the resources, focus, and flexibility to capitalise on significant growth opportunities ahead." Religare Enterprises is a diversified financial services group present across three verticals. It offers an integrated suite of financial services through its underlying subsidiaries and operating entities, including loans to SMEs, affordable housing finance, health insurance and retail broking.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ReligareEnterp_40544664620_28150.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1678074</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678074</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Infosys, HDFC Bank and BSE were the top traded contracts.

Infosys, HDFC Bank and BSE were the top traded contracts. The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,728, a premium of 45.25 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,682.75 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index rallied 211.65 points or 0.83% to 25,682.75. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 0.28% to 13.33. Infosys, HDFC Bank and BSE were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers ends with significant gains; Nifty settles above 25,650 marks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-ends-with-significant-gains-nifty-settles-above-25650-marks/1678070</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678070</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity indices ended with major gains today in a volatile session, supported by renewed buying in undervalued stocks and select sectors.

The headline equity indices ended with major gains today in a volatile session, supported by renewed buying in undervalued stocks and select sectors. The Nifty ended above the 25,650 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 650.39 points or 0.79% to 83,277.15. The Nifty 50 index rallied 211.65 points or 0.83% to 25,682.75. Over the past two consecutive trading sessions, the Nifty 50 has slipped 1.86%, while the BSE Sensex has declined 1.95% over the past three consecutive trading sessions. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.64% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index shed 0.16%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 0.28% to 13.33. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Realty index (up 1.59%), the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 1.50%) and the Nifty Private Bank index (up 1.19%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Media index (down 0.87%), Nifty Auto index (down 0.73%) and the Nifty Chemical index (down 0.09%) and the underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: India’s wholesale price index (WPI) inflation increased to 1.81% in January 2026 compared with 0.83% in December 2025. The positive rate of inflation in January 2026 was due to an increase in prices of the manufacture of basic metals, other manufacturing, non-food articles, food articles, and textiles, among others. Food inflation picked up to 1.41% in January after remaining flat at 0.00% in December. India’s foreign exchange reserves fell to $717.6 billion as of February 6, 2026, dropping by $6.71 billion, data from the Reserve Bank of India showed. Meanwhile, data showed a dip in foreign currency assets (FCAs), which declined by $7.66 billion to $570.05 billion during the week. Gold holdings also recorded a sharp drop by $14.2 billion to $123.47 billion. Meanwhile, Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) decreased by $132 million to $18.82 billion. India’s reserve tranche position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) edged down by $32 million to $4.71 billion. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.15% to 6.667 compared with the previous session close of 6.677. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6600 compared with its close of 90.6650 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.36% to Rs 155,333. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.08% to 96.91. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.10% to 4.056. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement lost 25 cents or 0.37% to $67.50 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets traded higher on Monday as investors digested the key points from this year’s Munich Security Conference. The event saw several European leaders and policymakers reiterate the need for greater defense spending to accelerate the continent’s strategic autonomy, with discussions of a common nuclear shield. In corporate earnings, Airbus, Nestlé, and Renault are among the companies scheduled to report results later this week. Asian indices ended mixed as several major financial centres remained closed for the Lunar New Year holiday, resulting in thin trading activity, while weak economic data from Japan weighed on investor sentiment. Markets in China, South Korea, Taiwan, and the United States were closed, keeping activity in currencies, commodities, and bond markets largely subdued. Japan reported that its economy grew just 0.1% on an annualized basis in the December quarter, much lower than expectations, mainly due to lower government spending. The weak data highlights the challenges facing Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and may strengthen the case for additional government spending to support growth. Wall Street markets were mostly steady on Friday after January inflation data came in largely in line with expectations. The S&P 500 ended flat at 6,836.17 points. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.2%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average edged up 0.1% to 49,500.93 points. Data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that consumer prices rose 0.2% in January compared to the previous month and increased 2.4% compared to a year earlier. The inflation numbers offered only limited support to stocks, as hopes of lower interest rates were offset by ongoing concerns about the impact of artificial intelligence on businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bull-market-1457119_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Energy Index gains 1.90%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-energy-index-gains-190/1678069</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678069</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Energy index ended up 1.90% at 36386.75 today.

Nifty Energy index ended up 1.90% at 36386.75 today. The index has gained 6.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Inox Wind Ltd dropped 4.88%, Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd rose 4.63% and Adani Green Energy Ltd added 4.29%. The Nifty Energy index has soared 19.00% over last one year compared to the 12.01% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSE index gained 1.63% and Nifty Realty index gained 1.59% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.83% to close at 25682.75 while the SENSEX increased 0.79% to close at 83277.15 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finance-background-picture-id625756386_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts rise]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-rise/1678068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678068</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators increased net short position in the Pound futures market, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators increased net short position in the Pound futures market, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 25810 contracts in the data reported through February 10, 2026. This was a weekly rise of 11899 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 650 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,650]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-650-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25650/1678066</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678066</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended with major gains today, supported by renewed buying in undervalued stocks and select sectors.

The key domestic indices ended with major gains today, supported by renewed buying in undervalued stocks and select sectors. The Nifty ended above the 25,650 mark. Realty, PSU bank and private bank shares advanced, while media and auto shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 650.39 points or 0.79% to 83,277.15. The Nifty 50 index rallied 211.65 points or 0.83% to 25,682.75. The Nifty 50 has slipped 1.86%, while the BSE Sensex has declined 1.95% over the past three consecutive trading sessions. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.64% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index shed 0.16%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,792 shares rose and 2,510 shares fell. A total of 194 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 0.28% to 13.33. Economy: India’s wholesale price index (WPI) inflation increased to 1.81% in January 2026 compared with 0.83% in December 2025. The positive rate of inflation in January 2026 was due to an increase in prices of the manufacture of basic metals, other manufacturing, non-food articles, food articles, and textiles, among others. Food inflation picked up to 1.41% in January after remaining flat at 0.00% in December. India’s foreign exchange reserves fell to $717.6 billion as of February 6, 2026, dropping by $6.71 billion, data from the Reserve Bank of India showed. Meanwhile, data showed a dip in foreign currency assets (FCAs), which declined by $7.66 billion to $570.05 billion during the week. Gold holdings also recorded a sharp drop by $14.2 billion to $123.47 billion. Meanwhile, Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) decreased by $132 million to $18.82 billion. India’s reserve tranche position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) edged down by $32 million to $4.71 billion. New listing: Shares of Fractal Analytics ended at Rs 847.40 on the BSE, a discount of 5.84% compared with the issue price of Rs 900. The scrip was listed at 900, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock has hit a high of 900 and a low of 832.10. On the BSE, over 4.21 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Shares of Aye Finance closed at Rs 128.90 on the BSE, a discount of 0.08% compared with the issue price of Rs 129. The scrip was listed at 129, matching the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock has hit a high of 132.75 and a low of 120.60. On the BSE, 13.16 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index surged 1.59% to 836.70. The index fell 2.11% over the previous two trading sessions. Signature Global India (up 5.52%), DLF (up 2.75%), Lodha Developers (up 2.37%), Phoenix Mills (up 2.3%), Anant Raj (up 2.04%), Godrej Properties (up 1.46%), Oberoi Realty (up 1.11%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.7%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Precision Wires India soared 15.14% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 98.89% to Rs 37.69 crore on a 36.55% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1336.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tenneco Clean Air India declined 2.18% after the company’s consolidated net profit dropped 5.21% to Rs 118.68 crore despite a 14.23% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1285.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. KFin Technologies rallied 4.02% after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 2.02% to Rs 91.99 crore on a 27.88% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 370.87 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Titagarh Rail Systems fell 1.38% after its consolidated net profit tanked 23.48% to Rs 48.03 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.77 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shakti Pumps India slumped 11.46% after its consolidated net profit declined 69.53% to Rs 31.70 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 104.05 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Ola Electric Mobility fell 6.86% after the company’s net loss for the quarter stood at Rs 487 crore, widening from Rs 418 crore in Q2 FY26 but narrowing compared with Rs 564 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 470 crore, declining 55.0% YoY from Rs 1,045 crore and 31.9% QoQ from Rs 690 crore. CRISIL rose 3.41% after the company reported a 7.5% increase in profit after tax to Rs 241.5 crore in Q4 2025, compared with Rs 224.7 crore in Q4 2024. Total income for Q4 2025 rose 17.5% to Rs 1,108.7 crore from Rs 943.2 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. GK Energy was locked in a 5% upper circuit after the company reported a 57.74% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 58.83 crore on a 43.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 460.20 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Vikran Engineering declined 10.60% after the company reported a 37.9% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 20.91 crore on a 0.5% rise in net sales to Rs 266.46 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. CarTrade Tech surged 5.79% after the company announced the rollout of its multi-agent AI ecosystem, a technology-led initiative aimed at enhancing customer experience and accelerating margin expansion across its platforms. Global Markets: European markets traded higher on Monday as investors digested the key points from this year’s Munich Security Conference. The event saw several European leaders and policymakers reiterate the need for greater defense spending to accelerate the continent’s strategic autonomy, with discussions of a common nuclear shield. In corporate earnings, Airbus, Nestlé, and Renault are among the companies scheduled to report results later this week. Asian indices ended mixed as several major financial centres remained closed for the Lunar New Year holiday, resulting in thin trading activity, while weak economic data from Japan weighed on investor sentiment. Markets in China, South Korea, Taiwan, and the United States were closed, keeping activity in currencies, commodities, and bond markets largely subdued. Japan reported that its economy grew just 0.1% on an annualized basis in the December quarter, much lower than expectations, mainly due to lower government spending. The weak data highlights the challenges facing Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and may strengthen the case for additional government spending to support growth. Wall Street markets were mostly steady on Friday after January inflation data came in largely in line with expectations. The S&P 500 ended flat at 6,836.17 points. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.2%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average edged up 0.1% to 49,500.93 points. Data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that consumer prices rose 0.2% in January compared to the previous month and increased 2.4% compared to a year earlier. The inflation numbers offered only limited support to stocks, as hopes of lower interest rates were offset by ongoing concerns about the impact of artificial intelligence on businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro speculative net longs climb to two and half year high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-speculative-net-longs-climb-to-two-and-half-year-high/1678064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678064</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market climbed near a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators in the Euro futures market climbed near a two and half year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Euro futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net long position of 180305 contracts in the data reported through February 10, 2026. This was a weekly addition of 16944 net long contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rajesh Exports Q3 PAT soars 101% YoY to Rs 72 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rajesh-exports-q3-pat-soars-101-yoy-to-rs-72-cr/1678063</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678063</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income from operations climbed 143.29% YoY to Rs 2,35,098.27 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total income from operations climbed 143.29% YoY to Rs 2,35,098.27 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 65.47 crore in Q3 FY26, up 50.78% from Rs 43.42 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 143.29% to Rs 2,35,043.50 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. During the quarter, cost of raw materials consumed stood at Rs 2,34,937.05 crore, up 143.46% YoY, while employee benefits expense was at Rs 61.83 crore, up 56.29% YoY. Rajesh Exports is one of the largest manufacturers of gold products in the world. The company exports its products to various countries around the world and also supplies its products in wholesale markets and jewellery showrooms across India. Shares of Rajesh Exports tanked 4.47% to Rs 170 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RajeshExports_61299734252_13051.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brainbees Solutions slumps after Q3 net loss widens to Rs 38 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brainbees-solutions-slumps-after-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-38-cr/1678061</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678061</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations climbed 11.57% YoY to Rs 2423.63 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operations climbed 11.57% YoY to Rs 2423.63 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax increased 73.48% YoY to Rs 11.12 crore in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, the company reported exceptional items totaling Rs 16.31 crore, primarily due to labour code compliance costs of Rs 13.95 crore. This was followed by gains of Rs 1.21 crore from the impairment of intangible assets. Additionally, based on a one-off, non-recurring event, a step-down subsidiary wrote off current assets, including inventories, amounting to Rs 1.14 crore. Adjusted EBITDA jumped 11% to Rs 153.8 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA margin fell to 6.3% in Q3 FY26 as against 6.4% in Q3 FY25. On a segmental front, during the quarter, revenue from India-multi channel business climbed 8.95% YoY to Rs 1,645.76 crore, The international business posted a 6.97% YoY growth to Rs 279.59 crore and the D2C arm, Globalbees, posted a revenue of Rs 515.03 crore, registering the growth of 21.97% YoY. During the quarter, online gross merchandise value (GMV) increased 10.08% YoY to Rs 2,831 crore while offline GMV rose 7.5% YoY to Rs 593.7 crore. Average order value (AOV) rose 0.34% to Rs 2,684 in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 2,675 in Q3 FY25. Brainbees Solutions operates in the wholesale trade and contract manufacturing of maternity, baby and kids products, while also offering education and training facilitation services. The company runs its own single brand retail chain under the Babyhug label, giving it a presence across both wholesale and retail channels. Its customers range from retailers in the mother and child segment to expecting mothers, parents of children up to 12 years old, and franchise partners and institutions in the education and training sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrainbeesSolutionsLtd_65573979_68149.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prime Minister highlights transformative role of AI across diverse sectors]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prime-minister-highlights-transformative-role-of-ai-across-diverse-sectors/1678059</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678059</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi today welcomed the world leaders, captains of industry, innovators, policymakers, researchers, and technology enthusiasts from across the globe to the AI Impact Summit at Bharat Mandapam, New Delhi.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi today welcomed the world leaders, captains of industry, innovators, policymakers, researchers, and technology enthusiasts from across the globe to the AI Impact Summit at Bharat Mandapam, New Delhi. The Summit, themed “Sarvajana Hitaya, Sarvajana Sukhaya — Welfare for All, Happiness for All”, reflects India’s commitment to harnessing Artificial Intelligence for human-centric progress and inclusive development. The Prime Minister highlighted the transformative role of AI across diverse sectors including healthcare, education, agriculture, governance, and enterprise. He expressed confidence that the deliberations at the Summit will enrich global discourse on innovation, collaboration, and responsible use of AI, shaping a future that is progressive, innovative, and opportunity-driven. Prime Minister Modi underscored India’s leadership in the global AI transformation, powered by the strength of its 1.4 billion people, robust digital public infrastructure, vibrant startup ecosystem, and cutting-edge research. He emphasized that India’s strides in AI reflect both ambition and responsibility, positioning the nation at the forefront of technological advancement.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-using-tablet-computer-with-magnifying-glass-pic_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brainbees Solutions Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brainbees-solutions-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678056</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678056</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps (India) Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd and PTC India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 16 February 2026.

Shakti Pumps (India) Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd and PTC India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 16 February 2026. Brainbees Solutions Ltd lost 11.21% to Rs 239.5 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.88 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 99845 shares in the past one month. Shakti Pumps (India) Ltd tumbled 10.30% to Rs 574.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62944 shares in the past one month. Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd crashed 9.93% to Rs 358. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 81235 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19745 shares in the past one month. Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd pared 9.13% to Rs 151.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 73176 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 40848 shares in the past one month. PTC India Ltd dropped 7.49% to Rs 171.1. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.56 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrainbeesSolutionsLtd_65573979_68149.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude oil sees mild selling pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-oil-sees-mild-selling-pressure/1678057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678057</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures hovered below $63 per barrel in early electronic trading on Monday as markets closely monitored a second round of US-Iran nuclear talks scheduled in Geneva.

WTI crude oil futures hovered below $63 per barrel in early electronic trading on Monday as markets closely monitored a second round of US-Iran nuclear talks scheduled in Geneva. Hopes that renewed diplomacy could ease geopolitical risks have kept traders cautious, limiting upside momentum. Oil prices weakened further last week after comments from US President Donald Trump raised expectations of a possible deal with Tehran within the next month. Brent crude slipped around 0.5% on the week, while WTI lost about 1%, reflecting reduced risk premiums. Beyond geopolitics, prices remain pressured by ample global supply. Reports suggest some OPEC+ members see scope to resume supply hikes as early as April, while the International Energy Agency reaffirmed expectations of a sizeable oil surplus in 2026 and trimmed its demand growth outlook.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold finds support from cooling inflation, Fed bets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-finds-support-from-cooling-inflation-fed-bets/1678054</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678054</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures recouped earlier losses to trade near $5,030 per ounce, finding support from a softer US dollar amid holiday-thinned trading.

Gold futures recouped earlier losses to trade near $5,030 per ounce, finding support from a softer US dollar amid holiday-thinned trading. The dollar index hovered below 97 as subdued US inflation data reinforced expectations that the Federal Reserve may begin easing policy later this year. US headline inflation slowed to 2.4% last month, helping gold secure a second consecutive weekly gain and underpinning medium-term rate-cut expectations. In domestic trade, April gold futures on the MCX slipped below Rs 155,000 per 10 grams, easing by Rs 441. Investor focus now shifts to the release of FOMC meeting minutes, the US advance GDP estimate, and PCE inflation data for clearer signals on the timing of policy easing. Geopolitical developments, including renewed US-Iran nuclear talks and negotiations aimed at ending the war in Ukraine, also remain firmly in focus.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Arkade Developers signs cluster redevelopment deal worth Rs 700-cr GDV ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/arkade-developers-signs-cluster-redevelopment-deal-worth-rs-700-cr-gdv/1678052</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678052</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project spans a total plot area of approximately 6,553 square metres and is planned as a large-scale cluster redevelopment with an estimated gross development value (GDV) of around Rs 700 crore.

The project spans a total plot area of approximately 6,553 square metres and is planned as a large-scale cluster redevelopment with an estimated gross development value (GDV) of around Rs 700 crore. Strategically situated along SV Road, the project offers strong connectivity to key business districts, social infrastructure, and major transport corridors in Mumbai’s western suburbs. Under the proposed development, Arkade Developers will deliver a modern residential project aligned with contemporary urban living standards, while upgrading lifestyle amenities and infrastructure for existing society members. The development further strengthens the company’s presence in the western suburbs, a key focus market. This follows the recent registration of a development agreement for a redevelopment project in Goregaon West, spanning 4,640.60 square metres with a projected GDV of Rs 350 crore. With the addition of the Malad West project, the company continues to expand its redevelopment pipeline across Western Mumbai, particularly in the Goregaon–Malad micro market. Amit Jain, chairman & managing director, Arkade Developers said “Cluster redevelopment remains a core growth driver for Arkade Developers, and this project at Malad West reinforces our commitment to transforming aging housing stock into futureready residential communities. Shree Rani Sati Nagar’s strategic location and scale make it a landmark opportunity, and we are confident of creating long-term value for residents, stakeholders, and homebuyers.” Arkade Developers is a real estate development company concentrating on the development of premium aspirational lifestyle residential premises in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India’s commercial capital. The company is engaged in the development of new projects (development/construction of residential premises on land acquired by the company) and redevelopment of existing premises. The company's consolidated net profit tumbled 19.54% to Rs 40.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 45.81 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 12.42% year-on-year to Rs 196.73 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter shed 0.33% to Rs 121.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArkadeDevelopersLtd_19074284_91895.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>