<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Corona Remedies gains as Q2 PAT climbs 22% YoY to Rs 52 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/corona-remedies-gains-as-q2-pat-climbs-22-yoy-to-rs-52-cr/1663125</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663125</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 21.67% year on year (YoY) to Rs 69.78 crore in Q2 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 21.67% year on year (YoY) to Rs 69.78 crore in Q2 FY26. Earnings Before Interest, Taxes, Depreciation, and Amortization (EBITDA) stood at Rs 78.47 crore, with EBITDA margin at 21.7% in Q2 FY26. Total expenditure climbed 14.4% YoY to Rs 282.66 crore. Raw material costs declined 9.3% YoY to Rs 25.9 crore. Employee expenses rose 17.3% YoY to Rs 103 crore. Interest costs eased 32.8% YoY to Rs 1.93 crore, while depreciation inched up 1.7% YoY to Rs 9.2 crore. On Half year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 35.10% to Rs 98.52 crore on 16.92% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 707.67 crore in H1 FY26, compared with H1 FY25. Nirav K. Mehta, MD and CEO, CORONA Remedies, said: “We are delighted to report a strong financial performance in Q2 and H1 FY26. Revenues for Q2 and H1FY26 grew by 15.1% and 17.0% respectively on a Y-o-Y basis, outperforming the IPM growth. Profit after tax for Q2 and H1FY26 grew by 21.8% and 35.1% respectively on a Y-o-Y basis while maintaining healthy return ratios. Our strong performance reflects the consistency of our strategy, disciplined execution and deep focus on our core therapeutic segments. By strengthening our field force, expanding our brand portfolio and maintaining a sharp focus on specialist’s prescriptions, we have continued to outperform the market while building a sustainable platform for long-term growth. Lastly, we are grateful to our bankers for their efforts in the successful listing of CORONA on the Indian stock exchanges. I would also like to thank the entire team at CORONA and our stakeholders for their continued support and faith in our business.” Corona Remedies is an India-focused branded pharmaceutical formulation company developing, manufacturing, and marketing products in women’s healthcare, cardio-diabeto, pain management, urology and other therapeutic areas.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoronaRemediesLtd_53198342_71174.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drift lower in early trade; VIX spurts 5.84%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drift-lower-in-early-trade-vix-spurts-584/1663122</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663122</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices trade with minor losses in early trade, weighed down by declines in IT stocks that dragged the broader market lower.

The domestic equity indices trade with minor losses in early trade, weighed down by declines in IT stocks that dragged the broader market lower. The Nifty traded below the 26,000 level. IT, pharma and financial services shares declined while media, metal and realty shares advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 130.93 points or 0.15% to 85,631.08. The Nifty 50 index shed 34.75 points or 0.13% to 26,293.80. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.10%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,514 shares rose and 1,800 shares fell. A total of 221 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 5.84% to 10. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 289.80 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 677.38 crore in the Indian equity market on 01 January 2026, provisional data showed. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. Stocks in Spotlight: Avenue Supermarts (Dmart) shed 0.67%. The company’s standalone revenue from operations jumped 13% to Rs 17,612.62 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 15,565.23 crore in Q3 FY25. Jammu & Kashmir Bank added 2.28% after the bank’s gross advances jumped 17.26% to Rs 1,16,247.92 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 99,133.35 crore as of 31 December 2024. Punjab National Bank (PNB) rallied 2.13% after the bank’s domestic deposits increased 8.32% to Rs 15,97,487 crore as of 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 14,74,760 crore posted on 31 December 2024. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.39% to 6.648 compared with previous session close of 6.609. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2350 compared with its close of 90.2050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement added 1.16% to Rs 137,344. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.36% to 98.77. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.05% to 4.189. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 5 cents or 0.08% to $60.70 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market began the first full trading week of 2026 on a stronger note after the U.S. said it had attacked Venezuela and captured President Nicolas Maduro over the weekend. Oil prices edged lower as markets weighed the potential impact of geopolitical tensions. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. Oil prices fell after the escalation involving the oil-rich nation. Brent crude prices slipped more than 1% earlier before paring losses, and were last trading 0.25% lower, while the West Texas Intermediate crude prices fell 0.4%. On Friday stateside, the first trading day of 2026, the S&P 500 closed slightly higher as gains in semiconductor names kept the index afloat. The benchmark closed up 0.19% at 6,858.47, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.03% to finish at 23,235.63. The two had been solidly positive earlier in the day, with the S&P 500 and the tech-heavy Nasdaq trading higher by 0.7% and 1.5% at their peaks, respectively. The Dow Jones Industrial Average moved up 319.10 points, or 0.66%, to settle at 48,382.39.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR stays battered beyond Rs 90/$ mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-stays-battered-beyond-rs-90-mark/1663123</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663123</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee continues to stay battered beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark on Monday as dollar moved a tad higher, extending gains for a fifth consecutive session after the U.S.

The Indian rupee continues to stay battered beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark on Monday as dollar moved a tad higher, extending gains for a fifth consecutive session after the U.S. attacked Venezuela and captured its president, Nicolas Maduro. Muted local equities also added pressure on the counter. INR opened at Rs 90.21 per dollar and fell to a low of 90.50 so far during the day. Rupee slipped below the 90-mark and settled the day lower by 22 paise at 90.20 against the US dollar on Friday, amid disappointing macroeconomic data and strengthening of the American currency in overseas markets. Persistent foreign fund outflows and strong dollar demand from importers further dented investor sentiment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Bank’s avg deposits climb 12% YoY in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-banks-avg-deposits-climb-12-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663121</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663121</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank’s average CASA deposits were Rs 8,98,400 crore for the December 2025 quarter, a growth of around 9.9% over Rs 8,17,600 for the corresponding December 2024 period.

The bank’s average CASA deposits were Rs 8,98,400 crore for the December 2025 quarter, a growth of around 9.9% over Rs 8,17,600 for the corresponding December 2024 period. The bank’s average time deposits were Rs 18,53,900 crore for the December 2025 quarter, a growth of around 13.4% over Rs 16,35,200 crore for the corresponding December 2024 period. The bank’s average advances under management (advances grossing up for inter-bank participation certificates, bills rediscounted and securitisation / assignment) were Rs 28,63,900 crore for the December 2025 quarter, a growth of around 9.0% over Rs 26,27,600 crore for the corresponding December 2024 period. In December 2025, the bank’s period-end deposits increased 11.5% year-on-year to Rs 28,59,500 crore, while end-period CASA deposits rose 10.1% year-on-year to Rs 9,61,000 crore. The bank’s period end time deposits jumped 12.3% to Rs 18,98,500 crore as of 31st December 2025, registering the growth of 12.3% compared with Rs 16,91,100 crore as of 31st December 2024. HDFC Bank is India's largest private sector lender. As of 30 September 2025, the bank's distribution network was at 9,545 branches and 21,417 ATMs across 4,156 cities / towns. In addition, the bank has 15,253 business correspondents, which are primarily manned by common service centres (CSC). The bank reported a 10.8% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 18,640 crore on a 10.3% increase in net revenue to Rs 45,900 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The counter declined 1.13% to Rs 989.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCBank_24534281400_4987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Avenue Supermarts’ Q3 revenue climbs 13% YoY to Rs 17,613 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avenue-supermarts-q3-revenue-climbs-13-yoy-to-rs-17613-cr/1663120</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663120</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total number of stores as of 31st December 2025 stood at 442 (including one store at Sanpada, Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra currently closed for customers due to reconstruction).

The total number of stores as of 31st December 2025 stood at 442 (including one store at Sanpada, Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra currently closed for customers due to reconstruction). Avenue Supermarts is a Mumbai-based company, which owns and operates D-Mart stores. D-Mart is a national supermarket chain that offers customers a range of home and personal products under one roof. It offers a wide range of products with a focus on foods, non-foods (FMCG) and general merchandise & apparel product categories. On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit jumped 3.85% to Rs 685.01 crore on a 15.45% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 16,676.30 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip fell 1.40% to settle at Rs 3,668.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AvenueSupermartsLtd_68548819828_40942.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd Surges 2.27%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-petroleum-corporation-ltd-surges-227/1663112</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663112</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd gained 2.27% today to trade at Rs 507.

Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd gained 2.27% today to trade at Rs 507. The BSE Oil & Gas index is up 0.36% to quote at 29015.56. The index is up 3.82 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd increased 0.97% and Indian Oil Corporation Ltd added 0.93% on the day. The BSE Oil & Gas index went up 8.19 % over last one year compared to the 8.1% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd has added 12.59% over last one month compared to 3.82% gain in BSE Oil & Gas index and 0.08% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 14620 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 1.23 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 507.6 on 05 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 287.55 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HPCL_59291502793_2305.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Orient Technologies Ltd Falls 1.73%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/orient-technologies-ltd-falls-173/1663113</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663113</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Orient Technologies Ltd lost 1.73% today to trade at Rs 439.4.

Orient Technologies Ltd lost 1.73% today to trade at Rs 439.4. The BSE Information Technology index is down 0.29% to quote at 37029.35. The index is down 0.9 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Datamatics Global Services Ltd decreased 1.67% and HCL Technologies Ltd lost 1.38% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 15.22 % over last one year compared to the 8.1% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Orient Technologies Ltd has added 28.52% over last one month compared to 0.9% fall in BSE Information Technology index and 0.08% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 3.27 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 7.89 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 613 on 20 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 267.5 on 18 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OrientTechnologiesLtd_43426305_92883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves rise by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-rise-by-329-billion-to-69661-billion/1663102</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663102</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2.

India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-2891849__340_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests flat opening for equites; oil prices in focus after US captures Venezuela President Maduro ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-flat-opening-for-equites-oil-prices-in-focus-after-us-captures-venezuela-president-maduro/1663099</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663099</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 5.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 5.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) bought shares worth Rs 289.80 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 677.38 crore in the Indian equity market on 01 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 2,978.80 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market began the first full trading week of 2026 on a stronger note after the U.S. said it had attacked Venezuela and captured President Nicolas Maduro over the weekend. Oil prices edged lower as markets weighed the potential impact of geopolitical tensions. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. Oil prices fell after the escalation involving the oil-rich nation. Brent crude prices slipped more than 1% earlier before paring losses, and were last trading 0.25% lower, while the West Texas Intermediate crude prices fell 0.4%. On Friday stateside, the first trading day of 2026, the S&P 500 closed slightly higher as gains in semiconductor names kept the index afloat. The benchmark closed up 0.19% at 6,858.47, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.03% to finish at 23,235.63. The two had been solidly positive earlier in the day, with the S&P 500 and the tech-heavy Nasdaq trading higher by 0.7% and 1.5% at their peaks, respectively. The Dow Jones Industrial Average moved up 319.10 points, or 0.66%, to settle at 48,382.39. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks powered higher on Friday, with the Nifty vaulting past the 26,300 mark after scaling a fresh record high in late trade. Market sentiment stayed buoyant throughout the session as strong Q3 corporate business updates fuelled earnings optimism and sparked broad-based buying. Auto and metal stocks led the rally, while FMCG and IT shares lagged, capping gains at the index level. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 573.41 points or 0.67% to 85,762.01. The Nifty 50 index climbed 182 points or 0.70% to 26,328.55.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Dmart, Mahindra & Mahindra, Jammu & Kashmir Bank, PNB, V2 Retail]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-dmart-mahindra-mahindra-jammu-kashmir-bank-pnb-v2-retail/1663097</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663097</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) are banned from F&O trading on 5 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) are banned from F&O trading on 5 January 2026. Stocks to Watch: Oil companies will be in focus following US attacks on Venezuela, as potential volatility in crude oil prices could impact the sector. Avenue Supermarts (Dmart)’s standalone revenue from operations jumped 13% to Rs 17,612.62 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 15,565.23 crore in Q3 FY25. Jammu & Kashmir Bank's gross advances jumped 17.26% to Rs 1,16,247.92 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 99,133.35 crore as of 31 December 2024. Punjab National Bank (PNB) domestic deposits increased 8.32% to Rs 15,97,487 crore as of 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 14,74,760 crore posted on 31 December 2024. Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services has reported overall disbursements of around Rs 17,600 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 7% year-on-year growth. Union Bank of India has reported a 7.42% rise in domestic advances to Rs 9,80,643 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 9,42,273 crore posted as of 31 December 2025. Corona Remedies reported a 21.75% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 52.32 crore on 15.05% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 361.13 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. V2 Retail reported strong operational momentum in the December quarter, driven by aggressive network expansion and its continued transition from a regional player to a national retail footprint. Standalone revenue rose 57% year-on-year to Rs 927 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 591 crore in the year-ago period, Bank of India reported a 12.50% YoY increase in global business to Rs 16,27,098 crore as of 31 December 2025. Global deposits stood at Rs 8,87,287 crore, reflecting an 11.64% YoY increase. Domestic deposits rose 12.80% YoY to Rs 7,65,500 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 6,78,626 crore a year earlier.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lokesh Machines bags Rs 22-cr order from Ministry of Defence]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lokesh-machines-bags-rs-22-cr-order-from-ministry-of-defence/1663096</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663096</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order involves the supply of 9×19 mm machine pistol sub-assemblies/components.

According to an exchange filing, the order involves the supply of 9×19 mm machine pistol sub-assemblies/components. The total value of the order stands at Rs 22,00,46,400 and it is to be executed on or before 19 March 2026. The company clarified that none of the promoters, promoter-group, or group companies have any interest in the entity awarding the order. It also stated that the order does not fall within related-party transactions. Lokesh Machines is engaged in the business of manufacture of special purpose machines (SPM), general purpose machines/CNC lathes (GPM), connecting rods and machining of cylinder blocks and heads. On a standalone basis, Lokesh Machines' net profit declined 81.74% to Rs 0.63 crore while net sales declined 33.05% to Rs 50.43 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. The counter shed 0.62% to Rs 169.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LokeshMach_84321725333_13320.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>