<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:36:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bankers assessed higher loan demand from most of the sectors of the economy during Q3:2025-26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bankers-assessed-higher-loan-demand-from-most-of-the-sectors-of-the-economy-during-q32025-26/1673196</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673196</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank released the results of 34th round of its quarterly Bank Lending Survey (BLS), which captures qualitative assessment and expectations of major scheduled commercial banks on credit parameters (viz., loan demand as well as terms and conditions of loans) for major economic sectors2.

Reserve Bank released the results of 34th round of its quarterly Bank Lending Survey (BLS), which captures qualitative assessment and expectations of major scheduled commercial banks on credit parameters (viz., loan demand as well as terms and conditions of loans) for major economic sectors2. The latest round of the survey, which was conducted during Q3:2025-26, collected senior loan officers’ assessment of credit parameters for Q3:2025-26 and their expectations for Q4:2025-26 and Q1, Q2 of 2026-27. Bankers assessed higher loan demand from most of the sectors of the economy during Q3:2025-26 as compared to the previous quarter. Majority of the responding bankers indicated easier loan terms and conditions. Bankers’ outlook on overall loan demand improved for Q4:2025-26, mainly driven by manufacturing, infrastructure, services, and retail/personal loans sectors. Overall, easy terms and conditions for loans are expected to prevail during the quarter. Responding bankers continue to expect increased loan demand and easier loan terms and conditions from all major sectors till Q2:2026-27.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Capacity utilisation in manufacturing sector increased marginally, says RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/capacity-utilisation-in-manufacturing-sector-increased-marginally-says-rbi/1673195</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673195</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank released the results of its 71st round of the quarterly Order Books, Inventories, and Capacity Utilisation Survey (OBICUS), which was conducted during Q3:2025-26 and covered 1,114 manufacturing companies.

Reserve Bank released the results of its 71st round of the quarterly Order Books, Inventories, and Capacity Utilisation Survey (OBICUS), which was conducted during Q3:2025-26 and covered 1,114 manufacturing companies. The survey provides a snapshot of the demand conditions in India’s manufacturing sector during July-September 2025. At the aggregate level, capacity utilisation (CU) in the manufacturing sector increased marginally to 74.3 per cent in Q2:2025-26 from 74.1 per cent in the previous quarter. However, the seasonally adjusted CU (CU-SA) declined by 100 basis points from the previous quarter and stood at 74.8 per cent in Q2:2025-26. Both CU and CU-SA for Q2:2025-26 increased by 10 basis points as compared to their levels in the corresponding quarter of the previous year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id5822566_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI says urban consumer confidence for current period changed marginally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-says-urban-consumer-confidence-for-current-period-changed-marginally/1673194</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673194</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank released the results of January 2026 round of its bi-monthly urban consumer confidence survey (UCCS).

Reserve Bank released the results of January 2026 round of its bi-monthly urban consumer confidence survey (UCCS). The survey collects current perceptions (vis-à-vis a year ago) and one year ahead expectations of households on general economic situation, employment scenario, overall price situation, own income and spending. The latest round of the survey was conducted during January 2-11, 2026, covering 5,933 respondents across 19 major cities. Consumer confidence for the current period changed marginally - the Current Situation Index (CSI) stood at 98.1 vis-à-vis 98.4 in the previous round. Consumer confidence for the year ahead ticked downward, owing mainly to lower expectations on general economic conditions, income and price level compared to the previous round. Thus, the Future Expectations Index (FEI), though in the optimistic zone, dropped by 2.2 points to 123.4.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/shopping-cart-2-1546163_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Inflation data, currency trends and employment data to remain in focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inflation-data-currency-trends-and-employment-data-to-remain-in-focus/1673193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673193</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian markets head into the trading week on a cautiously constructive note, anchored by supportive monetary and trade developments.

Indian markets head into the trading week on a cautiously constructive note, anchored by supportive monetary and trade developments. The Reserve Bank of India’s Monetary Policy Committee held the repo rate at 5.25% and maintained a neutral stance, reinforcing stability after recent volatility. This helped the Sensex rise nearly 266 points and the Nifty close above 25,650, while the rupee logged its strongest weekly gain in over three years, underpinned by optimism around new trade pacts. Investor sentiment was also boosted by the India–US trade deal, which spurred a powerful relief rally in early February. However, global risk-off pressures persisted, with tech stocks underperforming amid sell-offs in the U.S. and AI-related volatility spilling into Asian markets. Given this backdrop, prominent large-cap counters and export-linked sectors could remain in focus, with investors closely watching liquidity conditions, currency trends, and corporate earnings momentum. In India, the M3 Money Supply figures for the week ended on January 23 would be made public on Wednesday (11 February 2026). Money Supply M3 in India increased to 322144.23 INR Billion in the week ending December 31 from 246833.33 INR Billion two weeks before. On Thursday (12 February 2026), the Inflation Rate for the month of January 2026 would be made public. The consumer price inflation rate in India rose to 1.33% in December of 2025 from 0.71% in the earlier month, extending the normalization from the record low of 0.25% in October. Despite the second consecutive increase, the inflation rate remained sharply below the Reserve Bank of India's tolerance limit of 2%-6%. On Friday (12 February 2026), the wholesale price inflation (WPI) figures would be announced. India’s wholesale prices increased 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, rebounding from a 0.32% drop recorded in November. This marked the first increase in three months and the fastest pace since April, mainly supported by faster rises in manufacturing prices. Lastly, the foreign exchange reserves position for the week ended on February 06 would be unveiled on the same day. Foreign Exchange Reserves in India increased to $709,410 million in January 23 from $701,360 million in the previous week. In China, the inflation rate for January 2026 would be made public on Wednesday (11 February 2026). China’s annual inflation rate edged higher to 0.8% in December 2025 from 0.7% in the prior month, marking the highest level since February 2023. Wednesday would also see the release of the producer price inflation numbers for the month of January. China’s producer prices fell 1.9% year-on-year in December 2025, easing from a 2.2% decline in November and extending the contraction to a 39th consecutive month. On Friday (13 February 2026), the House Price Index data for January 2026 would be unveiled. China’s new home prices across 70 cities declined 2.7% year-on-year in December 2025, steeper than a 2.4% drop in the previous month. In the United States, the retail sales data for the month of December would be announced on Tuesday (10 February 2026). US retail sales rose 0.6% month-on-month in November 2025, the largest gain since July, rebounding from a revised 0.1% decline in October. On Wednesday (11 February 2026), the API Crude Oil Stock Change for the week ended on February 06 would be unveiled. US crude oil inventories plunged by 11.1 million barrels in the week ended January 30th, 2025, extending a 0.25 million-barrel draw in the prior week. The Non Farm Payrolls data for the month of January would also be announced on Wednesday. The US economy added 50K payrolls in December 2025, less than a downwardly revised 56K in November. Wednesday would also see the release of the unemployment rate for January 2026. The US unemployment rate edged down to 4.4% in December 2025, from a revised 4.5% in November, which had marked the highest level since October 2021. On Thursday (12 February 2026), the existing home sales data for January 2026 would be made public. Existing home sales in the United States surged by 5.1% from the previous month to an annualized rate of 4.35 million in December of 2025. Lastly on Friday (13 February 2026), the inflation rate for the month of January would be announced. The annual inflation rate in the US remained at 2.7% in December 2025, the same as in November.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee sheds around 30 paise against US dollar]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-sheds-around-30-paise-against-us-dollar/1673149</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673149</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee softened today as the US dollar stayed steady and local equities witnessed flat moves.

Indian Rupee softened today as the US dollar stayed steady and local equities witnessed flat moves. INR shed 32 paise to trade at 90.66 per US dollar, easing from near four-week high. The key equity benchmarks ended with minor gains today. The Nifty settled above the 25,650 mark. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the key policy rate - repo rate unchanged at 5.25%. The RBI has also revised GDP growth forecast for the ongoing financial year to 7.4% from 7.3% today. Real GDP growth for Q1 FY27 has also been revised to 6.9% from 6.7% and Q2 to 7% from 6.8%, with risks evenly balanced. On NSE, USD/INR futures closed up 0.32% at 92.71.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-markets-currency-trading-concept-picture-id609801990_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee sheds tears]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-sheds-tears/1673130</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673130</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.7125 per Dollar on Friday (06 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.4100 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures falls near one-week low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-copper-futures-falls-near-one-week-low/1673128</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673128</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures fell near one-week low today as risk appetite was tepid ahead of the weekend.

COMEX Copper futures fell near one-week low today as risk appetite was tepid ahead of the weekend. In Asia, Shanghai Composite index eased 0.25%. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index fell 1.20%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index cut recent losses and added 0.89%. European stocks edged up modestly. US tech counters fell further yesterday. The tech-heavy Nasdaq tumbled to its lowest closing level in over two months. COMEX Copper futures are under stress this week following the break under $6 per pound and currently trade at $5.81 per pound, down 0.16% on the day. The metal has lost around 2% this week, giving up some of the 4% rise in last month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/closeup-of-blue-chart-growth-progress-picture-id177428264_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end with decent gains amid budget boost & US trade deal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-with-decent-gains-amid-budget-boost-us-trade-deal/1673101</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673101</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks ended a volatile week with significant gains, as investors weighed the implications of the Union Budget 2026 and the India-US trade deal.

Domestic equity benchmarks ended a volatile week with significant gains, as investors weighed the implications of the Union Budget 2026 and the India-US trade deal. Initial sharp losses on Sunday due to higher STT on derivatives and other tax changes were offset by strong buying from Monday onwards, supported by robust infrastructure capex, fiscal consolidation measures, and foreign investment-friendly policies. The rally extended midweek, before profit booking trimmed some gains on Thursday, with minor advances on Friday helping indices close the week on a positive note. Overall, markets balanced short-term concerns with optimism on long-term growth, stable RBI policy, and strengthened trade ties. In the week ended on Friday, 06 February 2025, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 1,310.62 points or 1.59% to settle at 83,580.40. The Nifty 50 index rallied 373.05 points or 1.47% to settle at 25,693.70. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index fell 0.11% to close at 16,065.48. The BSE 250 Small-Cap index declined 0.42% to close at 6,311.44. Weekly Index Movement: The benchmark equity indices witnessed a sharp sell-off during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of the Union Budget 2026 by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,546 points or 1.88% to 80,722.94. The Nifty 50 index dropped 495.20 points or 1.96% to 24,825.45. Equity benchmarks staged a sharp comeback on Monday, breaking a two-session slide as investors weighed the union budget's implications for market sentiment and capital flows. The S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 943.52 points or 1.17% to 81,666.46. The Nifty 50 index jumped 262.95 points or 1.06% to 25,088.40. In the past two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.73% while the Nifty fell 0.91%. The key equity benchmarks ended sharply higher on Tuesday, rising for a second straight session on strong buying interest. The S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 2,072.67 points or 2.54% to 83,739.13. The Nifty 50 index added 639.15 points or 2.55% to 25,727.55. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.74% while the Nifty gained 3.63%. The key equity benchmarks eked out modest gains Wednesday, extending their rally to a third straight session. Sentiment remained supported by the landmark India-US trade agreement. The S&P BSE Sensex added 78.56 points or 0.09% to 83,817.69. The Nifty 50 index rose 48.45 points or 0.19% to 25,776. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.83% while the Nifty jumped 3.82%. The key equity benchmarks closed deep in the red on Thursday, breaking a three-day winning streak as investors locked in profits at stretched valuations. The S&P BSE Sensex slumped 503.76 points or 0.60% to 83,313.93. The Nifty 50 index fell 133.20 points or 0.52% to 25,642.80. Over the past three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex advanced 3.20%, while the Nifty gained 3.29%. The key equity benchmarks ended with minor gains on Friday. The S&P BSE Sensex added 266.47 points or 0.32% to 83,580.40. The Nifty 50 index rose 50.90 points or 0.20% to 25,693.70. Union Budget 2026: Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman used the Union Budget 2026 to underline a reform-heavy path built around fiscal consolidation, job creation and sharper global competitiveness. The Centre reiterated its medium-term debt sustainability goal, with the FRBM roadmap indicating a steady decline in the debt-to-GDP ratio and projecting central government debt at around 55.6% in BE 2026-27 versus 56.1% in RE 2025-26, framing the glide towards a sub 50% target by 2030 as a policy anchor rather than a hard statutory number. On the deficit side, the government stuck to its consolidation track, with the fiscal gap seen at 4.4% of GDP in RE FY26 and budgeted to narrow to 4.3% in BE FY27, a sequence that keeps the post pandemic promises on course while still giving room for capex-driven growth. On the expenditure and borrowing front, the Budget raised capital expenditure to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore for FY27, signalling another year of heavy public investment in infrastructure, especially in emerging tier 2 and tier 3 growth centres that are starting to look more like mini metros than satellite towns. To fund the gap, the Centre plans net market borrowing of Rs 11.54 lakh crore through dated securities, with the balance coming from small savings and other sources, in line with the glide path indicated in the Budget 2025 26 speech. That combination—slower deficit, still high capex and a calibrated borrowing programme—is meant to keep bond yields contained while nudging the baton from public to private capex over the medium term. Markets, however, zeroed in on the tax tweaks. On the indirect side, the Finance Bill, 2026 sharply increased the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives: STT on futures goes up from 0.02% to 0.05% of the traded value, while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium (and from 0.125% to 0.15% when options are exercised). That makes high-churn F&O strategies more expensive at the margin and nudges some speculative volume off the table, even as it modestly boosts revenue. On the direct tax side, the Income-tax Act, 2025 is slated to take full effect from 1 April 2026, with fresh slab structures, harmonised surcharge rules and a cleaned up TDS/TCS and penalty framework, all aimed at reducing litigation and making the law more “plain English” for taxpayers. The Budget also delivered compliance relief via Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rationalisation under the LRS and travel bucket. TCS on overseas tour packages has been pared down to a flat 2%, replacing the earlier structure that included higher 5–20% slabs and thresholds. Similarly, TCS on remittances under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme for education and medical treatment drops to 2% from 5%, with a higher trigger threshold, easing the cash flow pinch on families sending children abroad or paying for medical procedures. Alongside, the Bill tightens the architecture for revised and updated returns—allowing revised returns up to the end of the assessment year (or 12 months in the new Act), with a modest fee if filed late—while keeping the extended “updated return” window of up to four years, albeit at a steep additional tax to discourage strategic under reporting. For cross border and enforcement issues, the Budget has carved out a targeted Foreign Assets of Small Taxpayers Disclosure Scheme, 2026. The scheme ring fences smaller cases—undisclosed foreign assets and income up to defined ceilings—into a one time, time bound window where taxpayers can come clean by paying 30% tax plus a 100% penalty on that tax on previously untaxed foreign assets or income, or a flat Rs 1 lakh fee in benign cases where foreign assets bought out of already taxed income were not reported in the foreign asset schedule. In return, declarants get immunity from further tax, penalty and prosecution under the Black Money Act on the declared items. The exact opening and closing dates will be notified separately, but the policy signal is clear: clean up small legacy foreign asset issues before the information exchange net tightens further. On the business tax side, several structural tweaks stand out. First, supply of manpower is now explicitly included in the statutory definition of “work” for TDS purposes, putting manpower contracts clearly under the contractor TDS net at the familiar 1%-2% slabs depending on the payer’s status. Second, the Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) regime has been recalibrated. To encourage companies to shift to the new regime, set-off of brought forward MAT credit to be allowed to companies only in the new regime. Set-off using available MAT credit to be allowed to an extent of 1/4th of the tax liability in the new regime. MAT is proposed to be made final tax. There will be no further credit accumulation from 1st April 2026. The rate of final tax to be reduced to 14% from the current MAT rate of 15%. The brought forward MAT credit of taxpayers accumulated till 31st March 2026, will continue to be available to them for set-off as above. For non-resident and digital economy players, the government has doubled down on India as a data and cloud hub. Any foreign company that provides cloud services to customers globally by using data centre services from India to be provided Tax holiday till 2047. A safe harbour of 15% on cost to be provided if the company providing data centre services from India is a related entity. A safe harbour to non-residents for component warehousing in a bonded warehouse at a profit margin of 2% of the invoice value. The resultant tax of about 0.7 percent will be much lower than in competing jurisdictions. Exemption from income tax for 5 years to be provided to any non-resident who provides capital goods, equipment or tooling, to any toll manufacturer in a bonded zone. Exemption to global (non-India sourced) income of a non-resident expert, for a stay period of 5 years under notified schemes. Exemption from Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) to all non-residents who pay tax on presumptive basis. The Budget also rationalises a few smaller but high friction levies. On the collection side, TCS rate for sellers of specific goods namely alcoholic liquor, scrap and minerals will be rationalized to 2% and that on tendu leaves will be reduced from 5% to 2%. On capital markets, the long criticised buyback tax is being redesigned. Buyback for all types of shareholders to be taxed as capital gains. Promoters to pay an additional buyback tax, making effective tax 22% for corporate promoters and 30% for non-corporate promoters. Beyond taxes, the Budget leans hard into manufacturing, logistics and services as growth engines. Customs schedules have been overhauled to remove rate clutter, cut or eliminate basic customs duty on a basket of critical minerals and components for electronics, clean tech, batteries, telecom and shipping, and amend rates for shipbuilding, airports and select agri linked products, all with an eye on domestic value addition and supply chain resilience. Infrastructure plans—from PPP pipelines, a new asset monetisation plan and multimodal connectivity under PM Gati Shakti to continued support for Jal Jeevan, urban challenge funds and maritime corridors—are meant to keep the public investment cycle humming even as the deficit comes down. On the services and social side, the government has layered in measures such as a fresh Rs 10,000 crore fund of funds for startups, expanded skilling and research allocations, and sector specific pushes in tourism, medical tourism and urban livelihoods, framing the entire package as an attempt to deliver both hard infrastructure growth and more inclusive, employment rich development. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the key policy rate—repo rate—unchanged at 5.25%. Headline inflation during November and December remained below the tolerance band of the inflation target. The revised outlook for CPI inflation in Q1 and Q2 of next year, at 4% and 4.2%, respectively, is revised slightly upwards, said RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra. The Indian economy continues on a steady, improving trajectory, with real GDP poised to register significant higher growth of 7.4% this year, as compared to the previous year, amidst global headwinds, the governor noted. Going forward, economic activity is expected to hold up well in the next year, he added. Economy: India’s manufacturing activity recovered in January after losing momentum in December, though business confidence weakened. The HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rose to 55.4 in January from a two-year low of 55.0 in December, remaining well above the 50-mark that separates expansion from contraction. The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Services PMI rose to 58.5 in January from 58.0 in December. The flash score was 59.3. A score above 50.0 indicates expansion. The composite output index rose to 58.4 in January from December's 11-month low of 57.8, indicating that the latest sharp rate of expansion in the Indian private sector was boosted by stronger growth at goods producers as well as service providers. Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Auto fell 0.68%. The company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles rose 5.7%. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 3,486 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with a net profit of Rs 5,406 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. Bajaj Finance jumped 5.49%. The company reported a 6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,977.85 crore despite 17.63% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 21,213.89 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharti Airtel rose 3.57%. The company reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Data Patterns (India) rallied 1.96%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 30.54% to Rs 58.30 crore on a 47.92% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 173.13 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. Hitachi Energy India surged 16.27%. The company’s standalone net profit soared 90.29% to Rs 261.42 crore on 27.71% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2021.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Power Company shed 0.23%. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 25.1% to Rs 771.98 crore on 9.37% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 13,948.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. One Mobikwik Systems surged 10.48%. The company reported a profitable December quarter, driven by strong execution across its payments and financial services businesses and sharp operating discipline. On a consolidated basis, Mobikwik posted a net profit of Rs 4.05 crore in Q3 December 2025, reversing a loss of Rs 55.28 crore in Q3 December 2024 and a loss of Rs 28.62 crore in Q2 September 2025. Total income rose 8.29% YoY and 6.40% QoQ to Rs 297.22 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Ather Energy surged 13.61%. The company delivered its strongest-ever quarter performance, with robust growth in market share and revenue alongside a sharp narrowing of EBITDA losses. On a standalone basis, the company reported a net loss of Rs 84.60 crore in Q3 December 2025, narrowing sharply from a loss of Rs 197.80 crore in Q3 December 2024 and lower than the Rs 154.10 crore loss in Q2 September 2025. Bajaj Housing Finance rose 0.48%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 21.32% to Rs 664.89 crore on a 17.8% increase in total income to Rs 2,886.04 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Gokaldas Exports surged 41.82%. The company reported 70.97% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 14.61 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 50.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations shed 0.92% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 978.65 crore during the quarter. Global Markets: The German retail sales rose 0.1% month-on-month in December, reversing a 0.5% decline in the previous month. Euro zone inflation cooled to 1.7% in January, flash data from statistics agency Eurostat showed Wednesday. Core inflation, which excludes more volatile energy, food, alcohol and tobacco prices, stood at 2.2% in January, a touch down from the 2.3% seen in the year to December. The key inflation rate has now dipped below the European Central Bank’s 2% target. It’s likely to steer clear of any more rate cuts for the foreseeable future. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI, compiled by S&P Global, edged up to 50.3 in January from 50.1 in December. Since readings above 50 signal expansion and those below indicate contraction, the latest print points to a modest improvement. It was also the strongest showing since October, when the index stood at 50.6. ADP on Wednesday released its monthly look at private payroll growth for January, which showed an increase of just 22,000 on the month after a downwardly revised 37,000 increase in December.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dee Development bags Rs 90-cr windmill tower order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dee-development-bags-rs-90-cr-windmill-tower-order/1673082</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673082</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is scheduled for execution from May 2026 to January 2027.

The project is scheduled for execution from May 2026 to January 2027. DEE Development Engineers (DDEL) is an engineering company providing specialized process piping solutions for industries such as oil and gas, power (including nuclear), process industries, and chemicals through engineering, procurement, and manufacturing services. The company reported a 20.1% year-on-year drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.80 crore, despite a 39.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 270 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of DEE Development Engineers rose 1.89% to close at Rs 212.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DeeDevelopmentEngineersLtd_25916295_34369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Late buying powers benchmarks higher as RBI steadies sentiment]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/late-buying-powers-benchmarks-higher-as-rbi-steadies-sentiment/1673098</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673098</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks clawed back a portion of the previous session’s losses in a choppy trade on February 6 as confidence returned after the central bank’s policy verdict met expectations.

The domestic equity benchmarks clawed back a portion of the previous session’s losses in a choppy trade on February 6 as confidence returned after the central bank’s policy verdict met expectations. The Reserve Bank of India’s Monetary Policy Committee unanimously held the repo rate steady at 5.25% and maintained a neutral stance, helping steady investor nerves. Indices opened on a soft note amid weak Asian cues but staged a firm mid-session rebound, with aggressive buying in the final hour propelling indices to close near the day's highs. The Nifty reclaimed ground above the 25,650 mark, powered by strong gains in FMCG, consumer durables and private banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex added 266.47 points or 0.32% to 83,580.40. The Nifty 50 index rose 50.90 points or 0.20% to 25,693.70. ITC (up 5.21%), Bajaj Finance (up 1.79%) and Bharti Airtel (up 1.54%) supported the Nifty today. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.11% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.42%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,925 shares rose and 2,263 shares fell. A total of 183 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.86% to 11.94. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the repo rate unchanged at 5.25%. Headline inflation during November and December remained below the tolerance band of the inflation target. The revised outlook for CPI inflation in Q1 and Q2 of next year, at 4% and 4.2%, respectively, is revised slightly upwards, said RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra. The Indian economy continues on a steady, improving trajectory, with real GDP poised to register significant higher growth of 7.4% this year, as compared to the previous year, amidst global headwinds, the governor noted. Going forward, economic activity is expected to hold up well in the next year, he added. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper added 1.58% to 6.756 compared with previous session close of 6.651. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6700 compared with its close of 90.3400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.50% to Rs 152,830. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.17% to 97.80. The United States 10-year bond yield dropped 0.40% to 4.191. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 46 cents or 0.68% to $68.01 a barrel. Global market: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently up by 144 points, signaling a strong opening for US stocks today. European shares advanced while Asian indices ended lower on Friday, following the tech-driven sell-off on Wall Street. South Korea's market, which is heavily weighted in favor of companies in the chip and automotive industries, has seen sharp swings in the past week as sentiment over tech stocks sours. Pharmaceutical stocks in Japan also slumped on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled his website offering discounted prescription medicines. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 1.20% to close at 48,908.72, while the S&P 500 lost 1.23% declined to 6,798.40, pushing it into negative territory for the year. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite posted the biggest decline, tumbling 1.59% to end at 22,540.59. Tech giant Alphabet came under pressure after reporting fourth-quarter results and flagging a sharp rise in artificial intelligence spending, with capital expenditure totaling $185 billion for 2026. Qualcomm slid more than 8% after posting a weaker forecast because of a global memory shortage. Stocks in Spotlight: Shares of cigarette makers surged on bargain buying, with ITC jumping 5.21% and Godfrey Phillips India rallying 9.69%. A domestic brokerage said the worst appears to be behind for cigarette stocks, citing sharp price hikes that underline strong pricing power. The brokerage expects companies to roll out two to three staggered price increases over the coming months to offset the impact of higher taxes. Separately, an international brokerage noted that cigarette stocks are in a heavily sold zone and now offer comfort on valuations. Hitachi Energy India surged 14.30% after the company’s standalone net profit soared 90.29% to Rs 261.42 crore on 27.71% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2021.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles declined 1.14% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 3,486 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with a net profit of Rs 5,406 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) jumped 7.28% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed surged 142.38% to Rs 63.31 crore on a 26.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2873.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharti Airtel rose 2.32%. The company reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Data Patterns (India) rallied 7.78% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 30.54% to Rs 58.30 crore on a 47.92% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 173.13 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. BEML dropped 7.59% after the company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 22.38 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net profit of Rs 24.41 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations climbed 23.69% YoY to Rs 1083.27 crore during the quarter. Kriti Industries (India) rose 1.57% after the company’s consolidated net loss narrowed sharply to Rs 0.47 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 10.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales declined 35.3% YoY to Rs 135.79 crore during the quarter. Pitti Engineering declined 4.12% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 29.61% QoQ to Rs 28.22 crore despite a flat 0.06% decline in net sales to Rs 477.42 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit fell by 1.9%, despite a 15% increase in net sales in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. NCC added 3.03% after the company reported 36.60% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 122.46 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 193.18 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 8.91% YoY to Rs 4,868.29 crore during the third quarter of FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concepts-picture-id519261614_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1673069</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673069</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITC, Kaynes Technology India and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles were the top-traded contracts.

ITC, Kaynes Technology India and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles were the top-traded contracts. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,729.80, a premium of 36.1 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,693.70 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index rose 50.90 points or 0.20% to 25,693.70. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.86% to 11.94. ITC, Kaynes Technology India and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end with small gains; Nifty ends above 25,650 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-with-small-gains-nifty-ends-above-25650-mark/1672963</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672963</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with minor gains today, navigating the Union Budget, the India–US trade deal, an Anthropic AI–led shock to IT stocks, and the Reserve Bank of India’s repo rate policy.

The key equity benchmarks ended with minor gains today, navigating the Union Budget, the India–US trade deal, an Anthropic AI–led shock to IT stocks, and the Reserve Bank of India’s repo rate policy. The Nifty settled above the 25,650 mark. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex added 266.47 points or 0.32% to 83,580.40. The Nifty 50 index rose 50.90 points or 0.20% to 25,693.70. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.11% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.42%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.86% to 11.94. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty FMCG index (up 2.27%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 0.96%) and the Nifty Private Bank index (up 0.63%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 1.47%), the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.74%) and the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.62%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the key policy rate—repo rate—unchanged at 5.25%. Headline inflation during November and December remained below the tolerance band of the inflation target. The revised outlook for CPI inflation in Q1 and Q2 of next year, at 4% and 4.2%, respectively, is revised slightly upwards, said RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra. The Indian economy continues on a steady, improving trajectory, with real GDP poised to register significant higher growth of 7.4% this year, as compared to the previous year, amidst global headwinds, the governor noted. Going forward, economic activity is expected to hold up well in the next year, he added. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper added 1.58% to 6.756 compared with previous session close of 6.651. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6700 compared with its close of 90.3400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.50% to Rs 152,830. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.17% to 97.80. The United States 10-year bond yield dropped 0.40% to 4.191. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 46 cents or 0.68% to $68.01 a barrel. Global market: European equities traded on a mixed note on Friday, while Most Asian markets ended lower, following the tech-driven sell-off on Wall Street. South Korea’s market, which is heavily weighted in favor of companies in the chip and automotive industries, has seen sharp swings in the past week as sentiment over tech stocks sours. Pharmaceutical stocks in Japan also slumped on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled his website offering discounted prescription medicines. On the commodities front, spot silver prices climbed 3.28%, having crashed about 13% on Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 1.20% to close at 48,908.72, while the S&P 500 lost 1.23% declined to 6,798.40, pushing it into negative territory for the year. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite posted the biggest decline, tumbling 1.59% to end at 22,540.59. Tech giant Alphabet came under pressure after reporting fourth-quarter results and flagging a sharp rise in artificial intelligence spending, with capital expenditure totaling $185 billion for 2026. Qualcomm slid more than 8% after posting a weaker forecast because of a global memory shortage.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty FMCG Index gains 2.27%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-fmcg-index-gains-227/1672958</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672958</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty FMCG index ended up 2.27% at 51882.75 today.

Nifty FMCG index ended up 2.27% at 51882.75 today. The index has slipped 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, ITC Ltd rose 5.03%, Hindustan Unilever Ltd jumped 2.96% and United Breweries Ltd gained 2.76%. The Nifty FMCG index has fallen 7.00% over last one year compared to the 8.86% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty IT index has dropped 1.47% and Nifty MNC index increased 1.04% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 witnessed a rise of 0.20% to close at 25693.7 while the SENSEX increased 0.32% to close at 83580.4 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 266 pts higher; FMCG shares advance; VIX slides 1.86%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-266-pts-higher-fmcg-shares-advance-vix-slides-186/1672956</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672956</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with minor gains today, navigating the Union Budget, the India–US trade deal, an Anthropic AI–led shock to IT stocks, and the Reserve Bank of India’s repo rate policy.

The key equity benchmarks ended with minor gains today, navigating the Union Budget, the India–US trade deal, an Anthropic AI–led shock to IT stocks, and the Reserve Bank of India’s repo rate policy. The Nifty settled above the 25,650 mark. FMCG, consumer durables and private bank shares declined while IT, pharma and auto shares declined As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 266.47 points or 0.32% to 83,580.40. The Nifty 50 index rose 50.90 points or 0.20% to 25,693.70. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.11% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.42%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,916 shares rose and 2,273 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.86% to 11.94. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the key policy rate—repo rate—unchanged at 5.25%. Headline inflation during November and December remained below the tolerance band of the inflation target. The revised outlook for CPI inflation in Q1 and Q2 of next year, at 4% and 4.2%, respectively, is revised slightly upwards, said RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra. The Indian economy continues on a steady, improving trajectory, with real GDP poised to register significant higher growth of 7.4% this year, as compared to the previous year, amidst global headwinds, the governor noted. Going forward, economic activity is expected to hold up well in the next year, he added. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index added 2.24% to 51,896.25. The index declined 0.38% in the previous trading session. ITC (up 5.01%), Hindustan Unilever (up 3.1%), United Breweries (up 2.78%), Patanjali Foods (up 1.45%) and United Spirits (up 1.34%), Godrej Consumer Products (up 0.98%), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (up 0.88%), Dabur India (up 0.78%), Britannia Industries (up 0.73%) and Marico (up 0.62%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles declined 1.38% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 3,486 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with a net profit of Rs 5,406 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) jumped 7.18% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed surged 142.38% to Rs 63.31 crore on a 26.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2873.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharti Airtel rose 1.55%. The company reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Data Patterns (India) rallied 7.07% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 30.54% to Rs 58.30 crore on a 47.92% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 173.13 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. BEML dropped 6.76% after the company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 22.38 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net profit of Rs 24.41 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations climbed 23.69% YoY to Rs 1083.27 crore during the quarter. Hitachi Energy India surged 13.84% after the company’s standalone net profit soared 90.29% to Rs 261.42 crore on 27.71% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2021.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Gland Pharma shed 0.30%. The company announced that it has received approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) for Zoledronic Acid Injection, 4 mg/100 mL (0.04 mg/mL), in single-dose bags. Kriti Industries (India) rose 1.57% after the company’s consolidated net loss narrowed sharply to Rs 0.47 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 10.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales declined 35.3% YoY to Rs 135.79 crore during the quarter. Pitti Engineering declined 4.12% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 29.61% QoQ to Rs 28.22 crore despite a flat 0.06% decline in net sales to Rs 477.42 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit fell by 1.9%, despite a 15% increase in net sales in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. NCC added 2.60% after the company reported 36.60% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 122.46 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 193.18 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 8.91% YoY to Rs 4,868.29 crore during the third quarter of FY26. Global Markets: European equities traded on a mixed note on Friday, while Most Asian markets ended lower, following the tech-driven sell-off on Wall Street. South Korea’s market, which is heavily weighted in favor of companies in the chip and automotive industries, has seen sharp swings in the past week as sentiment over tech stocks sours. Pharmaceutical stocks in Japan also slumped on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled his website offering discounted prescription medicines. On the commodities front, spot silver prices climbed 3.28%, having crashed about 13% on Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 1.20% to close at 48,908.72, while the S&P 500 lost 1.23% declined to 6,798.40, pushing it into negative territory for the year. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite posted the biggest decline, tumbling 1.59% to end at 22,540.59. Tech giant Alphabet came under pressure after reporting fourth-quarter results and flagging a sharp rise in artificial intelligence spending, with capital expenditure totaling $185 billion for 2026. Qualcomm slid more than 8% after posting a weaker forecast because of a global memory shortage.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BEML slumps after posting Rs 22-cr net loss in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/beml-slumps-after-posting-rs-22-cr-net-loss-in-q3-fy26/1672846</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672846</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations climbed 23.69% YoY to Rs 1083.27 crore during the quarter.

Revenue from operations climbed 23.69% YoY to Rs 1083.27 crore during the quarter. The company reported pre-tax loss of Rs 25.41 crore during the quarter compared with pre-tax profit of Rs 29.58 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 30.78% to Rs 1,112.54 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 850.70 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 559.19 crore (up 41.57% YoY), employee benefit expenses was at Rs 222.58 crore (up 7.68% YoY), while finance cost stood at Rs 11.61 crore (down 30.48% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the company’s declared dividend of Rs 2.50 per share for FY26. The company had fixed the record date as on 13 February 2026 for payment of said interim dividend. BEML is a leading multi-technology 'Schedule A' company under the Ministry of Defence. It operates in three verticals viz. defence & aerospace, mining & construction and rail & metro. As of 31st December 2025, the Government of India held a 54.03% stake in BEML

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BEMLLtd_9365105403_2294.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashapura Minechem Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashapura-minechem-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1672841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672841</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[BEML Ltd, Nazara Technologies Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Cemindia Projects Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 February 2026.

BEML Ltd, Nazara Technologies Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Cemindia Projects Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 February 2026. Ashapura Minechem Ltd lost 10.66% to Rs 609 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 60466 shares in the past one month. BEML Ltd crashed 8.32% to Rs 1602.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 92071 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22381 shares in the past one month. Nazara Technologies Ltd tumbled 6.90% to Rs 257.9. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 12.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.12 lakh shares in the past one month. Poly Medicure Ltd fell 6.75% to Rs 1398.55. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11742 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 63784 shares in the past one month. Cemindia Projects Ltd corrected 6.06% to Rs 635.45. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 33771 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18230 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshapuraMinech_91041583902_3111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GNG Electronics hits the roof after robust Q3 results]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gng-electronics-hits-the-roof-after-robust-q3-results/1672829</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672829</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, PAT stood at Rs 38.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 102.8% YoY from Rs 19.1 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, PAT stood at Rs 38.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 102.8% YoY from Rs 19.1 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 18.5% from Rs 32.7 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations came in at Rs 487.2 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a strong 40.3% YoY growth over Rs 347.4 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 10.8% QoQ from Rs 439.9 crore in Q2 FY26. Gross profit stood at Rs 101.3 crore, up 24% YoY from Rs 81.7 crore. Gross margin came in at 20.8%, lower by 273 bps YoY but higher by 87 bps QoQ. Profit before tax stood at Rs 42.8 crore in Q3 FY26, up 104.3% vs Q3 FY25 and higher by 18.6% QoQ from Rs 36.1 crore reported in Q2 FY26. EBITDA rose sharply to Rs 54.6 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 32 crore in Q3 FY25, marking a 70.5% YoY increase. Sequentially, EBITDA increased 16.7% from Rs 46.8 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA margin improved to 11.2% from 9.2% in Q3 FY25 and 10.6% in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 26.9 crore, up 0.4% YoY. Finance cost was largely stable at Rs 9 crore compared with Rs 8.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Sharad Khandelwal, managing director, highlighted that accelerating AI adoption and supply-side constraints in new computing hardware are pushing customers toward refurbished enterprise-grade devices as a cost-efficient and scalable alternative. Management believes the company is well positioned to capitalise on favourable industry trends while focusing on disciplined execution and long-term value creation. GNG Electronics is India’s largest refurbisher of laptops and desktops and among the largest refurbishers of ICT devices globally. As of 31 March 2025, the company had a significant presence across India, the USA, Europe, Africa and the UAE. It follows a repair-over-replacement model and refurbished nearly 5.9 lakh devices in FY25, offering a portfolio of 5,840 SKUs spanning laptops, desktops, tablets, servers, smartphones, workstations and accessories.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GNGElectronicsLtd_47811715_91822.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold softens on profit-taking and Dollar strength]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-softens-on-profit-taking-and-dollar-strength/1672828</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672828</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures slipped below the $5,000 per ounce mark in electronic trade on Friday, with prices set to close the week with modest gains following last week’s extreme volatility, which saw swings of nearly $1,000.

Gold futures slipped below the $5,000 per ounce mark in electronic trade on Friday, with prices set to close the week with modest gains following last week’s extreme volatility, which saw swings of nearly $1,000. The precious metal faced headwinds from profit-taking after recent record highs, alongside renewed strength in the US dollar. The dollar found support after President Donald Trump nominated Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve Chair, with markets viewing Warsh as favoring a smaller balance sheet and a more measured approach to policy easing. Geopolitical sentiment also remained cautious, as the White House signaled a preference for diplomacy with Iran. On the domestic front, MCX April gold futures recovered from intraday lows and traded marginally higher after touching Rs 149,396 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siemens slips after PAT drops 26% YoY in December quarter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siemens-slips-after-pat-drops-26-yoy-in-december-quarter/1672830</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672830</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 14% to Rs 3,830.7 crore, compared with Rs 3,360 crore in the same quarter last year.

Revenue from operations rose 14% to Rs 3,830.7 crore, compared with Rs 3,360 crore in the same quarter last year. Profitability was impacted by forex losses and a one-time charge related to the implementation of the new labour codes. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 429.2 crore, down from Rs 489.1 crore a year ago. The quarter included exceptional items of Rs 74.3 crore, primarily on account of increased employee benefit provisions following the new labour codes effective 21 November 2025. On 8 August 2025, the board had approved changing the financial year from October–September to April-March. The current financial year spans 1 October 2024 – 31 March 2026 (18 months). Thereafter, FYs will run April-March. The company’s new orders during the quarter increased by 19% YoY to Rs 4,829 crore in December quarter, while order backlog grew by 7% at Rs 43,004 crore. Sunil Mathur, managing director and chief executive officer of Siemens, said, “India’s economic resilience continues to stand out even as adverse geopolitical developments and global uncertainties weigh on sentiment. Despite these external headwinds, Siemens Limited delivered a steady performance this quarter driven by disciplined execution and a healthy order book, resulting in an increase in revenue of 14%. All the businesses performed well during the quarter, contributing to a book-to-bill ratio of 1.26x, with Digital Industries now reflecting normalized operations. This is reflected in the company’s strong performance across all businesses during the quarter, including two significant order wins in the Mobility business. While the Smart Infrastructure business continued to demonstrate strong execution, the performance at the Digital Industries business is now showing signs of recovery, indicating that the destocking phase is now largely over. Looking ahead, we expect additional support from macroeconomic tailwinds as the recently signed India-EU Free Trade Agreement and the trade deal with the US begin opening new avenues for technology collaboration and exports. We welcome the government’s consistent focus on long-term economic growth and structural transformation in the Union Budget 2026-27. The record Rs 12.2 lakh crore capital expenditure allocation, sustained emphasis on infrastructure development, and a fiscal deficit target of around 4.3% indicate a continued and disciplined approach to strengthening India’s growth foundations." Siemens is a leading technology company focused on industry, infrastructure, and mobility.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Siemens_82042367344_514.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CL Educate Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cl-educate-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1672812</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672812</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vivid Mercantile Ltd, Tokyo Plast International Ltd, Orchasp Ltd and Digidrive Distributors Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 February 2026.

Vivid Mercantile Ltd, Tokyo Plast International Ltd, Orchasp Ltd and Digidrive Distributors Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 February 2026. CL Educate Ltd lost 20.00% to Rs 58.41 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 37427 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11709 shares in the past one month. Vivid Mercantile Ltd crashed 17.35% to Rs 7.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 44.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.77 lakh shares in the past one month. Tokyo Plast International Ltd tumbled 16.38% to Rs 100.05. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1229 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 347 shares in the past one month. Orchasp Ltd pared 11.36% to Rs 2.42. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.69 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 57316 shares in the past one month. Digidrive Distributors Ltd shed 10.90% to Rs 22.55. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6772 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3151 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CLEducateLtd_6722154754_26994.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>