<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:44:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR loses momentum tracking dollar strength overseas]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-loses-momentum-tracking-dollar-strength-overseas/1678826</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678826</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee lost momentum in opening trades on Friday tracking strength in dollar oversea.

The Indian rupee lost momentum in opening trades on Friday tracking strength in dollar oversea. The dollar index was hovering around a one-month high as minutes from the Fed’s latest meeting showed policymakers divided on the rate outlook, suggesting the next chair may face hurdles in delivering cuts. INR opened at Rs 90.94 to a dollar and hit a low of 90.97 so far during the day. Poor show in local equities also added pressure on the counter. A cautious undertone may prevail due to a combination of factors, including AI disruption fears, geopolitical tensions, a cautious retail outlook from Walmart and concerns about potential stress within the U.S. private credit market. Benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty tumbled around 1.5 percent each on Thursday. Foreign investors net sold shares worth Rs 881 crore on Thursday, while domestic institutional investors net sold shares to the extent of Rs 596 crore, according to provisional exchange data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pace Digitek gains after bagging Rs 891 million order from RailTel Corp]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pace-digitek-gains-after-bagging-rs-891-million-order-from-railtel-corp/1678825</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678825</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves deployment of IP-based video surveillance systems in LHB coaches for a customer of RailTel on a back-to-back basis.

The project involves deployment of IP-based video surveillance systems in LHB coaches for a customer of RailTel on a back-to-back basis. The contract includes a three-year warranty, followed by five years of comprehensive annual maintenance contract (CAMC). The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and is to be executed within eight months from the date of the Letter of Award, the company said. Pace Digitek clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity. The contract does not fall under related party transactions. Pace Digitek provides solutions for telecom infra and solar industries. It is involved in the manufacturing, installation and commissioning of DC Power systems, lithium batteries, monitoring systems and inverter. RailTel was incorporated in 2000, with the objective of creating nationwide broadband and VPN services, telecom, and multimedia networks to modernize the train control operation and safety system of Indian Railways. Shares of RailTel Corporation of India rose 0.38% to Rs 329.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PACEDIGITEKLIMITED_26475505_94643.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Steel Authority of India Ltd Spurts 0.74%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/steel-authority-of-india-ltd-spurts-074/1678814</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678814</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Steel Authority of India Ltd gained 0.74% today to trade at Rs 156.95.

Steel Authority of India Ltd gained 0.74% today to trade at Rs 156.95. The BSE Metal index is up 0.25% to quote at 39156.76. The index is up 3.83 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd increased 0.57% and APL Apollo Tubes Ltd added 0.55% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 35.76 % over last one year compared to the 8.63% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Steel Authority of India Ltd has added 7.28% over last one month compared to 3.83% gain in BSE Metal index and 0.44% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 10426 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 16.89 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 162.95 on 12 Feb 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 101.2 on 09 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SAIL_40802201738_2299.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices drift lower; breadth weak]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-drift-lower-breadth-weak/1678815</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678815</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in early trade, as weak global cues and escalating US–Iran tensions continued to dampen investor sentiment.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in early trade, as weak global cues and escalating US–Iran tensions continued to dampen investor sentiment. The Nifty traded below the 25,400 level. IT and media shares declined, while PSU bank and metal stocks advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 230.01 points or 0.28% to 82,268.13. The Nifty 50 index fell 64.70 points or 0.25% to 25,386.30. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.29% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.68%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,146 shares rose and 1,826 shares fell. A total of 151 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 880.49 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 596.28 crore in the Indian equity market on 19 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: ABB India rose 4.24%. The company reported an 18.19% decline in consolidated net profit to 432.27 crore in Q4 CY25 compared to Rs 528.41 crore posted in same quarter last year. However, revenue from operations rose 5.7% YoY to Rs 3,557.01 crore reported in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. CIE Automotive India jumped 3.06% after the company reported a 10.44% rise in consolidated net profit to 204.30 crore in Q4 CY25 compared to Rs 184.98 crore posted in same quarter last year. However, revenue from operations rose 13.41% YoY to Rs 2,392.99 crore reported in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. RailTel Corporation of India rose 0.05%. The company announced that it has secured a Rs 36 crore railway signalling project from the Deputy CSTE/P/CNB. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.52% to 6.709 compared with previous session close of 6.674. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9500 compared with its close of 90.6850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.18% to Rs 155,099. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.12% to 97.96. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.22% to 4.068. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 24 cents or 0.33% to $71.90 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian markets traded mostly lower on Friday, after all three major Wall Street indexes declined overnight, pressured by a drop in private credit stocks and Iran-U.S. tensions. Prospects of a strike on Iran have risen with U.S. President Donald Trump reportedly saying that he would take a call to decide on military action against Tehran in the next 10 days. This pushed Brent Crude higher, gaining 0.26%, to settle at $71.92. In Asia, investors assessed Japan's latest inflation data. The island nation's headline inflation rate fell from 2.1% in December to 1.5% in January, its lowest level since March 2022. The reading ended a run of 45 straight months in which inflation had remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target. The core inflation rate, which excludes fresh food prices, eased to 2%, the lowest level since January 2024. It was down from 2.4% in December. As per reports, despite the slowdown in headline inflation, the Bank of Japan is unlikely to delay rate hikes as fresh-food prices remain volatile, while energy costs fell after Japan scrapped its fuel tax in December. Japan’s manufacturing activity improved in February, with the S&P Global Japan Manufacturing PMI rising to 52.8 from 51.5 in January, marking the strongest expansion since May 2022. Growth was supported by firm domestic and overseas demand, with export orders rising at the fastest pace in eight years. While hiring growth eased from January’s peak, it remained solid. Input costs increased at a slightly faster pace. Manufacturers stayed optimistic about the year-ahead outlook, backed by stronger demand, semiconductor and AI-related orders, and ongoing product launches. Overnight on Wall Street, the US stocks closed lower on Thursday, pulling the S&P 500 close to flat for the year, as investors rotated out of financials and monitored escalating tensions between the US and Iran. Reflecting a surge in imports and a slump in exports, the Commerce Department released a report on Thursday showing the U.S. trade deficit unexpectedly widened in the month of December. The Commerce Department said the trade deficit grew to $70.3 billion in December from a revised $53.0 billion in November. The unexpectedly wider trade deficit partly reflected a continued surge in the value of imports, which shot up by 3.6 percent to $357.6 billion in December after spiking by 4.2 percent to $345.3 billion in November. The report also showed a continued slump in the value of exports, which tumbled by 1.7 percent to $287.3 billion in December after plunging by 3.4 percent to $292.3 billion in November. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 267.50 points, or 0.54%, closing at 49,395.16. The S&P 500 declined 0.28%, ending at 6,861.89, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.31% to 22,682.73. Financial stocks led the decline after Blue Owl Capital said it would tighten investor liquidity following the sale of $1.4 billion in loan assets, raising concerns about potential losses in the private credit market. Shares of Blue Owl dropped about 6%, while Blackstone and Apollo Global Management each fell more than 5%. Software stocks also remained under pressure amid persistent worries about artificial intelligence disruption. The sector has struggled in recent weeks as investors assess how AI could reshape enterprise software demand.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: RailTel Corp, Texmaco Rail & Engineering, GHV Infra Projects, IIFL Finance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-railtel-corp-texmaco-rail-engineering-ghv-infra-projects-iifl-finance/1678802</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678802</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&O trading on 20 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&O trading on 20 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: ABB India reported an 18.19% decline in consolidated net profit to 432.27 crore in Q4 CY25 compared to Rs 528.41 crore posted in same quarter last year. However, revenue from operations rose 5.7% YoY to Rs 3,557.01 crore reported in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. CIE Automotive India reported a 10.44% rise in consolidated net profit to 204.30 crore in Q4 CY25 compared to Rs 184.98 crore posted in same quarter last year. However, revenue from operations rose 13.41% YoY to Rs 2,392.99 crore reported in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. RailTel Corporation of India has announced that it has secured a Rs 36 crore railway signalling project from the Deputy CSTE/P/CNB. Texmaco Rail & Engineering has announced that it has executed a Strategic Joint Venture Shareholders’ Agreement with RVNL to build a rolling stock powerhouse and expand its rail EPC footprint. GHV Infra Projects has announced that it has secured a Rs 123 crore work order from Enmas EPC Power Projects for the supply of rooftop solar plants. IIFL Finance has announced that its board will meet on February 24 to consider raising up to Rs 10,000 crore through non-convertible debentures (NCDs). 5paisa Capital has announced that its board will meet on February 24 to consider a fund-raising proposal. Avenue Supermarts has announced that it has opened a new store in Rangareddy, Telangana, bringing its total store count to 449. Zydus Lifesciences has announced that the US FDA has completed an inspection of the company’s Ahmedabad unit with “nil” observations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GHV Infra secures RTS plants supply order worth 153-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ghv-infra-secures-rts-plants-supply-order-worth-153-cr/1678801</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678801</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order consists of supply, at the site of installation, of all materials required for the 28.83 MWp grid-connected rooftop solar (RTS) plants for 14,416 SC & ST consumers The scope includes solar panel, inverter, module mounting structure, distribution boards, cabling, earthing, etc.

The order consists of supply, at the site of installation, of all materials required for the 28.83 MWp grid-connected rooftop solar (RTS) plants for 14,416 SC & ST consumers The scope includes solar panel, inverter, module mounting structure, distribution boards, cabling, earthing, etc. In addition to material supply, the company will undertake installation, testing, and commissioning of the RTS plants for each of the 14,416 consumers. The order is valued at Rs 123 crore and it will be completed within period of 120 days. GHV Infra Projects operates in the infrastructure and construction sector as an engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) company. The firm undertakes projects across transportation infrastructure, water management, industrial development, building construction, and environment and energy sectors. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 391.6% to Rs 14.55 crore on 646.1% jump in net sales to Rs 137.73 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter hit the 5% upper circuit limit to close at Rs 351.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GHVInfraProjectsLtd_41118322_6087.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at green start for equities; US-Iran tensions continue to escalate]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-green-start-for-equities-us-iran-tensions-continue-to-escalate/1678803</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678803</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 54.00 points, suggesting a green start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 54.00 points, suggesting a green start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 880.49 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 596.28 crore in the Indian equity market on 19 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 1,076.63 crore in the cash market so far in February (till 19 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia markets traded mostly lower on Friday, after all three major Wall Street indexes declined overnight pressured by a drop in private credit stocks and Iran-U.S. tensions. Prospects of a strike on Iran have risen with U.S. President Donald Trump reportedly saying that he would take a call to decide on military action against Tehran in the next 10 days. This pushed Brent Crude higher, gained 0.26%, to settle at $71.92. In Asia, investors assessed Japan's latest inflation data. The island nation's headline inflation rate fell from 2.1% in December to 1.5% in January, its lowest level since March 2022. The reading ended a run of 45 straight months in which inflation had remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target. Core inflation rate, which excludes fresh food prices, eased to 2%, the lowest level since January 2024. It was down from 2.4% in December. As per reports, despite the slowdown in headline inflation, the Bank of Japan is unlikely to delay rate hikes as fresh-food prices remain volatile, while energy costs fell after Japan scrapped its fuel tax in December. Overnight on Wall Street, the US stocks closed lower on Thursday, pulling the S&P 500 close to flat for the year, as investors rotated out of financials and monitored escalating tensions between the US and Iran. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 267.50 points, or 0.54%, closing at 49,395.16. The S&P 500 declined 0.28%, ending at 6,861.89, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.31% to 22,682.73. Financial stocks led the decline after Blue Owl Capital said it would tighten investor liquidity following the sale of $1.4 billion in loan assets, raising concerns about potential losses in the private credit market. Shares of Blue Owl dropped about 6%, while Blackstone and Apollo Global Management each fell more than 5%. Software stocks also remained under pressure amid persistent worries about artificial intelligence disruption. The sector has struggled in recent weeks as investors assess how AI could reshape enterprise software demand. Domestic Market: In a dramatic reversal of recent gains, the Indian benchmark indices experienced a severe broad-based sell-off on Thursday, as the Sensex plummeted by 1,236 points and the Nifty 50 slipped below the 25,500 mark. This massive decline has reportedly wiped out over Rs 7.5 lakh crore in investor wealth in a single session. The crash was triggered by several factors, including escalating geopolitical tensions between the U.S. and Iran and a sharp spike in global crude oil prices. Additionally, deep-seated uncertainty regarding the U.S. Federal Reserve's interest rate trajectory weighed on sentiment following its latest meeting minutes. Despite a resilient opening, fueled by the IT sector, the market succumbed to aggressive profit booking as risk-off sentiment took hold. This dragged every major sectoral index, particularly auto, realty, and banking, into the red and the benchmark indices snapped their robust three-day winning streak. The barometer S&P BSE Sensex declined 1.48% to close at 82,498.14. The Nifty 50 index dropped 365 points or 1.41%, to end the session at 25,454.35.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>