<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:31:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Amagi Media Labs IPO ends with 15.82 times subscription ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/amagi-media-labs-ipo-ends-with-1582-times-subscription/1665502</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665502</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 43,13,69,036 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer.

The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 43,13,69,036 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 15.82 times. The issue opened for a bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it closed on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share. The IPO consists of a fresh issue of Rs 816.0 crore and offer for sale of 2,69,42,343 equity shares. At the upper end price, the issue size stands at Rs 1788.62 crore. The offer for sale (OFS) by PI Opportunities Fund-I includes up to 98,89,646 shares at the upper price band of Rs 361 per share, aggregating Rs 357.02 crore. Accel India VI (Mauritius) and Trudy Holdings are each offering up to 50,72,582 shares at the same price, amounting to Rs 183.12 crore apiece. In addition, PI Opportunities Fund-II is proposing to sell up to 3,411,792 shares at Rs 361 per share, valued at Rs 123.17 crore. Norwest Venture Partners plans to offload up to 3,381,721 shares worth Rs 122.08 crore, while multiple individual investors will collectively offer up to 228,024 shares, aggregating Rs 8.03 crore. Amagi Media Labs proposes to utilise Rs 550.06 crore from the net fresh issue proceeds towards technology and cloud infrastructure and the balance will be utilised towards funding inorganic growth through unidentified acquisitions and for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Amagi Media Labs on 12 January 2026, the company raised Rs 804.87 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 2.22 crore shares at Rs 361 each to 42 anchor investors. Amagi Media Labs (Amagi) is a software-as-a-service (SaaS) company that connects media companies to their audiences through cloud-native technology. Its platform helps content providers and distributors upload and deliver video over the internet (commonly known as streaming) through smart televisions, smartphones and applications, instead of traditional cable or set-top box services. It also helps monetize such content through targeted advertising services for advertisers. The company enables broadcaster, content owner, and streaming platform to launch, manage, and monetise live linear channels on Free Ad-supported Streaming TV (FAST) platforms such as Pluto TV, Samsung TV Plus, Roku Channel, and others. The company’s customers include global media companies such as Vevo, Lionsgate Studios, DAZN, E.W. Scripps, Sinclair, Inc., VIZIO, Roku, The Trade Desk, JioAds and the Tennis Channel. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 6.47 crore and income from operations of Rs 704.82 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBL Bank Q3 PAT surges over fivefold to Rs 214 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbl-bank-q3-pat-surges-over-fivefold-to-rs-214-cr/1665494</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665494</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income increased 2.33% YoY to Rs 4,71,700 crore as on 31st December 2025.

Total income increased 2.33% YoY to Rs 4,71,700 crore as on 31st December 2025. The company reported robust growth in profit despite earnings being impacted by a one-off pre-tax expense of Rs 32 crore arising from the revision in the definition of wages under the New Labour Codes, effective November 21, 2025. Operating profit, excluding the above one-off impact recorded in other income in Q3 FY25, rose 7% year-on-year and 25% quarter-on-quarter to Rs 912 crore during the quarter. Total deposits grew 12% YoY and 3% QoQ to 1,19,721 crore as of 31st December 2025. Net Advances grew 14% YoY and 3% QoQ to 1,03,086 crore as of 31st December 2025. CASA deposits increased 6% YoY to Rs 36,972 as of 31st December 2025. Retail advances expanded 10% YoY and 1% QoQ to Rs 60,611 crore, while wholesale advances registered strong growth of 21% YoY and 5% QoQ to Rs 42,475 crore as of 31 December 2025. Gross NPA ratio as of 31st December 2025 was 1.88% as against 2.32% as of 30th September 2025. Net NPA ratio as of 31st December 2025 was 0.55% as compared with 0.57% as of 30th September 2025. Provision Coverage Ratio including technical write offs was 93.2%. Total capital adequacy was 14.94% as of 31st December 2025 vs 15.02% as of 30th September 2025; CET 1 is 13.45% as of 31st December 2025 vs 13.51% as of 30th September 2025. R Subramaniakumar, MD & CEO, RBL Bank remarked, “Q3 FY26 marks another quarter of stable and consistent operational performance for the Bank. We continued to deliver strong growth in our focus areas, with secured retail advances and commercial banking driving asset side expansion while granular deposits supported on liability side. The collection efficiency in our JLG business has materially improved and disbursal run-rate are now close to normalised levels. Our core operating engine remains robust — anchored in disciplined execution, profitable Balance Sheet, and a sharper cross sell to our existing customer base. During the quarter, the Bank received shareholder approval for capital infusion by Emirates NBD PJSC and for amalgamation of its Indian branches with RBL. The Bank is awaiting regulatory approvals for the same.” RBL Bank provides a wide range of banking and financial services, including wholesale banking, retail banking, treasury operations, and other banking-related activities. As of 31st December 2025, the Bank has 1,921 total touch points of which 580 are bank branches and 1,341 business correspondent branches. Of 1,341 BC branches, 291 are banking outlets. RBL Finserve (RBL Finserve), a 100% subsidiary of the Bank, accounts for 1,084 business correspondent branches. The scrip rallied 4.28% to end at Rs 325.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RBLBankLtd_63443224104_5982.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Bank records PAT of Rs 11,318 crore in Q3; total advances rise to Rs 14.66 lakh crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-bank-records-pat-of-rs-11318-crore-in-q3-total-advances-rise-to-rs-1466-lakh-crore/1665493</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665493</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26.

Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26. Net interest margin was 4.30% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.25% in Q3 FY25. Non-interest income added up to Rs 7,525 crore (up 12.4% YoY) and fee income aggregated to Rs 6,180 crore (up 6.3% YoY) during the period under review. Operating expenses increased by 13.2% YoY to Rs 11,944 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 10,552 crore in Q3 FY25. This includes Rs 145 crore of provisions on an estimated basis pursuant to the new Labour Codes. There was a treasury loss of Rs 157 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared to gain of Rs 371 crore in Q3 FY25, primarily reflecting market movements. Provisions (excluding provision for tax) were Rs 2,556 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 1,227 crore in Q3 FY25. Following its annual supervisory review, RBI has directed the Bank to make a standard asset provision of Rs 1,283 crore in respect of a portfolio of agricultural priority sector credit facilities wherein the terms of the facilities were found to be not fully compliant with the regulatory requirements for classification as agricultural priority sector lending. “There is no change in asset classification or in the terms and conditions applicable to the borrowers or in the repayment behaviour of borrowers as per these terms. This additional standard asset provision will continue until the loans are repaid or renewed in conformity with the PSL classification guidelines,” the bank said in a statement. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 14,800 crore, up by _ % from Rs 15,660 crore in Q3 FY25. Total advances increased by 11.5% YoY to Rs 14,66,154 crore as on 31 December 2025. Total period-end deposits increased by 9.2% YoY to Rs 16,59,611 crore as on 31 December 2025. With the addition of 402 branches during 9M-2026, the Bank had a network of 7,385 branches and 11,983 ATMs & cash recycling machines as on 31 December 2025. The gross NPA ratio was 1.53% as on at 31 December 2025 compared to 1.96% as on 31 December 2024. The net NPA ratio was 0.37% as on 31 December 2025 compared to 0.42% as on 31 December 2024. The bank has written-off gross NPAs amounting to Rs 2,046 crore in Q3-2026. The provisioning coverage ratio on non-performing loans was 75.4% as on 31 December 2025. As on 31 December 2025, the bank held total provisions, other than specific provisions on fund-based outstanding to borrowers classified as non-performing, amounting to Rs 22,657 crore or 1.5% of loans. The bank’s total capital adequacy ratio as on 31 December 2025 was 17.34% and CET-1 ratio was 16.46% as compared to the minimum regulatory requirements of 11.70% and 8.20%, respectively. The bank’s consolidated profit after tax was Rs 12,538 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 12,883 crore in Q3-2025, down 2.68% YoY. Consolidated assets grew by 8.8% YoY to Rs 27,53,471 crore as on 31 December 2025. ICICI Bank (IBL) is a systemically important private sector bank in India. With a presence in banking, insurance, asset management, investment banking and private equity, the ICICI Group is a large player in the Indian financial system. The scrip had shed 0.46% to end at Rs 1411.65 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIBank_93786457618_5418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Q3 PAT climbs 11% YoY to Rs 18,564 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-bank-q3-pat-climbs-11-yoy-to-rs-18564-cr/1665488</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665488</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 11.05% YoY to Rs 24,259.94 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 11.05% YoY to Rs 24,259.94 crore during the quarter. Net interest income (NII) (interest earned less interest expended) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 grew by 6.4% to Rs 32,620 crore from Rs 30,650 crore for the quarter ended 31st December 2024. Operating profit before provisions and contingencies stood at Rs 27,097.80 crore as on 31st December 2025, registering the growth of 8.39% compared with 25,000.40 crore as on 31st December 2024. Operating expenses for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 were Rs 18,770 crore as on 3st December 2025. Operating expenses excluding the estimated impact of Rs 800 crore for employee benefits under the New Labour Code were Rs 17,970 crore, as against Rs 17,110 crore during the corresponding quarter of the previous year. The core cost-to-income ratio for the quarter was at 39.2%. Provisions and contingencies for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 were Rs 2,840 crore (after release of contingent provisions of Rs 1,040 crore primarily in respect of a large borrower group fulfilling certain conditions). The bank's average deposits were Rs 27,52,400 crore for the 31st December 2025, registering a growth of 12.2% over Rs 24,52,800 crore for the 31st December 2024, and 1.5% over Rs 27,10,500 crore for the 30th September 2025. Gross advance jumped 11.9% to Rs 28,44,600 crore as on 31st December 2025, recording the growth of 11.9% over 31st December 2024. Retail loans grew by 6.9%, small and mid-market enterprises loans grew by 17.2% and corporate and other wholesale loans grew by 10.3%. Overseas advances constituted 1.7% of total advances. Gross non-performing assets (GNNPA) stood at 1.24% as on 31st December 2025 unchanged from 1.24% as of 30 September 2025, and improved from 1.42% as of 31 December 2024. Net non-performing assets (NNPA) remained stable at 0.42% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 0.42% as of 30 September 2025, and declined from 0.46% as of 31 December 2024. The bank's total capital adequacy ratio (CAR) as per Basel Ill guidelines was at 19.9% as on 31st December 2025 (20.0% as on 31st December 2024) as against a regulatory requirement of 11.9%. Tier 1 CAR was at 17.8% and common equity tier 1 capital ratio was at 17.4% as of 31st December 2025. Risk-weighted Assets were at Rs 28,80,800 crore as on 31st December 2025. HDFC Bank is India's largest private sector lender. As of 31st December 2025, the bank's distribution network was at 9,616 branches and 21,176 ATMs across 4,170 cities/ towns as against 9,143 branches and 21,049 ATMs across 4,101 cities/ towns as of December 31, 2024. The counter rose 0.56% to settle at Rs 931.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCBank_24534281400_4987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sobha Q3 PAT drops 29% YoY to Rs 154 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sobha-q3-pat-drops-29-yoy-to-rs-154-cr/1665476</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665476</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) fell 30.31% YoY to Rs 205.34 crore in Q3 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) fell 30.31% YoY to Rs 205.34 crore in Q3 December 2025. Sales value stood at Rs 2,115 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 52% YoY and 11% QoQ. Average price realization stood was Rs 15,436 per square feet (Sq.Ft.). On nine month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 88.69% to Rs 101.57 crore on 14.46% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3,202.66 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Jagadish Nangineni, managing director, Sobha said, “The first nine months of FY26 have been truly exceptional for SOBHA, with our real estate sales reaching an all-time high of Rs 6,097 crore. This remarkable achievement is a testament to the enduring trust of our customers and the dedication of our aligned teams across every function and business vertical. We are confident that this strong momentum will sustain, fueled by our planned new project launches in a resilient Indian macroeconomic environment, even as we navigate heightened geopolitical volatility. A significant milestone this period was our entry into the vibrant Mumbai market with the launch of SOBHA Inizio, expanding our real estate presence to 13 cities across India. In Q3, we completed 915 homes, taking cumulative deliveries for the first nine months to 2,100 homes. While procedural delays in securing Occupancy Certificates (OCs) have temporarily moderated quarterly profitability, we remain fully confident in accelerating project completions moving forward, which will drive substantial improvements in our P&L performance. With gross debt at a prudent Rs 910 crore and a negative net debt, our robust balance sheet uniquely equips us to capitalize on emerging opportunities while effectively managing the inherent cyclicality of residential real estate." Sobha is the real estate brand in the country that offers international quality homes, and commercial and contractual projects delivered on time, through its backward integration model. The counter declined 1.34% to end at Rs 1,526.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Sobha_16954596303_27443.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Tech Q3 PAT tumbles 96%% QoQ to Rs 7 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-tech-q3-pat-tumbles-96-qoq-to-rs-7-cr/1665474</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665474</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s revenue increased 3.67% while profit declined 96.06% in Q3 FY26, respectively.

On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s revenue increased 3.67% while profit declined 96.06% in Q3 FY26, respectively. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 22.97 crore in Q2 FY26, down 89.83% QoQ and up 89.84% YoY. Excluding the one-time exceptional item related to the new labor code and one-off acquisition-related costs, net income stood at Rs 135 crore, with a net income margin of 9.9% during the quarter. Operating EBITDA stood at Rs 192.9 crore in Q3 FY26, down 7.2% QoQ. Operating EBITDA margin fell 14.1% in Q3 FY26 as against 15.1% in Q2 FY26 and 17.8% in Q3 FY25. Services segment revenue of Rs 1,060.2 crore in Q3 FY26, up 4.7% QoQ. In USD terms, services segment revenues came in at $118.6 million in Q3 FY26, up 2.6% QoQ. In Q3 FY26, [LTM] attrition came in at 15.8% compared with 15.1% in Q2 FY26. Workforce strength stood at 12,580 as on 31st December 2025. Warren Harris, chief executive officer (CEO) and managing director(MD), said: “Q3 demonstrated the resilience and strength of our business, delivering growth despite seasonal softness and temporary headwinds. With strong vertical performance, six strategic deal wins, and continued investment in delivery capacity, we are poised for a sharp acceleration in Q4. We expect sequential revenue growth of over 10%, signalling a clear inflection point. More importantly, the structural changes we’ve driven — portfolio diversification, reduced concentration risk, and the Es-Tec acquisition — have transformed our growth engine into one that is broader and stickier.” Uttam Gujrati, chief financial officer (CFO), said: “We made steady progress on our strategic priorities during the quarter. ES-Tec integration is on track and already creating joint opportunities. Margin headwinds from Q3 are behind us, and we expect to return to—and exceed—the Q2 adjusted margin run-rate. Our disciplined workforce strategy and investments in future-ready skills position us well for sustainable growth. We remain focused on delivering long-term value for our customers and shareholders.” Tata Technologies is a global product engineering and digital services company. The counter rose 0.58% to settle at Rs 650.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataTechnologiesLtd_16317199_18295.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yes Bank Q3 profit jumps 55% YoY as asset quality strengthens]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yes-bank-q3-profit-jumps-55-yoy-as-asset-quality-strengthens/1665469</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665469</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit also rose 45.4% sequentially from Rs 654 crore in Q2 FY26.

Profit also rose 45.4% sequentially from Rs 654 crore in Q2 FY26. Net interest income stood at Rs 2,466 crore, up 10.9% YoY and 7.2% QoQ, aided by a reduction in the cost of funds. Non-interest income came in at Rs 1,633 crore, rising 8% YoY, though 0.7% lower on a sequential basis. As a result, total income increased 9.7% YoY to Rs 4,098 crore, and was up 3.9% QoQ. On the cost side, operating expenses rose 7.8% YoY to Rs 2,865 crore, partly reflecting Rs 155 crore of gratuity provision linked to the statutory impact of the new labour codes. Excluding this one-off, cost growth remained well controlled. Consequently, operating profit stood at Rs 1,234 crore, up 14.3% YoY, though down 4.9% QoQ. Adjusted for the gratuity impact, operating profit rose 28.7% YoY to Rs 1,389 crore. Provisioning remained benign, with provisions falling sharply to Rs 22 crore, keeping net credit costs negligible for the quarter. Profit before tax jumped 47.7% YoY and 38.1% QoQ to Rs 1,212 crore, while tax expense rose to Rs 260 crore. This translated into the strong bottom-line growth. Margins also improved. Net interest margin expanded to 2.6%, up 20 bps YoY and 10 bps QoQ, while the cost-to-income ratio improved to 66.1% from 71.1% a year ago. On the balance sheet, CASA deposits rose 8.5% YoY to Rs 99,483 crore, with average quarterly balance growth of 13.6% YoY. Net advances stood at Rs 2,57,451 crore, up 5.2% YoY and 2.9% QoQ, supported by steady momentum across segments. Total disbursements increased 7% YoY to Rs 26,982 crore, led by nearly 15% YoY growth in retail asset disbursements. Asset quality continued to strengthen. The gross NPA ratio declined to 1.5%, down 10 bps YoY and QoQ, while the net NPA ratio improved to 0.3%, down 20 bps YoY. The provision coverage ratio rose to 83.3%, compared with 71.2% in Q3 FY25. Gross slippages reduced to Rs 1,050 crore, or 1.6% of advances, with retail slippages (3.7%) at their lowest level in seven quarters. Recoveries and upgrades totaled Rs 1,224 crore, including a Rs 555 crore gain from security receipts. Operationally, the bank continued to expand its footprint, opening 33 new branches during Q3 FY26, taking the total to 76 branches added in the first nine months, achieving 95% of its full-year branch expansion target. Yes Bank, a full-service commercial bank headquartered in Mumbai, offers a wide array of products, services, and digital solutions, catering to Retail, MSME, and Corporate clients. The bank operates its brokerage business through Yes Securities, a subsidiary of the bank. The bank has a pan-India presence including an International Banking Unit (IBU) at GIFT City, and a representative office in Abu Dhabi. Shares of Yes Bank rose 2.22% to settle at Rs 23.46 on 16 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/YesBank_75840425465_25267.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T Finance records 18% YoY increase in Q3 PAT; total book size rises to Rs 1.14 lakh crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-finance-records-18-yoy-increase-in-q3-pat-total-book-size-rises-to-rs-114-lakh-crore/1665446</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665446</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income jumped 18% to Rs 2,407 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,041 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net interest income jumped 18% to Rs 2,407 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,041 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating expense for the period under review was Rs 1,135 crore, up 7% YoY. Earnings before credit cost rose by 25% YoY to Rs 1,785 crore in the third quarter of FY26. Credit cost added up to Rs 792 crore in Q3 FY26, up 32% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 at Rs 993 crore, up by 20% from Rs 825 crore in Q3 FY25. For Q3 FY26, retailisation stood at 98% of overall book. Retail book as on 31 December 2025 stood at Rs 1,11,990 crore, up 21% YoY. Total book size was at Rs 1,14,285 crore as on 31 December 2025, up 20% YoY. Gross Stage-3 (GS3) improved sequentially by 10 basis points to 3.19% and Net Stage-3 (NS3) by 8 basis points to 0.92% in Q3 FY26. Return on assets (RoA) stood at 2.31% in Q3 FY26 as against 2.27% in Q3 FY25. RoE after exceptional items was at 11.07% in Q3 FY26 as against 10.21% in Q3 FY25. Consolidated CRAR ratio as on 31 December 2025 stood at 19.10%. Sudipta Roy, managing director & CEO, LTF, said: "Q3 FY26 for the financial services sector has been defined by a powerful convergence of favourable macro-tailwinds. The implementation of GST 2.0, good monsoons, and a series of repo rate cuts have seen a surge in consumption and created an environment for growth. In Q3FY26, LTF’s focus remained on delivering a standout performance across business segments. We registered the highest ever quarterly disbursements of Rs. 22,701 crore, up 49% YoY, and the retail portfolio reaching Rs.1,11,990 crore, reflecting a growth of 21% YoY leading to a PAT of Rs. 760 crore, up 21% YoY (without the impact of a one-time exceptional item). Our proprietary AI driven next-gen digital credit engine ‘Project Cyclops’ is now implemented in Personal Loans in addition to Two-wheeler, Farm Equipment, and SME Finance businesses. It will go live in Home Loans and LAP and Rural Group Loans and MFI businesses in FY27.” L&T Finance is a leading non-banking financial company (NBFC), offering a range of financial products and services. The scrip had added 0.19% to end at Rs 296.30 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LTFinanceLtd_36546723_41147.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quant Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quant-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1665445</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665445</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Quant Mutual Fund has announced that, Mr.

Quant Mutual Fund has announced that, Mr. Mahendra Kumar Jajoo (DIN: 06966229) has been appointed as Whole Time Director on the Board of quant Money Managers Limited (Asset Management Company to the Fund) with effect from January 14, 2026. Details of Mr. Mahendra Kumar Jajoo Age: 57 years Designation: Whole Time Director Qualification: B. Com, ACA, ACS, CFA (USA)

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis MF Announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-mf-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1665440</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665440</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the IDCW option of following schemes.

Axis Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the IDCW option of following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Axis Midcap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 3.39 Axis Midcap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.50 Axis Small Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 3.68 Axis Small Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.33 Axis Large & Mid Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.48 Axis Large & Mid Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.88 Axis ELSS Tax Saver Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 2.10 Axis ELSS Tax Saver Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.50 Axis Focused Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.58 Axis Focused Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 2.83 Axis Large Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.38 Axis Large Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.97 Axis Value Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.43 Axis Value Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.52

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Reliance Inds clocks PAT of Rs 22,290 crore in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/reliance-inds-clocks-pat-of-rs-22290-crore-in-q3-fy26/1665438</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665438</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) for the period under review was Rs 29,697 crore, up 3.7% YoY.

Profit before tax (PBT) for the period under review was Rs 29,697 crore, up 3.7% YoY. EBITDA improved by 6.1% to Rs 50,932 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 48,003 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin was 17.3% in Q3 FY26 as against 18% in Q3 FY25, down 70 basis points YoY. Finance costs increased by 7% YoY to Rs 6,613 crore ($ 736 million), largely due to operationalisation of 5G spectrum assets. Mukesh D. Ambani, chairman and managing director, Reliance Industries, said: “FY26 reflects consistent financial delivery and operational resilience across businesses. This quarter, Jio expanded its subscriber base further, through attractive propositions enabled by its comprehensive, indigenous technology stack tailored for Indian markets. The business delivered a robust financial performance with 16.4% growth in EBITDA. Our Retail business also had an eventful quarter, strengthening its portfolio with the onboarding of fresh new brands and product ranges. The demerger of consumer products business came into effect this quarter. Robust growth in O2C business was led by significantly higher fuel margins with favorable demand-supply dynamics, along with operational flexibility. I am happy to highlight the strong growth in our fuel retailing business, with continuing expansion of the Jio-bp network. Upstream segment EBITDA was impacted by lower volumes and prices. Reliance is entering a new phase of value creation with its initiatives in the AI and New Energy domains. I am confident that Reliance will play a pioneering role in the evolution of these epoch-defining technologies, providing sustainable solutions at scale for India and the world.” Jio Platforms Limited (JPL): JPL’s gross revenue increased by 12.7% to Rs 43,683 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 38,750 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 19,303 crore, higher by 16.4% as compared with the value of Rs 16,585 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. ARPU increased by 5.1% YoY to Rs 213.7 per subscriber per month with higher customer engagement, partly offset by promotional offers for unlimited 5G and fixed broadband services. Monthly churn was stable at 1.8%, with net subscriber addition of 8.9 million during the quarter. Reliance Retail Ventures Limited (RRVL): RRVL’s revenue was Rs 97,605 crore (up 8.1% YoY) while EBITDA from operations was Rs 6,770 crore (up 2.1% YoY) in Q3 FY26. The demerger of consumer products division was completed during the quarter. The business expanded its store network with 431 new store openings, taking the total store count to 19,979 with area under operation at 78.1 million square feet. JioMart crossed exit daily orders of 1.6 million and recorded 53% QoQ and over 360% YoY growth in average daily orders, establishing itself as the fastest-growing player in hyper-local commerce. Oil to Chemical (O2C) Segment: Revenue from O2C segment for 3Q FY26 rose by 8.4% YoY to Rs 162,095 crore ($18.0 billion). Production meant for sale increased by 1.7% on a YoY basis. Fuel retailing operations through Jio-bp expanded its network by 14% YoY to 2,125 outlets, driving volume growth of 24.7% for HSD and 20.8% for MS. Segment EBITDA for 3Q FY26 increased by 14.6% YoY to 16,507 crore ($ 1.8 billion) due to sharp increase in transportation fuel cracks and higher Sulphur realisation partially offset by weakness in downstream chemical margins and higher feedstock freight rates. Favorable ethane cracking economics and domestic market placements continued to support profitability. Reliance BP Mobility (RBML) (operating under brand Jio-bp) operated a country-wide network of 2,125 outlets as on 31 December 2025 as against 1,865 outlets as on 31 December 2024. Oil & Gas (Exploration and Production) Segment: Revenue for Q3 FY26 was Rs 5,833 crore, down 8.4% YoY. This was on account of lower volumes and price realisation for KGD6 gas and condensate. The average price realized for KGD6 gas was $9.65 per MMBTU in Q3 FY26 vis-à-vis $9.74 per MMBTU in Q3 FY25. The average price realised for CBM gas was $9.29 per MMBTU in Q3 FY26 vis-à-vis $10.58 MMBTU in Q3 FY25. JioStar Business: JioStar reported strong revenues of Rs 8,010 crore with EBITDA (including other income) of Rs 1,303 crore for 3Q FY26. Television network reached over 830 million viewers, delivering over 60 billion hours of watch time. JioHotstar averaged 450 million monthly active users (MAUs); up 13% QoQ and almost on par with the IPL quarter (Q1 FY26), clearly demonstrating the platform's momentum. The network's TV entertainment viewership share improved by 100 basis points YoY to 34.6%, further solidifying its position as a preferred entertainment destination. Reliance Industries is India's largest private sector company. Its activities span hydrocarbon exploration and production, petroleum refining and marketing, petrochemicals, advanced materials and composites, renewables (solar and hydrogen), retail and digital services. The scrip had shed 0.06% to end at Rs 1457.60 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RelianceInds_29114129325_476.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1665436</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665436</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the regular plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option and direct plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option of HDFC Arbitrage Fund.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 20 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the regular plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option and direct plan IDCW & monthly IDCW option of HDFC Arbitrage Fund. The amount of distribution (Rs per unit) will be: HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Regular Plan – Normal IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050 HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Direct Plan – Normal IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050 HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050 HDFC Arbitrage Fund – Wholesale Plan – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option (Payout & Reinvestment): 0.050

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Seamec says vessel SEAMEC Agastya back on hire after technical redressal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/seamec-says-vessel-seamec-agastya-back-on-hire-after-technical-redressal/1665369</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665369</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said the vessel resumed deployment after completion of technical redressal.

In a regulatory filing, the company said the vessel resumed deployment after completion of technical redressal. SEAMEC Agastya was rehired with effect from 16 January 2026. Seamec provides offshore support services. It undertakes support services through Diving Support Vessels (DSVs). These vessels are owned and operated by Seamec. The company's subsidiary companies owns and operates bulk carriers. On a consolidated basis, Seamec reported net loss of Rs 27.48 crore in Q2 September 2025 as against net profit of Rs 0.11 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales rose 10.87% YoY to Rs 97.42 crore in Q2 September 2025. Shares of Seamec fell 1.36% to settle at Rs 1056.65 on 16 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SEAMECLtd_17171034074_4760.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>