<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:44:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Auto gains after registering 25% YoY growth in Jan’26 auto sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-auto-gains-after-registering-25-yoy-growth-in-jan26-auto-sales/1670558</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670558</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic sales stood at 2.61 lakh units, up 26% YoY, while exports totalled 2.15 lakh units, marking a 25% YoY growth.

Domestic sales stood at 2.61 lakh units, up 26% YoY, while exports totalled 2.15 lakh units, marking a 25% YoY growth. Two-wheeler sales rose 24% to 4.06 lakh units, while commercial vehicle sales jumped 35% to 71,127 units in January 2026 over January 2025. On a year-to-date basis, Bajaj Auto registered an 8% growth in total auto sales, with 42.24 lakh units sold compared to 39.29 lakh units in the corresponding period last year. Bajaj Auto is engaged in the business of development, manufacturing, and distribution of automobiles such as motorcycles, commercial vehicles, electric two-wheelers, etc., and parts thereof. The company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on an 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajAuto_20897586_28074.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GoI announces the sale of two dated securities for a notified amount of &#8377;29,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/goi-announces-the-sale-of-two-dated-securities-for-a-notified-amount-of-837729000-crore/1670555</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670555</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.68% Government Security 2040” for a notified amount of ₹16,000 crore and “6.90% Government Security 2065” for a notified amount of ₹13,000 crore.

The Government of India (GoI) has announced the sale (re-issue) of “6.68% Government Security 2040” for a notified amount of ₹16,000 crore and “6.90% Government Security 2065” for a notified amount of ₹13,000 crore. The auction will be conducted using multiple price method. Both competitive and non-competitive bids for the auction should be submitted in electronic format on the Reserve Bank of India Core Banking Solution (e-Kuber system) on February 06, 2026 (Friday). GoI will have the option to retain additional subscription up to ₹2,000 crore against each security.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-picture-id156206355_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Housing Finance gains as Q3 PAT rallies 21% YoY to Rs 665 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-housing-finance-gains-as-q3-pat-rallies-21-yoy-to-rs-665-cr/1670556</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670556</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company posted a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 877.68 crore in Q3 FY26 versus Rs 713.02 crore a year ago.

The company posted a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 877.68 crore in Q3 FY26 versus Rs 713.02 crore a year ago. Exceptional items of Rs 13.14 crore were due to a one-time higher gratuity provision linked to New Labour Code changes. The company reported strong quarterly performance for Q3 FY26, with assets under management (AUM) rising 23% to Rs 1,33,412 crore as of 31 December 2025, up from Rs 1,08,314 crore a year ago. Net interest income rose 19% YoY to Rs 963 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 806 crore in Q3 FY25, while net total income climbed 24% to Rs 1,153 crore from Rs 933 crore. The operating expense ratio improved to 19% from 19.8% in the year-ago quarter. Loan losses and provisions rose to Rs 56 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 35 crore in Q3 FY25, including a Rs 10 crore management overlay release. Asset quality remained healthy, with gross and net NPAs at 0.27% and 0.11% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 0.29% and 0.13% a year ago. The provisioning coverage ratio on stage-3 assets stood at 59%, while the capital adequacy ratio, including Tier-II capital, was 23.15%. The company continues to enjoy the highest credit ratings of AAA/Stable for its long-term debt program and A1+ for short-term debt from CRISIL and India Ratings. Bajaj Housing Finance is a non-deposit-taking housing finance company (HFC) registered with the National Housing Bank (NHB) since 2015 and has been offering mortgage loans.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajHousingFinanceLtd_53485527_67886.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US-India agreement on trade deal: US to cut tariffs on India to 18%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-india-agreement-on-trade-deal-us-to-cut-tariffs-on-india-to-18/1670540</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670540</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India and the US agreed to a trade deal under which Washington will bring down reciprocal tariff on Indian goods to 18 per cent from current 25 per cent, US President Donald Trump said on Monday after a phone conversation with Prime Minister Narendra Modi.

India and the US agreed to a trade deal under which Washington will bring down reciprocal tariff on Indian goods to 18 per cent from current 25 per cent, US President Donald Trump said on Monday after a phone conversation with Prime Minister Narendra Modi. Trump claimed India will move forward to reduce "tariffs and non tariff barriers" against the US to zero. Modi said that when two large economies and the world’s largest democracies work together, it benefits our people and unlocks immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation. ”President Trump’s leadership is vital for global peace, stability, and prosperity. India fully supports his efforts for peace”, Modi further stated.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki India gains as production rises 9% YoY in Jan' 26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maruti-suzuki-india-gains-as-production-rises-9-yoy-in-jan-26/1670541</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670541</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total production of passenger vehicles stood at 221,977 units in January 2026, up 9.9% compared with 201,984 units produced in January 2025.

Total production of passenger vehicles stood at 221,977 units in January 2026, up 9.9% compared with 201,984 units produced in January 2025. However, light commercial vehicles production fell 14.34% to 4,169 units in January 2026 compared with 4867 units produced in January 2025. Meanwhile, the automaker reported total sales of 236,963 units in January 2026, registering an 11.6% YoY growth compared with 212,251 units sold in January 2025. In January 2026, the company’s total domestic sales (PV+LCV+OEM) rose 0.4% YoY to 185,943 units, export sales, however, surged 88.3% YoY to 51,020 units, marking an all-time monthly high. Maruti Suzuki India is engaged in the manufacture, purchase, and sale of motor vehicles, components, and spare parts (automobiles). The company reported a 4.08% YoY increase in net profit to Rs 3,879.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,726.9 crore in Q3 FY25, while revenue from operations rose 28.74% YoY to Rs 49,904.1 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axtel Industries rises after Q3 PAT spurts 145% YoY to Rs 8 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axtel-industries-rises-after-q3-pat-spurts-145-yoy-to-rs-8-cr/1670513</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670513</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales jumped 45.09% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 58.63 crore during the quarter.

Net sales jumped 45.09% year-over-year (YoY) to Rs 58.63 crore during the quarter. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 10.83 crore, up by 118.35% from Rs 4.96 crore in Q3 FY25. Total operating expenditure rose by 34.83% to Rs 49.24 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of material consumed was at Rs 22.85 crore (up 41.08% YoY), employee benefit expense stood at Rs 11.14 crore (up 7.43% YoY), and other expense was at Rs 10.84 crore (up 57.56% YoY) during the period under review. Axtel Industries (AIL) manufactures custom-designed food processing plants and machinery tailored to clients’ requirements.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AxtelIndustries_77645227543_2905.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR rebounds by over 1% in opening trades ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-rebounds-by-over-1-in-opening-trades/1670506</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670506</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee bounces back below Rs 91 per dollar mark in opening trades on Tuesday, extending previous day rebound.

The Indian rupee bounces back below Rs 91 per dollar mark in opening trades on Tuesday, extending previous day rebound. INR opened at Rs 90.30 per dollar and slipped to a low of 90.58 so far during the day. The counter is up more than 1% so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee gained 42 paise to close at 91.51 against the US dollar during the first session after Union Budget 2026-27. The counter was largely supported by sharp fall in international crude oil prices and positive cues from local equities. Crude oil prices are down more than 5 percent after U.S. President Donald Trump said he was hopeful of agreeing a deal with Iran. Indian shares bounced back on Monday after tumbling during the special weekend trading session on Sunday amid disappointment over the government's budget proposal to increase taxes on equity derivatives trading. The benchmark BSE Sensex jumped 943.52 points, or 1.17 percent, to 81,666.46, after having fallen nearly 2 percent the previous day - marking the second sharpest fall on Budget Day since 2014. The broader NSE Nifty index surged 262.95 points, or 1.06 percent, to 25,088.40.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex skyrockets 2,341 pts; Nifty jumps above 25,750 mark; VIX spurts 7.51%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-skyrockets-2341-pts-nifty-jumps-above-25750-mark-vix-spurts-751/1670504</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670504</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with strong gains in early trade after India and the United States finalised a long-awaited trade deal late Monday night.

The domestic equity indices traded with strong gains in early trade after India and the United States finalised a long-awaited trade deal late Monday night. Positive global cues and improved investor sentiment following the agreement boosted buying interest across sectors, lifting benchmark indices in the opening session. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark. All the sectoral indices traded in the green on the NSE with realty, financial services and auto shares gaining the most. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, zoomed 2,340.53 points or 2.89% to 84,021.86. The Nifty 50 index added 701.10 points or 2.83% to 25,789.80. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 3% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.73%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,894 shares rose and 404 shares fell. A total of 143 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 7.51% to 14.91. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,832.46 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,446.33 crore in the Indian equity market on 2 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Ather Energy added 4.86% after its consolidated net loss narrowed to Rs 84.6 crore in Q3 Fy26 compared with net loss of Rs 197.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 50.2% YoY to Rs 953.6 crore in Q3 FY26. Tata Chemicals shed 0.76%. The company’s consolidated net loss widened to Rs 93 crore compared with net loss of Rs 53 crore posted in corresponding period last year. Revenue from operations fell 1.11% YoY to Rs 3350 crore during the quarter. Bajaj Housing Finance added 1.94% after it has reported a 21.33% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 664.89 crore on 17.85% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2885.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.74% to 6.719 compared with previous session close of 6.769. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.4750 compared with its close of 91.4950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement added 3.04% to Rs 148,541. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.16% to 97.45. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.09% to 4.282. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell 20 cents or 0.30% to $66.10 a barrel. Global Markets: Most Asian indices rose on Tuesday after the U.S. and India trade deal, sparking a sharp risk-on move across the region. Japan's Nikkei 225 jumped nearly 3% and the Topix rose over 2%. South Korea’s Kospi surged about 5%, triggering a buy-side trading curb. U.S. stocks climbed overnight as Wall Street kicked off the new month on a positive note, with investors looking past recent volatility in silver and bitcoin and turning their focus to the upcoming earnings slate. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.05%, the S&P 500 gained 0.54%, and the Nasdaq Composite added 0.56%. Markets are also tracking key economic signals and cues from the Federal Reserve on interest rates, even as efforts continue in Washington to avert a partial government shutdown. Data releases have been disrupted, with the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics postponing the January jobs report and other labour data until federal operations resume.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Ports spurts after recording 12% YoY growth in Jan ’26 cargo volumes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-ports-spurts-after-recording-12-yoy-growth-in-jan-26-cargo-volumes/1670503</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670503</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The growth was driven by strong performance in containers (16% YoY), liquids (21% YoY), and dry cargo (8% YoY).

The growth was driven by strong performance in containers (16% YoY), liquids (21% YoY), and dry cargo (8% YoY). Logistics rail volume during Jan’26 stood at 59,308 TEUs, up 3% YoY, while GPWIS volume was recorded at 1.9 MMT, remaining flat on a YoY basis. On a year-to-date (YTD) basis till January 2026, APSEZ handled total cargo of 412.2 MMT, marking an 11% YoY increase, primarily led by container volumes, which rose 18% YoY. Logistics rail volume during YTD Jan’26 stood at 588,179 TEUs, up 10% YoY, while GPWIS volume was at 18 MMT, flat YoY. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) is the largest private port operator in India. APSEZ operates a portfolio of 15 domestic ports/terminals with an international presence at 4 global ports/terminals. Along with its port operations, it has its wide logistics network and offers various port-based marine services to its owned ports/terminals as well as other ports. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) has reported a 29% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,120 crore on a 30% rise in revenue to Rs 9,167 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The counter jumped 4.76% to Rs 1,402.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniPorts_15044199473_21281.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Network People Services Technologies Ltd Spurts 19.95%, BSE Information Technology index Gains 4.54%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-spurts-1995-bse-information-technology-index-gains-454/1670501</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670501</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Network People Services Technologies Ltd gained 19.95% today to trade at Rs 1425.

Network People Services Technologies Ltd gained 19.95% today to trade at Rs 1425. The BSE Information Technology index is up 4.54% to quote at 38269.21. The index is up 3.05 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Innovana Thinklabs Ltd increased 9.22% and Control Print Ltd added 8.81% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 8.06 % over last one year compared to the 10.54% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Network People Services Technologies Ltd has added 1.18% over last one month compared to 3.05% gain in BSE Information Technology index and 0.51% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 606 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2388 on 04 Aug 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 03 Feb 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Network-People-Services-Technologies-Ltd_97933685_75371.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty may take wing at opening bell as India-US trade ice melts]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-may-take-wing-at-opening-bell-as-india-us-trade-ice-melts/1670491</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670491</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 298.50 points, suggesting a strong start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 298.50 points, suggesting a strong start for the Nifty 50 today. India and the U.S. reached a major trade deal on Monday, with Washington cutting tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrapping the additional 25% penalty linked to India’s purchases of Russian oil. Trump said India would reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero and stop buying Russian crude, signalling a thaw in bilateral ties after months of tension. The deal boosts momentum toward a long-term trade target of $500 billion by 2030, lifts sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, and is expected to benefit export-heavy sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,832.46 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,446.33 crore in the Indian equity market on 2 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 1856.34 so far in February (till 2 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Most Asian indices rose on Tuesday after the U.S. and India trade deal, sparking a sharp risk-on move across the region. Japan's Nikkei 225 jumped nearly 3% and the Topix rose over 2%. South Korea’s Kospi surged about 5%, triggering a buy-side trading curb. U.S. stocks climbed overnight as Wall Street kicked off the new month on a positive note, with investors looking past recent volatility in silver and bitcoin and turning their focus to the upcoming earnings slate. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.05%, the S&P 500 gained 0.54%, and the Nasdaq Composite added 0.56%. Markets are also tracking key economic signals and cues from the Federal Reserve on interest rates, even as efforts continue in Washington to avert a partial government shutdown. Data releases have been disrupted, with the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics postponing the January jobs report and other labour data until federal operations resume. Domestic Market: Equity benchmarks staged a sharp comeback on Monday, breaking a two-session slide as investors weighed the union budget's implications for market sentiment and capital flows. Buying momentum returned despite proposals to raise securities transaction taxes on derivatives and the absence of fresh steps to lure foreign capital. The Nifty reclaimed territory above the 25,050 mark, powered by firm gains in auto, energy and metal stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 943.52 points or 1.17% to 81,666.46. The Nifty 50 index jumped 262.95 points or 1.06% to 25,088.40. In the past two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.73% while the Nifty fell 0.91%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Ather Energy, Tata Chemicals, APSEZ,  Maruti Suzuki India]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-ather-energy-tata-chemicals-apsez-maruti-suzuki-india/1670488</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670488</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 3 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 3 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Export and import oriented stocks will be in focus after India and United States signed a trade deal under which tariffs will be reduced from 50% to 18% while the additional 25% duty linked to the purchases of Russian crude oil will be eliminated. Ather Energy’s consolidated net loss narrowed to Rs 84.6 crore in Q3 Fy26 compared with net loss of Rs 197.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 50.2% YoY to Rs 953.6 crore in Q3 FY26. Tata Chemicals’ consolidated net loss widened to Rs 93 crore compared with net loss of Rs 53 crore posted in corresponding period last year. Revenue from operations fell 1.11% YoY to Rs 3350 crore during the quarter. Bajaj Housing Finance reported a 21.33% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 664.89 crore on 17.85% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2885.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. RailTel Corporation of India reported a 4.07% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 62.40 crore despite a 19% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Adani Ports & Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) handled total cargo of 44.8 MMT in January 2026, marking a 12% year-on-year increase. The growth was led by containers (up 16% YoY), liquids (up 21% YoY) and dry cargo (up 8% YoY). Maruti Suzuki India’s production volume increased 9.33% to 226,146 units in January 2025, compared with 206,851 units produced in January 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Chiraharit bags Rs 1-cr order from Larsen & Toubro for solar system project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/chiraharit-bags-rs-1-cr-order-from-larsen-toubro-for-solar-system-project/1670460</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670460</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the supply of pipes and fittings as per the bill of quantities (BOQ), along with installation services.

The order involves the supply of pipes and fittings as per the bill of quantities (BOQ), along with installation services. The project will be executed in Ranchi and includes both supply and service components. The company stated that the order will be completed within the mutually agreed timeline from the date of the work order. The total value of the contract stands at Rs 1,17,73,975.34. Chiraharit also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in Larsen & Toubro. Further, the company confirmed that the transaction does not fall under the category of related-party transactions in accordance with applicable regulatory norms. Chiraharit is engaged in turnkey EPC (Engineering, Procurement and Construction) projects focusing on two broad segments, viz., water-based and renewable energy-based. In the water sector, our focus is on the efficient and reliable movement of piped water in pressurised applications. The company reported a 745.9% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 6.26 crore in FY25, compared with Rs 0.74 crore in the corresponding previous year. Revenue from operations jumped 95.1% to Rs 59.63 crore in FY25, as against Rs 30.57 crore in FY24. Chiraharit shares debuted in the market on 8 October 2025. The scrip was listed at Rs 16.80, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The current price of Chiraharit shares has declined 4.25% to Rs 7.66.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ChiraharitLtd_99766171_95334.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>