<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:32:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Netweb Technologies India Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/netweb-technologies-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1663161</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663161</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ola Electric Mobility Ltd, PC Jeweller Ltd, Cyient Ltd and MTAR Technologies Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 January 2026.

Ola Electric Mobility Ltd, PC Jeweller Ltd, Cyient Ltd and MTAR Technologies Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 January 2026. Netweb Technologies India Ltd soared 10.48% to Rs 3342 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.51 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 42670 shares in the past one month. Ola Electric Mobility Ltd spiked 6.65% to Rs 43.63. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 185.56 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 108.15 lakh shares in the past one month. PC Jeweller Ltd surged 5.75% to Rs 10.11. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 66.69 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 45.3 lakh shares in the past one month. Cyient Ltd gained 5.58% to Rs 1168.45. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 45926 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 26838 shares in the past one month. MTAR Technologies Ltd rose 4.94% to Rs 2490.75. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 14759 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10772 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NetwebTechnologiesIndiaLtd_73333970_78854.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yes Bank's loan book rises to Rs 2.57 lakh crore in Q3 FY26; deposits up 5% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yes-banks-loan-book-rises-to-rs-257-lakh-crore-in-q3-fy26-deposits-up-5-yoy/1663159</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663159</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Deposits of the bank stood at Rs 292,484 crore during the period under review, up 5.5% YoY and 1.3% QoQ.

Deposits of the bank stood at Rs 292,484 crore during the period under review, up 5.5% YoY and 1.3% QoQ. The bank's CASA (current account savings account) ratio improved to 34% as of 31 December 2025, up from 33.1% a year earlier and 33.7% in the previous quarter. The credit-to-deposit ratio stood at 88% as of 31 December 2025, compared to 88.3% in the same period of the previous year and 84.5% in the previous quarter. The liquidity coverage ratio was at 123.8% as of 31 December 2025, as against 133.2% as of 31 December 2024 and 125.1% as of 30 September 2025. Yes Bank is a full-service commercial bank providing a complete range of products, services, and technology-driven digital offerings, catering to retail and MSME as well as corporate clients. The bank reported an 18.3% rise in net profit to Rs 654 crore on a 9.4% increase in total net income to Rs 3,945 crore in Q2 September 2025 as compared with Q2 September 2024. Shares of Yes Bank rose 0.58% to Rs 22.42 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/YesBank_75840425465_25267.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with minor cuts; realty shares rally for 3rd day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-minor-cuts-realty-shares-rally-for-3rd-day/1663155</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663155</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded between small gains and losses in the mid-morning trade as investors weighed robust corporate updates against rising geopolitical risks.

The key equity indices traded between small gains and losses in the mid-morning trade as investors weighed robust corporate updates against rising geopolitical risks. Early optimism over improving quarterly earnings was tempered by caution surrounding the implications of U.S. military action in Venezuela. The Nifty traded below 26,300 level. Realty shares extended gains for the three consecutive trading sessions. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 49.34 points or 0.06% to 85,712.67. The Nifty 50 index shed 2.65 points or 0.01% to 26,325.90. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.06% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.01%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,761 shares rose and 2,249 shares fell. A total of 208 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index rose 1.55% to 912.75. The index added 4.93% in the four consecutive trading session. Sobha (up 4.81%), Lodha Developers (up 3.76%), DLF (up 1.46%), Oberoi Realty (up 1.33%), Anant Raj (up 1.24%), Godrej Properties (up 1.18%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.99%), Phoenix Mills (up 0.22%) added. On the other hand, Brigade Enterprises (down 0.33%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.06%), edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: Bank of Maharashtra rose 1.31% after the bank reported a 15.30% year-on-year (YoY) increase in total deposits to Rs 3,21,695 crore as of 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 2,79,007 crore as of 31st December 2024. V-Mart Retail jumped 4.88% after the company’s revenue from operations for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 stood at Rs 1,126 crore, recording the growth of 10%, compared with Rs 1,027 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. CSB Bank jumped 7.08% after the bank’s total deposits climbed 21% to Rs 40,460 crore as on 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 33,407 crore as on 31st December 2024. Global Markets: Asia market began the first full trading week of 2026 on a stronger note after the U.S. said it had attacked Venezuela and captured President Nicolas Maduro over the weekend. Oil prices edged lower as markets weighed the potential impact of geopolitical tensions. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. Oil prices fell after the escalation involving the oil-rich nation. Brent crude prices slipped more than 1% earlier before paring losses, and were last trading 0.25% lower, while the West Texas Intermediate crude prices fell 0.4%. On Friday stateside, the first trading day of 2026, the S&P 500 closed slightly higher as gains in semiconductor names kept the index afloat. The benchmark closed up 0.19% at 6,858.47, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.03% to finish at 23,235.63. The two had been solidly positive earlier in the day, with the S&P 500 and the tech-heavy Nasdaq trading higher by 0.7% and 1.5% at their peaks, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nisus Finance Services rises after NCCCL bags Rs 112.5 crore Lodha order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nisus-finance-services-rises-after-ncccl-bags-rs-1125-crore-lodha-order/1663153</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663153</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NCCCL received a letter of award for the first residential tower at Lodha Alibaug in Mandwa.

NCCCL received a letter of award for the first residential tower at Lodha Alibaug in Mandwa. The project is part of a 200 plus acre township and falls under Phase 1 of the development. The order covers core RCC works for a high rise structure. It involves a built up area of about 7.26 lakh sq ft. The scope includes a G plus 3 podium, 35 upper floors, and ancillary structures. Construction is expected to begin around mid January 2026. The execution timeline is about 24 months. This is NCCCL's third project with the Lodha Group. NCCCL is a Mumbai-based engineering and construction company with a track record across residential, commercial, industrial, and institutional projects in India. Nisus Finance acquired a majority stake in NCCCL in August 2025. Nisus Finance Services Co specializes in urban infrastructure financing and private capital market transactions. As on H1 FY26, it is managing assets worth Rs 1906 crore. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Nisus Finance Services Co rose 46.06% to Rs 15.38 crore while total income surged 484.51% to Rs 113.57 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NisusFinanceServicesCoLtd_87296015_93509.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of Maharashtra gains after total deposits rise 15% YoY to Rs 3.21 lakh crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-maharashtra-gains-after-total-deposits-rise-15-yoy-to-rs-321-lakh-crore-in-q3/1663149</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663149</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total business grew 17.24% YoY to Rs 5,95,171 crore as of 31st December 2025, up from Rs 5,07,650 crore as of 31st December 2024.

The total business grew 17.24% YoY to Rs 5,95,171 crore as of 31st December 2025, up from Rs 5,07,650 crore as of 31st December 2024. CASA deposits stood at Rs 1,59,397 crore as of 31st December 2025, a 15.93% increase compared to Rs 1,37,494 crore a year ago. CASA ratio improved to 49.55% from 49.28% during the same period. Global advances rose 19.61% YoY to Rs 2,73,476 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 2,28,642 crore as of 31 December 2024. Bank of Maharashtra is engaged in providing banking services. The bank's segments include treasury, corporate/wholesale banking, retail banking, and other banking operations. The Government of India held a 79.60% stake in the bank as of 30 September 2025. Bank of Maharashtra’s standalone net profit jumped 23.09% to Rs 1,633.14 crore on 17.1% increase in total income to Rs 7,973.61 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofMaha_49685557243_5607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Timken India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-timken-india-ltd-counter/1663147</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663147</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Schaeffler India Ltd, Astrazeneca Pharma India Ltd, Gillette India Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 05 January 2026.

Schaeffler India Ltd, Astrazeneca Pharma India Ltd, Gillette India Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 05 January 2026. Timken India Ltd witnessed volume of 25719 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 16.76 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1534 shares. The stock increased 0.80% to Rs.3,074.70. Volumes stood at 3851 shares in the last session. Schaeffler India Ltd notched up volume of 16261 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 13.83 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1176 shares. The stock slipped 0.39% to Rs.3,857.80. Volumes stood at 324 shares in the last session. Astrazeneca Pharma India Ltd saw volume of 3976 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7.24 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 549 shares. The stock dropped 2.18% to Rs.8,424.00. Volumes stood at 353 shares in the last session. Gillette India Ltd recorded volume of 13798 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.05 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2280 shares. The stock lost 0.22% to Rs.8,199.90. Volumes stood at 1011 shares in the last session. Aegis Logistics Ltd registered volume of 58727 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.95 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 9868 shares. The stock rose 3.45% to Rs.751.15. Volumes stood at 10534 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimkenIndia_38040425983_2226.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[V-Mart Retail rallies after revenue jumps 10% YoY in Q3 FY26.]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/v-mart-retail-rallies-after-revenue-jumps-10-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663146</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663146</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The quarter witnessed a shift in sales owing to a larger share of Durga Puja festivities falling in Q2 in the current year, compared with the previous year.

The quarter witnessed a shift in sales owing to a larger share of Durga Puja festivities falling in Q2 in the current year, compared with the previous year. Same-store sales growth (SSSG) remained flat during the quarter, with V-Mart reporting nil growth, while Unlimited, the fashion retail chain acquired from Arvind Fashions in 2021, recorded a 2% increase. During the quarter, the company opened 23 and closed 2 stores. This brings year-to-date (YTD) additions to 63 and closures to 6, resulting in a total operating portfolio of 554 stores as at Q3 end. The 23 new stores include 5 stores in Uttar Pradesh, 4 stores in Gujarat, 3 stores Bihar, 2 stores each in Haryana, Madhya Pradesh & Tamil Nadu, and 1 store each in Delhi, Chhattisgarh, Uttarakhand, Jharkhand and Punjab. V-Mart operates a chain of value retail stores across multiple Indian cities. The company reported standalone net loss of Rs 8.87 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 56.51 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales surged 22.1% YoY to Rs 806.87 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VMartRetail_17420315948_34162.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Manulife MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-manulife-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1663152</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663152</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra Manulife Mutual Fund has announced 07 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

Mahindra Manulife Mutual Fund has announced 07 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Mahindra Manulife Aggressive Hybrid Fund: Regular Plan Monthly – IDCW: 0.18 Direct Plan Monthly – IDCW: 0.18

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tobacco Institute of India requests government to review and reconsider latest hike in taxes on Tobacco]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tobacco-institute-of-india-requests-government-to-review-and-reconsider-latest-hike-in-taxes-on-tobacco/1663143</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663143</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Tobacco Institute of India (TII) has said in a latest update that it is surprised by the unprecedented increase in duty announced on Wednesday on tobacco and related products.

The Tobacco Institute of India (TII) has said in a latest update that it is surprised by the unprecedented increase in duty announced on Wednesday on tobacco and related products. It noted that given the statements made by the government on more than one occasion, that the overall impact of the transition of taxes will be revenue neutral. Such a massive increase will cause immense hardship and loss to millions of farmers, MSMEs, retailers and local value chains nurtured by the Industry, besides providing a huge fillip to illicit industry and damaging national enterprises. TII requests the government to review the computations behind this extremely severe tax increase and reconsider the enormous hike given the huge implications. The Finance Ministry has amended the Central Excise Act, imposing an excise duty of Rs 2,050-Rs 8,500 per 1,000 sticks depending on the length of cigarettes. This will be in addition to a 40% GST.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-calculator-tax-return-taxes-1241517_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty pare losses; auto shares advance for 5th day in row]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-pare-losses-auto-shares-advance-for-5th-day-in-row/1663141</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663141</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks recovered from early losses to trade marginally higher in the morning trade as investors weighed robust corporate updates against rising geopolitical risks.

The key equity benchmarks recovered from early losses to trade marginally higher in the morning trade as investors weighed robust corporate updates against rising geopolitical risks. Early optimism over improving quarterly earnings was tempered by caution surrounding the implications of U.S. military action in Venezuela. The Nifty traded above the 26,350 mark, while auto shares extended gains for a fifth consecutive session. At 10:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 109.80 points or 0.11% to 85,854.13. The Nifty 50 index rose 29 points or 0.11% to 26,357.55. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.17% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.19%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,818 shares rose and 1,982 shares fell. A total of 238 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index rose 0.98% to 10,258.90. The index added surged 5.36% in the five consecutive trading session. Eicher Motors (up 1.21%), TVS Motor Company (up 0.98%), Hero MotoCorp (up 0.98%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 0.96%), Exide Industries (up 0.94%), Ashok Leyland (up 0.63%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 0.59%), Uno Minda (up 0.34%), Bajaj Auto (up 0.24%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 0.14%) added. On the other hand, Tube Investments of India (down 1.43%), Samvardhana Motherson International (down 0.94%) and Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 0.81%) eged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: CSB Bank jumped 7.08% after the bank’s total deposits climbed 21% to Rs 40,460 crore as on 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 33,407 crore as on 31st December 2024. Mini Diamonds (India) jumped 4.15% after the company announced that it has secured an export order worth $1.85 million (approximately Rs 16.65 crore) for the supply of lab-grown diamonds to a prominent overseas client based in Hong Kong. NIBE surged 5.46% after it has secured a domestic defence contract worth Rs 292.69 crore from the Indian Army under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of India rises as global business spurts 12% YoY in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-india-rises-as-global-business-spurts-12-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663139</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663139</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Global deposits stood at Rs 8,87,287 crore, reflecting an 11.64% YoY increase, while global gross advances rose 13.55% to Rs 7,39,811 crore on 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 6,51,507 crore on 31 December 2024.

Global deposits stood at Rs 8,87,287 crore, reflecting an 11.64% YoY increase, while global gross advances rose 13.55% to Rs 7,39,811 crore on 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 6,51,507 crore on 31 December 2024. Domestic gross advances also saw robust growth of 15.07%, reaching Rs 6,28,617 crore on 31 December 2025, up from Rs 5,46,268 crore in the same quarter last year. Domestic deposits rose 12.80% YoY to Rs 7,65,500 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 6,78,626 crore a year earlier. Bank of India is an India-based bank. The bank's segments include treasury operations, wholesale banking, and retail banking. The treasury operations segment includes the entire investment portfolio, which deals in government and other securities, money market operations, and foreign exchange operations. The company’s standalone net profit climbed 7.6% to Rs 2,554.57 crore on a 3.8% increase in total income to Rs 20,625.92 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofIndia_12067469065_5654.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Housing Finance clocks over 31% YoY growth in Q3 disbursements ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-housing-finance-clocks-over-31-yoy-growth-in-q3-disbursements/1663136</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663136</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Assets under management (AUM) grew by 23% to approximately Rs 1,33,400 crore as of 31 December 2025 as compared to Rs 1,08,314 crore as of 31 December 2024.

Assets under management (AUM) grew by 23% to approximately Rs 1,33,400 crore as of 31 December 2025 as compared to Rs 1,08,314 crore as of 31 December 2024. Accordingly, AUM in Q3 FY26 grew by approximately Rs 6,652 crore. The company’s loan assets (AR) stood at approximately Rs 1,17,290 crore as of 31 December 2025 as compared to Rs 95,570 crore as of 31 December 2024, up 22.7% YoY. Bajaj Housing Finance is registered with National Housing Bank (NHB) as a non-deposit taking housing finance company and has been engaged in the business of mortgage lending since FY2018. It is subsidiary of Bajaj Finance and part of Bajaj group. It got listed on the exchanges in September 2024 through an Initial Public Offering (IPO). The company had reported 18% rise in net profit to Rs 643 crore on a 34% increase in net interest income to Rs 956 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip rose 0.40% to currently trade at Rs 96.99 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajHousingFinanceLtd_53485527_67886.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan Bank jumps as total deposits rise 11% YoY in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-bank-jumps-as-total-deposits-rise-11-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663137</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663137</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank's total deposits declined by 0.9% compared with the Rs 158,075 crore reported in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

The bank's total deposits declined by 0.9% compared with the Rs 158,075 crore reported in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Bulk deposits stood at Rs 43,303 crore in Q3 FY26, down 2% YoY and 5.8% QoQ. The retail-to-total deposits ratio rose to 72.37% in the quarter ended 31 December 2025, compared to 68.65% recorded in the quarter ended 31 December 2024. The bank's CASA deposits stood at Rs 42,730 crore in Q3 FY26, down 4.5% YoY and 3.3% QoQ. The CASA ratio declined to 27.26% in the quarter ended 31 December 2025, compared to 31.73% in the quarter ended 31 December 2024 and 27.97% in the quarter ended September 2025. Loans and advances (on-book + PTC) increased by 10% to Rs 145,227 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 132,019 crore posted in the quarter ended 31 December 2024. On a QoQ basis, loans and advances (on-book + PTC) advanced 3.7% from Rs 140,041 crore. The bank's LCR as of 31 December 2025 stood approximately at 149.14%. Collection efficiency for the month of December 2025 was approximately 98.1%, compared with 97.8% in September 2025. The collection efficiency of the emerging entrepreneurs’ business (EEB) (micro) segment was 98%, and that of the non-EEB segment was 98.3% in December 2025. Bandhan Bank is a private sector bank. Its distribution network spans nearly 6,350 outlets. It added 9 lakh customers during the quarter, and current customers stand at over 3.23 crore customers. The bank currently has over 73,500 employees. The bank’s net profit plunged 88.1% year-on-year to Rs 112 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 937 crore in Q2 FY25, primarily due to a steep rise in provisions. Net total income declined 11.5% YoY to Rs 3,135 crore from Rs 3,543 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BandhanBankLtd_94952261769_68090.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CSB Bank hits record high on 21% YoY deposit growth in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/csb-bank-hits-record-high-on-21-yoy-deposit-growth-in-q3-fy26/1663133</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663133</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Of the total deposits, CASA increased 3% YoY to Rs 8,316 crore, while term deposits jumped 27% YoY to Rs 32,144 crore as of 31 December 2025.

Of the total deposits, CASA increased 3% YoY to Rs 8,316 crore, while term deposits jumped 27% YoY to Rs 32,144 crore as of 31 December 2025. Gross advance stood at Rs 37,208 crore as of 31st December 2025, registering the growth of 29% compared with Rs 28,915 crore as of 31st December 2024. Advances against gold & gold jewellery (excluding receivables secured against gold) jumped 46% YoY to Rs 19,023 crore as of 31st December 2025. CSB Bank offers a wide range of products and services to its customer, with particular focus on SME, Retail, and NRI customers and operates 838 branches as on 30 September 2025. The business is concentrated in Kerala with the remaining spread across Tamil Nadu, Andhra Pradesh, Karnataka, and Maharashtra. The bank’s standalone net profit jumped 15.8% to Rs 160.33 crore on 37% increase in total income to Rs 1458.36 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip hit an all-time high at Rs 519.95 in intraday today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CSBBankLtd_22037117_5525.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mini Diamonds India rises after bagging $1.85 million export order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mini-diamonds-india-rises-after-bagging-185-million-export-order/1663132</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663132</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order is expected to further strengthen its export momentum and international order pipeline.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order is expected to further strengthen its export momentum and international order pipeline. Continued demand from overseas buyers highlights MDIL’s ability to convert repeat enquiries into confirmed business across export markets. The latest order also adds to the company’s growing export traction from Hong Kong, reaffirming the region as a key market in its international export journey. The company added that this continued export traction aligns with MDIL’s strategy to deepen its presence in priority markets through disciplined execution, product consistency and customer continuity. It remains focused on strengthening operational readiness to service repeat orders, improving turnaround efficiency, and building a sustainable overseas order book, while continuing to explore additional opportunities across key international geographies. Commenting on the development, Upendra N. Shah, Chairman and Managing Director of Mini Diamonds (India), said that the export order reflects sustained confidence from our international customers and reinforces our ability to build repeat business in key overseas markets, including Hong Kong. Our focus remains on stringent quality standards, predictable delivery timelines, and disciplined execution to strengthen customer continuity. As we scale our export footprint, we are enhancing operational readiness and turnaround efficiency to support repeat orders and progressively larger requirements, while building a resilient and sustainable international order book.” Mini Diamonds (India) (MDIL) is engaged in the business of manufacturing and trading diamonds. The company reported a standalone net profit of Rs 1.82 crore in Q2 FY26, down 1.1% from Rs 1.84 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 12.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 100.46 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MiniDiamondsIndiaLtd_25057542520_2031.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NIBE gains on bagging Rs 293-cr defence order from Indian Army]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nibe-gains-on-bagging-rs-293-cr-defence-order-from-indian-army/1663131</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663131</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the manufacturing and supply of ground equipment, accessories, ESP and ammunition for a Universal Rocket Launcher System capable of integrating multiple rocket types, including long-range rockets with strike capabilities of 150 km and 300 km.

The order involves the manufacturing and supply of ground equipment, accessories, ESP and ammunition for a Universal Rocket Launcher System capable of integrating multiple rocket types, including long-range rockets with strike capabilities of 150 km and 300 km. As per the contract terms, the company is required to furnish a performance-cum-warranty bank guarantee equivalent to 10% of the total contract value within 30 days of signing the agreement. The contract will be executed in tranches over a period of 12 months. The total consideration of Rs 292.69 crore is inclusive of all taxes and duties. The company clarified that the order has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related-party transactions. Further, the promoters or promoter group entities do not have any interest in the awarding authority. NIBE operates in manufacturing critical components for the defence sector, electric vehicles (E-Vehicles), and software development. The company is engaged in fabrication and machining of components used in the defence sector, as well as assembly of components for E-vehicles. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 8.44 crore in Q2FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 9.12 crore posted in Q2FY25. Revenue from operations fell 46.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 73.37 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KavitaFabrics_98715753806_43224.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PNB rises as domestic deposits climb 8% YoY in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pnb-rises-as-domestic-deposits-climb-8-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663130</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663130</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank's domestic advances stood at Rs 11,67,801 crore on 31 December 2025, up 10.15% YoY and up 4.47% QoQ.

The bank's domestic advances stood at Rs 11,67,801 crore on 31 December 2025, up 10.15% YoY and up 4.47% QoQ. The bank’s global advances increased 10.98% YoY to Rs 12,32,245 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 11,10,292 crore a year earlier and rose 5.36% QoQ from Rs 11,69,592 crore as of 30 September 2025. As of 31 December 2025, the bank’s global deposits stood at Rs 16,60,385 crore, registering a growth of 8.54% YoY and 2.68% QoQ. The bank's global business stood at Rs 28,92,630 crore as of 31 December 2025, recording a growth of 9.57% YoY and 3.80% QoQ. The global credit-deposit ratio advanced to 74.21% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 72.58% recorded a year earlier on 31 December 2024. Punjab National Bank is engaged in treasury operations, corporate/wholesale banking, retail banking, digital banking, and others. As of 30th September 2025, the bank has 10,228 domestic branches and 2 international branches. Out of the total number of branches, the bank has 63.3% of branches in rural & semi-urban areas. The bank’s standalone net profit climbed 13.95% to Rs 4,903.73 crore on a 5.13% jump in total income to Rs 36,213.62 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[J&K Bank gains as gross advances grow 17% YoY in Q3FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jk-bank-gains-as-gross-advances-grow-17-yoy-in-q3fy26/1663129</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663129</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total business stood at Rs 2,72,109.27 crore as of 31 December 2025, up 13.34%, compared with Rs 2,40,080.49 crore as of 31 December 2024.

Total business stood at Rs 2,72,109.27 crore as of 31 December 2025, up 13.34%, compared with Rs 2,40,080.49 crore as of 31 December 2024. CASA deposits rose 1.25% YoY to Rs 68,736.27 crore as of 31 December 2025. CASA ratio reduced to 44.10% as of 31 December 2025 as against 48.17% as of 31 December 2024. Total deposits increased 10.58% to Rs 1,55,861.35 crore as of 31 Decemeber 2025, compared with Rs 1,40,947.14 crore as of 31 December 2024. Gross investment declined 2.07% to Rs 40,535.76 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 41,394.29 crore as of 31 December 2024. J&K Bank offers banking services under the three major divisions as support services, depository services, and third-party services. The bank reported a 1.91% jump in net profit to Rs 494.11 crore on a 2.04% decline in total income to Rs 3,446.71 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q1 FY26. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit declined 10.31%, and revenue rose 0.79% in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JKBank_38858702295_7311.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Finance gains as Q3 disbursements climb 7% YoY to Rs 17,600-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-finance-gains-as-q3-disbursements-climb-7-yoy-to-rs-17600-cr/1663127</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663127</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[For the nine months ended FY26, disbursements are seen at approximately Rs 43,900 crore, reflecting a 4% YoY increase, excluding finance leases.

For the nine months ended FY26, disbursements are seen at approximately Rs 43,900 crore, reflecting a 4% YoY increase, excluding finance leases. The company’s business assets are estimated at about Rs 1.29 lakh crore as of December 2025, marking a 12% growth on a year-on-year basis, supported by steady performance across lending segments. Asset quality remained stable, with collection efficiency estimated at 95% in Q3 FY26, unchanged from the same period last year. As of 31 December 2025, Stage-3 assets are estimated to be in the range of 3.9–4.0%, largely flat compared with 3.9% a year ago. Stage-2 assets are estimated at 5.4–5.5%, improving from 6.3% in the year-ago period, indicating better early-stage delinquencies. The company continued to maintain a strong liquidity position, with a liquidity buffer of over Rs 8,850 crore on its balance sheet. Mahindra Finance, part of the Mahindra Group, is one of India’s leading non-banking finance companies. Focused on the rural and semi-urban sector, the company has over 11 million customers. The company is a leading vehicle and tractor financier, provides loans to SMEs and also offers fixed deposits. The company has 1,352 offices and reaches out to customers spread over 5,16,000 villages and 8,000 towns across the country, transforming more than 1.1 crore lives. The NBFC’s standalone net profit jumped 54.08% to Rs 569.31 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 369.47 crore reported in Q2 FY25. Total income increased by 14.37% year on year to Rs 4,489.24 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MMFinServ_95105710_16795.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Corona Remedies gains as Q2 PAT climbs 22% YoY to Rs 52 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/corona-remedies-gains-as-q2-pat-climbs-22-yoy-to-rs-52-cr/1663125</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663125</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 21.67% year on year (YoY) to Rs 69.78 crore in Q2 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 21.67% year on year (YoY) to Rs 69.78 crore in Q2 FY26. Earnings Before Interest, Taxes, Depreciation, and Amortization (EBITDA) stood at Rs 78.47 crore, with EBITDA margin at 21.7% in Q2 FY26. Total expenditure climbed 14.4% YoY to Rs 282.66 crore. Raw material costs declined 9.3% YoY to Rs 25.9 crore. Employee expenses rose 17.3% YoY to Rs 103 crore. Interest costs eased 32.8% YoY to Rs 1.93 crore, while depreciation inched up 1.7% YoY to Rs 9.2 crore. On Half year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 35.10% to Rs 98.52 crore on 16.92% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 707.67 crore in H1 FY26, compared with H1 FY25. Nirav K. Mehta, MD and CEO, CORONA Remedies, said: “We are delighted to report a strong financial performance in Q2 and H1 FY26. Revenues for Q2 and H1FY26 grew by 15.1% and 17.0% respectively on a Y-o-Y basis, outperforming the IPM growth. Profit after tax for Q2 and H1FY26 grew by 21.8% and 35.1% respectively on a Y-o-Y basis while maintaining healthy return ratios. Our strong performance reflects the consistency of our strategy, disciplined execution and deep focus on our core therapeutic segments. By strengthening our field force, expanding our brand portfolio and maintaining a sharp focus on specialist’s prescriptions, we have continued to outperform the market while building a sustainable platform for long-term growth. Lastly, we are grateful to our bankers for their efforts in the successful listing of CORONA on the Indian stock exchanges. I would also like to thank the entire team at CORONA and our stakeholders for their continued support and faith in our business.” Corona Remedies is an India-focused branded pharmaceutical formulation company developing, manufacturing, and marketing products in women’s healthcare, cardio-diabeto, pain management, urology and other therapeutic areas.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoronaRemediesLtd_53198342_71174.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>