<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Avantel rises on bagging Rs 2-cr manufacturing order from Bharat Electronics]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avantel-rises-on-bagging-rs-2-cr-manufacturing-order-from-bharat-electronics/1662941</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662941</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of Bharat Electronics (BEL) gained 1.22% to currently trade at Rs 402.55 on the BSE.

Shares of Bharat Electronics (BEL) gained 1.22% to currently trade at Rs 402.55 on the BSE. The company said it has been awarded a domestic manufacturing contract by Bharat Electronics worth Rs 1.76 crore. The order is scheduled to be executed by July 2026. As part of the contract, a 5% performance bank guarantee has been stipulated. The company confirmed that neither the promoter nor promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity, and the order does not qualify as a related-party transaction. Avantel is engaged in the business of designing, developing, and maintaining wireless and satellite communication products, defence electronics, radar systems, and the development of network management software applications for its customers, majorly from the aerospace and defence sectors. The company’s consolidated net profit tanked 81.39% to Rs 4.26 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 22.89 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 28.42% year on year to Rs 55.41 crore in Q2 FY26. Bharat Electronics (BEL) is a Navratna PSU under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. It manufactures electronic products and systems for the army, navy, and air force. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 17.87% to Rs 1,287.77 crore on 25.78% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 5,792.09 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Avantel_19473582893_20881.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki rises as production jumps 34% YoY to 211,939 units in Dec’25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maruti-suzuki-rises-as-production-jumps-34-yoy-to-211939-units-in-dec25/1662938</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662938</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sequentially, the auto giant's total production rose 0.18% as compared with 211,555 units produced in November 2025.

Sequentially, the auto giant's total production rose 0.18% as compared with 211,555 units produced in November 2025. Passenger vehicle production stood at 208,591 units in December 2025, registering a 34.1% increase from 155,553 units produced in December 2024. Additionally, the production of light commercial vehicles reached 3,348 units in December 2025, up 59.35% year-on-year. Maruti Suzuki India is engaged in the manufacture, purchase, and sale of motor vehicles, components, and spare parts (automobiles). The company reported a 7.9% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,349 crore on a 12.8% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 40,138.70 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LIC Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lic-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1662940</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662940</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[LIC Mutual Fund has announced that Notice is hereby given to the investors/unitholders that Mr.

LIC Mutual Fund has announced that Notice is hereby given to the investors/unitholders that Mr. Sat Pal Bhanoo (Associate Director) has resigned from the Board of LIC Mutual Fund Trustee Private Limited with effect from close of business hours of 31(st) December 2025 on account of his superannuation from Life Insurance Corporation of India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Olectra Greentech rallies as Hyderabad EV plant starts operations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/olectra-greentech-rallies-as-hyderabad-ev-plant-starts-operations/1662936</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662936</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company declared 31 December 2025 as the commercial operation date for the plant at Seetharampur, Telangana.

The company declared 31 December 2025 as the commercial operation date for the plant at Seetharampur, Telangana. The Phase-I unit has a per-shift annual production capacity of 2,500 electric buses. This represents 50% of the planned per-shift capacity of 5,000 buses per year. The company said the declaration has been communicated to State Bank of India, the project lender. Olectra Greentech is engaged in the manufacturing of composite polymer insulators, electric buses, and electric trucks. The company's consolidated net profit rose 4.18% to Rs 49.55 crore while net sales rose 25.39% to Rs 656.62 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlectraGreentec_59554403015_22012.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Epigral slides after receiving Rs 53-cr income tax demand notice]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/epigral-slides-after-receiving-rs-53-cr-income-tax-demand-notice/1662937</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662937</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the assessment order pertains to Assessment Year 2022–23, corresponding to Financial Year 2021–22.

In an exchange filing, the company said the assessment order pertains to Assessment Year 2022–23, corresponding to Financial Year 2021–22. The order was passed under Section 143(3) read with Section 144C(13) of the Income-tax Act, 1961, along with a notice of demand issued under Section 156 of the Act, including applicable interest. Epigral stated that the assessment order was issued in the ordinary course of assessment proceedings and that it has adequate factual and legal grounds to substantiate its position. The company added that there is no financial impact on its financials, operations, or other business activities arising from the order. The company further said it believes the demand is not maintainable and is in the process of filing a rectification application and an appeal against the order within the prescribed timelines. The company received the demand notice on 31 December 2025, while the official announcement was made on 1 January 2026, after market hours. Epigral, formerly known as Meghmani Finechem, is a leading integrated manufacturer of chemicals in India. Epigral’s Dahej facility is a backward and forward integrated and automated complex with a well-planned infrastructure. In India, Epigral is the first to set up an epichlorohydrin plant and the largest capacity plant of CPVC. Epigral is also a leading manufacturer of caustic soda, caustic potash, chloromethanes, hydrogen peroxide, chlorine and hydrogen. The company reported 36% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 51 crore on a 7% fall in total revenue to Rs 589 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EpigralLtd_16655914_30111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks extend gains as Nifty trades above 26,250 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-extend-gains-as-nifty-trades-above-26250-mark/1662935</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662935</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,250 mark.

The key domestic indices traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,250 mark. Market sentiment remained positive supported by optimism over strong monthly auto sales data and sustained buying interest. Realty stocks extended their rally for a third straight trading session. At 11:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 358.64 points or 0.42% to 85,544.61. The Nifty 50 index climbed 108.45 points or 0.41% to 26,255. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.68% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.67%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,575 shares rose and 1,272 shares fell. A total of 203 shares were unchanged. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) – a single-figure indicator of sector performance – fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signalling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years. Amid a general lack of pressure on operating capacities, there was only a marginal increase in factory employment during December. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index climbed 1.42% to 897.90. The index jumped 3.23% for the three consecutive trading sessions. Godrej Properties (up 2.31%), Oberoi Realty (up 1.95%), DLF (up 1.83%), Anant Raj (up 1.57%) and Sobha (up 1.5%), Phoenix Mills (up 1.27%), Lodha Developers (up 1.2%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 1.1%), SignatureGlobal India (up 0.21%) and Brigade Enterprises (up 0.09%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: ACME Solar Holdings rose 0.78%. The company announced the incorporation of a wholly owned subsidiary, ACME Greentech Eighteen, to strengthen its presence in the renewable energy segment. Remsons Industries rallied 3.89% after the company has secured a Rs 60-crore order from a leading domestic commercial vehicle (CV) OEM. Global Market: South Korea’s Kospi hit a new record Friday as the Asia markets kicked off the new year on a positive trading note. Some Asian markets were still closed for the holidays, including Japan and mainland China. Meanwhile, Singapore’s economy expanded 5.7% year-on-year for the fourth quarter, driven mainly by strong manufacturing growth in the three months through December. The latest reading is faster than the revised 4.3% growth in the previous quarter. On Wednesday, Prime Minister Lawrence Wong announced in his New Year message that the country had clocked a stronger-than-expected 4.8% expansion for the full year of 2025. U.S. stock futures were looking up in early Asian hours, with S&P futures up by 0.15% and Nasdaq-100 futures climbing 0.12%. Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 0.16% higher. On Wednesday stateside, the S&P 500 dipped 0.74%, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and the Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 0.63%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bansal Wire climbs on strong Q3 volume growth]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bansal-wire-climbs-on-strong-q3-volume-growth/1662933</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662933</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total sales volume rose 31.7% YoY to 1,21,702 metric tonnes in Q3 FY26, compared with 92,410 metric tonnes in Q3 FY25.

Total sales volume rose 31.7% YoY to 1,21,702 metric tonnes in Q3 FY26, compared with 92,410 metric tonnes in Q3 FY25. Volumes were also up 6.18% QoQ from 1,14,609 metric tonnes in Q2 FY26. For the nine months ended FY26, cumulative volumes increased 37.88% YoY to 3,40,411 metric tonnes, from 2,46,888 metric tonnes in the corresponding period last year. Bansal Wire Industries is engaged in manufacturing of stainless steel wires. On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit declined 3.33% to Rs 38.32 crore while net sales rose 27.86% to Rs 1055.40 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BansalWireIndustriesLtd_46471053_25030.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bulgaria adopts the Euro, becomes 21st member of Euro area]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bulgaria-adopts-the-euro-becomes-21st-member-of-euro-area/1662934</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662934</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bulgaria has officially joined the euro zone, replacing its original currency Lev with the Euro and becoming the currency bloc’s 21st member.

Bulgaria has officially joined the euro zone, replacing its original currency Lev with the Euro and becoming the currency bloc’s 21st member. This effectively means that over 350 million Europeans are now using single currency. The last country to join the single currency group was Croatia in January 2023.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T’s Minerals & Metals business bags major EPC orders from SAIL & domestic metals customers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lts-minerals-metals-business-bags-major-epc-orders-from-sail-domestic-metals-customers/1662931</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662931</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘major’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 5,000 crore to Rs 10,000 crore.

As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘major’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 5,000 crore to Rs 10,000 crore. L&T and SAIL share a long-standing relationship spanning several decades, with the company having executed multiple metallurgical projects across the country. The latest orders further strengthen this partnership and support India’s steel capacity expansion and modernisation efforts. Under SAIL’s modernisation and expansion programme, the crude steel capacity of the IISCO Steel Plant at Burnpur, West Bengal, is set to be increased from 2.5 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) to 6.5 MTPA. As part of this expansion, L&T’s M&M business has been awarded the complete engineering, procurement and installation (EPI) package for key process plants, including the Coke Oven Battery, By-Product Plant, Basic Oxygen Furnace, and a specialised material handling equipment package, which together form the core of the new steel complex. Separately, at SAIL’s Bokaro Steel Plant (BSL) in Jharkhand, L&T has secured an order for setting up Sinter Plant #2 as part of a major upstream expansion project. In addition, the M&M business has bagged multiple orders for specialised material handling equipment, such as stacker reclaimers and wagon tipplers, from various customers across India, highlighting its strong capabilities across the minerals and metals value chain. D K Sen, Advisor to CMD, Development Projects & Minerals & Metals, L&T, said: “L&T has been a major contributor to India’s industrial growth story in the metals sector, and our association with SAIL is a proud chapter in our journey. These orders underscore L&T’s ability to deliver world-class metallurgical infrastructure with engineering precision, safety and sustainability at the core. We are privileged to contribute to SAIL’s expansion vision, which is vital to strengthening India’s self-reliance in steel production”. T Kumaresan, Senior Vice President & Head – Minerals & Metals, L&T, added: “The trust placed in L&T by SAIL once again validates our expertise in delivering complex, technology-intensive projects under challenging schedules. These wins reaffirm our commitment to delivering projects on time, demonstrate our technical capabilities and adherence to project timelines. This also brings out our capabilities in end-to-end execution of complex process packages. Larsen & Toubro is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services. The company reported a 15.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Steel Authority of India (SAIL) is the leading steel-making company in India. The company is a fully integrated iron and steel maker, producing both basic and special steels for domestic construction, engineering, power, railway, automotive, and defense industries, as well as for export markets. Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) fell 0.36% to Rs 147.92, while Larsen & Toubro (L&T) rose 0.32% to Rs 4,153.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1662932</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662932</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 06 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 06 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: ICICI Prudential Innovation Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.45 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.45 ICICI Prudential PSU Equity Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.60

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Idea receives Rs 638-cr GST penalty order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vodafone-idea-receives-rs-638-cr-gst-penalty-order/1662929</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662929</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The penalty has been imposed by the Office of the Additional Commissioner, Central Goods & Service Tax, Ahmedabad South, Ahmedabad.

The penalty has been imposed by the Office of the Additional Commissioner, Central Goods & Service Tax, Ahmedabad South, Ahmedabad. The order, passed under Section 74 of the CGST Act, confirms a penalty of Rs 637.90 crore along with applicable tax demand and interest. The order alleges short payment of tax and excess availment of Input Tax Credit (ITC). The company said The maximum financial impact is to the extent of tax demand, interest and penalty levied. Vodafone Idea stated that it does not agree with the order and will take appropriate legal action against it. The company received the show-cause notice on 31 December 2025, while the disclosure was made through an official filing on 1 January 2026 after market hours. India's third-largest telecom operator, Vodafone Idea is backed by Aditya Birla Group and Vodafone Group. The company holds 5G spectrum in 17 circles and mmWave spectrum in 16 circles, offering services across 2G, 4G and expanding 5G networks. The telco reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 5,524 crore in Q2 FY26, narrowing from a net loss of Rs 7,175.90 crore in the same quarter last year. Net sales increased 2.3% to Rs 11,169.60 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 10,918.20 crore posted in the same quarter last year. The counter rose 0.95% to Rs 11.73 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VodafoneIdea_33393045864_23040.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index trades on a softer note under 98 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-trades-on-a-softer-note-under-98-mark/1662927</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662927</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index lost ground at the start of the New Year, easing under 98 mark weighed down by policy uncertainty following President Donald Trump’s tariff measures.

The dollar index lost ground at the start of the New Year, easing under 98 mark weighed down by policy uncertainty following President Donald Trump’s tariff measures. US Nonfarm Payrolls (NFP) and unemployment rate data to be published next week could offer some hints about the health of the labour market and the US interest rate this year. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 97.95, down 0.10% on the day after having shed about 9% last year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under four schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-four-schemes/1662930</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662930</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 05 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 05 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: ICICI Prudential Equity - Arbitrage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.0500 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.0500 ICICI Prudential Multi - Asset Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.1600 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.1600 ICICI Prudential ICICI Prudential Large Cap Fund : Regular Plan – IDCW: 2.70 Direct Plan – IDCW: 2.70 ICICI Prudential Business Cycle Fund : Regular Plan – IDCW: 1.60 Direct Plan – IDCW: 1.60

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-lemon-tree-hotels-ltd-counter/1662926</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662926</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Devyani International Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd, Trent Ltd, Indiamart Intermesh Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 02 January 2026.

Devyani International Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd, Trent Ltd, Indiamart Intermesh Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 02 January 2026. Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd clocked volume of 11.92 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 13.23 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 90127 shares. The stock lost 0.64% to Rs.155.95. Volumes stood at 1.07 lakh shares in the last session. Devyani International Ltd registered volume of 19.26 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.28 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.32 lakh shares. The stock rose 1.89% to Rs.150.75. Volumes stood at 3.62 lakh shares in the last session. Sapphire Foods India Ltd clocked volume of 2.18 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.88 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 37031 shares. The stock lost 1.47% to Rs.257.50. Volumes stood at 29290 shares in the last session. Trent Ltd witnessed volume of 2.24 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.6 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 40049 shares. The stock increased 1.12% to Rs.4,346.00. Volumes stood at 10116 shares in the last session. Indiamart Intermesh Ltd clocked volume of 61505 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.04 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 12209 shares. The stock lost 0.65% to Rs.2,180.55. Volumes stood at 1621 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LemonTreeHotelsLtd_62193476144_40619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India manufacturing PMI weakens to 55 in December ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-manufacturing-pmi-weakens-to-55-in-december/1662923</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662923</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) – a single-figure indicator of sector performance – fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signalling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years.

The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) – a single-figure indicator of sector performance – fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signalling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years. The current figure was nevertheless above its long-run average. The end of the 2025 calendar year was characterised by a loss of growth momentum across several measures tracked by the HSBC India Manufacturing PMI® survey. Positive demand trends continued to underpin sharp increases in new business intakes and production, but rates of expansion eased on the back of competitive pressures and subdued sales of specific items. Employment rose at the slowest pace in the current 22-month period of job creation, while the latest upturn in buying levels was the least pronounced in two years.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ACME Solar Holdings incorporates wholly owned subsidiary ACME Greentech Eighteen]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acme-solar-holdings-incorporates-wholly-owned-subsidiary-acme-greentech-eighteen/1662922</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662922</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The newly incorporated subsidiary will focus on the development, establishment, and operation of power generation and renewable energy projects.

The newly incorporated subsidiary will focus on the development, establishment, and operation of power generation and renewable energy projects. ACME Greentech Eighteen was incorporated on 1 January 2026 and has its registered office in Gurugram, Haryana, India. The company has subscribed to 100% of the initial paid-up share capital of the subsidiary in cash, amounting to Rs 1 lakh, comprising 10,000 equity shares of face value Rs 10 each. ACME Solar Holdings is a fully integrated renewable energy company in India with a diversified portfolio across solar, wind, storage, hybrid and Firm and Dispatchable Renewable Energy (FDRE) projects. The company’s consolidated net profit stood at Rs 115.06 crore in Q2 FY26, up 652.51% as against Rs 15.29 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 80.18% YoY to Rs 467.74 crore in Q2 September 2025. The counter rose 0.17% to Rs 238.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ACMESolarHoldingsLtd_41904745_71636.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Remsons Industries rises on securing Rs 60-cr order from CV OEM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/remsons-industries-rises-on-securing-rs-60-cr-order-from-cv-oem/1662920</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662920</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract is for the supply of gear shifters with push-pull cables, with supplies set to begin from Q1 FY27.

The contract is for the supply of gear shifters with push-pull cables, with supplies set to begin from Q1 FY27. The order will be executed over a 60-month period, the company said. The order has been awarded by an Indian entity and is domestic in nature. Remsons Industries added that neither the promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction. The companys’s consolidated net profit jumped 29.7% to Rs 4.06 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 3.13 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 26.6% year on year to Rs 115.59 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RemsonsInds_7499839085_5266.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Bank jumps as total deposits climb 13% YoY to Rs 7.90 lakh crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-bank-jumps-as-total-deposits-climb-13-yoy-to-rs-790-lakh-crore-in-q3/1662921</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662921</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gross advances increased 14.5% to Rs 6.40 lakh crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 5.59 lakh crore as of 31 December 2024.

Gross advances increased 14.5% to Rs 6.40 lakh crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 5.59 lakh crore as of 31 December 2024. The bank’s total business grew 13.4% to Rs 14.30 lakh crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 12.61 lakh crore as of 31 December 2024. CASA deposits rose 19.4% year on year (YoY) to Rs 0.43 lakh crore as of 31 December 2025. However, the CASA (domestic) ratio moderated to 39.02%, compared with 40% in the corresponding period last year. Indian Bank has many deposit schemes tailored to suit the needs of its customers, both individuals and organizations. Credit/advances/loan schemes specifically designed for its customers. Also, it offers various novel services to customers, both individuals and organizations. The bank reported an 11.51% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 3,018.22 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 2,706.44 crore in Q2 FY25. Total income rose 7.35% YoY to Rs 19,076.57 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndianBank_77867287520_6061.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades near 26,250 mark; auto shares gear up]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-near-26250-mark-auto-shares-gear-up/1662917</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662917</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices traded with moderate gains in morning trade as the Nifty traded near the 26,250 mark.

The key domestic indices traded with moderate gains in morning trade as the Nifty traded near the 26,250 mark. Trading activity remained positive amid sustained buying interest, reflecting improved risk appetite among investors. Market participants will now turn their focus to the upcoming earnings season. Auto shares extended their rally for a fourth consecutive trading session. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 343.99 points or 0.40% to 85,532.59. The Nifty 50 index gained 101.90 points or 0.39% to 26,248.45. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.47% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.40%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,352 shares rose and 1,264 shares fell. A total of 201 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index jumped 1.07% to 28,786.65. The index jumped 4.33% for the four consecutive trading sessions. Hero MotoCorp (up 2.54%), TVS Motor Company (up 2.28%), Bosch (up 2.02%), Ashok Leyland (up 1.81%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 1.48%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 1.36%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.3%), Bharat Forge (up 0.98%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (up 0.95%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 0.71%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Punjab & Sind Bank rose 2.61% after the bank's gross advances increased by 15.25% to Rs 110,488 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 95,870 crore as of 31 December 2024. South Indian Bank added 2.11% after the private lender said that its gross advances jumped 11.27% to Rs 96,765 crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 86,966 crore as of 31 December 2024. Hyundai Motor India (HMIL) declined 2.06%. The company has recorded 6.6% year-on-year (YoY) growth in total monthly sales, clocking sales of 58,702 units in December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Devyani International rises after board OKs merger proposal with Sapphire Foods ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/devyani-international-rises-after-board-oks-merger-proposal-with-sapphire-foods/1662918</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662918</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Following this announcement, shares of Sapphire Foods India fell 2.35% to currently trade at Rs 255.20 on the BSE.

Following this announcement, shares of Sapphire Foods India fell 2.35% to currently trade at Rs 255.20 on the BSE. In a statement filed with the bourses yesterday, DIL stated that the proposed merger is subject to receipt of all the customary regulatory & statutory approvals, including approvals from the stock exchanges, the Competition Commission of India, the National Company Law Tribunals, and the shareholders and creditors of both the companies. The process of obtaining these approvals is expected to take approximately 12 to 15 months, following which the merger will become effective. “Upon completion, the transaction will result in DIL becoming one of the largest quick-service restaurant (QSR) operators in India by combining the operations of both companies, positioning the merged entity for the next phase of accelerated growth, scale, and profitability,” the company said in a statement. The merger of SFIL with DIL is structured through a share-swap mechanism. DIL will issue 177 equity shares of DIL for every 100 equity shares of SFIL. As part of the deal, group company Arctic International will acquire approximately 18.5% of SFIL’s paid-up equity share capital from the existing SFIL promoters, with an option to assign to a mutually agreed financial investor. The merged entity will focus on accelerated expansion of KFC as well as strengthening and revitalization of Pizza Hut for long-term sustainable growth. Yum! Brands has granted its approval for the consolidation of DIL and SFIL, it added. DIL will acquire 19 KFC restaurants currently operated by Yum! India in Hyderabad. It will pay a one-time charge to Yum! India towards merger approval and the licence fee for the additional territory. DIL further said that it is expecting an overall synergy of Rs 210 to 225 crore on an annual basis from 2nd full year operations of integrated company. The full integration of the two entities, along with the realization of the identified synergy benefits, is expected to be completed within 15 to 18 months from the effective date of the merger. Ravi Jaipuria, non-executive chairman of Devyani International, said: “The consolidation of Devyani International and Sapphire Foods India marks a significant milestone and a decisive leap forward in our growth journey, resulting in DIL holding franchise rights across the entire Indian market for KFC and Pizza Hut brands. The merger also adds a strong international presence in Sri Lanka, which complements our existing overseas operations. This combination will allow us to realize meaningful economies of scale, leverage a unified technology platform, and strengthen our supply-chain capabilities." Devyani International (DIL) is the largest franchisee of Yum Brands in India and one of the country’s leading quick service restaurant (QSR) operators. The company also operates Costa Coffee outlets across India under a franchise agreement. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 21.89 crore in Q2 FY26 as against a consolidated net profit of Rs 0.02 crore during the previous quarter ended September 2024. Sales rose 12.65% to Rs 1376.75 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Devyani-International_90569402_24609.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>