<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aurionpro Solutions surges after securing major data centre project from leading global developer ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aurionpro-solutions-surges-after-securing-major-data-centre-project-from-leading-global-developer/1678483</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678483</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[This win follows Aurionpro's recent data centre infrastructure expansion contract with a leading bank, underscoring growing trust from both banking and global data centre operators in its delivery capabilities.

This win follows Aurionpro's recent data centre infrastructure expansion contract with a leading bank, underscoring growing trust from both banking and global data centre operators in its delivery capabilities. The high-value deal is scheduled for implementation over the next three quarters and involves the design and execution of a brownfield facility in Mumbai. The scope includes a comprehensive solution covering engineering and construction services along with integrated testing and commissioning. The project will be delivered to global colocation standards within a live operational campus environment. As per a recent CBRE report, Mumbai continues to lead as India's data centre hub, accounting for 53% of the nation's total operational capacity. Bhaskar Bhattacharya, EVP & Head – Enterprise Business, Aurionpro, commented: “This strategic win underscores the confidence that leading global players continue to place in Aurionpro. India's data centre market is at an inflection point, driven by hyperscaler expansion, AI workload requirements, and sovereign infrastructure mandates." Aurionpro Solutions is a global enterprise technology leader pioneering intuitive-tech through deep-tech IPs and scalable products. With a strong presence across banking, payments, mobility, insurance, transit, data centers, and government sectors, Aurionpro is setting new benchmarks for AI innovation and impact. Its B2E (Business-to-Ecosystem) approach empowers entire ecosystems – driving growth, transformation, and scale across interconnected value chains. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Aurionpro Solutions declined 8% to Rs 44 crore while revenue rose 21% to Rs 371 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AurionproSol_26787240482_8040.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NDL Ventures Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ndl-ventures-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678481</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678481</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[BLB Ltd, Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd, Universus Photo Imagings Ltd and AGI Infra Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026.

BLB Ltd, Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd, Universus Photo Imagings Ltd and AGI Infra Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026. NDL Ventures Ltd spiked 20.00% to Rs 117.6 at 11:59 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 75000 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 869 shares in the past one month. BLB Ltd soared 16.88% to Rs 18. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 39025 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14473 shares in the past one month. Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd surged 16.50% to Rs 39.6. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.26 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3907 shares in the past one month. Universus Photo Imagings Ltd added 16.24% to Rs 330. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 8913 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 692 shares in the past one month. AGI Infra Ltd exploded 12.11% to Rs 269.95. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 2.29 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35400 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindujaVentures_56215755122_4093.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1678482</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678482</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 17 February 2026.

Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 17 February 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name (s) Existing Fund Manager(s) Proposed Fund Manager(s) Bandhan BSE Sensex ETF, Bandhan Nifty 50 ETF, Bandhan Nifty 50 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty 100 Index Fund , Bandhan Nifty200 Momentum 30 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty100 Low Volatility 30 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty IT Index Fund ,Bandhan Nifty Alpha 50 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty Smallcap 250 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty Total Market Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty Bank Index Fund, Bandhan BSE Healthcare Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty Midcap 150 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty 500 Value 50 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty 500 Momentum 50 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty 200 Quality 30 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty Alpha Low Volatility 30 Index Fund, Bandhan Nifty Next 50 Index Fund, Bandhan BSE India Sector Leaders Index Fund. Mr. Abhishek Jain Mr. Abhishek Jain Mr. Mayuresh Nagvekar

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ratnamani Metals & Tubes Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ratnamani-metals-tubes-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1678479</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678479</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Netweb Technologies India Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd and Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 18 February 2026.

Netweb Technologies India Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd and Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 18 February 2026. Ratnamani Metals & Tubes Ltd soared 14.88% to Rs 2472 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 16125 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7341 shares in the past one month. Netweb Technologies India Ltd surged 13.42% to Rs 3514.95. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.87 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.22 lakh shares in the past one month. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd spiked 11.38% to Rs 2303.05. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.95 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 52849 shares in the past one month. Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd spurt 9.07% to Rs 298.9. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 9.33 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.73 lakh shares in the past one month. Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd gained 8.49% to Rs 1167.65. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 15548 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21252 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RatnamaniMetals_68391757668_3124.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trishakti Industries bags Rs 42 lakh contract from Larsen & Toubro]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trishakti-industries-bags-rs-42-lakh-contract-from-larsen-toubro/1678476</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678476</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, Trishakti said the order involves the deployment of advanced machinery along with skilled manpower.

In a regulatory filing, Trishakti said the order involves the deployment of advanced machinery along with skilled manpower. The contract is for hiring of machines with manpower and is to be executed immediately, with a duration of five months. The broad commercial consideration for the contract stands at Rs 42 lakh. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in Larsen and Toubro. It further stated that the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Trishakti Industries is an infrastructure solutions provider specializing in the hiring of heavy earth-moving equipment. With a strong fleet of advanced machinery, it serves major sectors such as steel, cement, railways, and construction. Larsen & Toubro is a multinational conglomerate which is primarily engaged in providing engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) solutions in key sectors such as Infrastructure, Hydrocarbon, Power, Process Industries and Defence, Information Technology and Financial Services in domestic and international markets. Shares of Trishakti Industries rose 0.80% to Rs 151 while shares of Larsen & Toubro added 0.23% to Rs 4,289.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TrishaktiElectronicsIndustries_12352452_6237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharti Airtel arm receives RBI nod to operate as Type II NBFC-ND]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharti-airtel-arm-receives-rbi-nod-to-operate-as-type-ii-nbfc-nd/1678477</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678477</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The certificate, bearing Registration No.

The certificate, bearing Registration No. N-14.03676 dated 13 February 2026, has been issued under Section 45-IA of the RBI Act, 1934. With this approval, Airtel Money is authorised to commence the business of a non-banking financial institution without accepting public deposits, subject to the conditions prescribed by the RBI. In its regulatory filing, the company stated that it holds a valid Certificate of Registration dated February 13, 2026, issued by the RBI under Section 45-IA of the Reserve Bank of India Act, 1934. The company also clarified that the RBI does not undertake any responsibility or guarantee regarding the financial soundness of the company, the correctness of statements or representations made by it, or the repayment of deposits and discharge of liabilities. Bharti Airtel is a global communications solutions provider with over 600 million customers in 15 countries across India and Africa. Bharti Airtel reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter rose 0.16% to Rs 2,023 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BhartiAirtel_49342333843_15542.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dilip Buildcon gains after emerging as L-1 bidder for Rs 702 crore project in Gujarat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dilip-buildcon-gains-after-emerging-as-l-1-bidder-for-rs-702-crore-project-in-gujarat/1678478</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678478</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The tender, floated by the Narmada Water Resources, Water Supply & Kalpasar Department, is valued at Rs 702 crore.

The tender, floated by the Narmada Water Resources, Water Supply & Kalpasar Department, is valued at Rs 702 crore. The project involves the construction of a flood protection embankment on the Narmada River in the Bharuch District. Executed on an engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) basis, the project is scheduled for completion within a 24-month timeframe. Dilip Buildcon is presently in the business of development of infrastructure facilities on an Engineering Procurement and Construction basis (EPC) and undertakes contracts from various government and other parties and special purpose vehicles promoted by the company. The company's consolidated net profit surged to Rs 829.85 crore in the quarter ended December 2025 as against Rs 115.27 crore during the previous quarter ended December 2024. Sales declined 17.45% to Rs 2,137.90 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DilipBuildconLtd_92563827065_36662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITCONS E-Solutions bags order worth Rs 19 lakh ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itcons-e-solutions-bags-order-worth-rs-19-lakh/1678475</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678475</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order pertains to the deployment of six resources under manpower outsourcing services.

The order pertains to the deployment of six resources under manpower outsourcing services. The contract will be executed over a period of one year from 1 March 2026 to 28 February 2027, unless extended by mutual consent. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity. The company stated that the promoter/promoter group has no interest in the awarding authority, and the transaction does not fall under related party transactions. ITCONS E-Solutions is engaged in the business of recruitment and staffing services. On a full-year basis, the company’s net profit surged 70.2% to Rs 3.25 crore on a 96.4% rise in net sales to Rs 55.98 crore in FY25 over FY24. The counter declined 1.61% to Rs 370 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITCONSESolutionsLtd_70007426_78414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Info Edge (India) to pump Rs 30-cr in subsidiary, SIHL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/info-edge-india-to-pump-rs-30-cr-in-subsidiary-sihl/1678474</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678474</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SIHL is engaged mainly in direct or indirect investments in tech companies and related activities including investment in Alternative Investment Funds (AIF).

SIHL is engaged mainly in direct or indirect investments in tech companies and related activities including investment in Alternative Investment Funds (AIF). As of 31st March 2025, SIHL reported a profit of Rs 0.86 crore. The fresh capital infusion will enable SIHL to explore investment opportunities including contribution to AIF(s) and other general purposes. As a part of transaction, the company will acquire 14,01,214 compulsorily convertible debentures (CCDs) at an issue price of Rs 214.10 each including premium of Rs 114.10 per CCD. The said transaction will be completed within 30 days from the approval. Post this investment, SIHL remains the wholly owned subsidiary of the company. Info Edge (India) is India's premier online classifieds company in recruitment, matrimony, real estate, education and related services. The company reported a 23.11% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 246.45 crore on 13.85% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 764.55 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter declined 1.72% to Rs 1,111.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InfoEdgIndia_32670259917_18844.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 154 pts; IT shares lag]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-154-pts-it-shares-lag/1678472</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678472</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning trade amid profit booking in IT heavyweights and cautious global cues.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning trade amid profit booking in IT heavyweights and cautious global cues. The Nifty traded tad below the 25,700 level. IT shares declined after advancing in the previous two trading sessions. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 153.71 points or 0.18% to 83,297.25. The Nifty 50 index fell 31.20 points or 0.13% to 25,692.45. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.06% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index added 0.17%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,063 shares rose and 1,787 shares fell. A total of 198 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 2.28% to 32,321.90. The index rose 1.1% in the past two trading sessions. Persistent Systems (down 2.87%), LTIMindtree (down 2.6%), Tech Mahindra (down 2.16%), Mphasis (down 2.02%), Infosys (down 1.87%), Wipro (down 1.76%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 1.65%), HCL Technologies (down 1.59%), Coforge (down 1.55%) and Tata Consultancy Services (down 1.12%) jumped. Stocks in Spotlight: Blue Cloud Softech Solutions rose 2.53% after the company announced that it has received a Letter of Intent from the Department of Telecommunications. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) rose 0.86%. The company has announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance from Steel Authority of India (SAIL) for executing a Captive Power Plant (CPP) package. Bosch shed 0.27%. The company announced that its board approved the appointment of Tillmann Olsen as the chief financial officer (CFO) with effect from 1 June 2026. Global Markets: Asian stocks traded mixed on Wednesday amid renewed concerns over artificial intelligence that continued to weigh on global markets. Mainland China, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan and South Korea were among the markets closed for Lunar New Year holidays. The positive start in Asia followed a lackluster session on Tuesday on Wall Street as investors grappled with the outlook for the AI boom. Concerns that companies are over-investing, along with angst about the extent to which the nascent technology could disrupt labor markets, have fuelled investor jitters in recent weeks. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 0.07% to 49,533.19, the S&P 500 was up 0.10% at 6,843.22, and the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.14% to 22,578.38. The S&P 500 fell 0.88% initially before making up ground to close in positive territory. Brent and West Texas Intermediate crude oil futures were little changed on Wednesday after both slid to close at more than two-week lows in the previous session. Following talks in Geneva on Tuesday, Iran's foreign minister reportedly said Tehran and Washington reached an understanding on main "guiding principles" towards resolving their longstanding nuclear dispute, easing worries about a military conflict near the Strait of Hormuz that could disrupt global oil supply.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HSBC Global Equity Climate Change Fund of Fund Merger into HSBC Global Emerging Markets Fund]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hsbc-global-equity-climate-change-fund-of-fund-merger-into-hsbc-global-emerging-markets-fund/1678473</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678473</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund has approved the merger of HSBC Global Equity Climate Change Fund of Fund Merger into HSBC Global Emerging Markets Fund, with effect from 25 March 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/franklin-templeton-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-schemes/1678468</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678468</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Mutual Fund has announced 20 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Franklin Templeton Mutual Fund has announced 20 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Franklin India Conservative Hybrid Fund – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.080 Franklin India Conservative Hybrid Fund – Direct – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.100 Franklin India Equity Savings Fund – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.050 Franklin India Equity Savings Fund – Direct – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.070 Franklin India Equity Savings Fund – Quarterly IDCW Option: 0.140 Franklin India Equity Savings Fund – Direct – Quarterly IDCW Option: 0.160 Franklin India Small Cap Fund – IDCW Option: 4.500 Franklin India Small Cap Fund – Direct – IDCW Option: 5.500 Franklin India Flexi Cap Fund – IDCW Option: 4.200 Franklin India Flexi Cap Fund – Direct – IDCW Option: 5.500

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Artson gains after bagging purchase order from Tata Projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/artson-gains-after-bagging-purchase-order-from-tata-projects/1678464</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678464</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, Artson said the order pertains to the supply of finished structures and is domestic in nature.

In a regulatory filing, Artson said the order pertains to the supply of finished structures and is domestic in nature. The contract is an item-rate order and is to be executed over a period of four months. The original purchase order, executed on November 24, 2025, has been amended on 17 February 2026, with the value enhanced by Rs 4.62 crore. With this revision, the total order value stands at Rs 11.09 crore, including taxes. The company clarified that TPL, being its promoter/holding company, has an interest in the transaction. The order qualifies as a related party transaction (RPT) and has been undertaken in the ordinary course of business at arm’s length pricing. Artson is operating in one segment viz. Supply of equipments, steel structure and site services for mechanical works. The company reported standalone net loss of Rs 12.22 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net profit of Rs 6.38 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 79.4% year on year to Rs 31.96 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArtsonEngg_2613614434_2662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Blue Cloud Softech jumps on Unified License (VNO) approval]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/blue-cloud-softech-jumps-on-unified-license-vno-approval/1678462</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678462</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The LoI relates to a Unified License (Virtual Network Operator) – ISP Category "A" authorisation for National Area Service.

The LoI relates to a Unified License (Virtual Network Operator) – ISP Category "A" authorisation for National Area Service. The authorisation, subject to completion of regulatory formalities including payment of entry fee, submission of bank guarantees and execution of the licence agreement, will enable the company to provide internet services across India. Blue Cloud Softech Solutions said the licence will support its strategy to build an integrated digital infrastructure platform combining AI-native data centres, sovereign cloud services and secure connectivity. The company plans to integrate nationwide enterprise connectivity with its data centre and cloud infrastructure to offer end-to-end digital solutions to businesses and government institutions. The company also outlined plans to accelerate deployment of AI-powered hyperscale, edge and micro data centres, including expansion into Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities. It aims to develop a connectivity-led data centre ecosystem integrating ISP backbone, cloud infrastructure and AI compute capabilities. In addition, Blue Cloud Softech Solutions intends to deploy 5G Fixed Wireless Access infrastructure, enable Private Mobile Networks and expand managed surveillance services through its proprietary platform, as part of building a scalable national digital infrastructure platform. Blue Cloud Softech Solutions operates in AI-driven enterprise solutions, cybersecurity, secure connectivity and digital infrastructure services across domestic and international markets. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Blue Cloud Softech Solutions surged 97.66% to Rs 18.58 crore while net sales rose 80.90% to Rs 265.41 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BlueCloudSoftechSolutions_7849838.58445728_4210.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at SRF Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-srf-ltd-counter/1678460</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678460</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Apar Industries Ltd, Alkem Laboratories Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, NTPC Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 18 February 2026.

Apar Industries Ltd, Alkem Laboratories Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, NTPC Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 18 February 2026. SRF Ltd recorded volume of 2.98 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 17.96 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 16614 shares. The stock lost 0.57% to Rs.2,727.50. Volumes stood at 17712 shares in the last session. Apar Industries Ltd registered volume of 14330 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.48 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1512 shares. The stock rose 3.13% to Rs.9,844.05. Volumes stood at 1748 shares in the last session. Alkem Laboratories Ltd registered volume of 95274 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 13614 shares. The stock slipped 0.96% to Rs.5,402.20. Volumes stood at 855 shares in the last session. Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd registered volume of 1.48 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.73 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 21914 shares. The stock slipped 0.77% to Rs.1,719.10. Volumes stood at 17510 shares in the last session. NTPC Ltd saw volume of 15.59 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 4.53 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.44 lakh shares. The stock increased 0.38% to Rs.369.75. Volumes stood at 3.16 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SRF_56123073213_513.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India-France elevate relations to a "Special Global Strategic Partnership”]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-france-elevate-relations-to-a-special-global-strategic-partnership/1678456</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678456</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India and France on Tuesday resolved to further strengthen cooperation in innovation in different fields as Prime Minister Narendra Modi and French President Emmanuel Macron launched the India-France Year of Innovation.

India and France on Tuesday resolved to further strengthen cooperation in innovation in different fields as Prime Minister Narendra Modi and French President Emmanuel Macron launched the India-France Year of Innovation. The two Leaders reaffirmed their commitment to a rules-based order in the Indo-Pacific region and beyond. The elevation of the relationship will strengthen cooperation between the two countries in sectors of the future, so as to reinforce their sovereignty and decision-making autonomy, and to respond together to the major challenges confronting our world, including through cooperation between India and the European Union. Both leaders also underlined the key importance of strengthening EU-India relations and welcomed the historic summit between India and the EU, during which the negotiations of the India-EU Free Trade Agreement were concluded. The FTA will open opportunities for further economic collaboration between India, France and Europe, strengthening the competitiveness of our businesses, ushering in a new era of sustainable prosperity and resilient value chains. The two countries renewed the 10-year defence cooperation agreement and signed an MoU for manufacturing Hammer missiles in the country. The agreements were signed when Defence Minister Rajnath Singh and his French counterpart Catherine Vautrin co-chaired the sixth India-France Annual Defence Dialogue in the city. Further, they elevated their relations to a "special global strategic partnership" and vowed to boost cooperation in key sectors of defence, trade and critical minerals with Prime Minister Narendra Modi and French President Emmanuel Macron describing the bilateral ties as a "force for global stability" in the face of increasing geopolitical turbulence. The two sides inked a total of 21 agreements and documents providing for deepening of cooperation in an array of areas including critical minerals, defence, high technology, renewable energy, and health.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NDL Ventures Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ndl-ventures-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678426</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678426</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Globale Tessile Ltd, Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd, AGI Infra Ltd and Creative Newtech Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026.

Globale Tessile Ltd, Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd, AGI Infra Ltd and Creative Newtech Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026. NDL Ventures Ltd soared 20.00% to Rs 117.6 at 10:24 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 43614 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 869 shares in the past one month. Globale Tessile Ltd spiked 18.05% to Rs 13.34. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 504 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1618 shares in the past one month. Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd surged 17.80% to Rs 40.04. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 46036 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3907 shares in the past one month. AGI Infra Ltd jumped 13.75% to Rs 273.9. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.34 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35400 shares in the past one month. Creative Newtech Ltd advanced 13.64% to Rs 750. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 169 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindujaVentures_56215755122_4093.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sadhana-nitro-chem-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678427</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678427</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GE Power India Ltd, MRC Agrotech Ltd, Digicontent Ltd and Suratwwala Business Group Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026.

GE Power India Ltd, MRC Agrotech Ltd, Digicontent Ltd and Suratwwala Business Group Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 18 February 2026. Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd crashed 70.52% to Rs 1.66 at 10:25 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 5.7 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.77 lakh shares in the past one month. GE Power India Ltd tumbled 10.00% to Rs 496.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6.41 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.88 lakh shares in the past one month. MRC Agrotech Ltd lost 7.94% to Rs 39.1. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 10869 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 89666 shares in the past one month. Digicontent Ltd plummeted 7.07% to Rs 26.02. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4212 shares in the past one month. Suratwwala Business Group Ltd corrected 7.00% to Rs 28.18. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7849 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SadhanaNitro_2647717340_491.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index declines 2.20%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-declines-220/1678428</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678428</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index ended down 2.20% at 32346.2 today.

Nifty IT index ended down 2.20% at 32346.2 today. The index is down 17.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, LTIMindtree Ltd slipped 2.76%, Infosys Ltd fell 2.65% and Tech Mahindra Ltd shed 2.44%. The Nifty IT index is down 22.00% over last one year compared to the 11.88% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Metal index added 1.18% and Nifty PSU Bank index increased 0.99% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has declined 0.21% to close at 25671.35 while the SENSEX is down 0.27% to close at 83226.46 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concept-with-oil-rig-in-the-gulf-picture-id597_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Stainless Ltd Surges 2.64%, BSE Metal index Gains 1.15%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-stainless-ltd-surges-264-bse-metal-index-gains-115/1678429</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678429</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jindal Stainless Ltd gained 2.64% today to trade at Rs 760.15.

Jindal Stainless Ltd gained 2.64% today to trade at Rs 760.15. The BSE Metal index is up 1.15% to quote at 39490.63. The index is up 3.31 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Tata Steel Ltd increased 2.39% and Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd added 2.13% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 41.64 % over last one year compared to the 9.56% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Jindal Stainless Ltd has lost 5.48% over last one month compared to 3.31% gain in BSE Metal index and 0.02% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 17144 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 24223 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 883.25 on 07 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 497 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalStain_15230115440_24610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>