<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:18:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/INR futures gain marginally to settle at 121.42]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpinr-futures-gain-marginally-to-settle-at-12142/1663036</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663036</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures closed higher by 0.22% at 90.34.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures closed higher by 0.22% at 90.34. GBP/INR gained marginally at 121.42 whereas EUR/INR ended the day at 106. JPY/INR closed for the day at 57.70.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee Slumps Again]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-slumps-again/1663035</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663035</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.3400 per Dollar on Friday (02 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.1400 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end with major gains; Nifty ends at fresh high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-with-major-gains-nifty-ends-at-fresh-high/1663033</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663033</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian equity market ended the week with strong gains, with the Nifty 50 crossing the 26,300 level to hit a fresh record high, while the Sensex also posted solid gains.

The Indian equity market ended the week with strong gains, with the Nifty 50 crossing the 26,300 level to hit a fresh record high, while the Sensex also posted solid gains. Market sentiment was supported by strong Q3 corporate business updates and robust December auto sales. Macro data such as a sharp rebound in IIP growth and steady GST collections further lifted confidence. Broader markets outperformed, led by buying in auto and cyclical stocks. In the week ended on Friday, 02 January 2025, the S&P BSE Sensex rallied 720.56 points or 0.84% to settle at 85,762.01. The Nifty 50 index soared 286.25 points or 1.09% to settle at 26,328.55. The BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.97% to close at 47,539.18. The BSE Small-Cap added 0.79% to end at 51,920.13. Weekly Index Movement: The key equity barometers ended with modest losses on Monday. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 345.91 points or 0.41% to 84,695.54. The Nifty 50 index lost 100.20 points or 0.38% to 25,942.10. The key equity barometers ended marginally lower on Tuesday. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 20.46 points or 0.02% to 84,675.08. The Nifty 50 index lost 3.25 points or 0.01% to 25,938.85. The key equity barometers ended with substantial gains on Wednesday. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 545.52 points or 0.64% to 85,220.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 190.75 points or 0.74% to 26,129.60. The key equity barometers ended near the flat line on Thursday. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 32 points or 0.04% to 85,188.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 16.95 points or 0.06% to 26,146.55. The key equity indices ended with substantial gains on Friday. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 573.41 points or 0.67% to 85,762.01. The Nifty 50 index climbed 182 points or 0.70% to 26,328.55. Economy: India’s Index of Industrial Production (IIP) grew 6.7% year-on-year in November, accelerating from the upwardly revised 0.5% increase in the previous month. Growth was noted in manufacturing (8% vs 2% in October) on higher output of basic and fabricated metal products, pharmaceuticals, and motor vehicles. Growth was also sharp for mining (5.4% vs -1.8%) as the closure of the monsoon season supported operations. GST revenues in December showed a modest pickup, with gross collections rising to Rs 1.74 lakh crore, up 6.1% year on year and marking the fastest growth in three months after a softer November. However, the improvement was driven largely by imports, with GST from imports jumping nearly 20%, while domestic collections grew only 1.2%. After adjusting for refunds, net GST revenue stood at Rs 1.46 lakh crore, reflecting a muted 2.2% increase. Major industrial states such as Maharashtra, Gujarat, Karnataka and Tamil Nadu remained the biggest contributors, and overall trends suggest the economy continues to expand steadily, supported by import demand and gradual formalization. The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) – a single-figure indicator of sector performance – fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signalling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years. Amid a general lack of pressure on operating capacities, there was only a marginal increase in factory employment during December. Monthly Auto Sales: Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) rose 4.98%. The company reported 25% increase in total auto sales for December 2025, selling 86,090 vehicles during the period under review as against 68,814 vehicles sold in December 2024. Ashok Leyland rallied 8.27%. The company reported a 27% increase in total commercial vehicle sales to 21,533 units in December 2025, up from 16,957 units sold in December 2024. Maruti Suzuki India rose 2.23%. The company reported total sales of 2,17,854 units in December 2025, marking a 22.21% increase compared to 1,78,248 units sold in the same month last year. Eicher Motors added 0.09%. The company’s unlisted subsidiary, VE Commercial Vehicles (VECV), reported a 24.7% year-on-year jump in commercial vehicle (CV) sales to 10,384 units in December 2025. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) surged 10.90%. The company reported a net turnover of Rs 446.59 crore for December 2025, marking a 22.44% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 364.74 crore recorded in December 2024. Escorts Kubota gained 4.18%. The company’s agri-machinery business division sold 7,577 tractors in December 2025, registering a growth of 38.5% compared with 5,472 tractors sold in December 2024. TVS Motor Company advanced 7.28%. The company registered sales of 481,389 units in December 2025, which is 50% higher as compared with the 321,687 units sold in December 2024. Maruti Suzuki India rose 2.23%. The company’s total production rose 34.43% to 211,939 units in December 2025 as against 157,654 units recorded in December 2024. Hero MotoCorp added 5.23%. The company dispatched 456,479 motorcycles and scooters in December 2025, up 40% from 324,906 units in December 2024. Bajaj Auto jumped 4.79%. The company reported 14% increase in total auto sales for December 2025, selling 3.69 lakh units as against 3.23 lakh units sold in December 2024. Stocks in Spotlight: Shares of cigarette makers fell after the government imposed additional excise duty on cigarettes and introduced a Health and National Security Cess on pan masala, effective 1 February 2026. The move raises the tax burden above existing GST rates, with cigarettes attracting excise duty of Rs 2,050 to Rs 8,500 per thousand sticks and GST of 40% on tobacco products, which is expected to push up prices and weigh on sales volumes. Godfrey Phillips India fell 20.36%, ITC dropped 13.39%, while VST Industries slipped 2.16%. Sunteck Realty surged 6.18%. The GST authorities ruled in the company’s favour, fully setting aside a Rs 5.99 crore tax demand, along with interest and penalty, linked to Transferable Development Rights transactions for FY22. The order, passed on December 31, 2025, accepted Sunteck Realty’s submissions against a show cause notice issued in September under Section 73 of the GST Act. Lupin shed 0.23%. The company said that it has entered into an exclusive License, Supply, and Distribution Agreement with China-based Gan & Lee Pharmaceuticals for a novel fortnightly GLP-1 receptor agonist, Bofanglutide. Bofanglutide injection is indicated for the treatment of type 2 diabetes and for weight management in overweight or obese individuals. Vodafone Idea fell 1.33%. The company informed that it has received a penalty order amounting to Rs 637.90 crore under the Central Goods and Services Tax (CGST) Act, 2017. Global Market: Asia-Pacific: China: China’s economy ended the year on a slightly less gloomy note, as factory activity expanded in December for the first time since March, beating expectations, according to official data released Wednesday. The official manufacturing purchasing managers index rose to 50.1 in December, higher than the 49.2 reading that was recorded in November. A reading above 50 indicates expansion. Singapore: Singapore’s economy expanded 5.7% year-on-year for the fourth quarter, driven mainly by strong manufacturing growth in the three months through December. The latest reading is faster than the revised 4.3% growth in the previous quarter. Prime Minister Lawrence Wong announced in his New Year message that the country had clocked a stronger-than-expected 4.8% expansion for the full year of 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR slips and settles below Rs90/$ mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-slips-and-settles-below-rs90-mark/1663034</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663034</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee slipped below the 90-mark and settled the day lower by 22 paise at 90.20 (provisional) against the US dollar on Friday, amid disappointing macroeconomic data and strengthening of the American currency in overseas markets.

The Indian rupee slipped below the 90-mark and settled the day lower by 22 paise at 90.20 (provisional) against the US dollar on Friday, amid disappointing macroeconomic data and strengthening of the American currency in overseas markets. Persistent foreign fund outflows and strong dollar demand from importers further dented investor sentiment. However, weak crude oil prices and a surge in the domestic equities cushioned the downside. Meanwhile, Indian shares ended Friday's session notably higher despite persistent foreign fund withdrawals and lingering uncertainty over a trade deal with the United States. Investors shrugged off the results of survey data from S&P Global, which showed India's manufacturing activity expanded at the weakest pace in two years amid slower rises in output and new orders. The HSBC manufacturing Purchasing Managers' Index dropped to 55.0 in December from 56.6 in November. The benchmark BSE Sensex jumped 573.41 points, or 0.67 percent, to 85,762.01 as investors braced for the upcoming quarterly earnings season and the presentation of the Union Budget on February 1. The broader NSE Nifty index gained 182 points, or 0.70 percent, to close at 26,328.55.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PMI data, international trade figures and latest inflation prints to remain in focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pmi-data-international-trade-figures-and-latest-inflation-prints-to-remain-in-focus/1663039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663039</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equities begin 2026 on a resilient footing, supported by strong domestic macro cues and sectoral leadership from autos and metals.

Indian equities begin 2026 on a resilient footing, supported by strong domestic macro cues and sectoral leadership from autos and metals. The Nifty 50 notched a record high above 26,300 and the BSE Sensex climbed over 573 points, driven by auto sales strength and broad-based buying, which underpin improved Q3 earnings expectations. The Indian rupee continued to trade around 89.97 against the US dollar, suggesting persistent external pressures on capital flows. Globally, robust inflows into equity funds at year-end highlighted continued appetite for risk assets, which could extend to emerging markets including India. Given this backdrop, investors may favour structurally strong sectors and quality earnings, while remaining cautious on macro-sensitivities and currency dynamics as markets head into early reporting season. In India, the final reading for the HSBC Services PMI for December 2025 would be be released on Tuesday (06 January 2026). The HSBC India Services PMI fell to 59.1 in December 2025 from 59.8 in November, pointing to a slightly slower but still strong expansion in services activity, preliminary estimates showed. The final print for the HSBC Composite PMI would also be made public on the same day. The HSBC India Composite PMI fell to 58.9 in December 2025 from a final 59.7 in the prior month, flash data showed. It was the lowest reading since February, due to softer growth across manufacturing and service sectors. On Wednesday (07 January 2026), the M3 Money Supply figures for the week ended on December 26 would be made public. The Money Supply M3 in India increased to Rs 291,363.75 billion in the week ending November 28 from Rs 289,454.93 billion two weeks before. On Friday (09 January 2026), the year-on-year growth in bank loans for the period ended on December 26 would be announced. The value of loans in India increased 11.5 percent year-on-year in the fortnight ending 28 November 2025. On the same day, annual growth in deposits for the period ended on December 26 would also be made public. The value of deposits in India increased 10.2 percent year-on-year in the fortnight ending 28 November 2025. Friday would also see the release of the value of the Foreign Exchange Reserves for the week ended on January 02. Foreign Exchange Reserves in India increased to $693,320 million in December 19 from $688,950 million in the previous week. In China, the RatingDog Services PMI for the month of December would be announced on Monday (05 January 2026). The RatingDog China General Services PMI declined to 52.1 in November 2025, down from 52.6 in October. The latest reading marked the softest expansion in the services sector since June, as new business growth eased. The RatingDog Composite PMI for December 2025 would also be released on the same day. The RatingDog China General Composite PMI slipped to 51.2 in November 2025 from 51.8 in the previous month, marking its lowest level since July but still indicating private-sector expansion for the sixth consecutive month. On Wednesday (07 January 2026), the Foreign Exchange Reserves position for December 2025 would be made public. China’s foreign exchange reserves climbed by $3.0 billion to $3.346 trillion in November 2025, up from $3.343 trillion in October and compared with market expectations of $3.36 trillion. On Friday (09 January 2026), the Inflation Rate for December 2025 would be unveiled on Friday (09 January 2026). China’s annual inflation rate picked up to 0.7% in November 2025 from 0.2% in the prior month, aligning with market consensus and marking the highest level since February 2024. On the same day, the producer price inflation figures would also be made public. China’s producer prices fell 2.2% year-on-year in November 2025, slightly accelerating from a 2.1% decline in October and marking the 38th consecutive month of contraction. In the United States, the ISM Manufacturing PMI for the month of December would be released on Monday (05 January 2026). The ISM Manufacturing PMI for the US fell to 48.2 in November 2025, the lowest in four months, compared to 48.7 in September. The reading showed that the manufacturing sector contracted for the ninth consecutive month and at a faster pace. On Wednesday (07 January 2026), the ISM Services PMI for December 2025 would be announced. The ISM Services PMI for the US edged up to 52.6 in November 2025 from 52.4 in October, pointing to the strongest growth in the services sector in nine months. The API Crude Oil Stock Change for the week ended on January 02 would be made public would also be released on Wednesday. US crude oil inventories increased by 1.7 million barrels in the week ending December 26th, 2025, marking the second build after four weeks of draws, following a 2.4 million-barrel build the previous week. The Job Openings and Labor Turnover Survey (JOLTS) results for the month of November would also be made public on the same day. Job openings in the United States increased by 12,000 to 7.670 million in October 2025, up from 7.658 million in September, according to delayed data from the US Bureau of Labor Statistics. On Thursday (08 January 2026), the balance of trade data for the month of October would be announced. The US recorded a trade deficit of $52.8 billion in September 2025, the lowest since June 2020, compared to a $59.3 billion gap in August and forecasts of $63.3 billion. While rxports jumped 3% to $289.3 billion, imports rose at a slower 0.6% to $342.1 billion. On Friday (09 January 2026), the non-farm payrolls data for the month of December would be made public. US job growth totaled 64K in November, compared with a 105K loss in October. The unemployment rate for December 2025 would also be released on the same day. The US unemployment rate increased to 4.6% in November 2025 from 4.4% in September, marking the highest level since September 2021. Friday would also see the release of preliminary reading for the Michigan Consumer Sentiment for January 2026. The University of Michigan consumer sentiment for the US was revised lower to 52.9 in December 2025 from a preliminary of 53.3.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty vaults past 26,300, Sensex jumps 573 pts on earnings optimism]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-vaults-past-26300-sensex-jumps-573-pts-on-earnings-optimism/1663030</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663030</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks powered higher on Friday, with the Nifty vaulting past the 26,300 mark after scaling a fresh record high in late trade.

The key equity benchmarks powered higher on Friday, with the Nifty vaulting past the 26,300 mark after scaling a fresh record high in late trade. Market sentiment stayed buoyant throughout the session as strong Q3 corporate business updates fuelled earnings optimism and sparked broad-based buying. Auto and metal stocks led the rally, while FMCG and IT shares lagged, capping gains at the index level. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 573.41 points or 0.67% to 85,762.01. The Nifty 50 index climbed 182 points or 0.70% to 26,328.55. The Nifty hit a fresh record high of 26,340, and the Bank Nifty climbed to an all-time high of 60,203.75 in late trade. ICICI Bank (up 1.28%), Reliance Industries (up 1.10%) and HDFC Bank (up 0.92%) boosted the Nifty today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 0.97% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.79%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,772 shares rose and 1,449 shares fell. A total of 150 shares were unchanged. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI)—a single-figure indicator of sector performance—fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signaling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years. Amid a general lack of pressure on operating capacities, there was only a marginal increase in factory employment during December. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.38% to 6.606 as compared with the previous close of 6.581. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2000 compared with its close of 89.9850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.76% to Rs 136,830. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.19% to 98.47. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.34% to 4.164. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 04 cents or 0.07% to $60.81 a barrel. Global Markets: The Dow Jones Futures were up 178 points, indicating a strong opening in the US market today. European shares advanced on Friday, starting the first trading day of the year on a positive note. Asian indices ended higher to start the new year, with Hong Kong and South Korea leading the gains. South Korea’s Kospi index hit a new record on Friday, lifting investor sentiment across the region. Some Asian markets were still closed for the holidays, including Japan and mainland China. Meanwhile, Singapore’s economy expanded 5.7% year-on-year for the fourth quarter, driven mainly by strong manufacturing growth in the three months through December. The latest reading is faster than the revised 4.3% growth in the previous quarter. On Wednesday, Prime Minister Lawrence Wong announced in his New Year message that the country had clocked a stronger-than-expected 4.8% expansion for the full year of 2025. U.S. stock futures were looking up in early Asian hours, with S&P futures up by 0.15% and Nasdaq-100 futures climbing 0.12%. Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 0.16% higher. On Wednesday stateside, the S&P 500 dipped 0.74%, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and the Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 0.63%. Stocks in Spotlight: Coal India rallied 6.88% after the company announced that foreign coal consumers can now directly participate in its e-auction platform. In a regulatory filing, Coal India said it has permitted coal consumers located in the neighbouring countries like Bangladesh, Bhutan and Nepal, who wish to import coal from India, to directly participate in the Single Window Mode Agnostic (SWMA) auctions conducted by the company, effective 1 January 2026. Time Technoplast rose 4.38% after the company received regulatory approvals to manufacture and supply high-pressure Type-3 fully wrapped fibre reinforced composite cylinders for compressed gas applications. Bansal Wire Industries rose 1.95% after the company reported strong volume growth in Q3 FY26. Total sales volume rose 31.7% YoY to 1,21,702 metric tonnes in Q3 FY26, compared with 92,410 metric tonnes in Q3 FY25. Volumes were also up 6.18% QoQ from 1,14,609 metric tonnes in Q2 FY26. Maruti Suzuki India rose 1.47% after the company’s total production rose 34.43% to 211,939 units in December 2025 as against 157,654 units recorded in December 2024. Olectra Greentech jumped 4.05% after the company announced the start of commercial operations at its greenfield EV manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. The Phase-I unit has a per-shift annual production capacity of 2,500 electric buses. This represents 50% of the planned per-shift capacity of 5,000 buses per year. Sambhv Steel Tubes rose 1.70% after the company reported its highest-ever quarterly sales volume of value-added products in Q3 FY26, led by strong performance across segments. Remsons Industries rallied 4.47% after the company has secured a Rs 60-crore order from a leading domestic commercial vehicle (CV) OEM. The contract is for the supply of gear shifters with push-pull cables, with supplies set to begin from Q1 FY27. The order will be executed over a 60-month period, the company said. Punjab & Sind Bank jumped 5.01% after the bank's gross advances increased by 15.25% to Rs 110,488 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 95,870 crore as of 31 December 2024. South Indian Bank advanced 1.74% after the private lender said that its gross advances jumped 11.27% to Rs 96,765 crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 86,966 crore as of 31 December 2024. Hyundai Motor India (HMIL) declined 1.82%. The company has recorded 6.6% year-on-year (YoY) growth in total monthly sales, clocking sales of 58,702 units in December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper in demand, COMEX futures linger around five-month high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-in-demand-comex-futures-linger-around-five-month-high/1663012</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663012</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures consolidated around five-month high and generally remained steady on positive cues from Asian markets and tepid US dollar index.

COMEX Copper futures consolidated around five-month high and generally remained steady on positive cues from Asian markets and tepid US dollar index. The red metal currently trades at $5.72 per pound, up 0.75% on the day. It ended on a firm note in last month, clocking a spurt of nearly 8%. Focus is likely to stay on equities in near term. Asian stocks surged in thin holiday trade on Friday. Regional trading volumes remained thin due to holidays in Japan, China and New Zealand. However, Hong Kong's Hang Seng index soared 2.76% while South Korea’s KOSPI index hit a record high and added 2.30%. European market also edged up cautiously. MCX Copper broke above Rs 1300 per kg and currently linger at Rs 1310 per kg, up 1.42% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/blue-stock-chart-growth-picture-id174673054_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold rebounds, starts New Year on upbeat note]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-rebounds-starts-new-year-on-upbeat-note/1663010</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663010</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Gold futures rebounded today, witnessing good gains after testing a three-week low in last session.

COMEX Gold futures rebounded today, witnessing good gains after testing a three-week low in last session. The global markets are now slowly showing signs of normalcy as traders are coming back from Christmas and New Year holidays. COMEX Gold is up 1% at $4387 per ounce. The US dollar index is hovering around 98 mark, consolidating in a tight range amid lack of major economic cues. Gold will be eying the trends in currency markets in near term and clarity on Russia-Ukraine war will provide a much better understanding in terms of price action at the start of year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/closeup-of-blue-chart-growth-progress-picture-id177428264_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1663009</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663009</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,478.30, a premium of 149.75 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,328.55 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,478.30, a premium of 149.75 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,328.55 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index surged 182 points or 0.70% to 26,328.55. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 2.88% to 9.45. ITC, Coal India and HDFC Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 573 pts higher; Nifty ends at fresh high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-573-pts-higher-nifty-ends-at-fresh-high/1663007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663007</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended the session with solid gains, with the Nifty closing above the 26,300 mark after touching a record high in late trade.

The key equity benchmarks ended the session with solid gains, with the Nifty closing above the 26,300 mark after touching a record high in late trade. Market sentiment stayed upbeat throughout the day, supported by optimism over strong monthly auto sales data and continued buying interest across sectors. Attention is now shifting to the upcoming corporate earnings season, which is expected to guide market direction in the near term. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 573.41 points or 0.67% to 85,762.01. The Nifty 50 index climbed 182 points or 0.70% to 26,328.55. The Nifty hit a fresh record high of 26,340, and the Bank Nifty climbed to an all-time high of 60,203.75 in late trade. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 0.97% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.79%. The market breadth was strong. Among the sectoral indices, the Realty index (up 1.52%), the Nifty Metal index (up 1.47%) and the Nifty Auto index (up 1.13%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty FMCG index (down 1.19%), the Nifty IT index (up 0.39%) and the Nifty Private Bank index (up 0.40%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI)—a single-figure indicator of sector performance—fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signaling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years. Amid a general lack of pressure on operating capacities, there was only a marginal increase in factory employment during December. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.38% to 6.606 as compared with the previous close of 6.581. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2000 compared with its close of 89.9850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.76% to Rs 136,830. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.19% to 98.47. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.34% to 4.164. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 04 cents or 0.07% to $60.81 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares advanced on Friday, starting the first trading day of the year on a positive note. Asian markets ended higher to start the new year, with Hong Kong and South Korea leading the gains. South Korea’s Kospi index hit a new record on Friday, lifting investor sentiment across the region. Some Asian markets were still closed for the holidays, including Japan and mainland China. Meanwhile, Singapore’s economy expanded 5.7% year-on-year for the fourth quarter, driven mainly by strong manufacturing growth in the three months through December. The latest reading is faster than the revised 4.3% growth in the previous quarter. On Wednesday, Prime Minister Lawrence Wong announced in his New Year message that the country had clocked a stronger-than-expected 4.8% expansion for the full year of 2025. U.S. stock futures were looking up in early Asian hours, with S&P futures up by 0.15% and Nasdaq-100 futures climbing 0.12%. Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 0.16% higher. On Wednesday stateside, the S&P 500 dipped 0.74%, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and the Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 0.63%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty PSE Index rises 2.29%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-pse-index-rises-229/1663006</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663006</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty PSE index closed up 2.29% at 10130.05 today.

Nifty PSE index closed up 2.29% at 10130.05 today. The index is up 5.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Coal India Ltd gained 6.85%, NHPC Ltd rose 5.10% and NTPC Ltd jumped 4.70%. The Nifty PSE index is up 4.00% over last one year compared to the 8.85% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Energy index added 2.16% and Nifty Commodities index gained 1.57% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.70% to close at 26328.55 while the SENSEX added 0.67% to close at 85762.01 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/analysis-680571__340__stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty hits record high; broader mrkt outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-hits-record-high-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1663005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663005</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended with substantial gains today as the Nifty closed above the 26,300 level, touching record high in late trade.

The key equity indices ended with substantial gains today as the Nifty closed above the 26,300 level, touching record high in late trade. Market sentiment remained positive throughout the session, supported by optimism over strong monthly auto sales data and sustained buying interest. Investors are now turning their focus to the upcoming earnings season. Barring FMCG all the sectoral indices on the NSE were ended in green with Realty, PSU bank and metal shares lead the gains. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 573.41 points or 0.67% to 85,762.01. The Nifty 50 index climbed 182 points or 0.70% to 26,328.55. The Nifty hit a fresh record high of 26,340, and the Bank Nifty climbed to an all-time high of 60,203.75 in late trade. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 0.97% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.79%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,780 shares rose and 1,444 shares fell. A total of 147 shares were unchanged. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Manufacturing Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) – a single-figure indicator of sector performance – fell from 56.6 in November to 55.0 in December, signalling the weakest improvement in the health of the sector in two years. Amid a general lack of pressure on operating capacities, there was only a marginal increase in factory employment during December. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index jumped 1.52% to 898.80. The index rallied 3.33% for the third consecutive trading session. Anant Raj (up 5.71%), Godrej Properties (up 2.64%), Oberoi Realty (up 2.01%), Sobha (up 1.9%), Phoenix Mills (up 1.64%), Lodha Developers (up 1.2%), DLF (up 0.98%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.92%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Coal India rallied 6.88% after the company announced that foreign coal consumers can now directly participate in its e-auction platform. In a regulatory filing, Coal India said it has permitted coal consumers located in the neighbouring countries like Bangladesh, Bhutan and Nepal, who wish to import coal from India, to directly participate in the Single Window Mode Agnostic (SWMA) auctions conducted by the company, effective 1 January 2026. Maruti Suzuki India rose 1.47% after the company’s total production rose 34.43% to 211,939 units in December 2025 as against 157,654 units recorded in December 2024. Avantel added 0.73%. The company has received a manufacturing order worth Rs 1.76 crore from Bharat Electronics (BEL). Olectra Greentech jumped 4.05% after the company announced the start of commercial operations at its greenfield EV manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. The Phase-I unit has a per-shift annual production capacity of 2,500 electric buses. This represents 50% of the planned per-shift capacity of 5,000 buses per year. Sambhv Steel Tubes rose 1.70% after the company reported its highest-ever quarterly sales volume of value-added products in Q3 FY26, led by strong performance across segments. Remsons Industries rallied 4.68% after the company has secured a Rs 60-crore order from a leading domestic commercial vehicle (CV) OEM. The contract is for the supply of gear shifters with push-pull cables, with supplies set to begin from Q1 FY27. The order will be executed over a 60-month period, the company said. Punjab & Sind Bank jumped 5.01% after the bank's gross advances increased by 15.25% to Rs 110,488 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 95,870 crore as of 31 December 2024. South Indian Bank advanced 1.74% after the private lender said that its gross advances jumped 11.27% to Rs 96,765 crore as of 31 December 2025 as against Rs 86,966 crore as of 31 December 2024. Hyundai Motor India (HMIL) declined 1.82%. The company has recorded 6.6% year-on-year (YoY) growth in total monthly sales, clocking sales of 58,702 units in December 2025. Global Markets: European markets advanced on Friday, starting the first trading day of the year on a positive note. Asian markets ended higher to start the new year, with Hong Kong and South Korea leading the gains. South Korea’s Kospi index hit a new record on Friday, lifting investor sentiment across the region. Some Asian markets were still closed for the holidays, including Japan and mainland China. Meanwhile, Singapore’s economy expanded 5.7% year-on-year for the fourth quarter, driven mainly by strong manufacturing growth in the three months through December. The latest reading is faster than the revised 4.3% growth in the previous quarter. On Wednesday, Prime Minister Lawrence Wong announced in his New Year message that the country had clocked a stronger-than-expected 4.8% expansion for the full year of 2025. U.S. stock futures were looking up in early Asian hours, with S&P futures up by 0.15% and Nasdaq-100 futures climbing 0.12%. Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 0.16% higher. On Wednesday stateside, the S&P 500 dipped 0.74%, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and the Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 0.63%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD extends losing streak amid disappointing Eurozone manufacturing data]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-extends-losing-streak-amid-disappointing-eurozone-manufacturing-data/1663004</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663004</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[EUR/USD extends losing streak for the sixth straight session on Friday amid disappointing manufacturing activity figures in the Eurozone.

EUR/USD extends losing streak for the sixth straight session on Friday amid disappointing manufacturing activity figures in the Eurozone. Eurozone’s manufacturing sector suffered a setback at the end of the year, latest HCOB PMI data showed, with production levels decreasing for the first time since last February. The HCOB Eurozone Manufacturing PMI, a measure of the overall health of the eurozone manufacturing sector compiled by S&P Global, declined in December to 48.8, from 49.6 in November, taking it further below the 50.0 no-change mark. Declines in output and new orders were the main drivers, with Germany recording the steepest deterioration and weakest performance since February. The pair deepened slide below $1.18 mark and is quoting at $1.1760, down 0.17% on the day and lingering at their lowest level in one and half week. On the NSE, EUR/INR futures were up marginally at 106.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UCO Bank gains after total advances jump 16% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uco-bank-gains-after-total-advances-jump-16-yoy-in-q3/1663015</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663015</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) basis, the total advances grew by 5.19% in Q3 FY26.

On a quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) basis, the total advances grew by 5.19% in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, total business stood at Rs 5.54 lakh crore, registering a growth of 13.29% YoY and 3.36% QoQ. Total deposits increased to Rs 3.10 lakh crore, up 10.71% YoY and 1.64% QoQ. Domestic advances stood at Rs 2.15 lakh crore as of 31 December 2025, marking a growth of 5.39% QoQ and 17.49% YoY. Domestic deposits were at Rs 2.92 lakh crore, reflecting a 0.69% QoQ growth and a 10.19% YoY increase. The domestic CASA ratio improved to 38.41% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 38.11% as of 30 September 2025 and 37.97% as of 31 December 2024. The credit-deposit (CD) ratio strengthened to 78.61% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 75.47% as of 30 September 2025 and 74.45% as of 31 December 2024. UCO Bank is engaged in providing a wide range of banking and financial services, including retail banking, corporate banking, and treasury operations. The bank’s standalone net profit rose 2.8% to Rs 619.76 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 602.74 crore posted in Q2 FY25. The bank’s total income grew 4.9% to Rs 7,421.39 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UCOBank_60354133096_5475.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Green Energy rises after arm incorporates new wholly-owned subsidiary]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-green-energy-rises-after-arm-incorporates-new-wholly-owned-subsidiary/1663000</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663000</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Certificate of Incorporation was received on 2 January 2026.

The Certificate of Incorporation was received on 2 January 2026. AE5L has been incorporated with the objective of generating, developing, transforming, distributing, transmitting, selling, and supplying power or electrical energy using wind, solar, or other renewable energy sources. Adani Renewable Energy Holding Eleven holds 100% of AE5L’s share capital. AE5L is incorporated in India and registered with the Registrar of Companies, Gujarat, at Ahmedabad. It has an authorized capital and paid-up capital of Rs 1,00,000 each and is yet to commence business operations. Adani Green Energy is India’s largest and one of the leading renewable energy companies in the world enabling the clean energy transition. It develops, owns, and operates utility scale grid-connected solar, wind, hybrid and hydro pumped storage renewable power plants. The company has set a target of achieving 50 GW by 2030 aligned to India’s decarbonization goals. The company reported a 111.2% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 583 crore despite of 5.3% decline in net sales to Rs 2,824 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniGreenEnergyLtd_74416007001_70666.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India-UK CETA to Boost Trade Opportunities, Especially for Exporters in East and Northeast India]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-uk-ceta-to-boost-trade-opportunities-especially-for-exporters-in-east-and-northeast-india/1662997</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662997</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The India-UK Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA) is expected to be implemented in the first half of 2026, marking a new era in partnership between the two nations, British Deputy High Commissioner Andrew Fleming said.

The India-UK Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA) is expected to be implemented in the first half of 2026, marking a new era in partnership between the two nations, British Deputy High Commissioner Andrew Fleming said. Notably, the agreement is designed to offer opportunities for businesses of all sizes, particularly for exporters in West Bengal and the 12 states across East and Northeast India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-1714373__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coal India climbs after foreign buyers get direct access to SWMA E-Auctions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coal-india-climbs-after-foreign-buyers-get-direct-access-to-swma-e-auctions/1662995</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662995</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, Coal India said it has permitted coal consumers located in the neighbouring countries like Bangladesh, Bhutan and Nepal, who wish to import coal from India, to directly participate in the Single Window Mode Agnostic (SWMA) auctions conducted by the company, effective 1 January 2026.

In a regulatory filing, Coal India said it has permitted coal consumers located in the neighbouring countries like Bangladesh, Bhutan and Nepal, who wish to import coal from India, to directly participate in the Single Window Mode Agnostic (SWMA) auctions conducted by the company, effective 1 January 2026. Under the revised framework, foreign buyers are permitted to take part in SWMA auctions alongside domestic consumers. Earlier, coal consumers from across the border could access Coal India’s coal only through domestic traders, who were allowed to buy and sell coal without any end-use restrictions. Payment process would be transparent as per Foreign Exchange Management Act (FEMA) rules. While buyers from Nepal can make the payments in rupees as well as US Dollar, buyers from the other two countries are required to affect their payment in US Dollars, valuation of which would be on rupees. All operational and procedural modalities have been incorporated in the updated Scheme. Key provisions for foreign buyers include one-time registration, participation through digital bidding, advance electronic payments and export through notified logistics channels. “Opening SWMA e-auctions to foreign buyers reflects CIL’s calibrated approach to market expansion while fully safeguarding domestic coal requirements. This step enhances transparency, competition and global market integration” said a senior company official. Coal India is mainly engaged in mining and production of Coal and also operates Coal washeries. The major consumers of the company are power and steel sectors. Consumers from other sectors include cement, fertilizers, brick kilns. The company’s consolidated net profit tanked 30.32% to Rs 4,354.24 crore on a 1.10% fall in total income to Rs 32,327.16 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoalIndia_84226386779_12019.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Radico Khaitan Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/radico-khaitan-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1662989</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662989</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITC Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd, Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd and Karnataka Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 January 2026.

ITC Ltd, Sapphire Foods India Ltd, Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd and Karnataka Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 January 2026. Radico Khaitan Ltd tumbled 4.64% to Rs 3103.1 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 30070 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9194 shares in the past one month. ITC Ltd crashed 3.86% to Rs 349.9. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 74.73 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 37.9 lakh shares in the past one month. Sapphire Foods India Ltd lost 3.73% to Rs 251.6. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.85 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 40897 shares in the past one month. Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd shed 3.65% to Rs 578.85. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 27905 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21537 shares in the past one month. Karnataka Bank Ltd corrected 3.48% to Rs 199.7. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 9.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.04 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RadicoKhaitan_11315875496_2153.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cupid Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cupid-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662988</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662988</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, Kiri Industries Ltd and SRG Housing Finance Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 January 2026.

Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, Kiri Industries Ltd and SRG Housing Finance Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 January 2026. Cupid Ltd tumbled 19.99% to Rs 419.95 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 39.48 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.97 lakh shares in the past one month. Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd lost 19.99% to Rs 55.14. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 68.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7.75 lakh shares in the past one month. Vivimed Labs Ltd crashed 9.97% to Rs 15.08. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3516 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10126 shares in the past one month. Kiri Industries Ltd dropped 9.86% to Rs 617.1. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 14.83 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.26 lakh shares in the past one month. SRG Housing Finance Ltd slipped 7.54% to Rs 282. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 104 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 348 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cupid_16723626520_5185.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades near record highs; metal shares shine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-near-record-highs-metal-shares-shine/1662987</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662987</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key benchmark indices traded with strong gains in mid-afternoon trade, as the Nifty traded above the 26,300 level.

The key benchmark indices traded with strong gains in mid-afternoon trade, as the Nifty traded above the 26,300 level. Market sentiment remained upbeat, supported by optimism over robust monthly auto sales data and sustained buying interest. Metal stocks continued their rally for a fourth consecutive trading session. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 491.58 points or 0.58% to 85,683.42. The Nifty 50 index gained 163.70 points or 0.63% to 26,310.25. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.86% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.72%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,653 shares rose and 1,466 shares fell. A total of 183 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index added 1.09% to 11,378.75. The index jumped 5.47% for the four consecutive trading sessions. National Aluminium Company (up 3.97%), Hindalco Industries (up 3.06%), Hindustan Copper (up 2.31%), Hindustan Zinc (up 2%), Vedanta (up 1.76%), Welspun Corp (up 0.84%), NMDC (up 0.74%), Adani Enterprises (up 0.58%), Jindal Steel (up 0.54%) and JSW Steel (up 0.4%) surged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.40% to 6.607 as compared with the previous close of 6.581. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2200 compared with its close of 89.9850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 0.85% to Rs 136,962. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.13% to 98.41. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.31% to 4.163. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 18 cents or 0.30% to $61.03 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Tamilnad Mercantile Bank rose 2.27% after the company’s total advances jumped 16.30% to Rs 50,763 crore as of 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 43,650 crore as of 31 December 2024. Zota Health Care advanced 1.75% after the company announced significant expansion in its Davaindia store network, adding 276 new stores. The company’s COCO segment opened 231 stores in Q3 FY26, taking the total number of COCO stores managed by wholly owned subsidiary Davaindia Health Mart to 1,207 as of 30 September 2025. Rama Steel Tubes rose 0.32%. The company said that it has registered a sales volume of 58,974.55 ton in Q3 FY26, which is higher by 14.1% as compared with the volume of 51,669.01 ton recorded in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>