<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential MF resumes three overseas funds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mf-resumes-three-overseas-funds/1666693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666693</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund said it will resume subscriptions in three of its international schemes from 27 January 2026, while imposing investment caps to manage overseas exposure.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund said it will resume subscriptions in three of its international schemes from 27 January 2026, while imposing investment caps to manage overseas exposure. The fund house said fresh and additional investments in ICICI Prudential US Bluechip Equity Fund, ICICI Prudential NASDAQ 100 Index Fund, and ICICI Prudential Strategic Metal and Energy Equity Fund of Fund will be capped at Rs 2 lakh per PAN per month per scheme. The limit will apply across all modes, including lumpsum investments, switches, SIPs and STPs. For systematic investments, the AMC has set per-PAN limits based on frequency, with daily SIP or STP capped at Rs 10,000, weekly at Rs 50,000, fortnightly SIP at Rs 1 lakh, monthly SIP or STP at Rs 2 lakh, and quarterly SIP or STP at Rs 6 lakh. These limits will apply only to fresh subscriptions or new systematic registrations, while existing SIP and STP instalments will continue without restrictions. The fund house said it may consider suspending further subscriptions if the available overseas investment limit under any scheme approaches the regulatory cap. The move follows earlier restrictions imposed after Sebi directed mutual funds to halt fresh overseas investments as the industry-wide overseas investment limit was nearing exhaustion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/yellow-warning-mutual-funds-highway-road-sign-picture-id512_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shekhawati Industries Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shekhawati-industries-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1666684</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666684</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Muthoot Capital Services Ltd, Sudarshan Colorants India Ltd, Pavna Industries Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 22 January 2026.

Muthoot Capital Services Ltd, Sudarshan Colorants India Ltd, Pavna Industries Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 22 January 2026. Shekhawati Industries Ltd lost 14.26% to Rs 13.53 at 14:28 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 38841 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5383 shares in the past one month. Muthoot Capital Services Ltd crashed 13.40% to Rs 218.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 12627 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 895 shares in the past one month. Sudarshan Colorants India Ltd tumbled 12.13% to Rs 333.9. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4051 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1065 shares in the past one month. Pavna Industries Ltd fell 11.60% to Rs 16.77. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 16319 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10414 shares in the past one month. Shyam Telecom Ltd corrected 10.49% to Rs 10.15. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3590 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3064 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShekhawatiPoly_68841797628_37447.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel Corp rises on new order win]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-corp-rises-on-new-order-win/1666683</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666683</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RailTel said it has received a work order for providing services under an annual maintenance contract.

RailTel said it has received a work order for providing services under an annual maintenance contract. The order is valued at Rs 140.71 crore and is scheduled to be executed by 30 January 2031. The company clarified that the contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related-party transactions. RailTel Corporation, a "Navratna" PSU, is one of the largest neutral telecom infrastructure providers in the country, owning a Pan-India optical fiber network. As on December 2025, the Government of India held 72.84% stake in the company. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 4.72% to Rs 76.07 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 72.64 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 12.78% YoY to Rs 951.36 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 330 pts; FMCG shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-330-pts-fmcg-shares-advance/1666681</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666681</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade, as selective profit booking and continued FII selling kept investors cautious ahead of key Q3 earnings announcements and cues from the World Economic Forum in Davos.

The key equity barometers traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade, as selective profit booking and continued FII selling kept investors cautious ahead of key Q3 earnings announcements and cues from the World Economic Forum in Davos. The Nifty traded above the 25,200 level. FMCG shares advanced after declining in the previous two trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 329.93 points or 0.40% to 82,257.41. The Nifty 50 index rose 78.20 points or 0.31% to 25,236.05. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 1.06% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.98%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,866 shares rose and 1,272 shares fell. A total of 157 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.63% to 13.69. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index rose 0.76% to 51,793. The index dropped 1.33% in the past two trading sessions. Emami (up 3.29%), Radico Khaitan (up 3.12%), Britannia Industries (up 2.84%), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (up 2.68%), Dabur India (up 1.88%), Varun Beverages (up 1.67%), Nestle India (up 1.54%), Godrej Consumer Products (up 1.53%), Patanjali Foods (up 1.17%) and United Spirits (up 1.17%) gained. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.27% to 6.637 as compared with the previous close of 6.655. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6275 compared with its close of 91.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.78% to Rs 1,51,675. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.02% to 98.81. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.28% to 4.239. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 20 cents or 0.31% to $65.04 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: TANFAC Industries slipped 3.557% after the company reported a 55.3% drop in net profit to Rs 15.57 crore on a 2.7% fall in net sales to Rs 173.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. KEI Industries fell 1.02%. The company repo

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Schneider Electric Infrastructure Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-schneider-electric-infrastructure-ltd-counter/1666679</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666679</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PNB Housing Finance Ltd, Tata Communications Ltd, Waaree Energies Ltd, Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 22 January 2026.

PNB Housing Finance Ltd, Tata Communications Ltd, Waaree Energies Ltd, Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 22 January 2026. Schneider Electric Infrastructure Ltd witnessed volume of 49.87 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 19.93 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.50 lakh shares. The stock increased 9.95% to Rs.636.85. Volumes stood at 2.15 lakh shares in the last session. PNB Housing Finance Ltd witnessed volume of 61.8 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.56 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 7.22 lakh shares. The stock dropped 7.76% to Rs.858.30. Volumes stood at 8.37 lakh shares in the last session. Tata Communications Ltd witnessed volume of 16.99 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.85 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.48 lakh shares. The stock dropped 3.72% to Rs.1,557.60. Volumes stood at 9.95 lakh shares in the last session. Waaree Energies Ltd registered volume of 86.3 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.54 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 15.59 lakh shares. The stock rose 7.90% to Rs.2,610.00. Volumes stood at 17.65 lakh shares in the last session. Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd witnessed volume of 92.12 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.26 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 21.60 lakh shares. The stock dropped 7.10% to Rs.105.79. Volumes stood at 27.67 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SchneiderElect_84474111032_41218.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zee Entertainment gains as Q3 PAT skyrockets 103% QoQ to Rs 155 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zee-entertainment-gains-as-q3-pat-skyrockets-103-qoq-to-rs-155-cr/1666680</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666680</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, Zee Entertainment’s net profit surged 102.99% to Rs 155.29 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 76.5 crore in Q2 FY26.

On a consolidated basis, Zee Entertainment’s net profit surged 102.99% to Rs 155.29 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 76.5 crore in Q2 FY26. Total income rallied 15.17% to Rs 2,298.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Profit before tax from continuing operations soared 74.78% to Rs 201.7 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company's consolidated net profit tanked 5.07% while total income surged 14.16% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax from continuing operations rallied 1.97% YoY. EBITDA declined 24.46% to Rs 240.49 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 240.09 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin contracted to 10.5% in Q3 FY26 as against 16.1% in Q3 FY25. For the quarter, advertising revenue was Rs 1,050.2 crore (up 6.89% YoY), subscription revenue stood at Rs 378.4 crore (up 579.35% YoY), and revenue from other sales & services declined 46.66% YoY to Rs 18.4 crore. Zee Entertainment Enterprises (ZEEL) is a media & entertainment company offering entertainment content to diverse audiences. It is present across broadcasting, movies, music, digital, live entertainment, and theater businesses, both within India and overseas.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZeeEntertainmen_48983040733_3126.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Total outstanding credit to commercial sector gains 15% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/total-outstanding-credit-to-commercial-sector-gains-15-on-year/1666678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666678</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in a monthly update that during 2025-26 so far (up to December 31), total flow of financial resources to the commercial sector increased to Rs 30.8 lakh crore from Rs 21.3 lakh crore a year ago.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in a monthly update that during 2025-26 so far (up to December 31), total flow of financial resources to the commercial sector increased to Rs 30.8 lakh crore from Rs 21.3 lakh crore a year ago. Non-bank sources – corporate bond issuances, and foreign direct investment to India − showed a marked increase during the year so far. As on December 31, 2025, the total outstanding credit to the commercial sector rose by 15.0 per cent, with non-bank sources registering a growth of 16.4 per cent.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR depreciates 1.2% so far in January driven by persistent foreign fund outflows and heightened geopolitical tensions, says RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-depreciates-12-so-far-in-january-driven-by-persistent-foreign-fund-outflows-and-heightened-geopolitical-tensions-says-rbi/1666652</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666652</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee (INR) depreciated against the US dollar in December, pressured by foreign portfolio outflows and uncertainty surrounding the India-US trade deal, RBI noted in its January bulletin.

The Indian rupee (INR) depreciated against the US dollar in December, pressured by foreign portfolio outflows and uncertainty surrounding the India-US trade deal, RBI noted in its January bulletin. The volatility of the INR, as measured by the coefficient of variation, remained relatively lower than that of most major currencies. In January so far (up to 19th), the INR depreciated by 1.2 per cent over its end-December level. In real effective terms, the Indian rupee depreciated in December due to depreciation of INR in nominal effective terms and relatively lower inflation in India vis-à-vis its major trading partners. Net FPI registered outflows from both the equity and debt segments in December, amidst uncertainty surrounding the stalled India-US trade deal and the depreciation of the rupee but the country’s external sector remains resilient, as evidenced by the improved international investment position as at end-September 2025, the central bank noted. Comfortable foreign exchange reserves and a sustainable current account deficit continue to underpin India’s external sector stability, it said.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sagar Cements Q3 net loss widens to Rs 64 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sagar-cements-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-64-cr/1666651</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666651</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 4.72% YoY to Rs 590.54 crore in Q3 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 4.72% YoY to Rs 590.54 crore in Q3 December 2025. The company posted a pre-tax loss of Rs 73.83 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 64.23 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA remained flat at Rs 37.67 crore in Q3 FY26, while the operating EBITDA margin declined to 4% from 7% in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, sales volume jumped 2% to 10,23,289 MT compared with 10,04,397 MT recorded in Q3 FY25. As on 31 December 2025, the company’s net debt stood at Rs 1,54,435 crore. Sreekanth Reddy, Joint managing director, Sagar Cement, said, “Our performance for the quarter was largely in line with our expectations. Demand remained soft during the firsthalf, impacted by the extended monsoon and the festive season, but witnessed a gradual improvement towards theend of the quarter. Pricing also remained benign across most of our key markets. That said, we believe we will endthe fiscal on a positive note with overall volumes of around 6 million MT, supported by a pickup in demand and animproving pricing trend. Furthermore, we are working towards improving efficiencies and profitability through various cost initiatives, including WHRS and solar capacity additions, lead distance optimization, and plant upgrades. Additionally, weexpect improving cash flows and planned land monetization to support prudent growth going forward. On the capacity expansion front, our projects at Andhra Cements and Jeerabad are progressing as per plan. Theconstruction of the 6-stage preheater at the Dachepalli plant of Andhra Cements has been successfully completedand was recently commissioned. The 4.35 MW WHR project at the Gudipadu unit is expected to be commissioned bythe end of FY26. We also expect to commission expansion of the Jeerabad capacity from 1.0 MTPA to 1.5 MTPA byearly part of Q1 FY27 and the cement capacity at Dachepalli by August 2026. Going ahead, we remain committed to delivering sustainable and profitable growth by strengthening operationalexcellence, deepening our regional presence, and increasing the use of renewable energy across our manufacturingfootprint.” Sagar Cements is engaged in the business of manufacturing and selling cement. Shares of Sagar Cements rose 1.04% to Rs 189 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SagarCements_48885647539_1000.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jio Financial Services Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jio-financial-services-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1666637</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666637</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jio Financial Services Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Jio Financial Services Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 261.2, down 0.78% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25201.1. The Sensex is at 81970.15, up 0.07%.Jio Financial Services Ltd has eased around 12.55% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Jio Financial Services Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 1.95% in last one month and is currently quoting at 26963.5, up 0.31% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 72.39 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 106.01 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 260.9, down 1.06% on the day. Jio Financial Services Ltd jumped 2.09% in last one year as compared to a 8.6% rally in NIFTY and a 19.53% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 239.27 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JioFinancialServicesLtd_17889422_20712.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NMDC Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nmdc-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1666638</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666638</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NMDC Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

NMDC Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 78.43, down 0.27% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.17% on the day, quoting at 25201.1. The Sensex is at 81970.15, up 0.07%.NMDC Ltd has eased around 3.8% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which NMDC Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 7.62% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11438.95, up 0.92% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 119.03 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 320.56 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 78.15, down 0.55% on the day. NMDC Ltd jumped 15.19% in last one year as compared to a 8.6% rally in NIFTY and a 35.57% spurt in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 9.74 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NMDC_85653440841_12059.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with small gains; media shares advance; VIX jumps 1.97%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-small-gains-media-shares-advance-vix-jumps-197/1666639</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666639</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the afternoon trade amid profit booking and FII selling.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the afternoon trade amid profit booking and FII selling. Market participants remained cautious ahead of Q3 earnings and cues from the World Economic Forum. The Nifty traded above the 25,200 level. Realty and consumer durables shares declined while media, PSU Bank and pharma shares advanced. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 94.45 points or 0.11% to 82,001.08. The Nifty 50 index jumped 43.85 points or 0.17% to 25,201.35. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.72% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.65%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,771 shares rose and 1,314 shares fell. A total of 170 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.97% to 13.96. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 6,24,82,800 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 13:20 IST on Thursday (22 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.70 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Gainers & Losers: Dr Reddy's Laboratories (up 5.46%), Bharat Electronics (up 3.08%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 2.21%), Adani Enterprises (up 2.20%) and Coal India (up 1.87%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Eternal (down 1.82%), Titan Company (down 1.78%), SBI Life Insurance Company (down 1.47%), Jio Financial Services (down 0.68%) and Eicher Motors (down 0.63%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Dr Reddys Laboratories added 5.46%. The company reported 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,210 crore on a 4.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 8,753 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Eternal fell 1.82%. The company reported a 72.9% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 102 crore on 201.9% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 16,315 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Consumer jumped 9.13% after the company reported an 83.2% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 46.4 crore on 30.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 306 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (HPCL) shed 0.44%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 34.72% to Rs 4,072.49 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3,022.90 crore in Q3 FY25. The company's total income (excluding excise duty) rose 5.23% YoY to Rs 1,15,740.02 crore during the December 2025 quarter. Zydus Lifesciences rose 1.08% after the company announced the launch of the world’s first biosimilar of Nivolumab in India under the brand name Tishtha, aimed at treating multiple types of cancer. Global Markets: European markets opened higher on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said a “framework” agreement had been reached over Greenland, and called off imposing escalating tariffs on a group of European countries. Asian markets traded mixed, tracking overnight gains on Wall Street after U.S. President Donald Trump dialed back his threat to impose tariffs on European countries over Greenland. Trump also said at the World Economic Forum in Davos that he would not use force to acquire the Arctic island, calming nerves over a possible U.S. military action, adding that he had “formed the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland,” along with NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. Meanwhile, South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. U.S. equities leaped on Wednesday after President Donald Trump called off new Europe tariffs, saying a deal framework has been reached over Greenland. The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged 588.64 points, or 1.21%, to end at 49,007.23. The S&P 500 gained 1.16% and closed at 6,875.62, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.18% to settle at 23,224.82. Back in Washington, Supreme Court justices expressed skepticism about whether Trump has the authority to fire Lisa Cook as a Federal Reserve governor. During oral arguments Wednesday, Justice Brett Kavanaugh told a Trump administration lawyer that arguments the president can fire Cook without judicial review “would weaken, if not shatter, the independence of the Federal Reserve."

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Goa Carbon Q3 net loss widens to Rs 23 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/goa-carbon-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-23-crore/1666636</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666636</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue jumped 49.51% YoY to Rs 193.58 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 129.47 crore in the corresponding quarter last year.

However, revenue jumped 49.51% YoY to Rs 193.58 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 129.47 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. The company reported a pre-tax loss of Rs 20.93 crore in the third quarter of FY26, as against a pre-tax loss of Rs 10.39 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 55.22% YoY to Rs 220.90 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 203.60 crore (up 50.08% YoY), while employee benefits expense was Rs 6.08 crore (up 10.54% YoY) during the period under review. On a nine-month basis, the company reported a standalone net loss of Rs 52.73 crore in 9M FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 15.49 crore in 9M FY25, while revenue increased 31.68% YoY to Rs 495.04 crore during the period. Goa Carbon is in the business of manufacturing and selling calcined petroleum coke from its manufacturing facilities at Goa, Paradeep and Bilaspur. Shares of Goa Carbon shed 0.24% to currently trade at Rs 368.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GoaCarbon_83261298467_196.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oracle Financial Services rises after Q3 PAT jumps 13% YoY to Rs 609.6 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oracle-financial-services-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-13-yoy-to-rs-6096-cr/1666635</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666635</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 857.4 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025, up 11.4% as against Rs 770 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter the previous year.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 857.4 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025, up 11.4% as against Rs 770 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter the previous year. The company's operating income reached Rs 797 crore, reflecting a 14% YoY growth. On a segmental basis, the company’s product licenses and related activities stood at Rs 1,773.5 crore (up 13.61% YoY), and revenue from IT solutions and consulting services stood at Rs 192.4 crore (up 24.77). Avadhut Ketkar, chief financial officer, Oracle Financial Services Software, said, “The net profit margin for the quarter was 31% despite the effect of the new labour code-related accruals. Strong collections also helped ensure the days of sales outstanding (DSO) were reduced to 58 days at the end of the quarter. Our Remaining Performance Obligations as of December 31, 2025, are Rs. 7,107 Crore, 12% higher than as of September 30, 2025.” Oracle Financial Services Software is a world leader in providing products and services to the financial services industry and is a majority-owned subsidiary of Oracle Corporation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OracleFinServ_27814195267_13105.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd soars 2%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nazara-technologies-ltd-soars-2/1666634</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666634</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Nazara Technologies Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 282.7, up 2% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.37% on the day, quoting at 25250.25. The Sensex is at 82151.32, up 0.3%. Nazara Technologies Ltd has risen around 17.21% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Nazara Technologies Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 2.26% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1354, up 2.05% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 14.48 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 46.23 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 384.38 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NazaraTechnologies_39505358.8300902_33311.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen slips toward 158.5 as fiscal worries and risk appetite weigh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-slips-toward-1585-as-fiscal-worries-and-risk-appetite-weigh/1666633</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666633</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen weakened toward 158.5 per dollar on Thursday, staying under pressure as concerns over Japan’s fiscal outlook combined with an improvement in global risk sentiment.

The Japanese yen weakened toward 158.5 per dollar on Thursday, staying under pressure as concerns over Japan’s fiscal outlook combined with an improvement in global risk sentiment. On the domestic side, Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi called a snap election and signaled looser fiscal policy, including a proposal to scrap the 8% sales tax on food, which added to worries about public finances. Externally, risk appetite improved after US President Donald Trump reversed his stance on Greenland, stepping back from threats of heavy tariffs on several European countries and announcing in Davos that a framework for future Greenland-related deal with NATO had been reached. Attention now turns to the Bank of Japan, which is due to announce its policy decision on Friday. The central bank is widely expected to keep policy unchanged after lifting the overnight rate to 0.75% in December, the highest level in three decades. Markets will closely watch Governor Kazuo Ueda’s post-meeting comments for signals on the timing of the next rate hike, which could shape near-term moves in the yen.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index rebounds as Trump steps back from Europe tariff threat  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-rebounds-as-trump-steps-back-from-europe-tariff-threat/1666628</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666628</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index firmed up on Wednesday amid reports that US President Donald Trump said he would step back from imposing tariffs on goods from European nations opposing his effort to take possession of Greenland.

The dollar index firmed up on Wednesday amid reports that US President Donald Trump said he would step back from imposing tariffs on goods from European nations opposing his effort to take possession of Greenland. The index is seen recovering momentum from a two-week low but still lingers under 99 mark. Investors now look ahead to weekly jobless claims for fresh signals on the labor market, alongside delayed PCE inflation data. Currently, the dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 98.64, up 0.07% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trim most of gains; pharma snaps 9-day losses]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trim-most-of-gains-pharma-snaps-9-day-losses/1666629</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666629</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks pared most of the early gains in early afternoon trade amid profit booking and FII selling with the Nifty trading below 25,300.

The key equity benchmarks pared most of the early gains in early afternoon trade amid profit booking and FII selling with the Nifty trading below 25,300. Market participants remained cautious ahead of Q3 earnings and cues from the World Economic Forum. Pharma shares jumped after declining in the past nine trading consecutive sessions. At 12:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 241.43 points or 0.29% to 82,151.06. The Nifty 50 index jumped 104.45 points or 0.42% to 25,261.95. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.81% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.72%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,762 shares rose and 1,231 shares fell. A total of 196 shares were unchanged. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 1.74% to 14.02. The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures were trading at 25,282.40, at a premium of 20.45 points as compared with the spot at 25,261.95. The Nifty option chain for the 27 January 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 138.6 lakh contracts at the 26,000 strike price. Maximum put OI of 101.3 lakh contracts was seen at 25,000 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index added 1.30% to 21,864.70. The index tumbled 7.31% in the previous nine consecutive trading sessions. Dr Reddys Laboratories (up 5.56%), Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (up 1.97%), Lupin (up 1.62%), Aurobindo Pharma (up 1.36%), Alkem Laboratories (up 1.33%), Biocon (up 1.25%), Zydus Lifesciences (up 1.06%), Wockhardt (up 0.99%), Divis Laboratories (up 0.98%) and Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 0.74%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: eClerx Services rallied 4.64% after the company’s board is scheduled to meet on 28 January 2026 to deliberate on bonus shares and Q3 FY26 results. Anant Raj rose 1.20% after the company reported a 30.75% year-on-year (YoY) increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 110.32 crore recorded in the same quarter last year. Revenue from operations jumped 20% YoY to Rs 641.59 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. TANFAC Industries slipped 3.79% after the company reported 55.3% drop in net profit to Rs 15.57 crore on a 2.7% fall in net sales to Rs 173.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gravita India Q3 PAT climbs 25% YoY to Rs 98 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gravita-india-q3-pat-climbs-25-yoy-to-rs-98-cr/1666625</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666625</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 115.09 crore in the December 2025 quarter, up 29.15% from Rs 89.11 crore in the same period last year.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 115.09 crore in the December 2025 quarter, up 29.15% from Rs 89.11 crore in the same period last year. Total expenses decreased 2.40% YoY to Rs 913.64 crore during the quarter. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 914.62 crore (up 14.79% YoY), employee benefit expenses were Rs 45.92 crore (up 35.53% YoY) and finance costs declined 49.06% YoY to Rs 6.54 crore during the period under review. EBITDA stood at Rs 116.06 crore in Q3 FY26, up 13.48% YoY, while EBITDA margin rose to 11.41% from 10.26% in Q3 FY25. On the management commentary and business outlook, the company stated, “Gravita reported a stable performance in Q3 and 9MFY26, with consistent progress across operational and financial metrics across all key segments. In 9MFY26, the company delivered YoY growth of 5%, 9%, 15% and 32% in volumes, revenue, EBITDA and PAT, respectively, while maintaining a healthy ROIC of 25%. Higher contribution from value-added products and increased domestic scrap sourcing reflect efficiency gains from its integrated operating model. During 9MFY26, Gravita incurred capex of Rs 125 Cr. across its businesses. Aligned with its VISION 2029 strategy, Gravita continues to scale capacities across its established segments— lead, aluminum, plastics, rubber and turnkey solutions—with the ambition of exceeding 7 LTPA by FY28. In parallel, the company is building presence in emerging recycling verticals such as lithium-ion batteries, paper and steel. Management remains focused on delivering targeted volume growth, earnings expansion and ROIC above 25%, while progressively increasing the contribution of value-added products beyond 50% and non-lead businesses above 30%, anchored by a strong ESG framework. Supported by supply-chain strength, ongoing capacity additions, diversification initiatives, hedging mechanisms and disciplined execution amid a supportive policy environment, Gravita is well positioned to create sustained long-term value.” Gravita India is a manufacturer of lead, lead alloys & lead products, aluminum alloys & plastic granules, and offers turnkey solutions for the recycling industry and consultancy. Shares of Gravita India declined 2.20% to Rs 1,520 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GravitaIndia_26101386162_35607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lotus-chocolate-company-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1666623</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666623</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bajaj Consumer Care Ltd, Williamson Magor & Company Ltd, Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd and AksharChem (India) Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 22 January 2026.

Bajaj Consumer Care Ltd, Williamson Magor & Company Ltd, Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd and AksharChem (India) Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 22 January 2026. Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd surged 20.00% to Rs 667.2 at 11:58 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 23692 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7531 shares in the past one month. Bajaj Consumer Care Ltd soared 20.00% to Rs 297.05. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 15.19 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 23319 shares in the past one month. Williamson Magor & Company Ltd spiked 16.49% to Rs 33.9. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 4967 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 314 shares in the past one month. Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd exploded 16.13% to Rs 167. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 5005 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1387 shares in the past one month. AksharChem (India) Ltd spurt 14.75% to Rs 237.6. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 499 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 884 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LotusChocolate_22571601181_2252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>