<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:19:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR falls marginally to approch around 90 per US dollar mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-falls-marginally-to-approch-around-90-per-us-dollar-mark/1662868</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662868</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee closee at 89.99 against the US dollar, down 10 paise on the day.

Indian Rupee closee at 89.99 against the US dollar, down 10 paise on the day. Rupee has been sliding this week, easing from three week high against the US dollar. Overall market activity was thin today. Local shares ended a choppy session little changed on Thursday as most global equity and commodity markets remained closed on New Year's Day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-currency-trading-concept-picture-id504246822_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee posts marginal gain]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-posts-marginal-gain/1662867</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662867</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 90.1400 per Dollar on Thursday (01 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.1500 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end flat amid expiry volatility, Nifty ends below 25,150 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-flat-amid-expiry-volatility-nifty-ends-below-25150-mark/1662862</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662862</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Benchmark equity indices ended nearly flat as the expiry of weekly Sensex derivatives contracts capped gains in the absence of major economic cues.

Benchmark equity indices ended nearly flat as the expiry of weekly Sensex derivatives contracts capped gains in the absence of major economic cues. The Nifty closed below the 25,150 mark after giving up early advances, with auto and metal stocks rising while pharma and healthcare shares declined, as investors shifted focus to the upcoming earnings season. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 32 points or 0.04% to 85,188.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 16.95 points or 0.06% to 26,146.55. ITC (down 9.69%), Bajaj Finance (down 1.46%) and ICICI Bank (down 0.42%) were major index drags. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index climbed 0.27% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.02%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,211 shares rose and 1,952 shares fell. A total of 176 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 3.06% to 9.19. Economy: GST revenues in December showed a modest pickup, with gross collections rising to Rs 1.74 lakh crore, up 6.1% year on year and marking the fastest growth in three months after a softer November. However, the improvement was driven largely by imports, with GST from imports jumping nearly 20%, while domestic collections grew only 1.2%. After adjusting for refunds, net GST revenue stood at Rs 1.46 lakh crore, reflecting a muted 2.2% increase. Major industrial states such as Maharashtra, Gujarat, Karnataka and Tamil Nadu remained the biggest contributors, and overall trends suggest the economy continues to expand steadily, supported by import demand and gradual formalisation. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.03% to 6.590 as compared with the previous close of 6.588. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9750 compared with its close of 89.8800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.22% to Rs 135,750. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 98.28. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.65% to 4.177. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 49 cents or 0.80% to $60.84 a barrel. Global Markets: Major markets in the US, Europe and Asia are shut today on account of the New Year’s Day holiday. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back on Wednesday, though the index still closed out a bumper year. The broad market S&P 500 dipped 0.74% and closed at 6,845.50, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and ended at 23,241.99. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 303.77 points, or 0.63%, and settled at 48,063.29. Monthly Auto Sales: Tata Motors (formerly TML Commercial Vehicles) added 2.66% after the company’s total sales commercial vehicle (CV) jumped 25% to 42,508 units in December 2025 compared with 33,875 units sold in December 2024. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) rose 1.40% after the company reported 25% increase in total auto sales for December 2025, selling 86,090 vehicles during the period under review as against 68,814 vehicles sold in December 2024. Ashok Leyland rallied 3.13% after the company reported a 27% increase in total commercial vehicle sales to 21,533 units in December 2025, up from 16,957 units sold in December 2024. Maruti Suzuki India rose 0.15%. The company reported total sales of 2,17,854 units in December 2025, marking a 22.21% increase compared to 1,78,248 units sold in the same month last year. Eicher Motors added 0.45%. The company’s unlisted subsidiary, VE Commercial Vehicles (VECV), reported a 24.7% year-on-year jump in commercial vehicle (CV) sales to 10,384 units in December 2025. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) surged 8.31% after the company reported a net turnover of Rs 446.59 crore for December 2025, marking a 22.44% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 364.74 crore recorded in December 2024. Escorts Kubota gained 2.71% after the company’s agri-machinery business division sold 7,577 tractors in December 2025, registering a growth of 38.5% compared with 5,472 tractors sold in December 2024. Stocks in Spotlight: Shares of cigarette makers fell after the government imposed additional excise duty on cigarettes and introduced a Health and National Security Cess on pan masala, effective 1 February 2026. The move raises the tax burden above existing GST rates, with cigarettes attracting excise duty of Rs 2,050 to Rs 8,500 per thousand sticks and GST of 40% on tobacco products, which is expected to push up prices and weigh on sales volumes. Godfrey Phillips India fell 17.09%, ITC dropped 9.69%, while VST Industries slipped 1.01%. Sattrix Information Security hit an upper limit of 10% at Rs 263.90 after the company announced receipt of initial work orders from Hitachi Systems India. Sunteck Realty surged 8.19% after GST authorities ruled in the company’s favour, fully setting aside a Rs 5.99 crore tax demand, along with interest and penalty, linked to Transferable Development Rights transactions for FY22. The order, passed on December 31, 2025, accepted Sunteck Realty’s submissions against a show cause notice issued in September under Section 73 of the GST Act. Dr Reddy’s Laboratories declined 1.47%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories SA, Switzerland, has received a Complete Response Letter (CRL) from the USFDA for its Biologics License Application (BLA) for AVT03 (denosumab). Kalpataru Projects International (KPIL) shed 0.23%. The company along with its joint venture, has secured new orders worth approximately Rs 719 crore. Blue Dart Express gained 2.81% after tax authorities largely dropped a Rs 420.78 crore GST demand on its subsidiary Blue Dart Aviation. Dev Information Technology (IT) jumped 4.88% after the company secured a noteworthy order worth Rs 1.90 crore from the Directorate of Food and Civil Supplies, an undertaking of the Food, Civil Supplies and Consumer Affairs Department, Gujarat. KEC International rose 0.44%. The company announced that it has secured new orders totalling Rs 1,050 crore across its various business verticals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1662856</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662856</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,291, a premium of 144.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,146.65 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,291, a premium of 144.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,146.65 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index rose 16.95 points or 0.06% to 26,146.55. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 3.06% to 9.19. ITC, Vodafone Idea and Indus Tower were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks settle sideways; auto index outperforms; VIX slides 3.06% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-settle-sideways-auto-index-outperforms-vix-slides-306/1662855</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662855</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended near the flat line.

The key equity barometers ended near the flat line. The Nifty settled below 25,150 mark, trading activity was volatile and range-bound due to lack of major economic triggers, and the expiry of weekly Sensex derivatives contracts. Investors are now shifting focus to the upcoming earnings season. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 32 points or 0.04% to 85,188.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 16.95 points or 0.06% to 26,146.55. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index climbed 0.27% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.02%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 3.06% to 9.19. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Auto index (up 1.03%), the Nifty Realty index (up 0.84%) and the Nifty Metal index (up 0.79%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Media index (down 3.17%), the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.40%) and the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.19%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.03% to 6.590 as compared with the previous close of 6.588. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9750 compared with its close of 89.8800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.22% to Rs 135,750. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 98.28. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.65% to 4.177. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 49 cents or 0.80% to $60.84 a barrel. Global Markets: Major markets in the US, Europe and Asia will remain shut today on account of the New Year’s Day holiday. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back on Wednesday, though the index still closed out a bumper year. The broad market S&P 500 dipped 0.74% and closed at 6,845.50, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and ended at 23,241.99. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 303.77 points, or 0.63%, and settled at 48,063.29.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty FMCG Index registers a drop of 3.17%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-fmcg-index-registers-a-drop-of-317/1662854</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662854</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty FMCG index closed down 3.17% at 53718.5 today.

Nifty FMCG index closed down 3.17% at 53718.5 today. The index has lost 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, ITC Ltd fell 9.71%, United Spirits Ltd slipped 2.74% and Godrej Consumer Products Ltd jumped 1.73%. The Nifty FMCG index has decreased 6.00% over last one year compared to the 10.12% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Auto index increased 1.03% and Nifty Realty index added 0.84% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 added 0.06% to close at 26146.55 while the SENSEX has declined 0.04% to close at 85188.6 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/entrepreneur-1428452__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end sideways; auto shares surge ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-sideways-auto-shares-surge/1662852</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662852</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended near the flat line.

The key equity barometers ended near the flat line. The Nifty closed near 25,150 mark, trading activity was volatile and range-bound due to lack of major economic triggers, and the expiry of weekly Sensex derivatives contracts. Investors are now shifting focus to the upcoming earnings season. Auto shares witnessed buying demand for third consecutive trading session on the back of monthly sales announcements. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 32 points or 0.04% to 85,188.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 16.95 points or 0.06% to 26,146.55. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index climbed 0.27% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.02%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,211 shares rose and 1,952 shares fell. A total of 171 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index jumped 1.03% to 28,480.55. The index rallied 3.22% for the three consecutive trading sessions. Ashok Leyland (up 3.35%), Bajaj Auto (up 2.43%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 2.2%), TVS Motor Company (up 2%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.38%), Hero MotoCorp (up 1.2%), Tube Investments of India (up 0.91%), Eicher Motors (up 0.45%), Bosch (up 0.35%) and Exide Industries (up 0.25%) surged. Monthly Auto Sales: Tata Motors (formerly TML Commercial Vehicles) added 2.78% after the company’s total sales commercial vehicle (CV) jumped 25% to 42,508 units in December 2025 compared with 33,875 units sold in December 2024. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) rose 1.40% after the company reported 25% increase in total auto sales for December 2025, selling 86,090 vehicles during the period under review as against 68,814 vehicles sold in December 2024. Ashok Leyland rallied 3.13% after the company reported a 27% increase in total commercial vehicle sales to 21,533 units in December 2025, up from 16,957 units sold in December 2024. Maruti Suzuki India rose 0.15%. The company reported total sales of 2,17,854 units in December 2025, marking a 22.21% increase compared to 1,78,248 units sold in the same month last year. Eicher Motors added 0.45%. The company’s unlisted subsidiary, VE Commercial Vehicles (VECV), reported a 24.7% year-on-year jump in commercial vehicle (CV) sales to 10,384 units in December 2025. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) surged 8.36% after the company reported a net turnover of Rs 446.59 crore for December 2025, marking a 22.44% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 364.74 crore recorded in December 2024. Escorts Kubota gained 2.71% after the company’s agri-machinery business division sold 7,577 tractors in December 2025, registering a growth of 38.5% compared with 5,472 tractors sold in December 2024. Stocks in Spotlight: Dr Reddy’s Laboratories declined 1.47%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories SA, Switzerland, has received a Complete Response Letter (CRL) from the USFDA for its Biologics License Application (BLA) for AVT03 (denosumab). Kalpataru Projects International (KPIL) shed 0.23%. The company along with its joint venture, has secured new orders worth approximately Rs 719 crore. Blue Dart Express gained 2.81% after tax authorities largely dropped a Rs 420.78 crore GST demand on its subsidiary Blue Dart Aviation. Dev Information Technology (IT) jumped 4.88% after the company secured a noteworthy order worth Rs 1.90 crore from the Directorate of Food and Civil Supplies, an undertaking of the Food, Civil Supplies and Consumer Affairs Department, Gujarat. KEC International rose 0.44%. The company announced that it has secured new orders totalling Rs 1,050 crore across its various business verticals. Global Markets: Major markets in the US, Europe and Asia will remain shut today on account of the New Year’s Day holiday. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back on Wednesday, though the index still closed out a bumper year. The broad market S&P 500 dipped 0.74% and closed at 6,845.50, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and ended at 23,241.99. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 303.77 points, or 0.63%, and settled at 48,063.29.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index sees biggest annual fall since 2017]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-sees-biggest-annual-fall-since-2017/1662853</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662853</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar index saw sustained selling pressure last year.

The US dollar index saw sustained selling pressure last year. The index ended 2025 with its biggest annual drop since 2017, losing around 9.5%. Factors driving the downturn include potential Federal Reserve interest rate cuts, fiscal concerns, and ongoing political pressures from the Trump administration. The euro and British pound saw their strongest yearly gains in eight years, with the euro rising 13.5% and the pound soaring nearly 7.5%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-1-1236488_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India overtakes Japan to become world’s fourth-largest economy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-overtakes-japan-to-become-worlds-fourth-largest-economy/1662851</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662851</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India has overtaken Japan to emerge as the world’s fourth-largest economy.

India has overtaken Japan to emerge as the world’s fourth-largest economy. According to the government’s end-of-year economic review, India’s nominal GDP has reached $4.18 trillion, placing it behind only the United States, China and Germany. Official confirmation will follow once final annual GDP data is released in 2026, but International Monetary Fund (IMF) projections already indicate that India has crossed Japan.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/growth-1152553__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Force Motors gains after total sales climb 50% YoY in December 2025]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/force-motors-gains-after-total-sales-climb-50-yoy-in-december-2025/1662850</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662850</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s domestic sales jumped 48.72% to 2,952 units in December 2025, as against 1,985 units sold in December 2024.

The company’s domestic sales jumped 48.72% to 2,952 units in December 2025, as against 1,985 units sold in December 2024. The company’s exports soars 88.24% to 96 units in December 2025 compared to 51 units in the same period last year. Force Motors is engaged in manufacturing light commercial vehicles, utility vehicles, and engines. It is an automobile company with a focus on the design, development, and manufacture of a range of automotive components, aggregates, and vehicles. The company reported a 159.68% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 350.7 crore in Q2 FY25, compared with Rs 135.05 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Revenue from operations rose 7.21% to Rs 2,081.4 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 1,941.33 crore in Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ForceMotors_49967151331_53.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market Access Support Scheme to Boost Global Reach of Indian MSME and Priority Sector Exporters under EPM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-access-support-scheme-to-boost-global-reach-of-indian-msme-and-priority-sector-exporters-under-epm/1662848</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662848</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India launched the Market Access Support (MAS) Intervention under the Export Promotion Mission (EPM), a flagship initiative approved by the Union Cabinet.

The Government of India launched the Market Access Support (MAS) Intervention under the Export Promotion Mission (EPM), a flagship initiative approved by the Union Cabinet. The MAS Intervention is being implemented under the NIRYAT DISHA sub-scheme of EPM and is aimed at strengthening international market access for Indian exporters, particularly MSMEs, first-time exporters and firms from priority sectors. Under the Market Access Support Intervention, structured financial and institutional support will be provided for activities including Buyer-Seller Meets (BSMs), participation in international trade fairs and exhibitions, Mega Reverse Buyer-Seller Meets (RBSMs) organised in India, and trade delegations to priority and emerging export markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/keyboard-338517__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Motors rallies after total CV sales jumps 25% YoY to 42,508 units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-motors-rallies-after-total-cv-sales-jumps-25-yoy-to-42508-units/1662842</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662842</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sales of heavy commercial vehicle (HCV) trucks climbed 31% YoY to 12,483 units in December 2025, while intermediate, light and medium commercial vehicle (ILMCV) truck sales surged 40% YoY to 7,959 units.

Sales of heavy commercial vehicle (HCV) trucks climbed 31% YoY to 12,483 units in December 2025, while intermediate, light and medium commercial vehicle (ILMCV) truck sales surged 40% YoY to 7,959 units. Passenger carrier sales rose 1% to 4,167 units, while SCV cargo and pickup sales jumped 19% to 15,448 units during December 2025 over the year-ago period. Total domestic CV sales increased 24% YoY to 40,057 units in December 2025. For Q3 FY26, the company’s total sales rose 21% to 1,15,577 units, compared with 95,770 units in Q3 FY25. Girish Wagh, MD & CEO, Tata Motors Ltd., said, “The sales momentum ignited by GST 2.0 and the festive surge in Q2FY26 continued into Q3FY26, driving growth and lifting overall sentiment of the commercial vehicles industry. Tata Motors registered double-digit sales growth in Q3FY26, powered by a strong rebound in construction and mining activity post the extended monsoon, along with sustained demand from core sectors and auto logistics. Continued strength in SCVs and Pickups further amplified performance, resulting in wholesales of 1,15,577 units, with 21% year-on-year growth over Q3FY25 and 22% sequential growth over Q2FY26. Going forward, we expect demand to strengthen in Q4FY26 across most commercial vehicle segments. Key drivers in 2026 will include the government’s sustained infrastructure push and expansion in end-use sectors, both of which are expected to fuel positive momentum for the industry. With an optimised portfolio ensuring superior product availability, a decisive pricing strategy, and deeper customer engagement through intensified market activations, Tata Motors is well-poised to unlock demand across segments, paving the way for continued success.” Tata Motors (formerly TML Commercial Vehicles) is India’s largest and a globally renowned manufacturer of utility vehicles, pick-ups, trucks, and buses. Its advanced powertrains, connected technologies, and intelligent fleet solutions support a wide range of applications—from last-mile delivery to public transport.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataMotorsLtd_65899190_93137.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sattrix Information hits the roof on Hitachi work orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sattrix-information-hits-the-roof-on-hitachi-work-orders/1662843</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662843</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, Sattrix said the work orders are part of a partner managed services agreement signed on 2 December 2025.

In a regulatory filing, Sattrix said the work orders are part of a partner managed services agreement signed on 2 December 2025. Under the arrangement, Sattrix will provide managed security operations center services to Hitachi’s end customers on a white-label basis. The company said the engagement will cover end-to-end managed security operations, including 24/7 threat detection and incident response, supported by its advanced cybersecurity defence platform. Sattrix added that the partnership allows Hitachi to scale its security services portfolio while leveraging Sattrix’s technical expertise and infrastructure. Sattrix Information Security is a global cybersecurity solutions provider offering end-to-end, customer-focused services across India, the US, the Middle East and Malaysia, helping enterprises protect digital assets, ensure compliance and maintain business continuity through cloud-based and on-premise solutions. On a consolidated basis, Sattrix Information Security's net profit surged 404.71% to Rs 2.01 crore on 26.45% increase in net sales to Rs 28.06 crore in H1FY25 over H1FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SattrixInformationSecurityLtd_34558590_92934.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dev IT gains after bagging Rs 2-cr order ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dev-it-gains-after-bagging-rs-2-cr-order/1662844</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662844</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order is for the Relational Database Management System (RDBMS) software platform used in the digital portal to provide services including the e-Rasan application, My Ration mobile app & portal, Direct Benefit Transfer (DBT) portal, and Jan Seva & Digital Sevasetu app.

According to an exchange filing, the order is for the Relational Database Management System (RDBMS) software platform used in the digital portal to provide services including the e-Rasan application, My Ration mobile app & portal, Direct Benefit Transfer (DBT) portal, and Jan Seva & Digital Sevasetu app. The contract is expected to be executed over a period of approximately two months. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Dev Information Technology (Dev IT) is in the business of providing IT-enabled services. The company's consolidated net profit climbed 786.3% to Rs 71.88 crore on a 35% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 48.51 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DevInformationTechnologyLtd_93091952440_70312.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[M&M edges higher after clocking sales of 86,090 vehicles in Dec'25; tractor sales up 39% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mm-edges-higher-after-clocking-sales-of-86090-vehicles-in-dec25-tractor-sales-up-39-yoy/1662841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662841</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In the Utility Vehicles segment, Mahindra sold 50,946 vehicles in the domestic market, a growth of 23% YoY.

In the Utility Vehicles segment, Mahindra sold 50,946 vehicles in the domestic market, a growth of 23% YoY. The domestic sales for commercial vehicles stood at 24,786, a growth of 34% YoY. Total exports fell by 9% to 2,820 units in December 2025 from 3,092 units in December 2024. Nalinikanth Gollagunta, CEO, Automotive Division, M&M, said: "The calendar year 2025 ended on a positive note, with Mahindra clocking its highest-ever volumes in both SUVs and LCVs ( M&M’s Farm Equipment Business (FEB) has also announced its tractor sales numbers for December 2025. Total tractor sales during December 2025 were at 31,859 units as against 22,943 units for the same period last year, up 38.9% YoY. Domestic sales in December 2025 were at 30,210 units, as against 22,019 units in December 2024, reflecting a 37% year-on-year growth. Exports for the month stood at 1,649 units, a growth of 78%. Veejay Nakra, President – Farm Equipment Business, Mahindra & Mahindra, said: "Cash flow availability in the market has improved supported by favorable crop yields following the Kharif harvest. Additionally, conducive weather conditions and healthy reservoir levels have contributed to increase in Rabi sowing acreage, which is expected to sustain tractor demand in the coming months." Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) Group enjoys a leadership position in farm equipment, utility vehicles, information technology, and financial services in India. It is the world's largest tractor company by volume. It has a strong presence in renewable energy, agriculture, logistics, hospitality and real estate. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit surged 17.7% to Rs 4,520.52 crore on a 21.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 33,421.60 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashok Leyland gains after December sales jump 27% YoY to 21,533 units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashok-leyland-gains-after-december-sales-jump-27-yoy-to-21533-units/1662839</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662839</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total domestic sales climbed 26% YoY to 19,885 units during the month.

Total domestic sales climbed 26% YoY to 19,885 units during the month. Domestic sales of medium and heavy commercial vehicles (M&HCV) grew 29% to 13,553 units, while light commercial vehicle (LCV) sales rose 21% to 6,302 units in December 2025 over the year-ago period. Including exports, M&HCV sales increased 29% to 14,830 units, while LCV sales rose 22% to 6,703 units during the month. Ashok Leyland is engaged in the manufacture and sale of a wide range of commercial vehicles. The company also manufactures engines for industrial and marine applications, forgings, and castings. Ashok Leyland reported a marginal rise in standalone net profit to Rs 771.06 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 770.10 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 9.34% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 9,588.18 crore for the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokLeyland_6904859924_31.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godfrey Phillips India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godfrey-phillips-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1662838</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662838</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITC Ltd, TD Power Systems Ltd, Westlife Foodworld Ltd and Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 01 January 2026.

ITC Ltd, TD Power Systems Ltd, Westlife Foodworld Ltd and Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 01 January 2026. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd tumbled 16.80% to Rs 2297.5 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.23 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18379 shares in the past one month. ITC Ltd crashed 9.11% to Rs 366.3. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 104.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 32.65 lakh shares in the past one month. TD Power Systems Ltd lost 4.21% to Rs 671.95. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 23054 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35295 shares in the past one month. Westlife Foodworld Ltd plummeted 4.07% to Rs 539.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.54 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 37421 shares in the past one month. Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd fell 3.42% to Rs 1244.3. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 44538 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19601 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodfreyPhillips_19522234394_657.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sunteck Realty jumps as GST authority drops tax demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sunteck-realty-jumps-as-gst-authority-drops-tax-demand/1662837</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662837</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said the Office of Goods and Services Tax passed an order on 31 December 2025, accepting its submissions.

In a regulatory filing, the company said the Office of Goods and Services Tax passed an order on 31 December 2025, accepting its submissions. The order nullified the entire tax demand, along with interest and penalty. The demand had arisen from a show cause notice issued in September 2025 under Section 73 of the GST Act. It related to an alleged tax liability of about Rs 5.99 crore on Transferable Development Rights transactions for FY22. Sunteck Realty had earlier said the demand lacked merit. It argued that GST on the transaction was already paid by the supplier under the forward charge mechanism. The company had also flagged errors in the computation of the demand. Sunteck Realty is a Mumbai-based luxury real estate developer with a development portfolio of 50 million square feet across 32 projects. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 41.4% to Rs 48.97 crore on 49.3% increase in Revenue from operations to Rs 252.37 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SunteckRealty_87854270132_6838.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Softtech Engineers Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/softtech-engineers-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662835</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662835</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd, Prakash Steelage Ltd, Bonlon Industries Ltd and Rajdarshan Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 January 2026.

SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd, Prakash Steelage Ltd, Bonlon Industries Ltd and Rajdarshan Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 January 2026. Softtech Engineers Ltd lost 15.34% to Rs 315.8 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2894 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 76 shares in the past one month. SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd tumbled 6.52% to Rs 399. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9609 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7827 shares in the past one month. Prakash Steelage Ltd crashed 6.23% to Rs 5.42. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.09 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.11 lakh shares in the past one month. Bonlon Industries Ltd pared 6.19% to Rs 50.9. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 56864 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 71875 shares in the past one month. Rajdarshan Industries Ltd shed 6.14% to Rs 45.21. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 387 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SofttechEngineersLtd_72831194539_72475.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ceinsys Tech rallies after securing Rs 12-cr order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ceinsys-tech-rallies-after-securing-rs-12-cr-order/1662836</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662836</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the contract involves acting as a system integrator for the supply, implementation and support of a digital project management platform, including 5D-BIM, ERP and GIS systems, along with the establishment of an owner’s support office for the MPEW–ML project.

According to an exchange filing, the contract involves acting as a system integrator for the supply, implementation and support of a digital project management platform, including 5D-BIM, ERP and GIS systems, along with the establishment of an owner’s support office for the MPEW–ML project. The total order value stands at Rs 12,06,17,194.71 and the project will be executed up to 31 March 2026. The company said the order is an extension of existing contracts earlier awarded by MSRDC Tunnel for the same project. Ceinsys Tech had previously received the letter of award and extensions for the project in FY21 and FY23. Ceinsys Tech is primarily dealing in providing enterprise geospatial & engineering services and the sale of software and power generation. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 120.9% to Rs 25.74 crore on an 81.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 163.45 in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>