<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:21:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/INR and GBP/INR slumps by around 0.4% as rupee rebounds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurinr-and-gbpinr-slumps-by-around-04-as-rupee-rebounds/1663673</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663673</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures fell 0.21% to 90.01.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures fell 0.21% to 90.01. EUR/INR and GBP/INR also slumped by around 0.40% to close at 105.39 and 121.55 respectively. JPY/INR futures ended slightly lower by 0.15% at 57.80.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee sustains momentum]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-sustains-momentum/1663670</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663670</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 90.0150 per Dollar on Wednesday (07 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.2550 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR rebounds to one-week high ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-rebounds-to-one-week-high/1663667</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663667</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee rose 31 paise to close at 89.87 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday, a one-week high on falling international global crude oil prices.

The Indian rupee rose 31 paise to close at 89.87 (provisional) against the US dollar on Wednesday, a one-week high on falling international global crude oil prices. Besides, possible intervention by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) may also have supported the counter, although muted local equities capped upside. Indian shares ended slightly lower on Wednesday to extend losses for a third day running as rising geopolitical tensions and tariff-related concerns overshadowed investor optimism around the earnings outlook. The benchmark S&P/BSE Sensex dropped 102.20 points, or 0.12 percent, to 84,961.14, while the broader NSE Nifty index ended down 37.95 points, or 0.14 percent, at 26,140.75. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 90.20 against the US dollar and traded in the range of 89.75-90.23 before settling at 89.87 (provisional), up 31 paise from its previous close. The rupee snapped its four-day losing streak to appreciate 12 paise to settle at 90.18 against the American currency on Tuesday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian economy estimated to expand at 7.4% in FY26, buoyant growth seen in services sector]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-economy-estimated-to-expand-at-74-in-fy26-buoyant-growth-seen-in-services-sector/1663668</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663668</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian economy is estimated to have continued its growth momentum this fiscal with the FY26 rate of expansion seen at 7.4%, according to latest data from Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation.

Indian economy is estimated to have continued its growth momentum this fiscal with the FY26 rate of expansion seen at 7.4%, according to latest data from Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation. This marks a sharp rebound compared with 6.5% in the previous fiscal year, First Advance Estimates of Gross Domestic Product (GDP) data released by the government noted. Nominal GDP is estimated to grow at 8.0% in FY 2025-26. Buoyant Growth in Services Sector has been found to be a major driver in the estimated Real GVA growth rate of 7.3% in FY 2025-26. Financial, Real Estate & Professional Services and Public Administration, Defence & Other Services in the Tertiary Sector have also been estimated to attain a substantial growth rate of 9.9% at Constant Prices in FY 2025-26. Trade, Hotels, Transport, Communication & Services related to Broadcasting Sector has been estimated to grow by 7.5% at Constant Prices in FY 2025-26. Manufacturing and Construction in the Secondary Sector has been estimated to achieve a growth rate of 7.0% at Constant Prices in FY 2025-26. Agriculture & Allied Sector (3.1%) and Electricity, Gas, Water Supply & Other Utility Services Sector (2.1%) have seen moderate growth rate in GVA at Constant Prices during FY 2025-26. Government stated that Real Private Final Consumption Expenditure (PFCE) has been estimated to attain a growth rate of 7.0% during FY 2025-26. Gross Fixed Capital Formation (GFCF) has been estimated to have 7.8% growth rate at Constant Prices during FY 2025-26, compared to 7.1% growth rate in previous FY. There has been impressive recovery in manufacturing which rose from from 4.5 percent in the previous year and as tertiary sector which had expanded 7.2 percent in FY25. Real GDP or GDP at Constant Prices is estimated to attain a level of Rs 201.90 lakh crore in FY 2025-26, against the Provisional Estimates (PE) of GDP for the FY 2024-25 of Rs 187.97 lakh crore. Nominal GDP or GDP at Current Prices is estimated to attain a level of Rs 357.14 lakh crore in the FY 2025-26, against Rs 330.68 lakh crore in FY 2024-25. India’s per capita GDP growth is estimated to have hit 6.5% in FY26, up from 5.5% in previous fiscal to stand at Rs 142119.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks extend losses for third session, Nifty ends below 26,150 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-extend-losses-for-third-session-nifty-ends-below-26150/1663664</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663664</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks ended lower on Wednesday, extending losses for a third consecutive session, as persistent selling pressure in heavyweight stocks weighed on sentiment.

Domestic equity benchmarks ended lower on Wednesday, extending losses for a third consecutive session, as persistent selling pressure in heavyweight stocks weighed on sentiment. The Nifty ended below the 26,150 level amid mixed global cues, following geopolitical concerns linked to developments in Venezuela. Market participants also remained cautious as technical indicators pointed to a phase of consolidation. Auto and energy stocks declined, while IT and consumer durables stocks bucked the broader market weakness. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 120.20 points or 0.12% to 84,961.14. The Nifty 50 index dropped 37.95 points or 0.14% to 26,140.75. In three consecutive sessions, the Sensex declined 0.93% while the Nifty fell 0.71%. Maruti Suzuki India (down 2.81%), HDFC Bank (down 1.24%) and Bajaj Finance (down 0.78%) dragged the Nifty lower today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.47% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.12%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,104 shares rose and 2,068 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, down 0.64% to 9.95. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper added 0.12% to 6.620 compared with the previous session close of 6.612. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8750 compared with its close of 90.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement declined 0.62% to Rs 138,222. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.04% to 98.56. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.84% to 4.145. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement declined 54 cents or 89% to $60.16 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Wednesday as Eurozone inflation stood at 2% in December, according to flash data from Eurostat, easing from 2.1% in November and aligning with the European Central Bank’s (ECB) target. Core inflation, which excludes volatile components such as energy, food, alcohol, and tobacco, moderated to 2.3% in December from 2.4% in the previous month. Services inflation also cooled, easing to 3.4% from 3.5% in November. The ECB kept its key deposit facility rate unchanged at 2% in December, extending its pause for a fourth consecutive meeting, after last cutting rates in June. Germany’s unemployment rate remained unchanged at 6.3% in December 2025, according to data released Wednesday by the Federal Employment Agency. Most Asian markets ended higher on Wednesday, as investors continued to assess geopolitical risks after the U.S. attack on Venezuela and renewed rhetoric over Greenland. US President Donald Trump has discussed a range of options, including potential military measures, to acquire Greenland, with the White House describing the move as a national security priority. Meanwhile U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro. Overnight in the United States, stocks advanced as investors appeared to look past the Venezuela operation. The Dow and the S&P 500 both closed at all-time highs. The Dow advanced about 1%, while the S&P 500 gained 0.62%, extending their early-year rally. The NASDAQ Composite finished 0.65% higher, supported by strength in technology and semiconductor shares. Stocks in Spotlight: Indian Hotels Company fell 1.36% to Rs 715.95 after a foreign brokerage downgraded the stock to "equal-weight" from "overweight" and cut its target price to Rs 780 from Rs 811. Meesho hit a lower circuit of 5% to Rs 173.20 after the expiry of the one-month shareholder lock-in period. Around 10.99 crore shares, or nearly 2% of the company’s outstanding equity, have reportedly become eligible for trading following the end of the lock-in. However, this does not necessarily indicate immediate selling, as the expiry only allows these shares to be traded. CMS Info Systems rose 2.31% after the company announced it had secured a landmark Rs 1,000 crore integrated cash solutions contract from State Bank of India. Panorama Studios International rose 3.52% after the company announced a landmark multi-film collaboration with Malayalam actor and producer Nivin Pauly, involving a cumulative investment of Rs 100 crore. Info Edge (India) rose 1.95% after it posted strong performance in its recruitment segment, which saw revenues increase 10.99% YoY to Rs 548.3 crore on 31 December 2025, up from Rs 494 crore in the same period last year. Kalyan Jewellers India jumped 4.03% after the company’s consolidated revenue climbed approximately 42% YoY, driven by robust festive demand, strong same-store sales growth (SSSG), and sharp traction in its digital platform, Candere. Titan Company rose 3.94% after its domestic consumer businesses recorded around 40% year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26, with jewellery emerging as the biggest contributor. The jewellery portfolio posted about 41% YoY growth, supported by strong wedding and festive demand and improved performance across gold studded jewellery and gold coins. PTC Industries fell 0.85%. The company announced that it has received a prestigious order from the Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre (VSSC), a key centre of the Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO) to supply grade Titanium Ingots. Tata Power Company fell 1.40%. The company said that TP Solar has manufactured 940 MW of DCR solar cells in Q3 FY26 as compared with 196 MW of cells manufactured in the corresponding period last year, thereby registering an increase of nearly 5x on YoY basis. Jubilant Foodworks shed 1.79%. The company’s consolidated revenue stood at Rs 2,438.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 13.4% YoY. Domino’s recorded a Like-For-Like (LFL) growth of 5%. IRB Infrastructure Developers added 1.15% after the company has emerged as the selected bidder and received an LoA from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for tolling, operation, maintenance, and transfer of the Chandikhole–Bhadrak section of NH-16 in Odisha.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1663660</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663660</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,237.90, a premium of 97.15 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,140.75 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 26,237.90, a premium of 97.15 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,140.75 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index fell 37.95 points or 0.14% to 26,140.75. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.67% to 9.95. HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank and Titan Company were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty drop for 3rd day; broader mrkt outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-drop-for-3rd-day-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1663659</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663659</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with minor losses today, extending losses for a third straight session, as rising geopolitical tensions and renewed tariff-related concerns weighed on investor sentiment, capping optimism around the earnings outlook.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with minor losses today, extending losses for a third straight session, as rising geopolitical tensions and renewed tariff-related concerns weighed on investor sentiment, capping optimism around the earnings outlook. The Nifty settled below the 26,150 mark. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 120.20 points or 0.12% to 84,961.14. The Nifty 50 index dropped 37.95 points or 0.14% to 26,140.75. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.93% while the Nifty fell 0.71%. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.47% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.12%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, down 0.64% to 9.95. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty IT index (up 1.87%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 1.69%) and the Nifty Pharma index (up 0.69%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Auto index (down 0.80%), the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 0.66%) and the Nifty Realty index (down 0.50%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper added 0.12% to 6.620 compared with the previous session close of 6.612. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8750 compared with its close of 90.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement declined 0.62% to Rs 138,222. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.04% to 98.56. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.84% to 4.145. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement declined 54 cents or 89% to $60.16 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European markets declined on Wednesday as regional market jitters grow over U.S. President Donald Trump’s threat to annex Greenland. Eurozone inflation stood at 2% in December, according to flash data from Eurostat, easing from 2.1% in November and aligning with the European Central Bank’s (ECB) target. Core inflation, which excludes volatile components such as energy, food, alcohol, and tobacco, moderated to 2.3% in December from 2.4% in the previous month. Services inflation also cooled, easing to 3.4% from 3.5% in November. The ECB kept its key deposit facility rate unchanged at 2% in December, extending its pause for a fourth consecutive meeting, after last cutting rates in June. Germany’s unemployment rate remained unchanged at 6.3% in December 2025, according to data released Wednesday by the Federal Employment Agency. Most Asian markets ended higher on Wednesday, as investors continued to assess geopolitical risks after the U.S. attack on Venezuela and renewed rhetoric over Greenland. Australia’s Consumer Price Index (CPI) rose 3.4% year-on-year, easing from 3.8% recorded in October US President Donald Trump has discussed a range of options, including potential military measures, to acquire Greenland, with the White House describing the move as a national security priority. Meanwhile, U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro. Overnight in the United States, stocks advanced as investors appeared to look past the Venezuela operation. The Dow and the S&P 500 both closed at all-time highs. The Dow advanced about 1%, while the S&P 500 gained 0.62%, extending their early-year rally. The NASDAQ Composite finished 0.65% higher, supported by strength in technology and semiconductor shares.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crisil Ratings reaffirms ratings of Kabra Extrusiontechnik at 'A/A1' with 'negative' outlook]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crisil-ratings-reaffirms-ratings-of-kabra-extrusiontechnik-at-aa1-with-negative-outlook/1663655</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663655</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Crisil Ratings stated that the continuation of negative outlook takes into account subdued operational performance of the company in the first half of fiscal 2026.

Crisil Ratings stated that the continuation of negative outlook takes into account subdued operational performance of the company in the first half of fiscal 2026. Battery division continues to book operating losses, though a recovery in revenue was observed during the period. This, along with a slight decline in profitability from the traditional extrusion business due to a changes in the product mix, has led to an overall decline in the profitability of the company during the first half of fiscal year 2026. Despite moderation in the business risk, the financial risk profile and liquidity position of KEL remain adequate amid negligible long-term debt, moderate capex obligation, and free cash and equivalents of Rs 44 crore as on September 30, 2025. The financial risk profile of the company is expected to remain adequate, despite an increase in debt, due to a healthy net worth and limited long-term debt and capex obligations. Liquidity remains comfortable with free cash and liquid investment of Rs 44 crore as on 30 September 2025, which would be sufficient for repayment of debt obligations of remaining Rs 2.67 crore during the remaining half of fiscal 2026. Net cash accrual is expected to be in the range of Rs 28-30 crore, which will be sufficient for the annual capex plans of Rs 20-22 crore for fiscal 2026. The ratings continue to reflect KEL’s established market position in the extrusion machinery business and its adequate financial risk profile. These strengths are partially offset by exposure to intense competition in the extrusion machinery segment, working capital-intensive operations, and susceptibility to changes in government policies and customer concentration in the battery division. KEL is a part of the Kolsite group of companies. It manufactures plastic extrusion machinery and mono and multilayer blown film plants, used in industries such as pipes and packaging. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, operating income was Rs 221 crore and loss was Rs 6 crore, against Rs 216 crore and profit after tax of Rs 15 crore, respectively, during the corresponding period of the previous fiscal. The scrip had declined 0.86% to end at Rs 218.10 on the BSE today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KabraExtrusion_60412874996_1227.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index gains 1.87%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-gains-187/1663654</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663654</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index ended up 1.87% at 38688.8 today.

Nifty IT index ended up 1.87% at 38688.8 today. The index has gained 0.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Persistent Systems Ltd rose 4.23%, Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd jumped 3.15% and Coforge Ltd gained 2.68%. The Nifty IT index has fallen 11.00% over last one year compared to the 10.26% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Auto index has dropped 0.80% and Nifty Pharma index increased 0.69% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has declined 0.14% to close at 26140.75 while the SENSEX has slid 0.12% to close at 84961.14 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 120 pts lower; Nifty ends below 26,150 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-120-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-26150-mark/1663652</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663652</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with minor losses today, extending losses for a third straight session, as rising geopolitical tensions and renewed tariff-related concerns weighed on investor sentiment, capping optimism around the earnings outlook.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with minor losses today, extending losses for a third straight session, as rising geopolitical tensions and renewed tariff-related concerns weighed on investor sentiment, capping optimism around the earnings outlook. The Nifty settled below the 26,150 mark. IT, consumer durables and pharma shares advanced while auto, oil & gas and realty shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 120.20 points or 0.12% to 84,961.14. The Nifty 50 index dropped 37.95 points or 0.14% to 26,140.75. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.93% while the Nifty fell 0.71%. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.47% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.12%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,099 shares rose and 2,073 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index declined 0.80% to 26,692.40. The index rallied 4.81% in the past six consecutive trading session. Maruti Suzuki India (down 2.91%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 1.52%), Samvardhana Motherson International (down 1.3%), Exide Industries (down 1.29%), Mahindra & Mahindra (down 0.94%), Tube Investments of India (down 0.86%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 0.64%), TVS Motor Company (down 0.63%), Hero MotoCorp (down 0.36%) and Uno Minda (down 0.27%) declined. On the other hand, Bajaj Auto (up 1.37%), Eicher Motors (up 0.71%) and Bosch (up 0.47%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Info Edge (India) rose 1.95% after it posted strong performance in its recruitment segment, which saw revenues increase 10.99% YoY to Rs 548.3 crore on 31 December 2025, up from Rs 494 crore in the same period last year. Kalyan Jewellers India jumped 3.73% after the company’s consolidated revenue climbed approximately 42% YoY, driven by robust festive demand, strong same-store sales growth (SSSG), and sharp traction in its digital platform, Candere. Titan Company rose 3.96% after its domestic consumer businesses recorded around 40% year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26, with jewellery emerging as the biggest contributor. The jewellery portfolio posted about 41% YoY growth, supported by strong wedding and festive demand and improved performance across gold studded jewellery and gold coins. Lodha Developers shed 0.33%. The company reported pre-sales of Rs 5,620 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 25% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 4,510 crore in Q3 FY25. PTC Industries fell 0.85%. The company announced that it has received a prestigious order from the Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre (VSSC), a key centre of the Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO) to supply grade Titanium Ingots. Tata Power Company fell 1.53%. The company said that TP Solar has manufactured 940 MW of DCR solar cells in Q3 FY26 as compared with 196 MW of cells manufactured in the corresponding period last year, thereby registering an increase of nearly 5x on YoY basis. Jubilant Foodworks shed 1.79%. The company’s consolidated revenue stood at Rs 2,438.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 13.4% YoY. Domino’s recorded a Like-For-Like (LFL) growth of 5%. IRB Infrastructure Developers added 1% after the company has emerged as the selected bidder and received an LoA from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for tolling, operation, maintenance, and transfer of the Chandikhole–Bhadrak section of NH-16 in Odisha. Global Markets: European markets traded mixed on Wednesday as regional market jitters grow over U.S. President Donald Trump’s threat to annex Greenland. Euro zone inflation stood at 2% in December, according to flash data from Eurostat, easing from 2.1% in November and aligning with the European Central Bank’s (ECB) target. Core inflation, which excludes volatile components such as energy, food, alcohol and tobacco, moderated to 2.3% in December from 2.4% in the previous month. Services inflation also cooled, easing to 3.4% from 3.5% in November. The ECB kept its key deposit facility rate unchanged at 2% in December, extending its pause for a fourth consecutive meeting, after last cutting rates in June. Germany’s unemployment rate remained unchanged at 6.3% in December 2025, according to data released Wednesday by the Federal Employment Agency. Asian shares ended higher, with regional defense stocks snapping a two-day winning streak on Wednesday, as investors continued to assess geopolitical risks after the U.S. attack on Venezuela and renewed rhetoric over Greenland. Australia's consumer price index (CPI) rose at an annual pace of 3.4% in November, down from the 3.8% registered in the previous month. White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt reportedly said on Tuesday that President Donald Trump and his team were considering “a range of options” in order to acquire Greenland—including “utilizing the U.S. Military.” The statement further escalates the Trump administration’s already aggressive rhetoric about Greenland, which the president has long sought to make a part of the United States. U.S. crude futures fell 1.3% to $56.39 per barrel after U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro. Overnight in the United States, stocks advanced as investors appeared to look past the Venezuela operation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sri Lotus Developers jumps after entering Gift City with ultra-luxury project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sri-lotus-developers-jumps-after-entering-gift-city-with-ultra-luxury-project/1663649</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663649</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The expansion into GIFT City marks the company’s first project in Gujarat and a significant milestone in its expansion beyond its core Mumbai market.

The expansion into GIFT City marks the company’s first project in Gujarat and a significant milestone in its expansion beyond its core Mumbai market. The project will be undertaken through its subsidiary, Rise Root Projects, which has entered into a development agreement with Abhishek Bachchan having profit-sharing arrangement, enabling the company to leverage its core strengths in design, planning, development, and execution. The proposed development will comprise a thoughtfully planned mix of premium retail, Grade-A commercial office spaces and high-end residential units etc. The project is designed to address the growing demand from financial institutions, fintech firms and IT / ITeS companies. Supported by the company’s strong execution capabilities and proven track record of timely delivery, the project is expected to be completed over a period of 4 years post launch of the project. Anand K Pandit, chairman & managing director, Sri Lotus Developers & Realty, said, “We are pleased to announce our entry into the GIFT City Area, Gandhinagar with our flagship ultra luxury mixed use project. GIFT City is rapidly emerging as a premier global financial and business hub, supported by progressive policy initiatives, robust infrastructure development, and increasing interest from domestic and international investors. Our expansion into this market is driven by the objective of addressing the rising demand for premium and ultra-luxury residential and commercial spaces within the region.” Sri Lotus Developers & Realty is a Mumbai-based real estate developer focused on ultra-luxury and luxury residential and commercial projects in the western suburbs of the Mumbai Metropolitan Region (MMR). The company’s consolidated net profit fell 8.4% to Rs 46.15 crore despite of 43.5% jump in net sales to Rs 176.11 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SriLotusDevelopersRealtyLtd_58377396_94305.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD at around 4-week low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-at-around-4-week-low/1663648</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663648</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Euro extends recent streak of decline amid tight moves and lingers around a four week low against the dollar on Wednesday.

The Euro extends recent streak of decline amid tight moves and lingers around a four week low against the dollar on Wednesday. Firmness in dollar on safe haven demand amid ongoing geopolitical issues is adding pressure on the pair. Besides, softer-than-expected inflation figures from Germany and the downward revision of December's S&P Global manufacturing PMI data also hammered the single common currency. Germany's consumer price inflation eased more than expected to its lowest level in over a year in December. EUR/USD is currently trading at $1.1720, down marginally on the day. All eyes are now glued to US economic reports, mainly employment data for further cues on Federal policy stance. On the NSE, EUR/INR futures are down 0.40% at 105.36.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil under pressure as markets eye Venezuelan supplies, tanks to two-week low ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-under-pressure-as-markets-eye-venezuelan-supplies-tanks-to-two-week-low/1663642</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663642</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil prices extended losses after Washington and Caracas struck a deal to redirect Venezuelan oil — originally destined for China — to US refiners, a move that could soften market tightness.

WTI Crude oil prices extended losses after Washington and Caracas struck a deal to redirect Venezuelan oil — originally destined for China — to US refiners, a move that could soften market tightness. President Trump said the agreement, potentially worth up to $2 billion, aims to support Venezuelan production while diverting shipments from Asian buyers. WTI oil futures slipped nearly 2%, falling below $56 per barrel and tested two-week low. Oil benchmarks have been pressured by expectations of ample global oil supply in 2026, with some forecasts pointing to continued surplus conditions. At the same time, progress toward a US–Ukraine security agreement has raised the possibility of fewer restrictions on Russian crude exports, adding to the bearish sentiment. API figures showed U.S. crude inventories unexpectedly fell by about 2.8 million barrels last week, yet price weakness persists amid broader oversupply concerns.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-rigs-and-brightly-lit-industrial-site-at-night-picture-_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Profit booking pulls gold lower, geopolitics still offer support]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/profit-booking-pulls-gold-lower-geopolitics-still-offer-support/1663639</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663639</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices slipped to around $4450 per ounce in Asia trade as a stronger US dollar and profit-taking weighed on the metal.

Gold prices slipped to around $4450 per ounce in Asia trade as a stronger US dollar and profit-taking weighed on the metal. Market attention is now firmly on key US data releases, including ISM Services PMI, JOLTs job openings, weekly jobless claims and the December jobs report, which could shape Fed rate expectations. Earlier ISM manufacturing data showed the sharpest contraction since 2024, keeping growth concerns alive. Meanwhile, geopolitical risks continued to underpin sentiment after the US capture of Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro, renewed tensions involving Greenland, and rising friction between China and Japan. On the domestic front, MCX February gold futures traded 0.6% lower at ₹138300 per 10 grams, tracking weakness in global prices.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Refex Industries bags Rs 43.71-cr ash transportation order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/refex-industries-bags-rs-4371-cr-ash-transportation-order/1663638</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663638</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is scheduled to be executed over a period of four months.

The project is scheduled to be executed over a period of four months. Chennai-based Refex Industries has built a portfolio spanning ash and coal handling, wind energy, and green mobility solutions. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 20.5% to Rs 37.44 crore despite a 0.3% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 426.85 crore in Q2 Sept 2025 over Q2 Sept 2024. Shares of Refex Industries fell 1.55% to Rs 253.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RefexIndustries_41686862841_27794.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cipla Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cipla-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1663633</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663633</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services Ltd, CSB Bank Ltd, ZF Commercial Vehicle Control System India Ltd and Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 07 January 2026.

Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services Ltd, CSB Bank Ltd, ZF Commercial Vehicle Control System India Ltd and Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 07 January 2026. Cipla Ltd lost 4.26% to Rs 1465.2 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.55 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 95734 shares in the past one month. Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services Ltd tumbled 4.14% to Rs 358.95. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.09 lakh shares in the past one month. CSB Bank Ltd crashed 3.54% to Rs 517.2. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 57791 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 86720 shares in the past one month. ZF Commercial Vehicle Control System India Ltd pared 3.48% to Rs 14750.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 677 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 754 shares in the past one month. Allied Blenders & Distillers Ltd corrected 3.47% to Rs 532.15. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 65307 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 25511 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cipla_98183211605_114.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Consumer expects double-digit topline growth in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-consumer-expects-double-digit-topline-growth-in-q3-fy26/1663635</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663635</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company remains optimistic about a gradual improvement in consumption over the coming quarters, supported by falling inflation and improving affordability following lower GST rates.

The company remains optimistic about a gradual improvement in consumption over the coming quarters, supported by falling inflation and improving affordability following lower GST rates. Against this backdrop, the company’s standalone business is well positioned to deliver double-digit revenue growth for the quarter, backed by close to double-digit underlying volume growth (UVG), albeit on a supportive comparator. The outperformance continues to be led by the Home Care segment, where momentum remains robust and double-digit value growth is expected, supported by sustained consumer demand and effective in-market execution. Personal Care is expected to record mid-single-digit value growth, driven by a marked recovery in the soaps category. The company expects standalone EBITDA margins to revert to the normative range for the business, aided by favourable input costs, disciplined cost management, calibrated pricing actions, and improved operating leverage. In Indonesia, competitive pricing pressures across key categories persisted during the quarter. However, early signs of stabilisation are visible, with the company expecting an improvement in both revenue and profitability from FY27 onwards. Meanwhile, GAUM (Godrej Africa, USA and Middle East) continued to deliver a strong and consistent performance both on topline and bottom-line. The company said the cluster is on track to deliver FY26 in line with its guidance of double-digit growth in revenue and profit, underscoring the resilience of its turnaround strategy. Godrej Consumer Products is an Indian consumer goods company. The company's products include soap, hair colorants, toiletries and liquid detergents. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 6.5% to Rs 459.34 crore despite of 4.3% increase in net sales to Rs 3,802.46 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter fell 0.64% to Rs 1,245.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejConsumer_25192758531_21960.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Hotels slips after brokerage downgrade]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-hotels-slips-after-brokerage-downgrade/1663634</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663634</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The brokerage said Indian Hotels Company has built a strong hospitality ecosystem by leveraging the Taj brand, delivering industry-leading return ratios and healthy free cash flow generation.

The brokerage said Indian Hotels Company has built a strong hospitality ecosystem by leveraging the Taj brand, delivering industry-leading return ratios and healthy free cash flow generation. However, it noted that while the current revenue per available room (RevPAR) cycle remains strong, the scope for further upside surprises appears limited. The brokerage expects domestic hotel RevPAR growth of around 9-10% in Q3 FY26, with EBITDA likely to rise about 10% year-on-year. It, however, reduced its earnings per share estimates for FY26-28 by 2-3%, citing slightly lower RevPAR assumptions and margin expectations. The brokerage added that the stock's FY27 enterprise value to EBITDA multiple of 27.5x fairly captures the risk-reward balance. Indian Hotels Company operates a diversified portfolio of hospitality brands spanning luxury, upscale and lean luxe segments, led by the Taj brand, along with Claridges Collection, SeleQtions, Tree of Life, Vivanta, Gateway and Ginger. Founded by Jamsetji Tata, IHCL opened its first property, The Taj Mahal Palace in Mumbai, in 1903. As of now, the company has a portfolio of 602 hotels worldwide, including 247 properties under development, with a presence across four continents, 14 countries and more than 250 locations. On a consolidated basis, Indian Hotels Co's net profit declined 48.62% to Rs 284.92 crore while net sales rose 11.76% to Rs 2040.89 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndianHotels_18642202460_282.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound softens after tepid service sector data, FTSE eases from record high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-softens-after-tepid-service-sector-data-ftse-eases-from-record-high/1663632</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663632</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound fell yesterday, coming off a two and half month high despite Uk equities hitting record highs.

British Pound fell yesterday, coming off a two and half month high despite Uk equities hitting record highs. The UK service sector continued to see subdued growth at the end of the fourth quarter, final survey results from S&P Global showed on Tuesday. The S&P Global Services Purchasing Managers' Index posted 51.4 in December, up slightly from 51.3 in November. The flash score was 52.1. GBP/USD pair moved down 0.30% in last session and currently quotes down marginally at 1.3495. UK stocks are in red today with the benchmark FTSE100 index giving up half a percent on the day. On NSE, GBP/INR futures are trading at 121.43, down 0.52% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/california-software-company-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663631</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663631</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Balu Forge Industries Ltd, Orient Technologies Ltd, Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd and Orient Ceratech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 07 January 2026.

Balu Forge Industries Ltd, Orient Technologies Ltd, Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd and Orient Ceratech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 07 January 2026. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup crashed 10.87% to Rs 4.59 at 14:28 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2750 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2110 shares in the past one month. Balu Forge Industries Ltd tumbled 10.33% to Rs 523.25. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9.56 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 32396 shares in the past one month. Orient Technologies Ltd lost 9.45% to Rs 392.1. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5.44 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10.33 lakh shares in the past one month. Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd fell 9.09% to Rs 38. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 56836 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14138 shares in the past one month. Orient Ceratech Ltd plummeted 7.30% to Rs 47. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 92215 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 27364 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>