<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:38:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashapura Minechem Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashapura-minechem-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1672841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672841</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[BEML Ltd, Nazara Technologies Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Cemindia Projects Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 February 2026.

BEML Ltd, Nazara Technologies Ltd, Poly Medicure Ltd and Cemindia Projects Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 February 2026. Ashapura Minechem Ltd lost 10.66% to Rs 609 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.47 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 60466 shares in the past one month. BEML Ltd crashed 8.32% to Rs 1602.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 92071 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22381 shares in the past one month. Nazara Technologies Ltd tumbled 6.90% to Rs 257.9. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 12.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.12 lakh shares in the past one month. Poly Medicure Ltd fell 6.75% to Rs 1398.55. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11742 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 63784 shares in the past one month. Cemindia Projects Ltd corrected 6.06% to Rs 635.45. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 33771 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18230 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshapuraMinech_91041583902_3111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GNG Electronics hits the roof after robust Q3 results]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gng-electronics-hits-the-roof-after-robust-q3-results/1672829</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672829</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, PAT stood at Rs 38.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 102.8% YoY from Rs 19.1 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, PAT stood at Rs 38.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 102.8% YoY from Rs 19.1 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 18.5% from Rs 32.7 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations came in at Rs 487.2 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a strong 40.3% YoY growth over Rs 347.4 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 10.8% QoQ from Rs 439.9 crore in Q2 FY26. Gross profit stood at Rs 101.3 crore, up 24% YoY from Rs 81.7 crore. Gross margin came in at 20.8%, lower by 273 bps YoY but higher by 87 bps QoQ. Profit before tax stood at Rs 42.8 crore in Q3 FY26, up 104.3% vs Q3 FY25 and higher by 18.6% QoQ from Rs 36.1 crore reported in Q2 FY26. EBITDA rose sharply to Rs 54.6 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 32 crore in Q3 FY25, marking a 70.5% YoY increase. Sequentially, EBITDA increased 16.7% from Rs 46.8 crore in Q2 FY26. EBITDA margin improved to 11.2% from 9.2% in Q3 FY25 and 10.6% in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 26.9 crore, up 0.4% YoY. Finance cost was largely stable at Rs 9 crore compared with Rs 8.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Sharad Khandelwal, managing director, highlighted that accelerating AI adoption and supply-side constraints in new computing hardware are pushing customers toward refurbished enterprise-grade devices as a cost-efficient and scalable alternative. Management believes the company is well positioned to capitalise on favourable industry trends while focusing on disciplined execution and long-term value creation. GNG Electronics is India’s largest refurbisher of laptops and desktops and among the largest refurbishers of ICT devices globally. As of 31 March 2025, the company had a significant presence across India, the USA, Europe, Africa and the UAE. It follows a repair-over-replacement model and refurbished nearly 5.9 lakh devices in FY25, offering a portfolio of 5,840 SKUs spanning laptops, desktops, tablets, servers, smartphones, workstations and accessories.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GNGElectronicsLtd_47811715_91822.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold softens on profit-taking and Dollar strength]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-softens-on-profit-taking-and-dollar-strength/1672828</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672828</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures slipped below the $5,000 per ounce mark in electronic trade on Friday, with prices set to close the week with modest gains following last week’s extreme volatility, which saw swings of nearly $1,000.

Gold futures slipped below the $5,000 per ounce mark in electronic trade on Friday, with prices set to close the week with modest gains following last week’s extreme volatility, which saw swings of nearly $1,000. The precious metal faced headwinds from profit-taking after recent record highs, alongside renewed strength in the US dollar. The dollar found support after President Donald Trump nominated Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve Chair, with markets viewing Warsh as favoring a smaller balance sheet and a more measured approach to policy easing. Geopolitical sentiment also remained cautious, as the White House signaled a preference for diplomacy with Iran. On the domestic front, MCX April gold futures recovered from intraday lows and traded marginally higher after touching Rs 149,396 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siemens slips after Q1 PAT drops 26% YoY to Rs 269]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siemens-slips-after-q1-pat-drops-26-yoy-to-rs-269/1672830</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672830</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 14% to Rs 3,830.7 crore, compared with Rs 3,360 crore in the same quarter last year.

Revenue from operations rose 14% to Rs 3,830.7 crore, compared with Rs 3,360 crore in the same quarter last year. Profitability was impacted by forex losses and a one-time charge related to the implementation of the new labour codes. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 429.2 crore, down from Rs 489.1 crore a year ago. The quarter included exceptional items of Rs 74.3 crore, primarily on account of increased employee benefit provisions following the new labour codes effective 21 November 2025. The company’s new orders during the quarter increased by 19% to Rs 4,829 crore, while order backlog grew by 7% at Rs 43,004 crore. Sunil Mathur, managing director and chief executive officer of Siemens, said, “India’s economic resilience continues to stand out even as adverse geopolitical developments and global uncertainties weigh on sentiment. Despite these external headwinds, Siemens Limited delivered a steady performance this quarter driven by disciplined execution and a healthy order book, resulting in an increase in revenue of 14%. All the businesses performed well during the quarter, contributing to a book-to-bill ratio of 1.26x, with Digital Industries now reflecting normalized operations. This is reflected in the company’s strong performance across all businesses during the quarter, including two significant order wins in the Mobility business. While the Smart Infrastructure business continued to demonstrate strong execution, the performance at the Digital Industries business is now showing signs of recovery, indicating that the destocking phase is now largely over. Looking ahead, we expect additional support from macroeconomic tailwinds as the recently signed India-EU Free Trade Agreement and the trade deal with the US begin opening new avenues for technology collaboration and exports. We welcome the government’s consistent focus on long-term economic growth and structural transformation in the Union Budget 2026-27. The record INR 12.2 lakh crore capital expenditure allocation, sustained emphasis on infrastructure development, and a fiscal deficit target of around 4.3% indicate a continued and disciplined approach to strengthening India’s growth foundations." On August 8, 2025, the board had approved changing the financial year from October–September to April–March. The current financial year spans October 1, 2024 – March 31, 2026 (18 months). Thereafter, FYs will run April–March. Siemens is a leading technology company focused on industry, infrastructure, and mobility.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Siemens_82042367344_514.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CL Educate Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cl-educate-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1672812</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672812</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vivid Mercantile Ltd, Tokyo Plast International Ltd, Orchasp Ltd and Digidrive Distributors Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 February 2026.

Vivid Mercantile Ltd, Tokyo Plast International Ltd, Orchasp Ltd and Digidrive Distributors Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 February 2026. CL Educate Ltd lost 20.00% to Rs 58.41 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 37427 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11709 shares in the past one month. Vivid Mercantile Ltd crashed 17.35% to Rs 7.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 44.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.77 lakh shares in the past one month. Tokyo Plast International Ltd tumbled 16.38% to Rs 100.05. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1229 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 347 shares in the past one month. Orchasp Ltd pared 11.36% to Rs 2.42. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.69 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 57316 shares in the past one month. Digidrive Distributors Ltd shed 10.90% to Rs 22.55. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6772 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3151 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CLEducateLtd_6722154754_26994.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Kirloskar Brothers Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-kirloskar-brothers-ltd-counter/1672793</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672793</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Concord Biotech Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Life Insurance Corporation of India, Sai Life Sciences Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 06 February 2026.

Concord Biotech Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Life Insurance Corporation of India, Sai Life Sciences Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 06 February 2026. Kirloskar Brothers Ltd clocked volume of 14.98 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 26.32 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 56914 shares. The stock gained 5.62% to Rs.1,632.10. Volumes stood at 31060 shares in the last session. Concord Biotech Ltd witnessed volume of 20.01 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 20.09 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 99586 shares. The stock increased 10.69% to Rs.1,293.10. Volumes stood at 80462 shares in the last session. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd saw volume of 59.12 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 18.29 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.23 lakh shares. The stock increased 10.90% to Rs.2,198.10. Volumes stood at 1.98 lakh shares in the last session. Life Insurance Corporation of India registered volume of 138.94 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.16 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 9.17 lakh shares. The stock rose 6.97% to Rs.898.25. Volumes stood at 6.72 lakh shares in the last session. Sai Life Sciences Ltd clocked volume of 38.44 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.91 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4.86 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.34% to Rs.846.05. Volumes stood at 3.85 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KirlBrothers_10364475530_336.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market trade sideways; FMCG shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-trade-sideways-fmcg-shares-advance/1672794</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672794</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the mid- afternoon trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the mid- afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. FMCG shares advanced after declining for previous trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, rose 78.21 points or 0.09% to 83,392.14. The Nifty 50 index fell 32.35 points or 0.12% to 25,610.40. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.57% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.63%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,680 shares rose and 2,395 shares fell. A total of 196 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the key policy rate—repo rate—unchanged at 5.25%. Headline inflation during November and December remained below the tolerance band of the inflation target. The revised outlook for CPI inflation in Q1 and Q2 of next year, at 4% and 4.2%, respectively, is revised slightly upwards, said RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra. The Indian economy continues on a steady, improving trajectory, with real GDP poised to register significant higher growth of 7.4% this year, as compared to the previous year, amidst global headwinds, the governor noted. Going forward, economic activity is expected to hold up well in the next year, he added. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index added 1.78% to 51,637.20. The index declined 0.38% in the previous trading session. ITC (up 4.42%), United Breweries (up 3.57%), Hindustan Unilever (up 1.89%), Patanjali Foods (up 1.34%) and United Spirits (up 0.84%), Emami (up 0.57%), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (up 0.46%), Britannia Industries (up 0.45%), Marico (up 0.44%) and Dabur India (up 0.35%) added. On the other hand, Radico Khaitan (down 1.96%), Nestle India (down 0.68%) and Varun Beverages (down 0.06%) turned lower. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper added 1.11% to 6.725 compared with previous session close of 6.651. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7625 compared with its close of 90.3400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.48% to Rs 152,800. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.12% to 97.85. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.55% to 4.185. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 80 cents or 1.18% to $68.35 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: CESC declined 1.04% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 32.14% to Rs 304 crore on a 23.96% drop in revenue from operations to Rs 4,005 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Jubilant Pharmova declined 2.28% after the company reported 45% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 55.8 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 100.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose by 17% YoY to Rs 2,123 crore during the quarter. Alembic Pharmaceuticals fell 1.55%. The company announced that it has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for Carbidopa, Levodopa, and Entacapone tablets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MRF zooms after Q3 PAT more than doubles to Rs 692 cr; declares dividend of Rs 3/ share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mrf-zooms-after-q3-pat-more-than-doubles-to-rs-692-cr-declares-dividend-of-rs-3-share/1672786</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672786</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax soared 134.47% YoY to Rs 994.56 crore during the quarter, with exceptional items of Rs 77.20 crore related to labour code compliance.

Profit before exceptional items and tax soared 134.47% YoY to Rs 994.56 crore during the quarter, with exceptional items of Rs 77.20 crore related to labour code compliance. Total expenses increased 7.58% to Rs 7,180.45 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 6674.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 4,688.45 crore (up 0.69% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 522.48 crore (up 9.09% YoY) while finance cost stood at Rs 91.23 crore (down 2.58% YoY) during the period under review. On the margins front, MRF’s operating margin climbed 11.94% in Q3 FY26 from 6% in Q3 FY25. Net profit margin improved to 8.46%, up from 4.44% in Q3 FY25. Meanwhile, the company’s board declared a dividend of Rs 3 per share for FY26. The company has fixed Friday 13th February, 2026 as the record date. The dividend will be paid on or after Friday, 27th February 2026. MRF is engaged in the manufacture of rubber products such as tires, tubes, flaps, and tread rubber and/or trading in rubber and rubber chemicals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MRF_74566371174_391.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI announces regulatory policy measures relating to financial markets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-announces-regulatory-policy-measures-relating-to-financial-markets/1672763</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672763</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a statement on developmental and regulatory policies.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a statement on developmental and regulatory policies. Following regulatory policy measures relating to financial markets were announced. Development of corporate bond market: An active derivatives market can facilitate efficient management of credit risks, improve liquidity and efficiency in the corporate bond market and facilitate issuance of corporate bonds across the rating spectrum. An announcement was made in the Union Budget speech delivered on February 1, 2026, that total return swaps on corporate bonds and derivatives on corporate bond indices will be introduced. Accordingly, a regulatory framework to enable the introduction of derivatives on credit indices and total return swaps on corporate bonds will be issued shortly for public feedback. Foreign Exchange Dealings of Authorised Dealers: Banks and standalone primary dealers authorised under FEMA, 1999, access the foreign exchange market for market making, balance sheet management and hedging of risks. The regulatory framework governing the facilities for such Authorised Dealers (ADs) has been reviewed, rationalised and refined in view of the current market practices and requirements, domestically and globally. The revised framework provides these ADs with greater flexibility with respect to foreign exchange products, risk management and platforms. Review of the Voluntary Retention Route for FPI investment in debt instruments: The Voluntary Retention Route (VRR) was introduced by the Reserve Bank in March 2019 to provide an additional channel for investments by Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) with long-term investment interest in the Indian debt markets. Over the years, the Bank has been recalibrating the Route to improve operational flexibilities and ease of doing business. The VRR has been witnessing active investment by FPIs, and over 80 per cent of the current investment limit of ₹2.5 lakh crore has been utilised. With a view to ensuring predictability about the availability of investment limits under the VRR and to further increase ease of doing business, it has been decided that (a) investments under the VRR shall now be reckoned under the limit for FPI investments under the General Route; and (b) certain additional operational flexibilities will be provided to FPIs investing under the VRR. Necessary directions will be separately issued.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/seri-ilan-1568018_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CESC slips as Q3 PAT slides 32% QoQ to Rs 304 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cesc-slips-as-q3-pat-slides-32-qoq-to-rs-304-cr/1672731</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672731</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit increased 7.8%, supported by a 12.47% growth in net sales in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25.

On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit increased 7.8%, supported by a 12.47% growth in net sales in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) increased 6.35% YoY to Rs 385 crore in Q3 FY26. Total expenses increased 7.84% to Rs 3,877 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,595 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The cost of energy purchased stood at Rs 1,475 crore (up 15.78% YoY), employee benefit expenses were at Rs 391 crore (up 24.92% YoY), and finance costs stood at Rs 343 crore (up 1.18% YoY) during the period under review. CESC is engaged in the generation and distribution of electricity.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CESC_38062435381_99.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jubilant Pharmova slips after weak Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jubilant-pharmova-slips-after-weak-q3-performance/1672728</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672728</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue rose by 17% YoY to Rs 2,123 crore during the quarter.

Revenue rose by 17% YoY to Rs 2,123 crore during the quarter. While EBITDA improved by 5% to Rs 310 crore, EBITDA margin declined by 172 basis points to 14.5% in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 93.4 crore, down by 28% from Rs 130.5 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Shyam S Bhartia, chairman of Jubilant Pharmova, and Hari S Bhartia, co-chairman & non-executive director of Jubilant Pharmova, said: “Revenue growth is particularly driven by incremental revenue generation from the new & third line in CDMO Sterile Injectable business. We expect this growth momentum to continue as we make progress in the last quarter of current financial year. As we are consciously investing in Radiopharma, CDMO Sterile Injectables and CRDMO business to secure future growth, Net Debt / EBITDA remains range bound at 1.3x in Dec’25, lower from 1.5x in Sep’25. During Q3’FY26, we saw exceptional growth momentum in the Ruby-Fill installs. In the Allergy Immunotherapy business, we witnessed increase in demand from the US market. In the CDMO Sterile Injectables business, we ramped up revenue generation from technology transfer programs at Line 3 in Spokane. In the CRDMO business, we continue to invest in building CDMO capabilities. In the Generics business, we are foreseeing growth & profitability improvement. Lastly, in our Proprietary Novel drugs business, we continue to make progress in JBI-802 and JBI-778 clinical trials." Jubilant Pharmova is a company with a global presence that is involved in radiopharma, allergy immunotherapy, CDMO sterile injectables, contract research development and manufacturing organisation (CRDMO), generics and proprietary novel drugs businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JubilantLife_43860952950_592.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,600 level; IT shares lag]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25600-level-it-shares-lag/1672726</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672726</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in the afternoon trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,650 mark. IT, PSU bank and auto shares declined, while FMCG, private bank and consumer durables shares advanced. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, slipped 123.46 points or 0.15% to 83,190.47. The Nifty 50 index fell 67.95 points or 0.27% to 25,568.60. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.78% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.85%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,603 shares rose and 2,430 shares fell. A total of 168 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the key policy rate—repo rate—unchanged at 5.25%. Headline inflation during November and December remained below the tolerance band of the inflation target. The revised outlook for CPI inflation in Q1 and Q2 of next year, at 4% and 4.2%, respectively, is revised slightly upwards, said RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra. The Indian economy continues on a steady, improving trajectory, with real GDP poised to register significant higher growth of 7.4% this year, as compared to the previous year, amidst global headwinds, the governor noted. Going forward, economic activity is expected to hold up well in the next year, he added. Gainers & Losers: ITC (up 5.06%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (up 2.51%), Bharti Airtel (up 1.72%), Bajaj Finance (up 1.35%) and Hindustan Unilever (up 1.13%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (down 2.58%), HDFC Life Insurance Company (down 2.51%), Tech Mahindra (down 2.33%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 2.10%) and SBI Life Insurance Company (down 2.05%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles declined 1.76% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 3,486 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with a net profit of Rs 5,406 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) jumped 6.12% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed surged 142.38% to Rs 63.31 crore on a 26.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2873.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharti Airtel rose 1.79%. The company reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Data Patterns (India) rallied 6.64% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 30.54% to Rs 58.30 crore on a 47.92% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 173.13 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. Hitachi Energy India surged 13.22% after the company’s standalone net profit soared 90.29% to Rs 261.42 crore on 27.71% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2021.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European equities opened on a mixed note on Friday, with investors exercising caution as a busy week of corporate earnings announcements across the region drew to a close. Asian markets traded lower as South Korea led the losses on Friday, following the tech-driven sell-off on Wall Street. South Korea’s market, which is heavily weighted in favor of companies in the chip and automotive industries, has seen sharp swings in the past week as sentiment over tech stocks sours. Pharmaceutical stocks in Japan also slumped on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled his website offering discounted prescription medicines. On the commodities front, spot silver prices continued their decline, falling 1.63% after crashing about 13% on Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 1.20%, while the S&P 500 lost 1.23%, pushing it into negative territory for the year. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite posted the biggest decline, dropping 1.59%. Tech giant Alphabet came under pressure after reporting fourth-quarter results and flagging a sharp rise in artificial intelligence spending, with capital expenditure totaling $185 billion for 2026. Qualcomm slid more than 8% after posting a weaker forecast because of a global memory shortage.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alembic Pharma receives USFDA approval for Parkinson’s drug tablets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alembic-pharma-receives-usfda-approval-for-parkinsons-drug-tablets/1672722</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672722</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Stalevo Tablets, manufactured by Orion Corporation.

The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Stalevo Tablets, manufactured by Orion Corporation. These tablets are indicated for the treatment of Parkinson’s disease. With this approval, Alembic Pharmaceuticals now has a cumulative total of 234 ANDA approvals from the USFDA, including 214 final approvals and 20 tentative approvals. Alembic Pharmaceuticals, a vertically integrated research and development company, is engaged in the manufacture and marketing of generic pharmaceutical products across global markets. On the financial front, the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 184.71 crore in Q2 FY26, up 20.40% from Rs 153.41 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 15.90% year-on-year to Rs 1,910.15 crore in the quarter ended September 2025. Shares of Alembic Pharmaceuticals declined 2.17% to Rs 792.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlembicPharma_46538273359_40294.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index holds just under two-week high, US equities stay slippery]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-holds-just-under-two-week-high-us-equities-stay-slippery/1672719</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672719</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar index has eased from around two-week high but losses are being curbed.

The US dollar index has eased from around two-week high but losses are being curbed. Currency markets eyed status quo from major central banks like ECB and BOE. Major US indexes tumbled amid a broad tech pullback and disappointing labor data, with Qualcomm’s sharp drop weighing on sentiment while Treasury yields fell as investors shifted toward safety. In U.S. economic news, initial jobless claims surged to 231,000 for the week ended January 31, up 22,000 from the prior week and well above expectations. Job openings also declined to their lowest level in more than five years, signaling a cooling labor market. Due to a short government shutdown earlier this week, the Labor Department postponed its monthly jobs report to next Wednesday. This weighed on the US currency and the dollar index currently quotes at 97.70, almost unchanged on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ABB India Ltd soars 0.33%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/abb-india-ltd-soars-033-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1672715</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672715</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ABB India Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

ABB India Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 5789, up 0.33% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 25543.45. The Sensex is at 83161.28, down 0.18%. ABB India Ltd has risen around 9.25% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which ABB India Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.24% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36230.35, down 0.07% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.65 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.05 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5779, down 0.03% on the day. ABB India Ltd is up 1.82% in last one year as compared to a 8.42% spurt in NIFTY and a 10.33% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 69.19 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABB_25842664874_242.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Emami Ltd gains for fifth session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/emami-ltd-gains-for-fifth-session/1672716</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672716</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Emami Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

Emami Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 506.2, up 0.58% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 25543.45. The Sensex is at 83161.28, down 0.18%. Emami Ltd has dropped around 3.83% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Emami Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 3.72% in last one month and is currently quoting at 50731.65, up 1.52% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.23 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.72 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 26.96 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Emami_73966496059_6423.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd spurts 0.53%, up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/patanjali-foods-ltd-spurts-053-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1672717</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672717</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

Patanjali Foods Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 518.25, up 0.53% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 25543.45. The Sensex is at 83161.28, down 0.18%. Patanjali Foods Ltd has dropped around 10.1% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Patanjali Foods Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 3.72% in last one month and is currently quoting at 50731.65, up 1.52% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 11.5 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 24.52 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 519.2, up 0.65% on the day. Patanjali Foods Ltd is down 15.93% in last one year as compared to a 8.42% gain in NIFTY and a 6.55% gain in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 39.36 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RuchiSoyaInds_47333195530_704.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tips Music Ltd spurts 0.54%, gains for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tips-music-ltd-spurts-054-gains-for-five-straight-sessions/1672718</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672718</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tips Music Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

Tips Music Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 561.1, up 0.54% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 25543.45. The Sensex is at 83161.28, down 0.18%. Tips Music Ltd has added around 6.05% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Tips Music Ltd is a constituent, has added around 4.95% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1393, down 0.55% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 44127 shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.5 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 37.93 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TipsIndustries_17137674547_8022.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI announces policy measures relating to financial inclusion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-announces-policy-measures-relating-to-financial-inclusion/1672714</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672714</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a statement on developmental and regulatory policies.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a statement on developmental and regulatory policies. Following regulatory policy measures relating to financial inclusion were announced. Revision in Lead Bank Scheme: The Reserve Bank has undertaken a detailed review of the existing guidelines on Lead Bank Scheme (LBS). It is now proposed to issue a comprehensive set of instructions on the Scheme with a view to streamline the operational aspects. In the revised Scheme, the objectives of LBS and the framework to achieve them are proposed to be delineated clearly. The revised guidelines are expected to enhance the effectiveness of the Scheme. The draft Circular will be issued shortly for public consultation. In addition, the Reserve Bank will be launching a unified portal for reporting of Bank-wise LBS data which is currently fragmented across various portals. This is expected to significantly enhance the data quality and provide better insights towards achieving the objectives of LBS. Revision in the Guidelines of Kisan Credit Card (KCC): The Reserve Bank has comprehensively reviewed the KCC Scheme with a view to expand coverage, streamline operational aspects and address emerging requirements. It is now proposed to issue a revised set of instructions to banks on the Scheme, consolidating those on agriculture and allied activities. The proposed guidelines include, among others, standardisation of crop season, extension of KCC tenure to six years, alignment of drawing limit with Scale of Finance (SoF) for each crop season and inclusion of expenses on technological interventions. Review of guidelines relating to use of Business Correspondents (BCs) by banks: Business Correspondents have been functioning as critical enablers of last mile access to financial services, particularly in respect of underserved, rural, and remote locations. Reserve Bank had set up a committee, consisting of officials from Reserve Bank, DFS, IBA and NABARD, to comprehensively examine their operations and make suitable recommendations for enhancing their efficiency. Basis the Committee’s recommendations, the related regulatory guidelines are being reviewed, and the draft amendment directions will be placed for public consultations shortly. Enhancement in Collateral free loan limit from Rs 10 lakh to Rs 20 lakh: With a view to facilitate improved access to formal credit, support entrepreneurial activity and strengthen last mile credit delivery for Micro and Small Enterprises (MSEs) with limited collateral, it has been decided to enhance the limit of collateral free loans to MSEs from Rs 10 lakh to Rs 20 lakh. The above provisions shall be applicable to all loans to MSE borrowers sanctioned or renewed on or after April 01, 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/human-hand-add-a-coin-in-the-final-row-picture-id514573604_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Motors PV records Q3 loss of Rs 3,486 cr; JLR disruption weighs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-motors-pv-records-q3-loss-of-rs-3486-cr-jlr-disruption-weighs/1672711</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672711</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter.

Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. The performance continued to be impacted significantly by the cyber incident at JLR, as indicated earlier. The company reported a loss before exceptional items and tax of Rs 3,483 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 6,106 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Exceptional items totaled Rs 1,597 crore, comprising labour code charges of Rs 427 crore, employee separation costs of Rs 80 crore, supplier claim and cyber-related expenses of Rs 778 crore, and demerger-related expenses of Rs 421 crore. These were partly offset by a gain of Rs 109 crore from the reversal of restructuring costs. Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) revenue stood at euro 4.5 billion, down 39.4%YoY. Volumes impacted following the cyber incident and the time taken thereafter to distribute vehicles globally, as vehicle production returned to normal levels by mid-November. Volumes were also affected by the planned wind -down of legacy Jaguar models ahead of new Jaguar launch, a deterioration of market conditions in China, and ongoing incremental US tariffs impacting JLR’s US exports. Looking ahead, the company said JLR remains resilient and well placed to address the economic, geopolitical and policy challenges the industry faces. Investment spend is expected to remain at euro 18 billion over the five-year period from FY24. In light of the challenges faced, FY26 guidance is reaffirmed, with EBIT margin of 0% to 2% and free cash outflow of euro 2.2 billion to 2.5 billion. PB Balaji, chief executive officer, said: “Q3 was a challenging quarter for JLR with performance impacted by the production shutdown we initiated in response to the cyber incident, the planned wind down of legacy Jaguar, and US tariffs. Thanks to the commitment of our dedicated teams, we returned vehicle production to normal levels by mid-November, and we are focused on building our business back stronger. While the external environment remains volatile, we expect performance to improve significantly in the fourth quarter and we have clear plans to manage global challenges. We have a resilient business and remain focused on transformation. 2026 is set to be an exciting year for JLR as we develop our next generation vehicles, including the launch of Range Rover Electric and the unveiling of the first new Jaguar.” Meanwhile, revenue from Tata Passenger Vehicles jumped 24% YoY to Rs 15,317 crore during the quarter. Passenger vehicles (PV) and Electric Vehicle (EV) volumes during the quarter were at 1,71,000 units (up 22% YoY) driven by impact of reduction in GST rates and robust performance of products. Looking ahead, the company remains confident about the PV industry’s growth, supported by positive demand momentum following GST 2.0. With deliveries from recent launches commencing in Q4 and a strong pipeline of upcoming models, Tata Motors PV is well poised to accelerate its growth trajectory in FY27. Shailesh Chandra, managing director & CEO, Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles said: “In Q3 FY26, we recorded our highest-ever quarterly wholesales at 171k units, while retail sales crossed the 200k mark for the first time, driven by strong demand tailwinds from GST 2.0 and a robust festive season. With strengthened value proposition for our products, we witnessed robust demand during the quarter, with Nexon emerging as the highest-selling model in India in Q3, while Punch also saw enhanced volumes.” Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (formerly Tata Motors), part of the $180 billion Tata Group, is one of India’s leading automobile manufacturers, offering a diverse portfolio of cars and SUVs renowned for their design, safety, and performance. The counter shed 0.32% to Rs 372.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataMotors_19446492084_560.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>