<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:25:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of India global business spurts 12% YoY in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-india-global-business-spurts-12-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663080</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663080</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Global deposits stood at Rs 8,87,287 crore, reflecting an 11.64% YoY increase, while global gross advances rose 13.55% to Rs 7,39,811 crore on 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 6,51,507 crore on 31 December 2024.

Global deposits stood at Rs 8,87,287 crore, reflecting an 11.64% YoY increase, while global gross advances rose 13.55% to Rs 7,39,811 crore on 31 December 2025, compared to Rs 6,51,507 crore on 31 December 2024. Domestic gross advances also saw robust growth of 15.07%, reaching Rs 6,28,617 crore on 31 December 2025, up from Rs 5,46,268 crore in the same quarter last year. Domestic deposits rose 12.80% YoY to Rs 7,65,500 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 6,78,626 crore a year earlier. Bank of India is an India-based bank. The bank's segments include treasury operations, wholesale banking, and retail banking. The treasury operations segment includes the entire investment portfolio, which deals in government and other securities, money market operations, and foreign exchange operations. The company’s standalone net profit climbed 7.6% to Rs 2,554.57 crore on a 3.8% increase in total income to Rs 20,625.92 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Bank of India rallied 1.46% to close at Rs 149.15 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofIndia_12067469065_5654.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[V2 Retail Q3 revenue jumps 57% as store expansion lifts growth momentum]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/v2-retail-q3-revenue-jumps-57-as-store-expansion-lifts-growth-momentum/1663075</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663075</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Standalone revenue rose 57% year-on-year to Rs 927 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 591 crore in the year-ago period, delivering high double-digit growth on an already strong base.

Standalone revenue rose 57% year-on-year to Rs 927 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 591 crore in the year-ago period, delivering high double-digit growth on an already strong base. Same-store sales growth stood at 2% YoY, while normalized SSSG was about 12.8%, adjusted for the shift of the Durga Puja festive period to the September quarter. Combined sales across Q2 and Q3 FY26 grew 68%, the company said in a business update to stock exchanges. Store productivity also improved, with monthly sales per square foot rising to Rs 1,032 during the quarter, reflecting faster ramp-up of new stores. V2 Retail added 35 new stores in Q3, taking its total network to 294 stores with a retail footprint of about 31.93 lakh sq ft, largely concentrated in Tier 2 and Tier 3 cities. Operational performance was supported by data-led assortment curation and high sell-through rates, enabling the company to maintain healthy margins with minimal markdowns. Improved inventory management led to faster churn and reduced aged stock, keeping store assortments aligned with seasonal demand. For the nine months ended December 2025, standalone revenue from operations grew 63% to Rs 2,262 crore, while SSSG stood at around 8.6%. Monthly sales per square foot averaged Rs 981 during the period. The company added a net 105 stores in 9M FY26, underscoring its aggressive expansion strategy. Management said the strong performance of newer stores in markets such as Maharashtra, Punjab, Rajasthan and South India has reinforced confidence in scaling its value-and-variety retail model further. V2 Retail is one of the fastest-growing retail company in India and enjoys strong brand equity from customers across segments. The company offers a portfolio of products, including apparel and lifestyle products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/V2Retail_3344440892_27679.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Corona Remedies Q2 PAT climbs 22% YoY to Rs 52 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/corona-remedies-q2-pat-climbs-22-yoy-to-rs-52-cr/1663074</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663074</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 21.67% year on year (YoY) to Rs 69.78 crore in Q2 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 21.67% year on year (YoY) to Rs 69.78 crore in Q2 FY26. Earnings Before Interest, Taxes, Depreciation, and Amortization (EBITDA) stood at Rs 78.47 crore, with EBITDA margin at 21.7% in Q2 FY26. Total expenditure climbed 14.4% YoY to Rs 282.66 crore. Raw material costs declined 9.3% YoY to Rs 25.9 crore. Employee expenses rose 17.3% YoY to Rs 103 crore. Interest costs eased 32.8% YoY to Rs 1.93 crore, while depreciation inched up 1.7% YoY to Rs 9.2 crore. On Half year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 35.10% to Rs 98.52 crore on 16.92% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 707.67 crore in H1 FY26, compared with H1 FY25. Nirav K. Mehta, MD and CEO, CORONA Remedies, said: “We are delighted to report a strong financial performance in Q2 and H1 FY26. Revenues for Q2 and H1FY26 grew by 15.1% and 17.0% respectively on a Y-o-Y basis, outperforming the IPM growth. Profit after tax for Q2 and H1FY26 grew by 21.8% and 35.1% respectively on a Y-o-Y basis while maintaining healthy return ratios. Our strong performance reflects the consistency of our strategy, disciplined execution and deep focus on our core therapeutic segments. By strengthening our field force, expanding our brand portfolio and maintaining a sharp focus on specialist’s prescriptions, we have continued to outperform the market while building a sustainable platform for long-term growth. Lastly, we are grateful to our bankers for their efforts in the successful listing of CORONA on the Indian stock exchanges. I would also like to thank the entire team at CORONA and our stakeholders for their continued support and faith in our business.” Corona Remedies is an India-focused branded pharmaceutical formulation company developing, manufacturing, and marketing products in women’s healthcare, cardio-diabeto, pain management, urology and other therapeutic areas. Shares of Corona Remedies rallied 3.05% to close at Rs 1,445.70 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoronaRemediesLtd_53198342_71174.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[3C IT Solutions bags domestic orders worth nearly Rs 3.75 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/3c-it-solutions-bags-domestic-orders-worth-nearly-rs-375-crore/1663072</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663072</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[3C IT Solutions & Telecoms (India) said it has secured two domestic purchase orders aggregating nearly Rs 3.75 crore.

3C IT Solutions & Telecoms (India) said it has secured two domestic purchase orders aggregating nearly Rs 3.75 crore. The company received an order worth Rs 2.75 crore from Kay Kay Overseas Corporation for the supply of 1,000 Lenovo notebooks. Separately, Bajaj Housing Finance placed an order valued at Rs 99.94 lakh for the supply of 140 desktop computers. Both orders were received in the ordinary course of business. 3C IT Solutions & Telecoms (India) is engaged in the business of retail selling of laptops, accessories, related products and other networking components. On a standalone basis, the company reported net profit of Rs 0.14 crore in H1FY26 as against net loss of Rs 0.17 crore in H1FY25. Net sales declined 9.79% year-on-year to Rs 21.19 crore in H1FY26. Shares of 3C IT Solutions & Telecoms (India) fell 0.50% to settle at Rs 15.92 on Friday, 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/3CITSolutionsandTelecomsIndiaLtd_90374117_92886.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Bank of India domestic advances jumps 7% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-bank-of-india-domestic-advances-jumps-7-yoy-in-q3/1663073</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663073</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a quarter-on-quarter basis, domestic advances rose 4.07% to Rs 9,80,643 crore as of 31 December 2025.

On a quarter-on-quarter basis, domestic advances rose 4.07% to Rs 9,80,643 crore as of 31 December 2025. The bank’s domestic deposits increased 3.35% YoY to Rs 12,22,260 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 11,82,622 crore a year earlier, while declining 0.96% QoQ from Rs 12,34,088 crore as of 30 September 2025. Domestic CASA deposits were at Rs 4,15,001 crore during the quarter, registering a growth of 4.99% year on year (YoY) and 3.28% quarter on quarter (QoQ). The bank’s total global business as of 31 December 2024 stood at Rs 21,65,632 crore, up 4.70% YoY and 0.24% QoQ. Global gross advances gained 7.13% YoY and 4.27% QoQ to Rs 10,16,805 crore as of 31 December 2025. Global deposits stood at Rs 12,22,856 crore during the period under review (up 3.36% YoY and down 0.95% QoQ). Union Bank of India is engaged in the business of treasury operations, corporate and wholesale banking, retail banking operations, and other banking operations. The Government of India held a 74.76% stake in the bank. The public lender's standalone net profit declined 10% to Rs 4,249.08 crore on a 1.2% drop in total income to Rs 31,646.06 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Union Bank of India rose 2.21% to close at Rs 156.80 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnionBankI_88937846814_5493.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Finance Q3 disbursements climb 7% YoY to Rs 17,600-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-finance-q3-disbursements-climb-7-yoy-to-rs-17600-cr/1663071</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663071</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[For the nine months ended FY26, disbursements are seen at approximately Rs 43,900 crore, reflecting a 4% YoY increase, excluding finance leases.

For the nine months ended FY26, disbursements are seen at approximately Rs 43,900 crore, reflecting a 4% YoY increase, excluding finance leases. The company’s business assets are estimated at about Rs 1.29 lakh crore as of December 2025, marking a 12% growth on a year-on-year basis, supported by steady performance across lending segments. Asset quality remained stable, with collection efficiency estimated at 95% in Q3 FY26, unchanged from the same period last year. As of 31 December 2025, Stage-3 assets are estimated to be in the range of 3.9–4.0%, largely flat compared with 3.9% a year ago. Stage-2 assets are estimated at 5.4–5.5%, improving from 6.3% in the year-ago period, indicating better early-stage delinquencies. The company continued to maintain a strong liquidity position, with a liquidity buffer of over Rs 8,850 crore on its balance sheet. Mahindra Finance, part of the Mahindra Group, is one of India’s leading non-banking finance companies. Focused on the rural and semi-urban sector, the company has over 11 million customers. The company is a leading vehicle and tractor financier, provides loans to SMEs and also offers fixed deposits. The company has 1,352 offices and reaches out to customers spread over 5,16,000 villages and 8,000 towns across the country, transforming more than 1.1 crore lives. The NBFC’s standalone net profit jumped 54.08% to Rs 569.31 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 369.47 crore reported in Q2 FY25. Total income increased by 14.37% year on year to Rs 4,489.24 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of Mahindra & Mahindra Financial Services shed 0.30% to close at Rs 402.75 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MMFinServ_95105710_16795.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PNB records 8% YoY growth in domestic deposits in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pnb-records-8-yoy-growth-in-domestic-deposits-in-q3/1663070</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663070</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank's domestic advances stood at Rs 11,67,801 crore on 31 December 2025, up 10.15% YoY and up 4.47% QoQ.

The bank's domestic advances stood at Rs 11,67,801 crore on 31 December 2025, up 10.15% YoY and up 4.47% QoQ. The bank’s global advances increased 10.98% YoY to Rs 12,32,245 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 11,10,292 crore a year earlier and rose 5.36% QoQ from Rs 11,69,592 crore as of 30 September 2025. As of 31 December 2025, the bank’s global deposits stood at Rs 16,60,385 crore, registering a growth of 8.54% YoY and 2.68% QoQ. The bank's global business stood at Rs 28,92,630 crore as of 31 December 2025, recording a growth of 9.57% YoY and 3.80% QoQ. The global credit-deposit ratio advanced to 74.21% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 72.58% recorded a year earlier on 31 December 2024. Punjab National Bank is engaged in treasury operations, corporate/wholesale banking, retail banking, digital banking, and others. As of 30th September 2025, the bank has 10,228 domestic branches and 2 international branches. Out of the total number of branches, the bank has 63.3% of branches in rural & semi-urban areas. The bank’s standalone net profit climbed 13.95% to Rs 4,903.73 crore on a 5.13% jump in total income to Rs 36,213.62 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Punjab National Bank rallied 1.17% to close at Rs 125.40 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663069</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663069</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon Mutual Fund has announced that Notice is hereby given that Mr.

Nippon Mutual Fund has announced that Notice is hereby given that Mr. Ajay Patel, Deputy Head - Operations has ceased from the services of Nippon Life India Asset Management Limited due to superannuation with effect from the close of business hours on January 02, 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TRUST Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trust-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663068</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TRUST Mutual Fund has announced that NOTICE is hereby given that Mr.

TRUST Mutual Fund has announced that NOTICE is hereby given that Mr. Ameet Hariani has resigned as an Independent Director on the Board of TRUST AMC Trustee Private Limited with effect from December 31, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[J&K Bank gross advances grow 17% YoY in Q3FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jk-bank-gross-advances-grow-17-yoy-in-q3fy26/1663066</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663066</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total business stood at Rs 2,72,109.27 crore as of 31 December 2025, up 13.34%, compared with Rs 2,40,080.49 crore as of 31 December 2024.

Total business stood at Rs 2,72,109.27 crore as of 31 December 2025, up 13.34%, compared with Rs 2,40,080.49 crore as of 31 December 2024. CASA deposits rose 1.25% YoY to Rs 68,736.27 crore as of 31 December 2025. CASA ratio reduced to 44.10% as of 31 December 2025 as against 48.17% as of 31 December 2024. Total deposits increased 10.58% to Rs 1,55,861.35 crore as of 31 Decemeber 2025, compared with Rs 1,40,947.14 crore as of 31 December 2024. Gross investment declined 2.07% to Rs 40,535.76 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 41,394.29 crore as of 31 December 2024. J&K Bank offers banking services under the three major divisions as support services, depository services, and third-party services. The bank reported a 1.91% jump in net profit to Rs 494.11 crore on a 2.04% decline in total income to Rs 3,446.71 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q1 FY26. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit declined 10.31%, and revenue rose 0.79% in Q2 FY26. Shares of Jammu & Kashmir Bank rallied 1.29% to close at Rs 102.35 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JKBank_38858702295_7311.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1663067</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663067</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced that Ms.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced that Ms. Roshi Jain, Senior Fund Manager - Equities has resigned from the services of HDFC Asset Management Company Limited (“HDFC AMC”) and accordingly, has ceased to be a Key Personnel of HDFC AMC with effect from close of business hours of December 31, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NIBE bags Rs 293-cr defence order from Indian Army]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nibe-bags-rs-293-cr-defence-order-from-indian-army/1663062</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663062</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the manufacturing and supply of ground equipment, accessories, ESP and ammunition for a Universal Rocket Launcher System capable of integrating multiple rocket types, including long-range rockets with strike capabilities of 150 km and 300 km.

The order involves the manufacturing and supply of ground equipment, accessories, ESP and ammunition for a Universal Rocket Launcher System capable of integrating multiple rocket types, including long-range rockets with strike capabilities of 150 km and 300 km. As per the contract terms, the company is required to furnish a performance-cum-warranty bank guarantee equivalent to 10% of the total contract value within 30 days of signing the agreement. The contract will be executed in tranches over a period of 12 months. The total consideration of Rs 292.69 crore is inclusive of all taxes and duties. The company clarified that the order has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related-party transactions. Further, the promoters or promoter group entities do not have any interest in the awarding authority. NIBE operates in manufacturing critical components for the defence sector, electric vehicles (E-Vehicles), and software development. The company is engaged in fabrication and machining of components used in the defence sector, as well as assembly of components for E-vehicles. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 8.44 crore in Q2FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 9.12 crore posted in Q2FY25. Revenue from operations fell 46.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 73.37 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of NIBE rallied 9.21% to close at Rs 1,240.25 on the BSE on 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KavitaFabrics_98715753806_43224.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Torrent Pharma credit rating unchanged as India Ratings reaffirms AA+]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/torrent-pharma-credit-rating-unchanged-as-india-ratings-reaffirms-aa/1663060</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663060</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Torrent Pharmaceuticals said India Ratings and Research has reaffirmed the credit rating of the company’s existing banking facilities, issuer rating and non-convertible debentures at IND AA+ with a stable outlook.

Torrent Pharmaceuticals said India Ratings and Research has reaffirmed the credit rating of the company’s existing banking facilities, issuer rating and non-convertible debentures at IND AA+ with a stable outlook. The rating agency has also assigned a short-term rating of IND A1+ to Torrent Pharma's proposed commercial paper programme, indicating a strong degree of safety with respect to timely servicing of financial obligations. The company's securities transfer and stakeholders relationship committee will meet on 5 January 2026 to consider the issuance of secured non-convertible debentures through a private placement, within the borrowing limits already approved by the board in July 2025. Torrent Pharma is the flagship company of the Torrent Group. It is ranked 7th in the Indian Pharmaceuticals Market and is amongst the Top 5 in the therapeutics segments of Cardiovascular (CV), Gastro Intestinal (GI), Central Nervous System (CNS) and Cosmo-Dermatology. It is a specialty-focused company with 76% of its revenues in India from chronic & sub-chronic therapies. It has presence in 50+ countries and is ranked No. 1 amongst the Indian pharma companies in Brazil and Germany. Torrent has 8 manufacturing facilities, of which 5 are USFDA approved. On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit rose 30.46% to Rs 591 crore while net sales rose 14.66% to Rs 3246 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. Shares of Torrent Pharmaceuticals rose 0.96% to settle at Rs 3884.85 on Friday, 2 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TorrentPharma_35676110126_3616.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>