<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:50:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Olectra Greentech gains on bagging Rs 1,800 crore electric bus order from TGSRTC]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/olectra-greentech-gains-on-bagging-rs-1800-crore-electric-bus-order-from-tgsrtc/1679146</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679146</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to a regulatory filing, the LOAs relate to the supply, operation and maintenance of 1,085 electric buses.

According to a regulatory filing, the LOAs relate to the supply, operation and maintenance of 1,085 electric buses. The order includes 1,025 12-metre non-AC buses and 60 12-metre AC buses. The contract has been awarded under the Gross Cost Contract (GCC) / OPEX model for a period of 12 years. EVEY will procure the buses from Olectra, with deliveries scheduled over 20 months. Olectra said the supply value of the 1,085 buses is estimated at approximately Rs 1,800 crore. The company will also undertake maintenance of the buses during the contract period. The company clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It added that the proposed transactions between Olectra and EVEY qualify as related party transactions and will be conducted on an arm’s length basis. Olectra Greentech is engaged in the manufacturing of composite polymer insulators, electric buses, and electric trucks. The company's consolidated net profit rose 4.18% to Rs 49.55 crore while net sales rose 25.39% to Rs 656.62 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlectraGreentec_59554403015_22012.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patel Engg gains after securing  Rs 910-cr project in Himachal Pradesh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/patel-engg-gains-after-securing-rs-910-cr-project-in-himachal-pradesh/1679144</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679144</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scope of works under this package comprises the construction of three diversion tunnels, each with a diameter of 9.5 meters and lengths of 1379 meters, 1468 meters, and 1590 meters respectively.

The scope of works under this package comprises the construction of three diversion tunnels, each with a diameter of 9.5 meters and lengths of 1379 meters, 1468 meters, and 1590 meters respectively. The package also covers the development of three inlet and outlet portals for the diversion tunnels, along with the construction of access roads spanning 6 kilometers. In addition, the project involves the installation of hydro-mechanical gates for the diversion tunnels and the execution of instrumentation works to ensure operational efficiency and safety. The Renuka Ji Dam Project is a critical initiative aimed at enhancing water storage capacity, ensuring reliable water supply, and supporting hydropower generation. The order, valued at Rs 910 crore, is scheduled to be completed within 30 months. Kavita Shirvaikar, managing director, Patel Engineering said: "Being declared the L1 bidder for the Renuka Ji Dam Project is a proud milestone for us, reaffirming our strong capabilities in delivering large-scale infrastructure projects and our role as a trusted partner in India’s growth journey. This project not only strengthens our portfolio but also positions us to contribute meaningfully to sustainable water management and hydropower development. Looking ahead, we remain committed to leveraging innovation, engineering excellence, and execution efficiency to deliver projects that create lasting value for communities and drive the nation’s infrastructure forward." Patel Engineering operates in the hydropower, tunneling and irrigation segments. The company has executed projects in India and overseas, including more than 85 dams, 40 hydroelectric projects and over 300 km of tunneling for central PSUs and state government agencies. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 11.8% to Rs 70.35 crore despite a 2.8% increase in net sales to Rs 1,239.35 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PatelEngg_45399352434_1320.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IDFC First Bank Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/idfc-first-bank-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679140</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679140</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UPL Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Swan Corp Ltd and 63 Moons Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026.

UPL Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Swan Corp Ltd and 63 Moons Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026. IDFC First Bank Ltd crashed 16.34% to Rs 69.91 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 324.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.23 lakh shares in the past one month. UPL Ltd tumbled 14.85% to Rs 640.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 58346 shares in the past one month. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd lost 12.00% to Rs 2192. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2.14 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.57 lakh shares in the past one month. Swan Corp Ltd plummeted 6.75% to Rs 379.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.38 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 38621 shares in the past one month. 63 Moons Technologies Ltd corrected 6.71% to Rs 598.75. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11852 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10701 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDFCBank_27126132357_54759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AU Small Finance slumps after Haryana govt bars lender from govt business]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/au-small-finance-slumps-after-haryana-govt-bars-lender-from-govt-business/1679138</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679138</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a statement, the bank said that on 18 February 2026, it received a separate communication from the department seeking information regarding suspected unauthorised transactions between a government account and another customer account.

In a statement, the bank said that on 18 February 2026, it received a separate communication from the department seeking information regarding suspected unauthorised transactions between a government account and another customer account. The bank said it maintains a complete audit trail of transactions and that all relevant details have been recorded. It added that there is no indication of any financial impact on the bank or evidence of fraudulent activity involving the bank. As of 21 February deposits from the Government of Haryana with AU Small Finance Bank stood at Rs 538 crore across nearly 200 accounts, accounting for about 0.4% of the bank's overall deposits as of 31 December 2026. The bank said it continues to conduct an internal review of the matter. To ensure a fair and transparent process, certain employees have been placed off duty. AU Small Finance Bank also said it is engaging with the Government of Haryana to understand the reason for the de-empanelment. AU Small Finance Bank is engaged in providing a range of banking and financial services, including retail banking, wholesale banking, treasury operations, and other services. The bank reported a 26.34% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 667.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 528.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AUSmallFinanceBankLtd_26708448592_34695.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[N K Industries Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/n-k-industries-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679135</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679135</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd, Nova Agritech Ltd, Sri Havisha Hospitality & Infrastructure Ltd and Naksh Precious Metals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 February 2026.

Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd, Nova Agritech Ltd, Sri Havisha Hospitality & Infrastructure Ltd and Naksh Precious Metals Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 February 2026. N K Industries Ltd tumbled 15.78% to Rs 65.1 at 14:26 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 804 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 334 shares in the past one month. Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd lost 10.13% to Rs 884.35. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 17 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 152 shares in the past one month. Nova Agritech Ltd crashed 9.20% to Rs 29.69. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 33014 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13920 shares in the past one month. Sri Havisha Hospitality & Infrastructure Ltd corrected 7.87% to Rs 1.64. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5195 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7215 shares in the past one month. Naksh Precious Metals Ltd plummeted 7.76% to Rs 5.35. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1871 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9672 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NKIndustriesLtd_41969182627_4144.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold extends rally as tariff hikes and geopolitical risks lift safe-haven demand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-extends-rally-as-tariff-hikes-and-geopolitical-risks-lift-safe-haven-demand/1679130</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679130</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures rose more than 1% to trade near $5,200 per ounce during mid electronic trading on Monday, extending gains for a fourth consecutive week as renewed trade tensions sparked a flight to safe-haven assets.

Gold futures rose more than 1% to trade near $5,200 per ounce during mid electronic trading on Monday, extending gains for a fourth consecutive week as renewed trade tensions sparked a flight to safe-haven assets. Sentiment was driven by fresh tariff uncertainty after US President Donald Trump announced plans to raise global tariffs from 10% to 15%, following the US Supreme Court’s rejection of his reciprocal tariff proposal. The move weighed on the US dollar index, which slipped toward the 97 level, further supporting bullion prices. Gold also benefited from heightened geopolitical concerns surrounding stalled US–Iran nuclear talks, although negotiators are scheduled to meet again in Geneva later this week. Trading volumes are expected to rise as Chinese markets reopen after an extended holiday. Reflecting global strength, Multi Commodity Exchange of India gold futures for April 2 delivery climbed 1.5% to ₹159,272 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trades with decent gains; FMCG shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trades-with-decent-gains-fmcg-shares-rally/1679132</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679132</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the mid-afternoon trade despite concerns surrounding the recent U.S.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the mid-afternoon trade despite concerns surrounding the recent U.S. tariffs announcement. Investors will monitor crude oil and gold price movements. The Nifty traded above the 25,650 mark. FMCG shares advanced after declining in the past trading session. At 14:26 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 289.60 points or 0.35% to 83,104.31. The Nifty 50 index rose 72.55 points or 0.29% to 25,643.80. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index declined 0.52% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index advanced 0.19%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,821 shares rose and 2,376 shares fell. A total of 222 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index rose 0.45% to 52,004.55. The index declined 1.76% in the past trading session. United Spirits (up 2.62%), Godrej Consumer Products (up 1.51%), United Breweries (up 1.35%), Hindustan Unilever (up 1.20%), Tata Consumer Products (up 1.18%), Marico (up 1.05%), Nestle India (up 0.92%), Varun Beverages (up 0.63%), Dabur India (up 0.34%) and Britannia Industries (up 0.22%) advanced. On the other hand, Kwality Walls India (down 1.77%), ITC (down 0.52%) and Patanjali Foods (down 0.39%) edged lower. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.19% to 6.712 compared with the previous session close of 6.725. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.8325 compared with its close of 90.9450 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement advanced 1.31% to Rs 158,935. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.24% to 97.48. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.27% to 4.078. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement lost 84 cents or 1.17% to $70.92 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: IDFC First Bank slumped 16.47% after the bank said that it has uncovered fraudulent transactions worth around Rs 590 crore at one of its branches in Chandigarh, allegedly involving a few employees. Pine Labs added 3.34% after the company announced that it has won multiple landmark contracts from Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (HPCL), and Indian Oil Corporation (IOCL). Under the contracts executed with respective OMCs, Pine Labs will be entrusted with deploying, managing, and maintaining the digital payments infrastructure at petrol pumps and merchant outlets across India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at IDFC First Bank Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-idfc-first-bank-ltd-counter/1679129</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679129</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UPL Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, CCL Products (India) Ltd, Aegis Vopak Terminals Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 23 February 2026.

UPL Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, CCL Products (India) Ltd, Aegis Vopak Terminals Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 23 February 2026. IDFC First Bank Ltd registered volume of 5780.25 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 31.69 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 182.40 lakh shares. The stock slipped 15.99% to Rs.70.16. Volumes stood at 119.75 lakh shares in the last session. UPL Ltd saw volume of 187.49 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.4 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 15.12 lakh shares. The stock dropped 14.96% to Rs.639.80. Volumes stood at 24 lakh shares in the last session. BLS International Services Ltd witnessed volume of 198.79 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.91 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 16.69 lakh shares. The stock increased 7.49% to Rs.288.50. Volumes stood at 13.08 lakh shares in the last session. CCL Products (India) Ltd registered volume of 20.53 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.17 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.51 lakh shares. The stock rose 5.30% to Rs.1,046.70. Volumes stood at 3.38 lakh shares in the last session. Aegis Vopak Terminals Ltd recorded volume of 44.45 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.03 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.33 lakh shares. The stock gained 9.47% to Rs.230.74. Volumes stood at 7.36 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDFCBank_27126132357_54759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UPL plunges as restructuring plan flags leverage risks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/upl-plunges-as-restructuring-plan-flags-leverage-risks/1679128</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679128</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company announced restructuring plan to consolidate its India and international crop protection businesses into a new listed entity, UPL Global Sustainable Agri Solutions (UPL Global).

The company announced restructuring plan to consolidate its India and international crop protection businesses into a new listed entity, UPL Global Sustainable Agri Solutions (UPL Global). Under the scheme, UPL will first amalgamate UPL Sustainable Agri Solutions (SAS) with itself. This will be followed by a vertical demerger of its India crop protection business into UPL Global, along with the amalgamation of UPL Corp, which houses the international crop protection business, into UPL Global. UPL Global Sustainable Agri Solutions will be listed on stock exchanges and will house both the India and international crop protection platforms upon completion of the proposed steps. Meanwhile, the domestic brokerage has downgraded the stock to ‘hold’ from ‘buy’, citing unresolved concerns around leverage and dilution following the restructuring. Although it marginally raised its target price to Rs 816 per share from Rs 806 earlier implying an upside of around 28% from current levels. The brokerage cautioned near-term risks continue to cap investor confidence. The brokerage flagged that the exercise does not materially reduce net debt at the group level, with leverage being redistributed between the two resulting listed entities. Mike Frank, CEO of UPL Global, added, “Bringing our crop protection businesses under one platform creates the world’s second largest listed pure-play crop protection platform. With a presence in more than 140 countries, this unified platform will enable us to deliver innovations to farmers faster, more efficiently to gain greater market share. This will position us to strengthen operational synergies and drive long-term value for our stakeholders." Bikash Prasad, Group CFO of UPL, said, “This structural simplification strengthens our financial foundation and accelerates our journey towards a more efficient and resilient UPL. By driving deleveraging, reinforcing balance sheet strength, and improving return metrics, we are creating a sharper, more focused organization designed to deliver sustainable long-term value for all shareholders.” UPL is a global provider of sustainable agricultural products and solutions that cover the entire agrifood value chain. It is one of the largest agriculture companies worldwide, serving growers in more than 140 countries. UPL comprises of four pure-play platforms that include UPL Corporation (UPL Corp); UPL Sustainable Agri Solutions (UPL SAS); Advanta Enterprises; and Superform Chemistries (formerly known as UPL Speciality Chemicals). The company’s consolidated net profit declined 52.2% to Rs 396 crore despite 12.5% increase in net sales jumped 12.5% YoY to Rs 12,269 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UPL_77209428989_2461.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude corrects under $66 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-corrects-under-66-per-barrel/1679126</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679126</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures slipped below $66 per barrel on Monday, retreating from a six-month high as investors weighed the prospects of a potential Iran–US nuclear agreement and its implications for global supply.

WTI crude oil futures slipped below $66 per barrel on Monday, retreating from a six-month high as investors weighed the prospects of a potential Iran–US nuclear agreement and its implications for global supply. A third round of talks is scheduled later this week in Geneva, according to Oman’s foreign minister Badr Albusaidi, even as concerns persist over the risk of military escalation between the two sides. Tensions remain elevated following warnings from Donald Trump, alongside reports of an increased US military presence in the Middle East. Adding to downside pressure, renewed trade uncertainty emerged after plans to raise global tariffs to 15%, clouding the oil demand outlook.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc inks MoU with Tripura Group to set up manufacturing unit at Zinc Park, Bhilwara]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-inks-mou-with-tripura-group-to-set-up-manufacturing-unit-at-zinc-park-bhilwara/1679125</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679125</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agreement marks an important milestone in Hindustan Zinc’s plan to build India’s first integrated downstream industrial hub dedicated to zinc-based value chains.

The agreement marks an important milestone in Hindustan Zinc’s plan to build India’s first integrated downstream industrial hub dedicated to zinc-based value chains. Under the agreement, Hindustan Zinc will provide assured raw material linkage to Tripura Group’s proposed unit at the Zinc Industrial Park, supported by a committed long-term offtake arrangement. The partnership reflects a shared commitment to building a robust downstream zinc ecosystem, with investment and production plans aligned to drive scale, efficiency, and sustainable industrial growth in the region. Arun Misra, chief executive officer (CEO), Hindustan Zinc, said “Zinc Park is a strategic initiative that translates our long-term vision for a resilient and competitive metal value chain into concrete action. Our partnership with Tripura Group demonstrates how targeted collaboration can unlock downstream value and accelerate Makein-India manufacturing. The assured supply arrangements, coupled with performance-linked incentives and renewable energy commitments, will provide investors with the confidence to scale. We are determined to build an ecosystem that supports MSME growth, creates local jobs, and drives technological improvements across the zinc value chain.” Hindustan Zinc is engaged in exploring, extracting and processing of minerals. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 45.5% to Rs 3,897.28 crore on 27.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 10,627 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Hindustan Zinc rose 0.31% to Rs 591.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade in positive terrain; European mrkt decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-in-positive-terrain-european-mrkt-decline/1679123</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679123</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with decent gains in the afternoon trade despite concerns surrounding the recent U.S.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with decent gains in the afternoon trade despite concerns surrounding the recent U.S. tariffs announcement. Investors will monitor crude oil and gold price movements. The Nifty traded above the 25,650 mark. IT, metal and realty shares declined while PSU Bank, auto and FMCG shares advanced. At 13:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 341.97 points or 0.41% to 83,157.46. The Nifty 50 index jumped 90.05 points or 0.35% to 25,663.50. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index declined 0.41% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index advanced 0.33%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,884 shares rose and 2,252 shares fell. A total of 231 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 1.16% to 14.20. Gainers & Losers: Adani Ports (up 2.39%), Kotak Bank (up 2.21%), HDFC Life Insurance (up 1.82%), SBI Life Insurance (up 1.58%) and Power Grid Corporation of India (up 1.52%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Hindalco Industries (down 2.91%), ONGC (down 2.14%), Infosys (down 1.93%), Wipro (down 1.93%) and Kwality Wall’s (India) (down 1.80%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Dee Development Engineers surged 15.33% after the company announced that it, along with its material subsidiary, has secured contracts aggregating approximately Rs 173 crore. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone added 2.44% after the company’s subsidiary Adani Gangavaram Port signed a memorandum of understanding with NMDC, a Government of India enterprise, and Vale S.A., Brazil. Axis Bank added 1.36% after the bank has clarified that it has neither submitted nor is planning to submit any bid for a stake in CreditAccess Grameen. Morepen Laboratories zoomed 17.48% after the company announced that it has secured a multi-year contract development and manufacturing organization (CDMO) mandate valued at approximately Rs 825 crore from a leading global pharma major. JSW Infrastructure advanced 1.80% after the company‘s board approved the issuance of 25 crore equity shares with face value of Rs 2 each, to fund its multi year expansion program IDFC First Bank slumped 16.24% after the bank said that it has uncovered fraudulent transactions worth around Rs 590 crore at one of its branches in Chandigarh, allegedly involving a few employees. Lotus Chocolate Company declined 1.59% after the company announced temporary shutdown of its manufacturing facility situated in Sangareddy, Telangana for 15 days from 24 February 2026. Global Markets: European market declined as investors await for Italy inflation data later this week. Asian stock markets traded mostly with gains on Monday as investors monitored developments related to the United States tariffs. While the Supreme Court ruled on Friday that the Trump administration unlawfully imposed the measures last year, US President Donald Trump used different legal means to raise global levies to 15% from 10% over the weekend. Markets in China and Japan were closed for a holiday. On Friday, U.S. stocks rose after the Supreme Court ruling, potentially providing relief for companies burdened by higher costs from the duties and easing concern about sticky inflation still plaguing the U.S. economy. The S&P 500 advanced 0.69% and closed at 6,909.51, while the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9% and settled at 22,886.07. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 230.81 points, or 0.47%, and ended at 49,625.97. The 30-stock index recovered from a 200-point loss earlier in the session on disappointing economic data. Data released on Friday showed that the US economy expanded an annualized 1.4% in Q4 2025, the least since Q1 2025, following a 4.4% growth in Q3 and well below widely reported forecasts of 3%, the advance estimate showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coforge Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coforge-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1679121</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679121</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Coforge Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Coforge Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1291.7, down 3.65% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.29% on the day, quoting at 25644.85. The Sensex is at 83125.93, up 0.38%.Coforge Ltd has eased around 22.39% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Coforge Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 18.25% in last one month and is currently quoting at 32004.05, down 1.49% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 32.41 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 30.19 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1291.2, down 3.75% on the day. Coforge Ltd tumbled 15.34% in last one year as compared to a 13.71% rally in NIFTY and a 20.08% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 61.88 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoforgeLtd_47640546_24978.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welspun Corp Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/welspun-corp-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1679122</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679122</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Welspun Corp Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Welspun Corp Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 782.7, down 0.1% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.29% on the day, quoting at 25644.85. The Sensex is at 83125.93, up 0.38%.Welspun Corp Ltd has gained around 8.43% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Welspun Corp Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.58% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11989.95, down 0.76% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.3 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.71 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 27.28 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WelspunCorp_23409759814_7947.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pine Labs edges higher after signing multi-year contracts with BPCL, HPCL & IOCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pine-labs-edges-higher-after-signing-multi-year-contracts-with-bpcl-hpcl-iocl/1679116</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679116</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the contracts executed with respective OMCs, Pine Labs will be entrusted with deploying, managing, and maintaining the digital payments infrastructure at petrol pumps and merchant outlets across India.

Under the contracts executed with respective OMCs, Pine Labs will be entrusted with deploying, managing, and maintaining the digital payments infrastructure at petrol pumps and merchant outlets across India. These are multi-year contracts aimed at leveraging the expertise of Pine Labs in managing the payment rails for swifter, secure, seamless money movements at the point of sale. These will collectively cumulate to nearly 130,000 digital payments acceptance devices to be instantly deployed and maintained pan India. For IOCL specifically, Pine Labs will also be managing their loyalty rewards platform called XTRAPOWER, in popular use by lakhs of fleet operators in India. The program built on robust API integrations caters to fuel management, fleet analytics, trip management, secure Chip and PIN digital payment transactions including card, mobile, and RFID payments. B Amrish Rau, CEO, Pine Labs, said: “By combining our tech prowess with the massive retail footprints of top OMCs in India, we are enabling a tech-first and robust payments infra and a world-class prepaid loyalty rewards ecosystem. Software-first approach of Pine Labs will ensure faster product feature rollouts, minimal on-site intervention, and a unified payments and rewards/loyalty platform for accelerated digitisation of fuel retail commerce in India." Pine Labs is a technology company focused on digitizing commerce through digital payments and issuing solutions for merchants, consumer brands and enterprises, and financial institutions. The company reported net profit of Rs 42.39 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 56.67 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales jumped 23.7% YoY to Rs 744.27 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PineLabsLtd_41545070_77096.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/j-b-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1679113</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679113</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2032.7, up 1.62% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.36% on the day, quoting at 25662.7. The Sensex is at 83141.63, up 0.39%. J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd has risen around 8.27% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 3.27% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22452.4, up 0.21% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.34 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.97 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 44.18 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JBChemPharm_56046055785_303.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bhartiya International rises after India Ratings revises rating outlook to 'stable’ ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bhartiya-international-rises-after-india-ratings-revises-rating-outlook-to-stable/1679112</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679112</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has reaffirmed the company’s long-term rating and short-term rating at ‘IND BBB’ and ‘IND A2’, respectively.

The agency has reaffirmed the company’s long-term rating and short-term rating at ‘IND BBB’ and ‘IND A2’, respectively. India Ratings and Research stated that it had previously placed the rating on ‘Rating Watch with Negative Implications’, due to uncertainty over the impact of the US tariff on the company’s operations. The agency had resolved the ‘Rating Watch’ in view of the reduction in the tariff to 18% from 50% and the improvement in the company’s operating performance in 9M FY26. The affirmation reflects the continued growth in BIL’s revenue during FY25-9MFY26, and India Ratings’ expectation of a sustained increase in the same in the medium term. The ratings also factor in an improvement in the credit metrics in FY25, and the likelihood of continued improvement in the same in the medium term. Furthermore, the EBITDA margins increased in 9M FY26, and are likely to see further improvement in the medium term. The ratings are supported by BIL’s established market position and strong customer relationships. However, the ratings are constrained by BIL’s elongated working capital cycle due to the integrated nature of operations, multi-location manufacturing base, and seasonality in sales and raw leather availability. Bhartiya International (BIL) exports leather garments and accessories to the US, Italy, France, Spain, and Austria, among others. BIL sources leather from India, Europe, the Middle East, Latin America and other Asia Pacific counties. The company has manufacturing facilities in Bengaluru (Karnataka), Chennai (Tamil Nadu) and Nellore (Andhra Pradesh) with a design studio in Milan via its 100%-owned Italian subsidiary, Ultima S.A. The company had reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 6.70 crore in the quarter ended December 2025 as against net loss of Rs 1.51 crore during the previous quarter ended December 2024. Sales rose 39.16% to Rs 365.95 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BhartiyaIntl_77405956214_4418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with moderate gains; auto shares advance ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-moderate-gains-auto-shares-advance/1679111</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679111</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in early afternoon trade.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in early afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,650 mark. Auto shares advanced after declining for previous trading session. At 12:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 292.53 points or 0.35% to 83,115.64. The Nifty 50 index surged 81.30 points or 0.32% to 25,652.55. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.43% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index added 0.32%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,904 shares rose and 2,168 shares fell. A total of 228 shares were unchanged. Derivatives: The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.24% to 13.49. The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures were trading at 25,670.70, at a premium of 18.15 points as compared with the spot at 25,652.55. The Nifty option chain for the 24 February 2026 expiry showed a maximum call OI of 229.1 lakh contracts at the 25,700 strike price. Maximum put OI of 134.8 lakh contracts was seen at 25,700 strike price. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index auto 0.62% to 28,018.20. The index tanked 2.10% in the past trading session. Bharat Forge (up 2.08%), Eicher Motors (up 1.19%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 0.99%), TVS Motor Company (up 0.96%) and Bajaj Auto (up 0.74%), Ashok Leyland (up 0.67%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 0.62%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (up 0.59%), Exide Industries (up 0.22%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 0.03%) added. On the other hand, Tube Investments of India (down 1.87%), Samvardhana Motherson International (down 0.51%) and Uno Minda (down 0.31%) edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: IDFC First Bank slumped 16.20% after the bank said that it has uncovered fraudulent transactions worth around Rs 590 crore at one of its branches in Chandigarh, allegedly involving a few employees. R&B Denims advanced 1.93% after the company secured sales orders aggregating to around Rs 215.88 crore for the supply of around 12,000,000 meters of denim fabric products from established merchant exporters. Morepen Laboratories zoomed 14.48% after the company announced that it has secured a multi-year contract development and manufacturing organization (CDMO) mandate valued at approximately Rs 825 crore from a leading global pharma major.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/akme-fintrade-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1679108</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679108</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Arihant Capital Markets Ltd, DEE Development Engineers Ltd, V R Films & Studios Ltd and Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 February 2026.

Arihant Capital Markets Ltd, DEE Development Engineers Ltd, V R Films & Studios Ltd and Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 February 2026. Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd surged 19.39% to Rs 7.02 at 23-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 8.74 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.21 lakh shares in the past one month. Arihant Capital Markets Ltd soared 13.99% to Rs 85.45. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 65074 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14319 shares in the past one month. DEE Development Engineers Ltd spiked 13.17% to Rs 262. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 13.53 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10210 shares in the past one month. V R Films & Studios Ltd spurt 11.70% to Rs 14.7. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 359 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1585 shares in the past one month. Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd jumped 10.71% to Rs 62. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 3149 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 716 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AkmeFintradeIndiaLtd_46552741_74863.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Morepen Laboratories Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/morepen-laboratories-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1679102</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679102</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, CIE Automotive India Ltd and Kitex Garments Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026.

Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, BLS International Services Ltd, CIE Automotive India Ltd and Kitex Garments Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 February 2026. Morepen Laboratories Ltd surged 15.01% to Rs 45.21 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 46.1 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.4 lakh shares in the past one month. Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd soared 9.95% to Rs 390.8. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 88032 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 31068 shares in the past one month. BLS International Services Ltd spiked 8.23% to Rs 290.65. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 13.23 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5.42 lakh shares in the past one month. CIE Automotive India Ltd exploded 7.07% to Rs 502.7. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.5 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15656 shares in the past one month. Kitex Garments Ltd added 6.15% to Rs 197.55. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 4.24 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.48 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MorepenLabs_34238238875_2685.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>