<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siyaram Recycling Inds bags Rs 14-cr order from The Supreme Industries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siyaram-recycling-inds-bags-rs-14-cr-order-from-the-supreme-industries/1662211</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662211</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total order value is Rs 1,43,36,410.

The total order value is Rs 1,43,36,410. The order, awarded by a domestic entity, is on a fixed-cost basis and is scheduled to be executed within six months. The company stated that neither its promoters nor promoter group or group companies have any interest in the entity awarding the contract. The transaction is not classified as a related-party transaction. Siyaram Recycling Industries is primarily engaged in the recycling of brass scrap. Supreme Industries is India’s leading plastics product manufacturer, offering a wide and comprehensive range of plastic products in India. The company operates in various product categories viz. plastic piping system, cross laminated films & products, protective packaging products, industrial moulded components, moulded furniture, storage & material handling products, performance packaging films and composite lpg cylinders. Shares of Siyaram Recycling Industries rose 0.07% to Rs 54.20 while Supreme Industries added 0.20% to Rs 0.20% to Rs 3,278.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiyaramRecyclingIndustriesLtd_80297349_92151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1662210</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662210</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 30 December 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 30 December 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit. Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 26,000 level; realty shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-26000-level-realty-shares-decline/1662209</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662209</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning trade as investors stayed cautious amid FII selling.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning trade as investors stayed cautious amid FII selling. The Nifty traded below the 26,000 level. Realty shares tumbled for second consecutive trading session. At 11:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 283.06 points or 0.33% to 84,758.39. The Nifty 50 index lost 71.10 points or 0.27% to 25,970.20. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.39%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 0.50%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,472 shares rose and 2,550 shares fell. A total of 232 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 0.57% to 878.15. The index dropped 0.79% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Anant Raj (down 2.37%), Phoenix Mills (down 0.82%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 0.71%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.51%), DLF (down 0.46%), Lodha Developers (down 0.45%), Brigade Enterprises (down 0.41%) and Sobha (down 0.36%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Ceigall India rallied 2.29% after the company’s subsidiary, Ceigall Infra Projects has received a LoA from Madhya Pradesh Road Development Corporation for the construction of the Indore–Ujjain access-controlled four-lane greenfield highway. Vikran Engineering surged 5.31% after it has secured letter of awards (LoA) from M.P. Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of power plants with a total capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh. Jindal Steel advanced 1.86% after the company announced a significant expansion of its structural steel manufacturing capabilities at its Raigarh facility. This expansion would double the company’s existing structural steel capacity from 1.2 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) to 2.4 MTPA by mid 2028. Global Markets: Most Asian markets advanced on Monday as investors kicked off the final trading week of the year. Prices of spot silver rose to a fresh record high of above $80 per ounce before pulling back sharply to $77. Silver’s recent surge was driven by speculative buying and lingering supply tightness, said experts. Media report further stated silver’s rally this year reflects a depletion of freely traded inventory, amplifying price moves as demand increases. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 reached a new high and posted weekly gains as traders came back from the Christmas holiday. The broad market index closed down 0.03% to end at 6,929.94. At its high, the S&P 500 was up 0.2%, reaching 6,945.77. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.09% and closed at 23,593.10. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 20.19 points, or 0.04%, and settled at 48,710.97.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves rise near record]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-rise-near-record/1662208</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662208</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's forex reserves rose by USD 4.368 billion to USD 693.318 billion during the week ended December 19, the Reserve Bank said on Friday.

India's forex reserves rose by USD 4.368 billion to USD 693.318 billion during the week ended December 19, the Reserve Bank said on Friday. Reserve have neared record high. The overall kitty had increased by USD 1.689 billion to USD 688.949 billion in the previous week. For the week ended December 19, foreign currency assets, a major component of the reserves, increased by USD 1.641 billion to USD 559.428 billion. Value of the gold reserves increased by USD 2.623 billion to USD 110.365 billion during the week while Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) were up by USD 8 million to USD 18.744 billion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T Transportation Infrastructure secures Hyderabad Greenfield Radial Road contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-transportation-infrastructure-secures-hyderabad-greenfield-radial-road-contract/1662207</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662207</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore.

As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore. The order covers Phase-2 of the Greenfield Radial Road, involving construction of a 22.3 km, 3+3 lane access-controlled radial road in Ranga Reddy district. L&T’s scope includes a 3.6 km viaduct, minor bridges, underpasses, culverts, service roads on both sides, retention structures, storm water drainage, footpaths, cycle tracks, and landscaping. This is the first of several planned radial roads linking Hyderabad’s Outer Ring Road to the upcoming regional ring road. The project aims to enhance regional connectivity and support development by improving access to IT hubs, Electronic City, the Young India Skills University, and Bharat Future City. Larsen & Toubro is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services. The company reported a 15.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Larsen & Toubro rose 0.01% to currently trade at Rs 4,045.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coforge to acquire Encora in $2.35 billion share swap deal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coforge-to-acquire-encora-in-235-billion-share-swap-deal/1662203</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662203</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Encora is one of the select tech services firms founded with an AI native DNA providing engineering services to Fortune 1000 enterprises and digital-native companies.

Encora is one of the select tech services firms founded with an AI native DNA providing engineering services to Fortune 1000 enterprises and digital-native companies. The firm operates at the convergence of AI, cloud and data, with capabilities spanning intelligent process design, agent native product engineering, core modernization, AI foundation, data readiness, and AIOps. Encora has built one of the industry’s first composable agentic AI platforms — AIVATM, and has deep partnerships with AWS, Microsoft, Google and Snowflake. Encora’s FY26E revenue is $600 million with an Adjusted EBITDA margin of approximately 19%. Coforge will acquire the business from Advent, Warburg Pincus and other minority shareholders for an enterprise value of $2.35 billion. The transaction will be funded through a preferential allotment of equity shares representing an equity value of approximately $1.89 billion, pursuant to which Encora shareholders will hold approximately 20% of the expanded share capital of Coforge upon completion of the transaction. Coforge’s acquisition of Encora is set to create a technology services powerhouse with an estimated total revenue of $2.5 billion. Within this structure, the combination of AI-led engineering, data, and cloud services is projected to deliver $2 billion in revenue by fiscal year 2027. The AI-led product engineering segment alone is expected to grow into a business worth over $1.25 billion. Additionally, cloud services are estimated to reach approximately $500 million, while data engineering is forecasted to contribute more than $250 million to the firm's total revenue. The combined business is expected to operate at an EBIT margin of 14% and the acquisition is expected to be EPS accretive in FY27. Sudhir Singh, chief executive officer and executive director, Coforge, said: "The Encora acquisition is a defining moment for our organization. It establishes a scaled AI-led engineering capability moat for the firm underpinned by capabilities to help create enterprise data cores and cloud foundations purpose built for AI.” Coforge is a global tech services and solutions provider, that leverages emerging technologies and deep domain expertise to deliver real-world business impact for its clients. The scrip shed 0.64% to currently trade at Rs 1662.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoforgeLtd_47640546_24978.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEPC gains on bagging Rs 230-crore order ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sepc-gains-on-bagging-rs-230-crore-order/1662201</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662201</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order is for the design, construction, furnishing, and equipping of a third vertical shaft at the Chikla Mine in Maharashtra.

According to an exchange filing, the order is for the design, construction, furnishing, and equipping of a third vertical shaft at the Chikla Mine in Maharashtra. The project will be executed on a turnkey basis. The total value of the contract stands at Rs 230 crore. The timeline for execution of the order will be mutually agreed upon by both parties. SEPC provides end-to-end solutions to engineering challenges, offering multidisciplinary design, engineering, procurement, construction, and project management services. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 262.4% to Rs 8.30 crore on an 8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 237.42 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. MOIL is a Schedule 'A' Miniratna Category-I public sector undertaking (PSU) that is engaged in the business of mining and supplying manganese. At present, the company operates its underground and opencast mines located in the Nagpur and Bhandara districts of Maharashtra and Balaghat district of Madhya Pradesh. The company's net profit jumped 40.99% to Rs 70.44 crore on a 19.24% increase in revenue to Rs 348.05 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The counter rose 0.44% to Rs 367.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShriramEPC_87688887012_28369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at HFCL Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-hfcl-ltd-counter/1662200</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662200</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[JM Financial Ltd, Graphite India Ltd, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 29 December 2025.

JM Financial Ltd, Graphite India Ltd, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 29 December 2025. HFCL Ltd clocked volume of 151.6 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.73 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 17.37 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.88% to Rs.65.74. Volumes stood at 97.48 lakh shares in the last session. JM Financial Ltd recorded volume of 10.06 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 7.65 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.31 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.07% to Rs.144.20. Volumes stood at 1.37 lakh shares in the last session. Graphite India Ltd clocked volume of 2.44 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 5.92 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 41219 shares. The stock gained 4.36% to Rs.608.55. Volumes stood at 83052 shares in the last session. Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd recorded volume of 39259 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 3.61 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10871 shares. The stock lost 2.28% to Rs.1,460.00. Volumes stood at 29899 shares in the last session. Home First Finance Company India Ltd notched up volume of 21572 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 3.05 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7067 shares. The stock slipped 0.15% to Rs.1,113.65. Volumes stood at 2772 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HFCL_23392864533_1189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis CRISIL IBX SDL June 2034 Debt Index Fund Merger into Axis Gilt Fund]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-crisil-ibx-sdl-june-2034-debt-index-fund-merger-into-axis-gilt-fund/1662199</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662199</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund has approved the merger of Axis CRISIL IBX SDL June 2034 Debt Index Fund Merger into Axis Gilt Fund, with effect from 03 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Diamond Power Infra bags Rs 66-cr power cable order from Hild Projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/diamond-power-infra-bags-rs-66-cr-power-cable-order-from-hild-projects/1662194</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662194</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The purchase order has been awarded on a “kms rate basis with PV formulae” and is scheduled for execution between 1 January 2026 and 30 June 2026.

The purchase order has been awarded on a “kms rate basis with PV formulae” and is scheduled for execution between 1 January 2026 and 30 June 2026. Diamond Power Infrastructure is engaged in the business of manufacturing transmission & distribution of power products & services in India. The company's consolidated net profit zoomed 593.3% to Rs 27.73 crore on a 75.1% surge in net sales to Rs 438.33 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Diamond Power Infrastructure shed 0.32% to Rs 139.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DiamondPower_44345217117_3225.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index net speculative shorts fall further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-net-speculative-shorts-fall-further/1662193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662193</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index speculative shorts have come off their record level for more than a decade, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

US dollar index speculative shorts have come off their record level for more than a decade, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of US dollar index futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of -4595 contracts in the data reported through December 16, 2025, showing a further decrease of 9279 net short positions compared to the previous week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty pare early gains; metal shares shine  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-pare-early-gains-metal-shares-shine/1662195</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662195</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks pared all gains and traded with minor losses in morning trade amid persistent FII selling.

The key equity benchmarks pared all gains and traded with minor losses in morning trade amid persistent FII selling. The Nifty traded below the 26,050 mark after touching day’s high of 26,106.80 in early trade. Metal stocks soared for eight consecutive trading sessions. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 46.97 points or 0.06% to 84,994.48. The Nifty 50 index fell 4.55 points or 0.02% to 26,037.75. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.06% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.11%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,638 shares rose and 2,178 shares fell. A total of 240 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index jumped 1.38% to 10,954.90. The index rallied 4.69% for the eight straight trading sessions. Hindustan Copper (up 8.44%), Steel Authority of India (up 4.1%), Tata Steel (up 2.24%), Vedanta (up 2.15%), Jindal Steel (up 1.71%), Hindustan Zinc (up 1.67%), Welspun Corp (up 1.39%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 1.32%), JSW Steel (up 1%) and APL Apollo Tubes (up 0.71%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: VA Tech Wabag shed 0.83%. The company has received a letter of award from the Saudi Water Authority for a large repeat EPC order to build a 50 MLD advanced BWRO plant at Aljouf, Saudi Arabia. JD Cables declined 1.42%. The company announced that it has secured orders worth Rs 8.81 crore from reputed EPC contractors for cable supply operations in Bihar and Jharkhand. Solarworld Energy Solutions surged 9.10% the company announced that it has received a letter of award for the EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project worth Rs 725.33 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ceigall India rises as subsidiary secures Rs 1,089-cr Indore–Ujjain road project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ceigall-india-rises-as-subsidiary-secures-rs-1089-cr-indoreujjain-road-project/1662192</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662192</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves development of a 48.10-km highway, including the Simhastha bypass, at a bid project cost of Rs 1,089 crore.

The project involves development of a 48.10-km highway, including the Simhastha bypass, at a bid project cost of Rs 1,089 crore. The construction is scheduled to be completed within 24 months from the date of appointment. Ceigall will undertake construction of the highway infrastructure in line with HAM guidelines, aimed at improving connectivity between Indore and Ujjain, easing traffic congestion and enabling safe, efficient and high-speed travel to key economic and religious centres in Madhya Pradesh. This LOA further strengthens Ceigall’s robust order book in the roads and highways segment and underscores its growing footprint in executing large-scale hybrid annuity projects for state road development authorities. The project aligns with Ceigall’s long-term strategy of contributing to India’s infrastructure growth through sustainable, efficient and future-ready transportation corridors. Commenting on the development, Ramneek Sehgal, chairman & MD, Ceigall India, said, “The Indore–Ujjain Greenfield Highway is a strategically important infrastructure project for Madhya Pradesh. Receiving this LOA from MPRDC reinforces our strong execution capabilities in complex HAM projects and our commitment to building high-quality road infrastructure. We look forward to delivering this project with a focus on safety, durability and timely execution.” Ceigall India is an infrastructure engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) company undertaking specialized structural works such as elevated roads, flyovers, bridges, railway overbridges, tunnels, highways, expressways, and runways. The principal business operations are broadly divided into EPC projects and hybrid annuity model (HAM) projects. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Ceigall India declined 13.86% to Rs 57.99 crore while net sales rose 4.45% to Rs 806.57 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CeigallIndiaLtd_68678209_85110.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund announces change in Exit Load Structure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dsp-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-exit-load-structure/1662191</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662191</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund has announced change in exit load structure under following scheme stands revised with effect from January 01, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Exit Load: Name of the Scheme Existing Exit Load Revised Exit Load DSP Credit Risk Fund If the units redeemed or switched out are upto 10% of the units (the limit) purchased or switched in within 12 months from the date of allotment NIL If units redeemed or switched out are in excess of the limit within 12 months from the date of allotment 1% If units are redeemed or switched out on or after 12 months from the date of allotment NIL If the units are redeemed or switched out within 12 months from the date of allotment 3% If units are redeemed or switched out on or after 12 months from the date of allotment

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India has the potential to become the world's food basket, says PM Modi]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-has-the-potential-to-become-the-worlds-food-basket-says-pm-modi/1662188</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662188</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Addressing the 5th National Conference of Chief Secretaries, Prime Minister Modi said India has the potential to become the world's food basket and the country must move towards high-value agriculture, horticulture, animal husbandry, dairying and fisheries and become a major food exporter.

Addressing the 5th National Conference of Chief Secretaries, Prime Minister Modi said India has the potential to become the world's food basket and the country must move towards high-value agriculture, horticulture, animal husbandry, dairying and fisheries and become a major food exporter. He said the conference is being held at a time when India is witnessing next-generation reforms. The PM said India has boarded the "Reform Express" and its primary engine is the country's youth and demography. That is why, it is the government's endeavour to empower this demography, he said. He also called upon states to encourage manufacturing, boost 'ease of doing business' and strengthen the services sector to make India a global services giant.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikran Engg rallies on bagging LOAs for 45.75 MW solar PV Capacity]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikran-engg-rallies-on-bagging-loas-for-4575-mw-solar-pv-capacity/1662187</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662187</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the awards, Vikran Engineering will act as a Renewable Power Generator (RPG) for the implementation of the grid-connected solar photovoltaic (PV) based solar power plants.

Under the awards, Vikran Engineering will act as a Renewable Power Generator (RPG) for the implementation of the grid-connected solar photovoltaic (PV) based solar power plants. The projects will have a power purchase tenure of 25 years, with tariffs ranging between Rs 2.75 per kWh to Rs 2.80 per kWh, as specified in the LOAs The projects will be developed under the Surya Mitra Krishi Feeders Scheme, with feeder solarisation as part of the PM KUSUM-C scheme, for sale of power to Madhya Pradesh Power Management Company (MPPMCL). Vikran Engineering is a diversified EPC player. The company provides end-to-end turnkey solutions spanning conceptualization, design, supply, installation, testing, and commissioning, enabling it to capture the full value chain of project execution. On a standalone basis, net profit of Vikran Engineering rose 339.42% to Rs 9.14 crore while net sales increased 10.71% to Rs 176.29 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VikranEngineeringLtd_15725401_76742.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Steel rises on plans to double Raigarh facility's steel production capacity by 2028]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-steel-rises-on-plans-to-double-raigarh-facilitys-steel-production-capacity-by-2028/1662186</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662186</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[This expansion would double the company’s existing structural steel capacity from 1.2 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) to 2.4 MTPA by mid 2028.

This expansion would double the company’s existing structural steel capacity from 1.2 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) to 2.4 MTPA by mid 2028. The expansion will substantially enhance the availability of heavy and ultra-heavy structural steel sections in India. As part of this project, Jindal Steel will commission a new, dedicated structural steel mill, alongside advanced upstream and downstream technology upgrades. This will enable the manufacture of larger, heavier, and more complex parallel flange sections required for next-generation infrastructure and energy projects. The company currently manufactures parallel flange sections ranging from 100 mm to 900 mm, with sectional weights of up to 333 kg per metre. With the ongoing expansion, production capability will extend to ultra-heavy sections reaching 1,100 mm depth and 1,500 kg per metre. Subrat Panda, Head – Structures & CSB, Jindal Steel, said: "Doubling our structural steel capacity at Raigarh is a strategic step towards building long-term domestic capability for large and complex projects. With the ability to manufacture the largest parallel flange sections in India, we are enabling faster execution, improved design efficiency, and reduced dependence on imports for critical infrastructure and energy applications." Jindal Steel and Power is the flagship company of Jindal Group, an industrial powerhouse which has a strong presence in the steel, power, mining, and infrastructure sectors globally. The scrip fell 1.03% to currently trade at Rs 976.34 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalSteelLtd_73073935_20287.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Solarworld Energy spurts on bagging Rs 725-cr order from NTPC Renewable Energy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/solarworld-energy-spurts-on-bagging-rs-725-cr-order-from-ntpc-renewable-energy/1662184</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662184</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project is scheduled to be completed in the financial year 2026–27, in accordance with the terms of the order.

The project is scheduled to be completed in the financial year 2026–27, in accordance with the terms of the order. The company clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It also stated that the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions under applicable regulatory norms. Solarworld Energy Solutions is a leading renewable energy company. It offers end-to-end solar EPC, large-scale solar park development, and customized rooftop and ground-mounted solar solutions for commercial, industrial, and utility clients. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 58.3% to Rs 9.29 crore on a 2.9% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 137.88 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SolarworldEnergySolutionsLtd_63857359_94042.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VA Tech Wabag secures large EPC order from Saudi Water Authority]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/va-tech-wabag-secures-large-epc-order-from-saudi-water-authority/1662183</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662183</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the order, Wabag will design, supply, construct and commission the BWRO plant within 14 months.

Under the order, Wabag will design, supply, construct and commission the BWRO plant within 14 months. The facility will treat raw water sourced from borewell fields containing rare elements and will feature a robust pre-treatment system using ceramic membrane technology, followed by micron cartridge filtration and reverse osmosis to ensure long-term reliability and sustainable water supply for the region. The company said it has received the LoA and contracting formalities will commence shortly. The effective date for the start of project execution will be announced after the contract is signed. Commenting on this development, Phani Sathish Kadiyala, Country Manager & Branch GM – KSA said, “We are honoured to receive this repeat order from our esteemed customer, SWA, and sincerely thank them for their continued confidence in WABAG. This award reflects the Kingdom’s proactive adoption of next-generation water treatment technologies and further reinforces WABAG’s leadership in advanced technology solutions such as BWRO, SWRO, and recycle-and-reuse systems. We remain fully committed to delivering this state-of-the-art facility to the highest standards of quality, reliability, and performance, aligned with the Kingdom’s Vision and its focus on sustainable, technology-driven water infrastructure.” Va Tech Wabag is engaged in the business of the water treatment field. Its principal activities include design, supply, installation, construction, and operational management of drinking water, wastewater treatment, industrial water treatment, and desalination plants. The company reported standalone net profit surged 22.05% to Rs 70.3 crore on a 12.51% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 690 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip rose 0.28% to currently trade at Rs 1,283.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VaTechWabag_99536256518_36019.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JD Cables bags Rs 9 crore cable supply order in Bihar & Jharkhand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jd-cables-bags-rs-9-crore-cable-supply-order-in-bihar-jharkhand/1662179</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662179</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract entails the manufacture and supply of 831 km of cables across Bihar and Jharkhand, covering a wide range of products such as Aerial Bunched XLPE Cable, LT XLPE AB Cable, and Control Cable, including manufacturing, testing, and delivery.

The contract entails the manufacture and supply of 831 km of cables across Bihar and Jharkhand, covering a wide range of products such as Aerial Bunched XLPE Cable, LT XLPE AB Cable, and Control Cable, including manufacturing, testing, and delivery. JD Cables is engaged in the manufacturing of cables and conductors that cater to the power transmission and distribution sector. The company’s standalone net profit surged 384.1% to Rs 22.17 crore in FY25, driven by a 148.5% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 250.33 crore, compared with FY24. Shares of JD Cables rose 0.64% to Rs 206 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JDCablesLtd_48912059_95607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>