<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee nears four-week high against US dollar, weak equities cap advances]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-nears-four-week-high-against-us-dollar-weak-equities-cap-advances/1672351</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672351</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee saw modest gains today as sentiments continued to stay supported after announcement of a deal between India and the US to cut the highest US tariff rate imposed on any major economy.

Indian Rupee saw modest gains today as sentiments continued to stay supported after announcement of a deal between India and the US to cut the highest US tariff rate imposed on any major economy. INR currently quotes at 90.32, appreciating 13 paise on the day. It hit near 90 per US dollar mark, approaching around four-week high. INR held steady despite firm US dollar. The US dollar index edged up above 97 mark today, adding to recent gains as the index moved up further from four-year low. However, local stocks stay under stress. The key equity benchmarks ended with significant losses today, snapping a three-day rally as investors booked profit at elevated levels. The broader market also mirrored weak trends to trade under pressure.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee posts gain]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-posts-gain/1672330</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672330</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 90.4100 per Dollar on Thursday (05 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.5500 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper tests lows under $5.80 per pound]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-tests-lows-under-580-per-pound/1672327</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672327</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures stayed under pressure and overall price action was tight amid weak equities.

COMEX Copper futures stayed under pressure and overall price action was tight amid weak equities. In Asia, Shanghai Composite index fell 0.64%, giving up gains added in last session. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index added 0.14%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index stayed weak and shed 0.88%. European stocks fell with major indices losing around half a percent. US tech counters stayed under stress. The Nasdaq tumbled 1.5% to test one month low. COMEX Copper futures are currently trading at $5.84 per pound, down marginally on the day after testing lows under $5.80 per pound earlier. The metals segment is under stress as the US dollar index is at a two-week high of 97.70 right now, trading up marginally on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id51_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharti Airtel Q3 PAT drops 55% YoY to Rs 6,630 cr; ARPU jumps over 5% to Rs 259]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharti-airtel-q3-pat-drops-55-yoy-to-rs-6630-cr-arpu-jumps-over-5-to-rs-259/1672281</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672281</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company reported a 19.62% YoY revenue growth, supported by robust performance across India and Africa.

The company reported a 19.62% YoY revenue growth, supported by robust performance across India and Africa. Profit before exceptional items and tax (PBT) climbed 34.36% YoY to Rs 12,558.1 crore in Q3 FY26. Exceptional items of Rs 256.8 crore pertained to labour codes compliance. Consolidated EBITDA stood at Rs 31,144 crore in Q3 December 2025, registering the growth of 25.2% YoY with EBITDA margin of 57.7%. India revenues for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 39,226 crore, recording a YoY growth of 13.2% & QoQ growth of 1.4%. India Mobile revenue recorded a YoY increase of 9.1%, led by improved realizations and growing customer base. Average Revenue Per User (ARPU) for the quarter was at Rs 259, up 5.71% compared with Rs 245 in Q3 FY25, while revenue from the Africa region in Q3 FY26, reported in constant currency terms, jumped 24.7% YoY. During the quarter, the company added 1,147 towers and 16,338 mobile broadband base stations. In Q3 FY26, the Homes business reported 32.6%YoY revenue growth, supported by sustained improvement in customer acquisitions. During the quarter, the company added 1.2 million customers, to reach a total customer base of 13.1 million. In Q3 FY26, digital TV achieved revenues of Rs 755 crore. Total customer base stands at 15.4 million. Consolidated Net Debt to EBITDA ratio (annualized) stands at 1.47 times as compared to 1.98 times as on December 31, 2024. Gopal Vittal, executive vice chairman, said: “Q3 FY26 marked another strong quarter, with consolidated revenue of Rs 53,982 crore, a growth of 3.5% sequentially, underpinning our strategy of a diversified and resilient portfolio. India revenue including passive infrastructure services increased by 1.4% sequentially. Africa delivered yet another quarter of exceptional performance with constant currency revenue growth of 5.8%.One of the reasons for our stepped up performance in Africa is the deployment of our home grown digital stack that has sharpened our go to market excellence, the secret sauce of Airtel. India mobile recorded sequential growth of 1.9%, driven by our focus on winning with quality customers and a consistently improving portfolio mix. We added 4.4 million customers with an industry-leading ARPU of Rs 259. The Homes business maintained strong growth momentum, crossing a quarterly revenue run-rate of Rs 2,000 crore. We added 1.2 million customers, our highest ever quarterly additions. Our IPTV offering continues to see acceleration in net additions, strengthening our convergence strategy. Airtel Business recorded a revenue growth of 1.5% sequentially. Our digital services portfolio is seeing solid growth momentum supported by Airtel Cloud, Cybersecurity, Financial services, and IoT. “ Bharti Airtel is a global communications solutions provider with over 600 million customers in 15 countries across India and Africa. The counter declined 1.65% to settle at Rs 1992.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BhartiAirtel_49342333843_15542.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1672229</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672229</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,720, a premium of 77.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,642.80 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,720, a premium of 77.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,642.80 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index declined 133.20 points or 0.52% to 25,642.80. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 0.69% to 12.17. Trent, Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) and PB Fintech (Policy Bazaar) were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks pull back after three-day rally ahead of RBI policy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-pull-back-after-three-day-rally-ahead-of-rbi-policy/1672158</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672158</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks closed deep in the red on Tuesday, breaking a three-day winning streak as investors locked in profits at stretched valuations.

The key equity benchmarks closed deep in the red on Tuesday, breaking a three-day winning streak as investors locked in profits at stretched valuations. The rally, fuelled by optimism around the India-US trade deal, ran into selling as caution crept in ahead of the Reserve Bank of India’s monetary policy decision due on Friday. Weakness was not limited to frontline stocks, with the broader market also sliding under pressure. The Nifty 50 slipped below the 25,650 mark, dragged down by sharp losses in metal, consumer durables and auto stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex slumped 503.76 points or 0.60% to 83,313.93. The Nifty 50 index fell 133.20 points or 0.52% to 25,642.80. Over the past three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex advanced 3.20%, while the Nifty gained 3.29%. Bharti Airtel (down 1.66%), Reliance Industries (down 1.02%) and ICICI Bank (down 0.98%) dragged the Nifty lower. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.43% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.81%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,737 shares rose and 2,447 shares fell. A total of 164 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.69% to 12.17. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.54% to 6.659 compared with previous session close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.3375 compared with its close of 90.4700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 0.68% to Rs 152,000. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.18% to 97.83. The United States 10-year bond yield advanced 0.05% to 4.280. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement dropped 95 cents or 1.37% to $68.51 a barrel. Global Market: Most European stocks declined on Thursday as traders digested regional earnings and awaited interest rate decisions from the European Central Bank and the Bank of England, due later in the day. Most Asian indices ended lower as the tech sell-off on Wall Street gained momentum, with cryptocurrencies also falling. Bitcoin declined more than 2%, hovering below the $71,400 level. Wall Street slipped on Wednesday, with the technology rout deepening amid AI disruption worries, while investors digested Alphabet’s earnings and fresh labour market signals. The broader S&P 500 index slid 0.51% and closed at 6,882.72, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 260.31 points, or 0.53%, and settled at 49,501.30. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1.51% to end at 22,904.58. Meanwhile, ADP on Wednesday released its monthly look at private payroll growth for January, which showed an increase of just 22,000 on the month after a downwardly revised 37,000 increase in December. Alphabet reported earnings after the bell. The Google parent reported solid advertising revenue and reiterated plans for heavy investment in AI infrastructure, but investors remained cautious about the near-term impact on profitability. Qualcomm shares slid nearly 10% in post-market trading after the company forecast second-quarter revenue and profit below market estimates, citing a global memory chip shortage that is expected to dampen mobile phone sales and broader device demand. Stocks in Spotlight: PB Fintech spurted 7.80% after the company cancelled its board meeting scheduled for 5 February 2026, to consider a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP). Earlier, PB Fintech had informed exchanges that the board would meet to evaluate a potential fund raise to support inorganic growth through investments, acquisitions or partnerships in India and overseas. The cancellation signalled that the proposed capital raise will not be pursued for now, easing near-term dilution concerns and lifting investor sentiment. Indian Oil Corporation (IOCL) added 1.74% after the company’s standalone net profit surged 321.98% to Rs 12,125.86 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 2,873.53 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 5.43% YoY to Rs 2,04,424.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,93,899.5 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Metropolis Healthcare rose 4% after its consolidated profit after tax rose 33.7% YoY to Rs 42 crore in Q3FY26, compared with Rs 31 crore in Q3FY25. Revenue from operations increased 25.8% YoY to Rs 406 crore in Q3FY26, compared with Rs 323 crore in Q3FY25. Trent added 2.95% after the company reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hexaware Technologies slumped 7.25% after the company reported weaker profitability for the quarter, impacted by labour code-related costs. On a consolidated basis, reported profit declined 9.1% YoY to Rs 291.6 crore in Q4CY25, compared with Rs 320.7 crore in Q4CY24. On a sequential basis, reported profit fell 21.2% QoQ from Rs 369.9 crore in Q3CY25. The quarter was impacted by an expense of Rs 111.1 crore related to the implementation of new labour codes, which weighed on reported profitability. Revenue in rupee terms rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 3,478.2 crore in Q4CY25, compared with Rs 3,154.4 crore in Q4CY24. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue was marginally lower by 0.2% from Rs 3,483.6 crore in Q3CY25. JSW Cement added 6.37% after it has reported consolidated net profit of Rs 149.02 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 68.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.16% YoY to Rs 1621.22 crore in Q3 FY26. Keystone Realtors declined 4.32% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 77.57% to Rs 3.38 crore on a 42.64% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 266.17 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Timken India fell 1.87% after the company reported a 30.2% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 54.56 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 78.21 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Revenue from operations rose 14.1% to Rs 779.67 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 683.35 crore in Q3 FY25. Tata Power Company declined 1.89% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 25.1% to Rs 771.98 crore on 9.37% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 13,948.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Lloyds Engineering Works jumped 3.30% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 70.86% to Rs 61.03 crore on 2.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 272.45 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Parag Milk Foods slumped 8% after the company reported an 18% drop in consolidated profit to Rs 30 crore despite a 14% rise in revenue to Rs 1,013 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Automotive Axles fell 7.17% after the company’s standalone net profit declined 1.94% to Rs 38.81 crore on a 5.94% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 562.29 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. Uno Minda added 2.16% after the company reported an 18.13% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 300.48 crore on a 19.93% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 5,018.06 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Suzlon Energy declined 3.86% after the company’s consolidated net profit dropped 65.2% to Rs 445.28 crore despite a 9.38% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 4,228.18 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Quality Power Electrical Equipments rallied 6.35% after its consolidated net profit zoomed 220.69% to Rs 62.76 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 19.57 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RVNL Q3 PAT rises 4% YoY to Rs 323 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rvnl-q3-pat-rises-4-yoy-to-rs-323-crore/1672157</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672157</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 2.56% YoY to Rs 4,684.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 2.56% YoY to Rs 4,684.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a sequential basis, the company’s consolidated net profit rose 40.18%, while revenue declined 8.55%. Total expenses increased 2.17% YoY to Rs 4,577.43 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,480.08 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating expenses stood at Rs 4,354.14 crore (up 3.19% YoY), while employee benefit expenses were Rs 50.80 crore (up 0.27% YoY) during the period under review. Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 415.12 crore in Q3 FY26, up 0.53% from Rs 412.90 crore reported in Q3 FY25. On a nine-month basis, the company’s net profit declined 16.37% YoY to Rs 687.63 crore, while revenue from operations rose 1.63% year-on-year to Rs 13,716.21 crore in 9M FY26, compared with 9M FY25. Meanwhile, the company’s board has approved an interim dividend of Rs 1 per share (10% of the paid-up share capital) for the financial year 2025–26. The interim dividend shall be paid on or before Friday, 6 March 2026. The record date for ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders for the payment of the interim dividend for FY2025–26 is Wednesday, 11 February 2026. Rail Vikas Nigam is in the business of executing all types of railway projects, including new lines, doubling, gauge conversion, railway electrification, metro projects, workshops, major bridges, construction of cable-stayed bridges, institution buildings, etc. The counter slipped 1.42% to Rs 316.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailVikasNigam_10861613_26721.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Finance Corporation posts PAT of Rs 4,763.33 crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-finance-corporation-posts-pat-of-rs-476333-crore-in-q3/1672156</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672156</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Interest income rose by 12.2% to Rs 13,935.87 crore in the third quarter from Rs 12,417.22 crore recorded in the same period last year.

Interest income rose by 12.2% to Rs 13,935.87 crore in the third quarter from Rs 12,417.22 crore recorded in the same period last year. Total expenses for the period under review added up to Rs 8,703.36 crore, up 9.2% YoY. Finance cost in Q3 FY26 inched up by 7.9% YoY to Rs 8,329.4 crore. Impairment charge on financial instruments was Rs 5.15 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 74.48 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 5,957.34 crore, up by 17.3% from Rs 5,079.30 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. As on 31 December 2025, gross NPA and net NPA were at 1.64% and 0.26%, respectively. The company held 84% provisioning against Stage III assets at the end of December 2025 period. Disbursements increased by 15.4% to Rs 39,411 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 34,151 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s gross loan assets as on 31 December 2025 were Rs 5,69,627 crore as against Rs 5,03,824 crore as on 31 December 2024, up 13.1% YoY. As of 31 December 2025, the company's outstanding borrowings totaled Rs 4,77,308 crore. The majority of this debt is comprised of domestic bonds, which account for a 56% share, while rupee term loans (RTLs) and foreign currency borrowings each contribute 20% to the total. On a consolidated basis, the company has reported 5.8% increase in net profit to Rs 8,211.90 crore on a 8.6% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 29,094.81 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Power Finance Corporation, incorporated in 1986, is a non-banking financial company (NBFC) with infrastructure finance company status. It was set up by the Government of India (GoI) as a specialised development financial institution to fund projects in the domestic power sector. The GoI held a 56% stake in the company as on 31 December 2025. PFC provides loans for a range of power sector activities including generation, distribution, transmission, and plant renovation and maintenance, and other infrastructure projects.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerFinCorpn_2130951000_12068.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end sharply lower; PSU Bank index rallies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-sharply-lower-psu-bank-index-rallies/1672116</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672116</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with significant losses today, snapping a three-day rally as investors booked profit at elevated levels.

The key equity benchmarks ended with significant losses today, snapping a three-day rally as investors booked profit at elevated levels. The broader market also mirrored weak trends to trade under pressure. The Nifty settled below the 25,650 mark. The S&P BSE Sensex slumped 503.76 points or 0.60% to 83,313.93. The Nifty 50 index fell 133.20 points or 0.52% to 25,642.80. Over the past three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex advanced 3.20%, while the Nifty gained 3.29%. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.43% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.81%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.69% to 12.17. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 0.38%), the Nifty FMCG index (down 0.38%) and the Nifty Oil& Gas index (down 0.11%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Metal index (down 1.02%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (down 0.82%) and the Nifty Auto index (down 0.58%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel has started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.54% to 6.659 compared with previous session close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.3375 compared with its close of 90.4700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 0.68% to Rs 152,000. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.18% to 97.83. The United States 10-year bond yield advanced 0.05% to 4.280. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement dropped 95 cents or 1.37% to $68.51 a barrel. Global Market: European stocks traded lower on Thursday as traders digested regional earnings and awaited interest rate decisions from the European Central Bank and the Bank of England, due later in the day. Asian markets ended lower as the tech sell-off on Wall Street gained momentum, with cryptocurrencies also falling. Bitcoin declined more than 2%, hovering below the $71,400 level. In US market, the S&P 500 fell on Wednesday as the sell-off in technology stocks intensified. The broad market index slid 0.51% and closed at 6,882.72, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 260.31 points, or 0.53%, and settled at 49,501.30. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1.51% to end at 22,904.58. Meanwhile, ADP on Wednesday released its monthly look at private payroll growth for January, which showed an increase of just 22,000 on the month. That’s below the gain of 45,000 jobs that was forecasted and widely reported in the media.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index falls 1.02%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-falls-102/1672093</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672093</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index closed down 1.02% at 11921.2 today.

Nifty Metal index closed down 1.02% at 11921.2 today. The index has gained 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Vedanta Ltd dropped 4.74%, Hindustan Zinc Ltd shed 4.45% and Hindalco Industries Ltd slipped 3.06%. The Nifty Metal index has soared 41.00% over last one year compared to the 8.21% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty India Consumption index has dropped 0.59% and Nifty Auto index is down 0.58% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 0.52% to close at 25642.8 while the SENSEX has slid 0.60% to close at 83313.93 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/high-returns-picture-id534684138_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market snaps 3-days gaining streak; Nifty settles below 25,650 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-snaps-3-days-gaining-streak-nifty-settles-below-25650-mark/1672092</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672092</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with significant losses today, snapping a three-day rally as investors booked profit at elevated levels.

The key equity benchmarks ended with significant losses today, snapping a three-day rally as investors booked profit at elevated levels. The broader market also mirrored weak trends to trade under pressure. The Nifty settled below the 25,650 mark. Barring PSU bank stocks, all other sectoral indices on the NSE ended in the red. As per provisional closing data, the S&P BSE Sensex, slumped 503.76 points or 0.60% to 83,313.93. The Nifty 50 index fell 133.20 points or 0.52% to 25,642.80. Over the past three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex advanced 3.20%, while the Nifty gained 3.29%. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.43% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.81%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,574 shares rose and 2,483 shares fell. A total of 189 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.69% to 12.17. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel has started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index tanked 1.02% to 11,921.20. The index rallied 6.12% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Vedanta (down 4.77%), Hindustan Zinc (down 4.51%), Hindalco Industries (down 3.21%), National Aluminium Company (down 3.11%), NMDC Ltd (down 1.5%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 1.49%), Hindustan Copper (down 1.15%), Jindal Stainless (down 0.52%) declined. On the other hand, Welspun Corp (up 3.14%) ,Tata Steel (up 1.07%) and Jindal Steel (up 1.02%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Indian Oil Corporation (IOCL) added 1.79% after the company’s standalone net profit surged 321.98% to Rs 12,125.86 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 2,873.53 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 5.43% YoY to Rs 2,04,424.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,93,899.5 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Metropolis Healthcare rose 3.85% after its consolidated profit after tax rose 33.7% YoY to Rs 42 crore in Q3FY26, compared with Rs 31 crore in Q3FY25. Revenue from operations increased 25.8% YoY to Rs 406 crore in Q3FY26, compared with Rs 323 crore in Q3FY25. Trent added 2.99% after the company reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JSW Cement added 5.73% after it has reported consolidated net profit of Rs 149.02 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 68.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.16% YoY to Rs 1621.22 crore in Q3 FY26. Keystone Realtors declined 4.32% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 77.57% to Rs 3.38 crore on a 42.64% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 266.17 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Timken India fell 1.87% after the company reported a 30.2% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 54.56 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 78.21 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Revenue from operations rose 14.1% to Rs 779.67 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 683.35 crore in Q3 FY25. Tata Power Company declined 1.84% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 25.1% to Rs 771.98 crore on 9.37% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 13,948.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Lloyds Engineering Works jumped 4.52% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 70.86% to Rs 61.03 crore on 2.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 272.45 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Parag Milk Foods slumped 8.01% after the company reported an 18% drop in consolidated profit to Rs 30 crore despite a 14% rise in revenue to Rs 1,013 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Automotive Axles fell 7.17% after the company’s standalone net profit declined 1.94% to Rs 38.81 crore on a 5.94% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 562.29 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. Uno Minda added 2.16% after the company reported an 18.13% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 300.48 crore on a 19.93% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 5,018.06 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Suzlon Energy declined 3.98% after the company’s consolidated net profit dropped 65.2% to Rs 445.28 crore despite a 9.38% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 4,228.18 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Quality Power Electrical Equipments rallied 5.35% after its consolidated net profit zoomed 220.69% to Rs 62.76 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 19.57 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European stocks traded lower on Thursday as traders assessed regional earnings reports. Asian markets ended lower as the tech sell-off on Wall Street gained momentum, with cryptocurrencies also falling. Bitcoin declined more than 3%, hovering just above the $73,000 level, after falling below that mark earlier. The S&P 500 fell on Wednesday as the sell-off in technology stocks intensified. The broad market index slid 0.51% and closed at 6,882.72, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average added 260.31 points, or 0.53%, and settled at 49,501.30. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1.51% to end at 22,904.58. Meanwhile, ADP on Wednesday released its monthly look at private payroll growth for January, which showed an increase of just 22,000 on the month. That’s below the gain of 45,000 jobs that was forecasted and widely reported in the media.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id51_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ministry of Power says there is adequate availability of power, installed generation capacity stands at 513.730 GW]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ministry-of-power-says-there-is-adequate-availability-of-power-installed-generation-capacity-stands-at-513730-gw/1672066</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672066</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Power stated in a latest update that there is adequate availability of power in the country.

Ministry of Power stated in a latest update that there is adequate availability of power in the country. Present installed generation capacity of the country is 513.730 GW. Government of India has addressed the critical issue of power deficiency by adding 289.607 GW of fresh generation capacity since April, 2014 transforming the country from power deficit to power sufficient. Country has successfully met the all-time maximum demand of 250 GW last year. The gap between ‘Energy Supplied’ and ‘Energy Requirement’ has declined from 0.5% during FY 2022-23 to ‘NIL’ during the current year. Similarly, the Peak Demand not met has declined from 4.0% during 2022-23 to almost “NIL” during the current year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Oil Corp gains as Q3 PAT jumps 322% YoY to Rs 12,126 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-oil-corp-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-322-yoy-to-rs-12126-cr/1672037</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672037</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 5.43% YoY to Rs 2,04,424.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,93,899.5 crore reported in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 5.43% YoY to Rs 2,04,424.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,93,899.5 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax jumped 360.84% to Rs 15,991.56 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 3,470.08 crore reported in the same period a year ago. Domestic sales increased 4.98% to 26.015 million metric tons (MMT), while export sales fell 13.66% to 1.169 MMT in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. During the quarter, the refineries' throughput was 19.427 MMT (up 7.27% YoY), and the pipelines' throughput was 27.557 MMT (up 10.65% YoY). The company's revenue from petroleum products stood at Rs 217,890.01 crore (up 7.31% YoY), income from petrochemicals revenue was at Rs 6,935.77 crore (down 3.69% YoY), and revenue from gas stood at Rs 11,690.82 crore (up 6.01% YoY) during the period under review. The average gross refining margin (GRM) for the year April-December 2025 is $8.41 per bbl (April-December 2024: $3.69 per bbl). The core GRM, or the current price GRM for the year April–December 2025 after offsetting inventory loss/gain, comes to $9.86 per bbl. On the margins front, the operating margin improved to 7.23% in Q3 FY26, as compared to 1.49% in Q3 FY25. Similarly, net profit margin increased to 5.23%, up from 1.33% in the corresponding quarter of the previous fiscal year, indicating improved operational performance. Indian Oil Corporation is a Maharatna PSU under the Government of India, with operations spanning the entire hydrocarbon value chain, including refining, pipeline transportation, and marketing of petroleum products, as well as exploration and production, natural gas, and petrochemicals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IOCL_64283819279_12002.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Marksans Pharma gains after Q3 PAT rises 8% YoY to Rs 113 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/marksans-pharma-gains-after-q3-pat-rises-8-yoy-to-rs-113-crore/1672068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672068</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) declined 5.13% YoY to Rs 150.62 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) declined 5.13% YoY to Rs 150.62 crore during the quarter. EBITDA increased 23.2% YoY to Rs 160.7 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 130.5 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 21.3% in Q3 FY26 from 19.1% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, revenue from the US and North America stood at Rs 412.4 crore (up 16.9% YoY), while revenue from the UK and Europe stood at Rs 258.2 crore (up 0.2% YoY). Revenue from Australia and New Zealand stood at Rs 61.4 crore (up 30.1% YoY) in Q3 FY26. Revenue from the Rest of the World (RoW) declined 7.2% YoY to Rs 22.4 crore during the period under review. As of 31 December 2025, the company’s cash balance stood at Rs 824.2 crore. Research and development (R&D) expenditure for 9MFY26 was Rs 62 crore, accounting for 3% of consolidated revenue. Mark Saldanha, managing director of the company, said, “We delivered a stable and resilient performance in Q3 FY26, with operating revenue growing 10.6% YoY, supported by steady execution across key markets and improved seasonal demand. Margins expanded sequentially, driven by soft raw material costs, favorable currency movements, and an improving product mix, while EBITDA growth reflected operating leverage. During the quarter, we took measured steps to strengthen our global footprint through new subsidiaries in Europe and Canada, positioning the company for long-term growth in regulated markets. We remain disciplined, execution-focused, and committed to delivering sustainable growth and long-term shareholder value.” Marksans Pharma is primarily engaged in the business of research, manufacture, marketing and sale of pharmaceutical formulations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarksansPharma_64790772854_3285.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Metropolis Healthcare jumps as Q3 PAT climbs 33.7% YoY; 3:1 bonus announced]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/metropolis-healthcare-jumps-as-q3-pat-climbs-337-yoy-31-bonus-announced/1672032</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672032</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, profit after tax rose 33.7% YoY to Rs 42 crore in Q3FY26, compared with Rs 31 crore in Q3FY25.

On a consolidated basis, profit after tax rose 33.7% YoY to Rs 42 crore in Q3FY26, compared with Rs 31 crore in Q3FY25. Revenue from operations increased 25.8% YoY to Rs 406 crore in Q3FY26, compared with Rs 323 crore in Q3FY25. Profit before exceptional item and tax stood at Rs 66 crore in Q3FY26, up 56.5% YoY, while the quarter included an exceptional charge of Rs 9 crore related to the impact of the new labour code. EBITDA stood at Rs 95 crore in Q3FY26, up 32.4% YoY from Rs 72 crore in Q3FY25. EBITDA margin expanded to 23.4% in Q3FY26 from 22.2% in the year-ago quarter, reflecting an improvement of 120 bps. Total cost increased by 23.9% YoY, rising to Rs 311 crore in Q3FY26 from Rs 251 crore in Q3FY25. Depreciation rose 14.3% YoY to Rs 32 crore from Rs 28 crore a year ago. Finance costs increased 50.0% YoY to Rs 6 crore from Rs 4 crore. Operationally, patient volumes and test volumes grew 14% YoY and 13% YoY, respectively, supported by steady demand trends, deeper penetration in Tier II and Tier III markets, and a favourable mix shift toward complex and specialised testing. B2C revenues grew 19% YoY, while B2B revenues increased around 35% YoY, driven by network expansion and improved service levels. TruHealth and Specialty portfolios recorded growth of around 37% YoY and 34% YoY, respectively. Revenue per test and revenue per patient rose 11% YoY and 10% YoY. North India contributed 17% of revenue, while Tier III cities posted 16% revenue growth and accounted for 24% of overall revenues. Recent acquisitions including Core Diagnostics, Scientific Pathology in Agra, Dr. Ahuja’s Pathology and Imaging Center in Dehradun, and Ambika Pathology Laboratory in Kolhapur were integrated as planned. Meanwhile, the company's board approved a 3:1 bonus issue of equity shares. Metropolis Healthcare is India’s second-largest pathology laboratory chain, offering diagnostic testing and related services across a nationwide network, with a strong presence in specialised and preventive healthcare diagnostics.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MetropolisHealthcareLtd_18318340_65221.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pound slumps over half a percent against dollar; BoE interest rate decision in focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pound-slumps-over-half-a-percent-against-dollar-boe-interest-rate-decision-in-focus/1672031</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672031</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Pound slumped by over half a percent against dollar on Thursday to its lowest level in two weeks ahead of Bank of England’s interest rate decision.

Pound slumped by over half a percent against dollar on Thursday to its lowest level in two weeks ahead of Bank of England’s interest rate decision. Broad strength in the greenback is adding pressure on the GBP/USD counter that is currently quoting at $1.3584, down 0.57% on the day. Trump’s pick of hawkish Fed chair is also seen capping gains in the basket currencies. The counter is abating from 4-year high levels attained last week. The dollar index is holding at 97.70, up 0.20% on the day. Investors will now focus on US JOLTS Job Openings data for December and Fed speakers for further cues. ECB monetary policy announcement is also slated for later in the day. On the NSE, GBP/INR futures are down more than 1% at 122.75.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suzlon Energy slips after Q3 PAT tumbles 65% QoQ to Rs 445 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suzlon-energy-slips-after-q3-pat-tumbles-65-qoq-to-rs-445-cr/1672029</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672029</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue jumped 15.08% and 42.42% in Q3 FY26, respectively.

On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue jumped 15.08% and 42.42% in Q3 FY26, respectively. Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 44.83% YoY to Rs 566.75 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA stood at Rs 739 crore, registering the growth of 47.8% compared with Rs 500 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. EBITDA margin expanded 17.5% in Q3 FY26 as against 16.8% in Q3 FY25. Net volumes rose 38.03% to 617 MW in Q3 FY26 compared with 447 MW in Q3 FY25. Net cash stood at Rs 1,556 crore as of 31st December 2025 Girish Tanti, vice chairman, Suzlon Group, said, “We have initiated Suzlon 2.0, a comprehensive business transformation strategy aimed at establishing ourselves as a full-stack clean energy solutions conglomerate. This strategic shift broadens our scope across wind, solar, storage, and emerging clean energy technologies, enabling us to offer integrated solutions to our customers. Key growth priorities under Suzlon 2.0 include launching DevCo as a standalone FDRE project development vertical, transforming OMS into a digital-first platform, setting up smart manufacturing facilities, and capitalizing on global opportunities. Our recognition as one of the world's top 10 most sustainable companies underscores the success of this direction. As electric mobility gains traction, AI capacity expands, and industrial decarbonisation accelerates, the green transition is gaining significant momentum." JP Chalasani, chief executive officer, Suzlon Group, said, “Our closing order book of 6.4 GW stands higher than the opening orderbook for the quarter, despite the highest-ever deliveries in 30 years. This reflects the demand for our solutions and the effectiveness of our execution. Our balanced EPC strategy – targeting around 50% share of the EPC business by 2028 is progressing steadily, with the EPC share increasing from 20% to 27% this quarter. Our project development pipeline of 25+ GW is also complementing this strategy to augur growth for us. The success of this shift is enhancing revenue visibility, improving project control, and will continue to be a big growth driver for the group.” Rahul Jain, chief financial officer, Suzlon Group, said, “Q3 FY26 marks another milestone in Suzlon’s growth journey, with our highest-ever quarterly deliveries of 617 MW in India resulting in strong upswing across all financial metrics. Our performance in the first nine months — driven by 66% growth in deliveries, and a 77% increase in EBITDA — demonstrates the strength of our integrated business model and disciplined execution. Driven by strong fundamentals, rising C&I demand, and a market shift towards FDRE tenders, our accelerated execution ramp-up is translating into robust operating performance. As India’s wind sector accelerates, Suzlon’s end-to-end capabilities, competitive cost structure, and customer-centric approach position us uniquely to deliver sustainable value for all stakeholders.” The Suzlon Group is a leading global renewable energy solutions provider, with around 21.5 GW of wind energy capacity installed across 17 countries.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuzlonEnergy_13614358127_13872.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tube-investments-of-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1672028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672028</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hexaware Technologies Ltd, Websol Energy System Ltd, Ashapura Minechem Ltd and Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 February 2026.

Hexaware Technologies Ltd, Websol Energy System Ltd, Ashapura Minechem Ltd and Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 05 February 2026. Tube Investments of India Ltd lost 9.91% to Rs 2375.95 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 79725 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15970 shares in the past one month. Hexaware Technologies Ltd crashed 7.21% to Rs 640.5. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.94 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 47901 shares in the past one month. Websol Energy System Ltd tumbled 7.15% to Rs 68.01. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.88 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.32 lakh shares in the past one month. Ashapura Minechem Ltd corrected 6.96% to Rs 679.55. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 70235 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 58170 shares in the past one month. Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd fell 6.89% to Rs 15. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 66.86 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 49.85 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TubeInvestmentsofIndiaLtd_81529932771_40963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quality Power Electrical spurts as Q3 skyrockets 221% YoY to Rs 63 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quality-power-electrical-spurts-as-q3-skyrockets-221-yoy-to-rs-63-cr/1672023</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672023</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25.

Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax were at Rs 74.34 crore in Q3 FY26, zoomed 240.69% as against Rs 21.82 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA gained 222.35% to Rs 79.3 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 24.6 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The EBITDA margin reduced to 27.9% in Q3 FY26 as against 30.8% in Q3 FY25. Bharanidharan Pandyan, joint managing & whole-time director, said, “The global power transmission and grid equipment market continues to see steady investment driven by renewable integration, inter-regional transmission links and the need for grid stability. Utilities and large industrial networks are increasingly focusing on high-voltage and power quality solutions that improve network reliability and operating efficiency. In this environment, Quality Power continues to focus on technology-led offerings, export-oriented growth and deeper value chain participation across high-voltage systems.” The consolidated order book stands at approximately Rs 8,950 million, offering healthy revenue visibility across a diversified mix of product categories and geographies. The order pipeline reflects steady demand and supports execution-led growth over the near to medium term. On its Strategic Developments, the company completed the acquisition of a 50% equity stake in Sukrut Electric Company, resulting in a joint venture with Yash Highvoltage. Sukrut operates in the electrical equipment manufacturing space, including panels, instruments, and related assemblies, which is well aligned with the group’s core business segments. The partnership is expected to support product portfolio expansion, enable cross-supply opportunities, and enhance access to OEMs and utility customers. Post-acquisition, the company has nominated directors to Sukrut’s board to ensure governance oversight and operational alignment with group objectives. Meanwhile, the company’s manufacturing expansion and integration initiatives are progressing largely in line with planned schedules. The construction timeline for the Sangli plant has been advanced to June 2026 from the earlier target of September 2026. Capacity expansion at the Cochin facility has been completed and is now operational, while capacity enhancement at the Mehru Bhiwadi plant is progressing well, with full completion targeted by Q4 FY2026. In addition, the magnet-wire backward integration line remains under execution and is progressing in line with earlier guidance. Overall, these initiatives are aimed at reducing dependence on external suppliers for critical inputs, improving delivery timelines, and strengthening control over product quality and testing standards. On its outlook, demand for advanced transmission and grid-support equipment is expected to remain strong, supported by sustained investments in new transmission capacity and the upgradation of existing networks to enhance reliability and grid stability. Against this backdrop, the company continues to focus on disciplined project execution while expanding manufacturing capacity and strengthening its technology capabilities. These initiatives are likely to support sustainable growth over the medium term, although execution efficiency, input cost trends, and broader market conditions will remain key monitorables. Quality Power Electrical Equipments is engaged in the business of energy transition equipment and power technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/QualityPowerElectricalEquipmentsLtd_48177673_54766.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Secmark Consultancy Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/secmark-consultancy-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1672022</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672022</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[N K Industries Ltd, Sarla Performance Fibers Ltd, Hybrid Financial Services Ltd and Ravinder Heights Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 February 2026.

N K Industries Ltd, Sarla Performance Fibers Ltd, Hybrid Financial Services Ltd and Ravinder Heights Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 February 2026. Secmark Consultancy Ltd lost 19.99% to Rs 85.85 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 3776 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 501 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd crashed 18.85% to Rs 68.1. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1521 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 167 shares in the past one month. Sarla Performance Fibers Ltd tumbled 11.31% to Rs 82.01. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 30042 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8617 shares in the past one month. Hybrid Financial Services Ltd pared 9.81% to Rs 20.78. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3012 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4273 shares in the past one month. Ravinder Heights Ltd fell 9.40% to Rs 45.57. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 315 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1648 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SecMarkConsultancyLtd._72779962_75094.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>