<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:26:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper gains around 1%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-gains-around-1/1668209</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668209</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures jumped above $5.90 per pound amid supportive equities and a very weak undertone in the US dollar index.

COMEX Copper futures jumped above $5.90 per pound amid supportive equities and a very weak undertone in the US dollar index. Copper currently quotes up around 1% at $5.91 per pound. Broad undertone stays positive for the metal as China's industrial profits rose 0.6% in 2025 from a year earlier, snapping three consecutive years of declines. Meanwhile, in Asia, Shanghai Composite index added 0.27% while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index soared 2.58%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index edged up modestly as strength in Japanese Yen capped gains. European stocks saw lax moves ahead of US Fed monetary policy meeting. The US stocks closed mixed as strength in tech and energy boosted the Nasdaq and S&P 500 to new highs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ACC posts PAT of Rs 404 crore in Q3; clocks cement sales volume of 11.3 million tonnes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acc-posts-pat-of-rs-404-crore-in-q3-clocks-cement-sales-volume-of-113-million-tonnes/1668204</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668204</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operation rose by 8.6% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,483 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operation rose by 8.6% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,483 crore in Q3 FY26. Cement sales volumes added up to 11.3 million tonnes (up 15% YoY) and that of Ready-Mix Concrete aggregated to 0.97 million cubic metres (up 36% YoY). Total expenses increased 19% to Rs 6,114 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5,144 crore a year ago, led by higher power and fuel costs, freight and forwarding expenses, and depreciation charges. Operating EBITDA declined 37.3% to Rs 700 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,116 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 was 10.8% as against 18.7% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 460 crore in Q3 FY26, down by 68.9% from Rs 1,477 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Vinod Bahety, whole-time director & CEO, ACC, said: “We have sustained our growth momentum with another strong quarter, delivering our highest ever quarterly volumes. Higher trade and premium cement sales, alongside continued expansion in RMX, have supported better realizations than industry peers and strengthened our market position in core regions. We remain focused on resolving specific cost levers as part of our blueprint, particularly power costs, increasing the share of green power, fuel efficiency, improved WHRS and AFR utilization, and tighter logistics costs. The proposed integration into the ‘One Cement Platform’ is expected to accelerate both efficiency and growth, enabling deeper synergies across procurement, manufacturing and distribution once statutory approvals are completed. On the market side, our premium portfolio, led by ACC Gold, continues to deliver superior EBITDA margins, and the increasing share of Trade and Premium is expected to sustain realization advantages.” ACC Limited, a subsidiary of Ambuja Cements and part of the diversified Adani Group, is a building materials and concrete solutions company. The company operates 20 cement manufacturing sites, 117 ready-mix concrete plants, and a nationwide network of channel partners. The scrip had shed 0.18% to end at Rs 1685.50 on the BSE today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ACC_61889094494_6.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee suffers loss`]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-suffers-loss/1668203</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668203</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 92.0850 per Dollar on Wednesday (28 January 2026), versus its previous close of 91.6625 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India industrial output grows at two-year high of 7.8% in December]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-industrial-output-grows-at-two-year-high-of-78-in-december/1668188</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668188</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's industrial production growth accelerated to over a two-year high of 7.8 per cent in December 2025, driven by strong performances in mining, manufacturing and electricity, according to official data released on Wednesday.

India's industrial production growth accelerated to over a two-year high of 7.8 per cent in December 2025, driven by strong performances in mining, manufacturing and electricity, according to official data released on Wednesday. The factory output, measured in terms of the Index of Industrial Production (IIP), expanded by 3.7 per cent in December 2024. The growth rates of the three sectors, Mining, Manufacturing and Electricity for the month of December 2025 are 6.8 percent, 8.1 percent and 6.3 percent respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/female-manager-working-on-tablet-in-factory-picture-id52704_commodities.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD extends gains, tests four and half year high above 1.2000]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-extends-gains-tests-four-and-half-year-high-above-12000/1668162</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668162</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro bounced impressively today, breaking above 1.2000 mark to hit a four and half year high as markets eyed the latest comments from the US President Donald Trump.

Euro bounced impressively today, breaking above 1.2000 mark to hit a four and half year high as markets eyed the latest comments from the US President Donald Trump. Dollar sank yesterday as US Dollar index saw its biggest single-day drop since US President Donald Trump's tariff tantrum in April last year. The President believes that the currency has not excessively weakened. This is weighing on the currency markets heavily and the EUR/USD pair is currently quoting flat at 1.1995. Eurozone data was supportive for the single currency as German consumer confidence is set to improve in February, driven by strong rebounds in income expectations and willingness to buy. Survey data published jointly by NIQ/GfK and the Nuremberg Institute for Market Decisions showed that its forward-looking consumer climate indicator rose more-than-expected to -24.1 from -26.9 in January. On NSE, EUR/INR futures jumped to 110.44, up more than 1% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/INR futures seen fast approaching 110 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurinr-futures-seen-fast-approaching-110-mark/1668160</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668160</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures climbed 0.23% to end at 92.08.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures climbed 0.23% to end at 92.08. GBP/INR and EUR/INR also added over half a percent to settle at 126.36 and 109.94 respectively. Meanwhile, JPY/INR futures climbed over 1.5% to close at 60.44.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices rally for second session on India-EU FTA optimism]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-rally-for-second-session-on-india-eu-fta-optimism/1668148</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668148</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended higher for a second straight session on Wednesday, as improved risk appetite lifted sentiment.

The key equity benchmarks ended higher for a second straight session on Wednesday, as improved risk appetite lifted sentiment. Optimism around the conclusion of the India-EU free trade agreement and supportive global cues underpinned the rally. Meanwhile, a stable rupee and steady crude oil prices added comfort for investors. The Nifty closed above the 25,300 mark led by firmness in energy and metal shares. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 487.20 points, or 0.60%, to 82,344.68, while the Nifty 50 gained 167.35 points, or 0.66%, to settle at 25,342.75. Over the past two sessions, the Sensex has risen 0.99% and the Nifty has climbed 1.17%. Bharat Electronics (up 9.21%), Bajaj Finance (up 2.33%) and Reliance Industries (up 1.30%) boosted the Nifty today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 1.69%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.81%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,920 shares rose and 1,315 shares fell. A total of 145 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 6.41% to 13.53. Indian Politics: Ajit Pawar, NCP chief and Maharashtra’s Deputy Chief Minister, died in a plane crash near Baramati on Wednesday while travelling from Mumbai. Four others, including the pilot and his security personnel, were also killed. The small aircraft, a Learjet 45 operated by VSR, crashed during a landing attempt near Baramati airport about 45 minutes after takeoff, as Pawar was on his way to attend public meetings ahead of the local body polls. The 66-year-old leader was the nephew of Sharad Pawar and the cousin of Supriya Sule, both of whom were in Delhi and later arrived in Baramati. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.33% to 6.697 as compared with the previous close of 6.719. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.7800 compared with its close of 91.6850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 4.09% to Rs 164,150. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.43% to 96.16. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.62% to 4.249. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 41 cents or 0.61% to $67.16 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares declined on Wednesday as investors digested a wave of corporate earnings while cautiously awaiting the latest interest rate decision from the U.S. Federal Reserve on Wednesday. Most Asian indices ended higher, with strong gains in technology and AI-related shares. Overnight in the U.S., the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.91% to settle at 23,817.10, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average broke ranks, losing 408.99 points, or 0.83%, and settling at 49,003.4, while the S&P 500 added 0.41% to end at 6,978.60. The S&P 500 futures edged higher ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision and earnings reports from major tech companies. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy. New Listing: Shares of Shadowfax Technologies ended at Rs 109.90 on the BSE, a discount of 11.37% as compared with the issue price of Rs 124. The stock debuted at Rs 113 on the BSE, a discount of 8.87% over the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 119.55 and a low of 109. On the BSE, 33.05 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Stocks in Spotlight: TVS Motor Company rallied 4.72% after its standalone net profit jumped 52.04% to Rs 940.37 crore on 37.14% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 12,476.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. During the quarter under review, the company’s electric vehicle (EV) sales rose 40% year on year to a record 1.06 lakh units in the quarter ended December 2025, compared with 0.76 lakh units in the corresponding period last year. Vodafone Idea advanced 1.02% after the company’s consolidated net loss narrowed to Rs 5,286 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6,609 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue for the quarter stood at Rs 11,323 crore, up 1.9% YoY. Bharat Electronics (BEL) surged 8.90% after its standalone net profit jumped 20.81% to Rs 1,590.06 crore on 23.72% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,121.98 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company’s order book position stood at Rs 73,015 crore as of 1 January 2026. Maruti Suzuki India (MSIL) fell 2.39%. The car major reported a 4.08% YoY rise in net profit to Rs 3,879.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,726.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 29.2% YoY to Rs 47,534.4 crore, driven by a sharp recovery in the Indian car market led by the small car segment. Sunteck Realty rose 1.62%. The company reported a 33.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 56.84 crore on a 112.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 344.12 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Vishal Mega Mart tanked 4.12%. The company reported a 19.10% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 312.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 262.72 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 17.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 3,670.41 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Mahindra Logistics surged 15.82% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25 Mahindra Logistics surged 14.65% to Rs 337 after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25.. Motilal Oswal Financial Services surged 7.69% after the company reported a strong set of earnings for the quarter ended December 2025. The company’s profit after tax (PAT), including treasury income and other comprehensive income (OCI), jumped 58% year on year to Rs 721 crore in Q3 FY26, aided by healthy traction in its asset and private wealth management businesses. Total revenue improved 11% to Rs 1,497 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,345 crore in Q3 FY25. Bondada Engineering declined 3.58%. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 119.12% to Rs 54.19 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 24.73 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 89.40% year on year (YoY) to Rs 712.27 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concepts-picture-id519261614_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles in negative amid sustained foreign fund outflows]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-in-negative-amid-sustained-foreign-fund-outflows/1668146</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668146</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee pared initial gains and settled for the day in the negative territory, down 11 paise at 91.79 (provisional) against the US dollar, as the support from the retreating dollar index was negated by sustained foreign fund outflows.

The Indian rupee pared initial gains and settled for the day in the negative territory, down 11 paise at 91.79 (provisional) against the US dollar, as the support from the retreating dollar index was negated by sustained foreign fund outflows. Rupee opened higher as the US dollar index softened and a long-awaited trade breakthrough with Europe offered quiet reassurance. Domestic shares also rose notably on Wednesday, extending gains from the previous session after the announcement of a free trade agreement (FTA) between India and the European Union (EU). The benchmark BSE Sensex jumped 487.20 points, or 0.60 percent, to 82,344.68 while the broader NSE Nifty index closed up 167.35 points, or 0.66 percent, at 25,342.75. However, selling pressure from foreign funds and ongoing geopolitical tensions dented investors' sentiments. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 91.60 and touched an early high of 91.50, but pared the gains to touch an intra-day low of 91.83 against the greenback.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Life Q3 PAT rises 5% YoY to Rs 577 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-life-q3-pat-rises-5-yoy-to-rs-577-cr/1668147</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668147</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net premium income jumped 21.82% to Rs 30,245.32 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 24,827.54 crore in Q3 FY25.

Net premium income jumped 21.82% to Rs 30,245.32 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 24,827.54 crore in Q3 FY25. On a nine-month basis, the company’s standalone net profit increased 4.11% YoY to Rs 1,665.66 crore in 9M FY26, while net premium income rose 24.14% YoY to Rs 14,578.16 crore. Gross Written Premium (GWP) stood at Rs 73,350 crore in 9M FY26, marking a 20.28% increase from Rs 60,980 crore in 9M FY25. Of this, New Business Premium (NBP) rose 19% to Rs 31,330 crore, while Renewal Premium (RP) increased 21% to Rs 42,020 crore. During 9M FY26, Individual New Business Premium grew 14% YoY to Rs 22,550 crore, while Annualised Premium Equivalent (APE) increased 16% to Rs 18,520 crore. Value of New Business (VoNB) improved 17% YoY to Rs 5,040 crore in 9M FY26 from Rs 4,290 crore in 9M FY25. The New Business Margin expanded to 27.2% in 9M FY26 from 26.9% a year ago. Indian Embedded Value (IEV) jumped 18% YoY to Rs 80,130 crore in 9M FY26, while IEV per share rose to Rs 79,900 from Rs 68,000 in 9M FY25. Assets under Management (AuM) rose 16% YoY to Rs 5,11,710 crore in 9M FY26, while net worth increased to Rs 19,010 crore from Rs 16,590 crore a year earlier. The company maintained its leadership position in Individual Rated Premium at Rs 16,680 crore, with a 25.6% private market share in 9M FY26. In 9M FY26, growth in 13th-month persistency (based on premium considering regular premium/limited premium payment under the individual category) in 9M FY26 was 101 bps due to its focus on improving the quality of business and customer retention. Amit Jhingran, MD & CEO of SBI Life, stated, “The life insurance industry witnessed improved momentum during the third quarter, supported by recent regulatory measures and a gradual shift in customer preference towards higher sum assured products. The exemption of GST on individual policies contributed to improved affordability and aided demand during the quarter. During Q3, SBI Life reported an acceleration in growth compared to the first half of the financial year, resulting in improved performance for the nine-month period. The growth was primarily volume-driven, supported by an increase in the number of individual policies sold during the quarter. The Company’s product mix during 9MFY26 reflected evolving customer preferences, with contributions from ULIPs and participating and non-participating savings products. The protection segment recorded strong year-on-year growth in premium and sum assured during the period. The company reported stable value of new business (VNB) margins and steady VNB growth for the nine-month period. SBI Life remains focused on maintaining a balanced approach to growth and profitability. The company continues to strengthen its product portfolio, distribution capabilities and operational efficiencies, while adhering to prudent risk management practices. As one of the leading life insurance companies in India, SBI Life remains committed to increasing insurance penetration while delivering long-term value to all stakeholders." SBI Life's diverse range of products caters to individuals as well as group customers through protection, pension, savings and health solutions. The counter rose 0.79% to Rs 2,055 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SBILifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_43034021988_22045.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1668144</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668144</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,456, a premium of 113.25 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,342.75 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,456, a premium of 113.25 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,342.75 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index rose 167.35 points or 0.66% to 25,342.75. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 6.41% to 13.53. Bharat Electronics (BHEL), HDFC Bank and Maruti Suzuki India were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Base year for GDP estimates being revised to 2022-23 to reflect new economic structures]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/base-year-for-gdp-estimates-being-revised-to-2022-23-to-reflect-new-economic-structures/1668138</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668138</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Government noted in a latest update that base year for Gross Domestic Product or GDP estimates being revised to 2022-23 to reflect new economic structures.

Government noted in a latest update that base year for Gross Domestic Product or GDP estimates being revised to 2022-23 to reflect new economic structures. CPI base year is revised to 2024, updating the consumption basket and weights for both rural and urban households. IIP is being revised to 2022-23, aligned with the new national accounts series. Informal sector measurement has improved with quarterly QBUSE bulletins. District-level estimation has become a core design feature across PLFS, ASUSE, and NSS surveys. Public access to official data has been expanded through GoIStats, e-Sankhyiki, and the revamped Microdata Portal, supporting transparency and data reuse. Periodic base year updates ensure that GDP and other indices reflect the current economic structure and relative prices, which tend to evolve over time. The base year is revised periodically to better capture the structural changes happening in the economy by updating the methodology of compilation and incorporation of new data sources. Moreover, rebasing allows adoption of international best practices in methodology as recommended by bodies like the UN Statistical Commission. Aligning with updated global standards ensures that India’s statistics remain comparable and methodologically sound in light of new guidance on measuring the digital economy, supply-use tables, etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/growth-1152553__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 487 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,300 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-487-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25300-level/1668133</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668133</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with modest gains today, extending their rally for a second consecutive day, supported by optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA).

The key equity barometers ended with modest gains today, extending their rally for a second consecutive day, supported by optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA). Market sentiment was further bolstered by steady cues from the rupee and crude oil prices, ongoing Q3 earnings, and anticipation ahead of Larsen & Toubro’s Q3 results. The Nifty settled above the 25,300 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 487.20 points or 0.60% to 82,344.68. The Nifty 50 index added 167.35 points or 0.66% to 25,342.75. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 0.99% while the Nifty rose 1.17%. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 1.69%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.81%. The market breadth was strong. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 6.41% to 13.53. Among the sectoral indices, the Oil & Gas index (up 3.40%), the Nifty Metal index (up 2.34%) and the Nifty Media index (up 2.13%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty FMCG index (down 0.70%), the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.22%) and the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.20%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Indian Politics: Ajit Pawar, NCP chief and Maharashtra’s Deputy Chief Minister, died in a plane crash near Baramati on Wednesday while travelling from Mumbai. Four others, including the pilot and his security personnel, were also killed. The small aircraft, a Learjet 45 operated by VSR, reportedly crashed during a landing attempt near Baramati airport about 45 minutes after takeoff, as Pawar was on his way to attend public meetings ahead of the local body polls. Television visuals showed fire and wreckage at the site, while media reports said all five people on board died. The 66-year-old leader was the nephew of Sharad Pawar and the cousin of Supriya Sule, both of whom were in Delhi and later arrived in Baramati. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.33% to 6.697 as compared with the previous close of 6.719. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.7800 compared with its close of 91.6850 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 4.09% to Rs 164,150. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.43% to 96.16. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.62% to 4.249. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement declined 41 cents or 0.61% to $67.16 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares declined on Wednesday as investors digested a wave of corporate earnings while cautiously awaiting the latest interest rate decision from the U.S. Federal Reserve. Investors will also be keeping an eye on the U.S. earnings calendar on Wednesday, with Microsoft, Meta Platforms, and Tesla set to post their quarterly financial results after the closing bell. Apple will post its results on Thursday. Most Asian markets ended higher, with strong gains in technology and AI-related shares. Meanwhile, Australia saw its headline inflation come in at 3.6% for the last quarter of 2025, its highest level of inflation in six quarters. Overnight in the U.S., the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.91% to settle at 23,817.10, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average broke ranks, losing 408.99 points, or 0.83%, and settling at 49,003.4, while the S&P 500 added 0.41% to end at 6,978.60. The S&P 500 futures edged higher ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision and earnings reports from major tech companies. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty PSE Index gains 4.61%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-pse-index-gains-461/1668127</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668127</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty PSE index closed up 4.61% at 10179.5 today.

Nifty PSE index closed up 4.61% at 10179.5 today. The index has gained 5.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Oil India Ltd added 9.35%, Bharat Electronics Ltd jumped 8.91% and Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd rose 8.32%. The Nifty PSE index has soared 17.00% over last one year compared to the 10.39% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Energy index gained 4.18% and Nifty Metal index increased 2.34% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 witnessed a rise of 0.66% to close at 25342.75 while the SENSEX recorded a gain of 0.60% to close at 82344.68 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end with strong gains; broader mrkt outperform]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-with-strong-gains-broader-mrkt-outperform/1668126</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668126</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The equity benchmarks posted significant gains in a volatile trading session, extending their rally for a second consecutive day, supported by the optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA).

The equity benchmarks posted significant gains in a volatile trading session, extending their rally for a second consecutive day, supported by the optimism surrounding the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA). Investors tracked movements in the rupee and crude oil prices, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements, and geopolitical developments, while also tracking upcoming Q3 result of Larsen & Toubro. The Nifty ended above the 25,300 level. Oil & gas, metal and media shares advanced while FMCG and pharma shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 487.20 points or 0.60% to 82,344.68. The Nifty 50 index added 167.35 points or 0.66% to 25,342.75. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 0.99% while the Nifty rose 1.17%. The broader market outperformed frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 1.69%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 1.81%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,945 shares rose and 1,291 shares fell. A total of 144 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 6.93% to 13.45. New Listing: Shares of Shadowfax Technologies ended at Rs 109.90 on the BSE, representing a discount of 11.37% as compared with the issue price of Rs 124 The stock debuted at Rs 113 on the BSE, exhibiting a discount of 8.87% over the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 119.55 and a low of 109. On the BSE, over 33.05 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Indian Politics: Ajit Pawar, NCP chief and Maharashtra’s Deputy Chief Minister, died in a plane crash near Baramati on Wednesday while travelling from Mumbai. Four others, including the pilots and his security personnel, were also killed. The small aircraft, a Learjet 45 operated by VSR, reportedly crashed during a landing attempt near Baramati airport about 45 minutes after take-off, as Pawar was on his way to attend public meetings ahead of the local body polls. Television visuals showed fire and wreckage at the site, while media reports said all five people on board died. The 66-year-old leader was the nephew of Sharad Pawar and the cousin of Supriya Sule, both of whom were in Delhi and later arrived in Baramati. Stocks in Spotlight: TVS Motor Company rallied 4.72% after its standalone net profit jumped 52.04% to Rs 940.37 crore on 37.14% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 12,476.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. During the quarter under review, the company’s electric vehicle (EV) sales rose 40% year on year to a record 1.06 lakh units in the quarter ended December 2025, compared with 0.76 lakh units in the corresponding period last year. Vodafone Idea advanced 1.02% after the company’s consolidated net loss narrowed to Rs 5,286 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6,609 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue for the quarter stood at Rs 11,323 crore, up 1.9% YoY. Bharat Electronics (BEL) surged 8.90% after its standalone net profit jumped 20.81% to Rs 1,590.06 crore on 23.72% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,121.98 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company’s order book position stood at Rs 73,015 crore as of 1 January 2026. Maruti Suzuki India (MSIL) declined 2.39%. The company reported a 4.08% YoY rise in net profit to Rs 3,879.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,726.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 29.2% YoY to Rs 47,534.4 crore, driven by a sharp recovery in the Indian car market led by the small car segment. Sunteck Realty rose 1.62%. The company reported a 33.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 56.84 crore on a 112.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 344.12 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Vishal Mega Mart tanked 4.12%. The company reported a 19.10% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 312.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 262.72 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 17.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 3,670.41 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Mahindra Logistics surged 15.33% after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25 Mahindra Logistics surged 14.65% to Rs 337 after the company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 3.25 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 9.03 crore in Q3 FY25.. Motilal Oswal Financial Services surged 7.69% after the company reported a strong set of earnings for the quarter ended December 2025. The company’s profit after tax (PAT), including treasury income and other comprehensive income (OCI), jumped 58% year on year to Rs 721 crore in Q3 FY26, aided by healthy traction in its asset and private wealth management businesses. Total revenue improved 11% to Rs 1,497 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,345 crore in Q3 FY25. Bondada Engineering declined 3.58%. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 119.12% to Rs 54.19 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 24.73 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 89.40% year on year (YoY) to Rs 712.27 crore in Q3 FY26. Nesco shed 1.48%. The company reported a 4.82% YoY decline in net profit to Rs 104.64 crore in Q3 FY26, on a 20.03% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 247.92 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets declined on Wednesday as investors digested a wave of corporate earnings and remained cautious ahead of the U.S. Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision, due later in the day. Investors will also be keeping an eye on U.S. earnings calendar on Wednesday with Microsoft, Meta Platforms, and Tesla set to post their quarterly financial results after the closing bell. Apple will post its results on Thursday. Most Asian markets ended higher, with strong gains in technology and AI-related shares. Meanwhile, Australia saw its headline inflation come in at 3.6% for the last quarter of 2025, its highest level of inflation in six quarters. Overnight in the U.S., the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.91% to settle at 23,817.10, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average broke ranks, losing 408.99 points, or 0.83%, and settling at 49,003.4 while S&P 500 added 0.41% to end at 6,978.60. The S&P 500 futures edged higher ahead of the Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision and earnings reports from major tech companies. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki Q3 PAT jumps 4% YoY to Rs 3,879 crore despite margin pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maruti-suzuki-q3-pat-jumps-4-yoy-to-rs-3879-crore-despite-margin-pressure/1668117</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668117</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The auto major said that net profit was impacted by a one-time cost of Rs 593.9 crore on account of the new labour codes.

The auto major said that net profit was impacted by a one-time cost of Rs 593.9 crore on account of the new labour codes. Total revenue from operations rose 28.74% YoY to Rs 49,904.1 crore, driven by a sharp recovery in the Indian car market led by the small car segment. During the quarter, MSIL recorded its highest-ever quarterly domestic sales of 5,64,669 units, compared with 4,66,993 units a year earlier. The small car segment in the 18% GST bracket accounted for 68,328 units of incremental volumes. Total sales stood at a record 667,769 units, including exports of 103,100 units. Profit before tax (PBT) increased 4.0% YoY to Rs 4,917.3 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,726.0 crore a year ago. Operating EBITDA rose 10% YoY to Rs 5,571.7 crore; however, the EBITDA margin contracted to 11.7% from 13.8% in Q3 FY25 due to higher input and employee costs. Total expenses jumped 31.18% YoY to Rs 46,127.3 crore in Q3 FY26. Purchase of stock in trade was at Rs 5,853.9 crore (up 24.32% YoY), and employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 2,700.9 crore (up 51.18% YoY). During the quarter, Suzuki Motor Gujarat was amalgamated with Maruti Suzuki with effect from 1 December 2025. Accordingly, the financial statements have been restated from 1 April 2025, the appointed date under the scheme of amalgamation. Maruti Suzuki India is engaged in the manufacture, purchase, and sale of motor vehicles, components, and spare parts (automobiles). Shares of Maruti Suzuki India declined 2.43% to close at Rs 14,871 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Holdings jumps on strong Q3 earnings]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-holdings-jumps-on-strong-q3-earnings/1668115</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668115</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit attributable to owners rose 27.7% YoY to Rs 493.16 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 386.04 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit attributable to owners rose 27.7% YoY to Rs 493.16 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 386.04 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, net profit increased 11.4% from Rs 442.87 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations climbed 34.5% YoY to Rs 15,275.63 crore, up from Rs 11,359.16 crore a year earlier. Sequentially, revenue grew 5% over Rs 14,549.15 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 1,414.10 crore in Q3 FY26, up 38.5% versus Q3 FY25 and higher by 10.3% compared with Q2 FY26. Total expenditure increased 33.8% YoY to Rs 13,824.10 crore in Q3 FY26. Cost of materials consumed and cost of services rose 30.9% YoY to Rs 8,406.73 crore. Employee benefit expenses increased 33.3% YoY to Rs 1,205.88 crore. Finance costs climbed 18% YoY to Rs 650.83 crore. TVS Holdings (formerly Sundaram-Clayton) is a registered Core Investment Company ('CIC').

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SundaramClayton_31280805885_538.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AB Real Estate Q3 net loss widens to Rs 73 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ab-real-estate-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-73-crore/1668116</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668116</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income declined 56.70% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 90.33 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total income declined 56.70% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 90.33 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Total expenses fell 15.94% YoY to Rs 207.02 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of land, construction, and other related real estate development expenses stood at Rs 22.47 crore (down 81.24% YoY), while employee benefit expenses rose 37.66% YoY to Rs 59.61 crore during the period under review. During Q3 FY26, the company recorded a pre-tax loss before exceptional items of Rs 118.26 crore, compared with a pre-tax loss of Rs 37.64 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 22.29 crore in Q3 FY26. On the segmental front, revenue from real estate income stood at Rs 64.44 crore (down 64.68% YoY), while revenue from others stood at Rs 16.50 crore (down 10.85% YoY) during the period under review. On a nine-month basis, the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 114.06 crore in 9M FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 30.23 crore in 9M FY25, while revenue declined 60.34% YoY to Rs 321.77 crore in 9M FY26. Aditya Birla Real Estate (formerly known as Century Textiles and Industries) was established in 1897. It has a presence in the cotton textiles, pulp & paper, and real estate sectors. The counter rallied 3.24% to Rs 1,308.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CenturyTextiles_5324653027_107.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude oil near four-month high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-oil-near-four-month-high/1668106</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668106</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil prices held near a four-month high around $62 per barrel as traders weighed supply disruptions, geopolitical risks, and a weaker US dollar.

Oil prices held near a four-month high around $62 per barrel as traders weighed supply disruptions, geopolitical risks, and a weaker US dollar. US crude production was cut by up to 2 million barrels per day after a severe winter storm, tightening near-term supply, while President Trump’s renewed warnings toward Iran kept risk premiums elevated. Markets also monitored the growing US military presence in the Middle East, heightening concerns over potential disruptions to global flows. Adding support, API data showed US crude inventories fell by 0.25 million barrels last week, reinforcing signs of tightening fundamentals. Meanwhile, the US dollar slid to a four-year low, dropping under 96 boosting demand for dollar-denominated commodities and helping oil prices remain firm despite recent gains.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-on-the-north-sea-picture-id48328_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BEL spurts as Q3 PAT jumps 21% YoY to Rs 1,590 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bel-spurts-as-q3-pat-jumps-21-yoy-to-rs-1590-cr/1668105</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668105</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 2,147.68 crore in the third quarter of FY26, registering a growth of 22.43% on YoY basis.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 2,147.68 crore in the third quarter of FY26, registering a growth of 22.43% on YoY basis. Total expenses rose 22.02% YoY to Rs 5,133.82 crore in the December 2025 quarter. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 7,121.98 crore (up 23.72%) while employee benefits expenses were at Rs 813.68 crore (up 22.29% YoY) during the period under review. The company’s order book position stood at Rs 73,015 crore as of 1 January 2026. On consolidated basis, the company's net profit jumped 20.45% to Rs 1,579 crore on 23.96% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,153.85 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Electronics (BEL) is a Navratna PSU under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. It manufactures electronic products and systems for the army, navy, and air force.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatElectron_81586952923_2298.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CSB Bank Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/csb-bank-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1668104</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668104</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Radico Khaitan Ltd, Tata Consumer Products Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd and Cartrade Tech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 28 January 2026.

Radico Khaitan Ltd, Tata Consumer Products Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd and Cartrade Tech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 28 January 2026. CSB Bank Ltd tumbled 16.31% to Rs 418.15 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.59 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.07 lakh shares in the past one month. Radico Khaitan Ltd lost 6.03% to Rs 2746. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 17718 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 36361 shares in the past one month. Tata Consumer Products Ltd crashed 5.30% to Rs 1125. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2.85 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 36517 shares in the past one month. Home First Finance Company India Ltd dropped 4.97% to Rs 1190. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 33000 shares in the past one month. Cartrade Tech Ltd slipped 4.52% to Rs 2427.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.4 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16216 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CSBBankLtd_22037117_5525.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>