<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:27:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[The Wealth Company Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/the-wealth-company-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1662790</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662790</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Wealth Company Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026.

The Wealth Company Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Managers New Fund Managers The Wealth Company Flexi Cap Fund For Equity Ms. Aparna Shanker For Debt 1. Mr. Umesh Sharma 2. Mr. Varun Nanavati For Equity Ms. Aparna Shanker For Debt 1. Mr. Umesh Sharma 2. Mr. Neeraj Jain The Wealth Company Ethical Fund Ms. Aparna Shanker 1. Ms. Aparna Shanker 2. Ms. Saloni Kapadia The Wealth Company Multi Asset Allocation Fund 1. Ms. Aparna Shanker 2. Mr. Umesh Sharma 3. Mr. Varun Nanavati For Equity Ms. Aparna Shanker For Debt Mr. Umesh Sharma For Commodity Mr. Niranjan Das

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Weighted average lending rate stood at 8.71% at end Nov-25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/weighted-average-lending-rate-stood-at-871-at-end-nov-25/1662789</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662789</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India stated yesterday that the weighted average lending rate (WALR) on fresh rupee loans of SCBs stood at 8.71 per cent in November 2025 (8.61 per cent in October 2025).

Reserve Bank of India stated yesterday that the weighted average lending rate (WALR) on fresh rupee loans of SCBs stood at 8.71 per cent in November 2025 (8.61 per cent in October 2025). The WALR on outstanding rupee loans of SCBs declined to 9.21 per cent in November 2025 from 9.24 per cent in October 2025. RBI noted that 1-Year median Marginal Cost of Funds based Lending Rate (MCLR) of SCBs moderated to 8.45 per cent in December 2025 from 8.50 per cent in November 2025. Meanwhile, the he weighted average domestic term deposit rate (WADTDR) on fresh rupee term deposits of SCBs stood at 5.59 per cent in November 2025 (5.57 per cent in October 2025).The WADTDR on outstanding rupee term deposits of SCBs declined to 6.73 per cent in November 2025 from 6.78 per cent in October 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growth-on-coin-pile-business-conceptual-picture-id489_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade with minor gains; auto shares accelerate]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-with-minor-gains-auto-shares-accelerate/1662787</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662787</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices traded with decent gains in mid-morning trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark.

The key domestic indices traded with decent gains in mid-morning trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark. Market sentiment remained positive amid optimism over monthly auto sales data, even as the New Year holiday kept volumes light. Auto shares jumped on the back of monthly sales announcements, extending gains for the third consecutive trading session. At 11:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 104.08 points or 0.12% to 85,326.44. The Nifty 50 index climbed 38.25 points or 0.15% to 26,167.85. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.14% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 0.03%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,086 shares rose and 1,633 shares fell. A total of 228 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index added 0.77% to 28,405.65. The index jumped 2.95% for the three consecutive trading sessions. Ashok Leyland (up 2.6%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 1.34%), TVS Motor Company (up 1.24%), Tube Investments of India (up 0.87%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 0.38%), Bharat Forge (up 0.34%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 0.31%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 0.24%), Uno Minda (up 0.11%) and Bajaj Auto (up 0.07%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: VST Tillers Tractors rose 0.04%. The company reported an 29.77% increase in total sales to 4,376 units in December 2025, up from 3,372 units sold in December 2024. Escorts Kubota advanced 1.54% after the company’s agri-machinery business division sold 7,577 tractors in December 2025, registering a growth of 38.5% compared with 5,472 tractors sold in December 2024. Kalpataru Projects International (KPIL) shed 0.74%. The company along with its joint venture, has secured new orders worth approximately Rs 719 crore. Global Market: Both the US and major Asian markets will remain shut today on account of the New Year’s Day holiday. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back on Wednesday, though the index still closed out a bumper year. The broad market S&P 500 dipped 0.74% and closed at 6,845.50, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and ended at 23,241.99. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 303.77 points, or 0.63%, and settled at 48,063.29.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NCC bags orders worth Rs 1,237-cr in December]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ncc-bags-orders-worth-rs-1237-cr-in-december/1662786</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662786</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the buildings division accounted for orders worth Rs 704.67 crore, while the transportation division received orders valued at Rs 532.57 crore.

According to an exchange filing, the buildings division accounted for orders worth Rs 704.67 crore, while the transportation division received orders valued at Rs 532.57 crore. The company clarified that the orders were received in the normal course of business and do not include any internal orders. It added that the promoters, promoter group and group companies have no interest in the entities awarding the projects, and the contracts do not qualify as related party transactions. NCC is engaged in the infrastructure sector, primarily in the construction of industrial and commercial buildings, housing projects, roads, bridges and flyovers, water supply and environment projects, mining, power transmission lines, irrigation and hydrothermal power projects, etc. The company reported a 5.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 154.70 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 162.96 crore recorded in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations also declined 12.6% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 4,543.01 crore in Q2 FY26. The counter rose 0.84% to Rs 161.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NCC_71121013216_2598.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1662785</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662785</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026.

SBI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) SBI ELSS Tax Saver Fund Mr. Dinesh Balachandran Mr. Milind Agrawal SBI Dividend Yield Fund Mr. Rohit Shimpi Mr. Nidhi Chawla

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SSWL gains after reporting 22% YoY rise in net turnover for December 2025]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sswl-gains-after-reporting-22-yoy-rise-in-net-turnover-for-december-2025/1662784</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662784</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s gross turnover rose 15.98% to Rs 515.87 crore in December 2025, up from Rs 444.81 crore posted in the same month last year.

The company’s gross turnover rose 15.98% to Rs 515.87 crore in December 2025, up from Rs 444.81 crore posted in the same month last year. In value terms, the aluminium products segment recorded a robust 42% YoY growth, while the tractor segment grew by 59% YoY. However, the truck segment jumped 14% YoY, the 2- and 3-wheeler segment gained 60% YoY, the passenger car–steel segment dropped 22% YoY, and the overall exports segment plunged 20% YoY in December 2025. In volume terms, the aluminium products segment surged 38% YoY, the tractor segment increased 37% YoY, and the truck segment grew 57% YoY. Meanwhile, the 2- and 3-wheeler segment jumped 60% YoY, the passenger car–steel segment declined 17% YoY, and the overall exports segment tumbled 54% YoY during the review period. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) is engaged in the manufacturing of steel wheel rims catering to different segments of the automobile industry. The firm operates in the automotive wheel segment. Its geographical segments include India and overseas. The company reported a 23% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 35.52 crore on a 9.6% rise in net sales to Rs 1,200.57 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SteelStrWheel_50831874606_1338.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Commercial banks remain in sound health, NPA ratio at multi-decade low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/commercial-banks-remain-in-sound-health-npa-ratio-at-multi-decade-low/1662783</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662783</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic financial system remains resilient, backed by strong capital positions, ample liquidity, easy financial conditions and low market volatility, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) said in its December 2025 Financial Stability Report (FSR).

The domestic financial system remains resilient, backed by strong capital positions, ample liquidity, easy financial conditions and low market volatility, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) said in its December 2025 Financial Stability Report (FSR). The country's scheduled commercial banks remain in sound health, with strong capital and liquidity buffers, improved asset quality and robust profitability, the report said. Stress tests showed banks would be able to withstand losses under hypothetical adverse scenarios while maintaining capital well above regulatory minimums. The central bank noted that under a baseline scenario, the gross non-performing assets (GNPA) ratio of banks is expected to improve further to 1.9 per cent by March 2027. As of September 2025, the GNPA ratio stood at 2.1 per cent, a multi-decade low, according to the half-yearly report.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Blue Dart Express Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-blue-dart-express-ltd-counter/1662780</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662780</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[V-Guard Industries Ltd, Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd, Adani Total Gas Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 01 January 2026.

V-Guard Industries Ltd, Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd, Adani Total Gas Ltd, Godfrey Phillips India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 01 January 2026. Blue Dart Express Ltd recorded volume of 24092 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 23.82 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1011 shares. The stock gained 4.62% to Rs.5,776.50. Volumes stood at 502 shares in the last session. V-Guard Industries Ltd clocked volume of 1.2 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 12.85 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9329 shares. The stock gained 2.52% to Rs.335.20. Volumes stood at 12459 shares in the last session. Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd registered volume of 4.62 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 12.07 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 38282 shares. The stock rose 0.53% to Rs.884.45. Volumes stood at 44994 shares in the last session. Adani Total Gas Ltd saw volume of 6.11 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.04 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 76060 shares. The stock increased 7.23% to Rs.608.00. Volumes stood at 56469 shares in the last session. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd witnessed volume of 1.02 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 6.35 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 16129 shares. The stock dropped 9.65% to Rs.2,494.95. Volumes stood at 28534 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BlueDartExp_90292738126_4177.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's mobile subscribers base sees mild rise in Nov-25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-mobile-subscribers-base-sees-mild-rise-in-nov-25/1662778</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662778</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Offical data showed that India's wireless (mobile) subscribers increased from 1171.87 million at the end of October 2025 to 1173.88 million at the end of November 2025 thereby registering a monthly growth rate of 0.17%.

Offical data showed that India's wireless (mobile) subscribers increased from 1171.87 million at the end of October 2025 to 1173.88 million at the end of November 2025 thereby registering a monthly growth rate of 0.17%. Wireless (mobile) subscription in urban areas increased from 639.99 million at the end of October 2025 to 641.83 million at the end of November 2025 and wireless (mobile) subscription in rural areas increased from 531.88 million to 532.06 million during the same period. The monthly growth rates of urban and rural wireless (mobile) subscription were 0.29% and 0.03% respectively. The wireless tele-density in India decreased slightly from 83.47% at the end of October 2025 to 83.46% at the end of November 2025. The urban wireless tele-density increased from 126.50% at the end of October 2025 to 127.19% at the end of November 2025. The rural wireless tele-density decreased from 59.17% to 58.94% during the same period. The share of urban and rural wireless subscribers in the total number of wireless subscribers was 54.76% and 45.24% respectively, at the end of November 2025. The number of wireless (Mobile + Fixed Wireless Access) subscribers increased from 1184.62 million at the end of October 2025 to 1187.48 million at the end of November 2025, thereby registering a monthly growth rate of 0.24%. Total wireless subscription in urban areas increased from 647.82 million on 31st October 2025 to 650.22 million on 30th November 2025. The subscription in rural areas also increased from 536.80 million to 537.26 million during the same period. The monthly growth rate of urban and rural wireless subscriptions was 0.37% and 0.09% respectively. The number of wireline subscribers increased from 46.75 million at the end of October 2025 to 47.05 million at the end of November 2025. The net increase in the wireline subscriber base was 0.30 million with a monthly growth rate of 0.63%. The overall wireline tele-density in India increased from 3.29% at the end of October 2025 to 3.31% at the end of November 2025. Urban and rural wireline tele-density were 8.20% and 0.56% respectively, as on 30th November 2025. The share of urban subscribers and rural subscribers in total wireline subscribers were 89.14% and 10.86% respectively, at the end of November 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/mobile-phone-android-apps-phone-163065_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee slides amid cautious undertone in equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-slides-amid-cautious-undertone-in-equities/1662774</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662774</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee added to recent losses today.

Indian rupee added to recent losses today. INR ended the last year on a tepid note, losing around 6% this year and is not far from record lows against the US dollar. Overall mood is cautious as trades in global fx markets around year-end though there is a modest uptick in the US dollar index. INR has slipped 7 paise at 89.95 per US dollar. Local equities are quoting on a very flat note, starting the new year in a cautious manner.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growing-from-coin-jar-picture-id622446130_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades near 26,150 mark; FMCG shares drop]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-near-26150-mark-fmcg-shares-drop/1662772</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662772</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade as the Nifty traded near the 26,150 mark.

The key equity indices traded with minor gains in early trade as the Nifty traded near the 26,150 mark. Trading activity remained range-bound amid the absence of strong global economic triggers, the New Year holiday and the expiry of the weekly Sensex derivatives contract. FMCG shares declined after advancing in the past trading session. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 28.29 points or 0.03% to 85,248.89. The Nifty 50 index 9.90 points or 0.08% to 26,148.55. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.26% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index dropped 0.27%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,876 shares rose and 1,610 shares fell. A total of 211 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index declined 2.17% to 54,274.60. The index jumped 0.80% in the past trading session. ITC (down 5.37%), United Spirits (down 0.8%), Radico Khaitan (down 0.7%), Tata Consumer Products (down 0.64%), Emami (down 0.58%), Hindustan Unilever (down 0.5%), Dabur India (down 0.41%), Varun Beverages (down 0.33%), Marico (down 0.28%) and United Breweries (down 0.25%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Kalpataru Projects International (KPIL) declined 1.19%. The company along with its joint venture, has secured new orders worth approximately Rs 719 crore. Blue Dart Express spurted 5.15% after tax authorities largely dropped a Rs 420.78 crore GST demand on its subsidiary Blue Dart Aviation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VST Tillers reports 30% YoY sales growth in December 2025]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vst-tillers-reports-30-yoy-sales-growth-in-december-2025/1662771</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662771</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s power tiller sales grew by 26.10% to 3,792 units in December 2025, compared to 3,007 units in the same month last year.

The company’s power tiller sales grew by 26.10% to 3,792 units in December 2025, compared to 3,007 units in the same month last year. Tractor sales also grew 60% to 584 units in December 2025, up from 365 units sold in December 2024. VST Tillers Tractors is engaged in the manufacturing of power tillers and diesel engines. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 44.24% to Rs 24.98 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 44.80 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 11.19% year-on-year to Rs 315.15 crore for the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of VST Tillers shed 0.31% to Rs 6,244.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VSTTillTract_79364939960_2531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Escorts Kubota gains after December 2025 sales rise 39% YoY to 7,577 units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/escorts-kubota-gains-after-december-2025-sales-rise-39-yoy-to-7577-units/1662770</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662770</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic tractor sales rose 36.1% to 6,828 units in December 2025, compared with 5,016 units sold in December 2024.

Domestic tractor sales rose 36.1% to 6,828 units in December 2025, compared with 5,016 units sold in December 2024. Exports jumped 64.3% to 749 units in December 2025, as against 456 units in December 2024. On a quarterly basis, the company’s agri-machinery business division sold 36,955 tractors in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of 13.5% compared with 32,556 tractors sold in Q3 FY25. Meanwhile, the company’s construction equipment business division sold 812 machines in December 2025, registering a decline of 7% from 873 machines sold in December 2024. On a quarterly basis, the construction equipment business division sold 1,716 machines in Q3 FY26, registering a decline of 13.7% from 1,989 machines sold in Q3 FY25. Escorts Kubota is primarily engaged in the business of manufacturing agricultural tractors, engines for agricultural tractors, construction, earthmoving, and material handling equipment; round and flat tubes; heating elements; and double-acting hydraulics. Escorts Kubota’s consolidated net profit declined 1.87% to Rs 318.16 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 324.23 crore posted in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 22.58% year on year (YoY) to Rs 2,791.56 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Escorts_12276934110_161.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Timex Group slips after OFS concludes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/timex-group-slips-after-ofs-concludes/1662766</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662766</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Promoter Timex Group Luxury Watches BV offered a base lot of 45.09 lakh shares, representing 4.47% of the company’s equity.

Promoter Timex Group Luxury Watches BV offered a base lot of 45.09 lakh shares, representing 4.47% of the company’s equity. The offer included an oversubscription option for an additional 4.47%, taking the total potential divestment to 90.18 lakh shares, or 8.93%. The floor price was set at Rs 275 per share, a discount of 21.82% to the stock’s closing price of Rs 351.75 on 26 December 2025. The OFS opened on December 29 for non-retail investors. Retail investors participated on December 30, along with non-retail bidders carrying forward unallotted bids. The offer was conducted through a special window on the BSE and NSE during market hours. On Day 1 (T-day), as of 15:30 IST, the OFS received subscription for 3,80,41,244 shares. It was subscribed 468.68% on the total non-retail offer size of 81,16,650 shares. On Day 2 (T+1 day), the OFS received subscription for 45,65,547 shares. It was subscribed 50.62% on the total offer size of 90,18,500 shares. As of September 2025, the promoter held a 59.93% stake in Timex Group India. Timex Group India designs, manufactures, and markets innovative timepieces and is part of Timex Group, a privately held company headquartered in Middlebury, Connecticut, with multiple operating units and over 2,000 employees worldwide. In India, TGIL manages a portfolio of brands including Timex, Versace, Guess, Gc, Philipp Plein, Plein Sport, Ferragamo, Nautica, Ted Baker, adidas, and UCB. It retails via more than 5,000 offline trade stores and key online marketplaces, along with over 40 exclusive franchise stores under the Just Watches and Timex World banners. On a standalone basis, net profit of Timex Group India rose 69.74% to Rs 30.23 crore while net sales rose 39.98% to Rs 243.67 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimexGroup_79144198960_3143.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kalpataru Projects bags new orders worth Rs 719 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kalpataru-projects-bags-new-orders-worth-rs-719-crore/1662764</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662764</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The new orders include a contract for an elevated metro rail project in Thane, Maharashtra.

The new orders include a contract for an elevated metro rail project in Thane, Maharashtra. Manish Mohnot, MD & CEO, KPIL, said, “We are delighted with the new order win in our Urban Infrastructure business. The elevated metro rail order in Thane has strengthen our presence in the growing urban transportation EPC business, reinforcing our confidence in the growth potential of our Urban Infra business in India. Our strong order intake, diversified order book and robust execution places us favourably to deliver on our growth targets in the coming quarters.” On a consolidated basis, net profit of Kalpataru Projects International rose 91.27% to Rs 240.05 crore while net sales rose 32.43% to Rs 6528.57 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. KPIL is one of the largest specialized EPC companies engaged in power transmission & distribution, buildings & factories, water supply & irrigation, railways, oil & gas pipelines, urban mobility (flyovers & metro rail), highways and airports. KPIL is currently executing projects in over 30 countries and has a global footprint in 75 countries. Shares of Kalpataru Projects International rose 0.09% to Rs 1,202.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KalpataruPower_75778021409_4518.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Blue Dart Express spurts as GST demand on subsidiary largely dropped]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/blue-dart-express-spurts-as-gst-demand-on-subsidiary-largely-dropped/1662744</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662744</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a regulatory filing, the company said the adjudicating authority, through an order dated 30 December 2025, set aside about Rs 420.78 crore of the total proposed demand for the period April 2021 to March 2023.

In a regulatory filing, the company said the adjudicating authority, through an order dated 30 December 2025, set aside about Rs 420.78 crore of the total proposed demand for the period April 2021 to March 2023. The demand had primarily related to issues concerning determination of place of supply and availment of input tax credit under the CGST, TNGST and IGST laws. The authority has confirmed a residual GST demand of Rs 64.98 lakh, along with applicable interest of Rs 41.71 lakh and a penalty of Rs 6.49 lakh. The company said the tax and interest have been voluntarily accepted and discharged by the subsidiary to avoid prolonged litigation. Blue Dart Express added that the final order is not expected to have any material impact on the financials, operations, or business activities of the company or its subsidiary. Blue Dart Express is South Asia's premier express air and integrated transportation & distribution company. The company’s standalone net profit climbed 30.8% to Rs 79.50 crore on 7% increase in net sales to Rs 1,549.33 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BlueDartExp_90292738126_4177.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NBCC (India) wins Rs 220-cr construction contracts from Canara Bank, Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nbcc-india-wins-rs-220-cr-construction-contracts-from-canara-bank-navodaya-vidyalaya-samiti/1662742</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662742</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company will undertake the planning, designing, and execution of Canara Bank’s Head Office Annex Building in Bengaluru, valued at Rs 163.12 crore.

The company will undertake the planning, designing, and execution of Canara Bank’s Head Office Annex Building in Bengaluru, valued at Rs 163.12 crore. In addition, NBCC has received orders for the construction of a boys’ dormitory with four warden residences at JNV Jalna, Maharashtra, worth Rs 9.01 crore, and the permanent campus at JNV Medchal, Telangana, valued at Rs 48.18 crore. NBCC (India) is in business and operates in three major segments, namely project management consultancy, real estate, and engineering procurement & construction. As on September 2025, the Government of India held 61.75% in the company. The company's consolidated net profit advanced 25.21% to Rs 156.68 crore on an 18.99% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,910.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of NBCC (India) rose 0.29% to Rs 122.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NBCC_1807915630_13166.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge higher in early trade; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-strong/1662738</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662738</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices opened with slight gains in early trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark.

The key equity indices opened with slight gains in early trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark. Market activity is expected to stay range-bound in the absence of strong global economic triggers and due to the New Year holiday. Trading may witness volatility due to the expiry of the weekly Sensex derivatives contract. Auto stocks will be in focus as companies announce their monthly sales numbers. Media, auto and IT shares rally while FMCG, pharma and PSU Bank shares declined. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 98.47 points or 0.12% to 85,319.07. The Nifty 50 index added 36.90 points or 0.15% to 26,167.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.07%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 1,706 shares rose and 1,046 shares fell. A total of 139 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,492.04 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 6,542.14 crore in the Indian equity market on 31 December 2025, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: NBCC (India) advanced 1.15% after the company said it has secured multiple construction orders aggregating Rs 383 crore from Canara Bank and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Titagarh Rail Systems rose 0.83%. The company said its board has approved a business transfer agreement to transfer its Shipbuilding, Marine and Systems (SMS) business to its arm, Titagarh Naval Systems, in a transaction valued at Rs 114.9 crore, which will be executed in accordance with the terms of the pact. Dr Reddy’s Laboratories shed 0.87%. The company said its Switzerland-based arm has received a complete response letter (CRL) from the US Food and Drug Administration for the biologics license application of its proposed biosimilar AVT03. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.24% to 6.592 as compared with the previous close of 6.576. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9900 compared with its close of 89.8800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement shed 0.04% to Rs 135,390. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 98.28. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.65% to 4.177. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement declined 49 cents or 0.80% to $60.84 a barrel. Global Markets: Both the US and major Asian markets will remain shut today on account of the New Year’s Day holiday. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back on Wednesday, though the index still closed out a bumper year. The broad market S&P 500 dipped 0.74% and closed at 6,845.50, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and ended at 23,241.99. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 303.77 points, or 0.63%, and settled at 48,063.29.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Time Technoplast bags Rs 51-cr supply order from HPCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/time-technoplast-bags-rs-51-cr-supply-order-from-hpcl/1662737</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662737</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order is for supply of rigid polymer packaging products, namely Conipack pails, to be delivered as per HPCL’s schedule.

The order is for supply of rigid polymer packaging products, namely Conipack pails, to be delivered as per HPCL’s schedule. Payments under the contract will be secured through an appropriate financial instrument. The supplies are to be dispatched in line with the delivery schedule over a period of up to two years. The company clarified that the order does not involve any promoter or promoter group interest and does not fall under related party transactions. Time Technoplast is a global manufacturer of polymer products with operations across multiple countries. Its portfolio spans industrial packaging solutions, lifestyle products, automotive components, infrastructure / construction related products, material handling solutions & composite cylinders. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Time Technoplast rose 17.04% to Rs 115.44 crore while net sales rose 10.3% to Rs 1,511.11 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Time Technoplast rose 0.49% to Rs 189 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimeTechnoplast_46114320009_27753.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd Spurts 14.78%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/optiemus-infracom-ltd-spurts-1478/1662735</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662735</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd gained 14.78% today to trade at Rs 580.

Optiemus Infracom Ltd gained 14.78% today to trade at Rs 580. The BSE Telecommunication index is up 0.53% to quote at 3139.3. The index is up 2.02 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, ADC India Communications Ltd increased 1.89% and Vodafone Idea Ltd added 1.86% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 9.36 % over last one year compared to the 8.6% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Optiemus Infracom Ltd has added 3.39% over last one month compared to 2.02% gain in BSE Telecommunication index and 0.14% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 9857 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 793 on 06 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 01 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OptiemusInfra_38144306001_5004.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>