<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:28:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Fiscal deficit at 54.5% of FY26 budget estimates]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fiscal-deficit-at-545-of-fy26-budget-estimates/1669331</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669331</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Centre’s fiscal deficit narrowed 6.4% year-on-year to Rs 8.56 lakh crore in April–December FY26, according to data released by the Ministry of Finance.

Centre’s fiscal deficit narrowed 6.4% year-on-year to Rs 8.56 lakh crore in April–December FY26, according to data released by the Ministry of Finance. The Government of India has received Rs 25,25,156 crore (72.2% of corresponding BE 2025-26 of Total Receipts) upto December, 2025 comprising Rs 19,39,254 crore of Tax Revenue (Net to Centre), Rs 5,39,855 crore of Non-Tax Revenue and Rs 46,047 crore of Non-Debt Capital Receipts. Rs 10,38,164 crore has been transferred to State Governments as Devolution of Share of Taxes by Government of India during this period which is Rs 1,37,014 crore higher than the previous year. Total Expenditure incurred by Government of India is Rs 33,80,998 crore (66.7% of corresponding BE 2025-26), out of which Rs 25,93,063 crore is on Revenue Account and Rs 7,87,935 crore is on Capital Account. Out of the Total Revenue Expenditure, Rs 9,11,059 crore is on account of Interest Payments and Rs 3,17,490 crore is on account of Major Subsidies. The deficit for the current FY accounted for 54.5% of the full-year Budget estimate of Rs 15.69 lakh crore, marking an improvement from 56.7% in the corresponding stretch last year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background-picture-i_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Non-food bank credit gains around 14.4% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/non-food-bank-credit-gains-around-144-on-year/1669330</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669330</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released data on sectoral deployment of bank credit for the month of December 2025, collected from 41 select scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) which together account for about 95 per cent of the total non-food credit by all SCBs.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released data on sectoral deployment of bank credit for the month of December 2025, collected from 41 select scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) which together account for about 95 per cent of the total non-food credit by all SCBs. On a year-on-year (y-o-y) basis, non-food bank credit grew by 14.4 per cent as on the fortnight ended December 31, 2025, compared to 11.1 per cent during the corresponding fortnight of the previous year (i.e., December 27, 2024). Credit to agriculture and allied activities registered a y-o-y growth of 12.1 per cent (12.5 per cent in the corresponding fortnight of the previous year). Credit to industry recorded a y-o-y growth of 13.3 per cent, compared with 7.5 per cent in the corresponding fortnight of last year. While credit to ‘Micro and Small’ showed sharp acceleration in growth, ‘Medium’ industries continued to exhibit robust expansion. Credit to large industries also picked up. Among major industries, outstanding credit to ‘infrastructure’, ‘all engineering’, ‘basic metal and metal products’, ‘chemical and chemical products, ‘textiles’ and ‘petroleum, coal products and nuclear fuels’ registered resilient y-o-y growth. RBI noted that credit to services sector registered a growth rate of 15.3 per cent y-o-y (11.5 per cent in the corresponding fortnight of the previous year), supported by higher. growth in segments such as ‘non-banking financial companies’ (NBFCs), ‘trade’ and ‘commercial real estate’. Credit to personal loans segment recorded a y-o-y growth of 14.4 per cent, as compared with 12.0 per cent a year ago. While segments such as ‘vehicle loans’ and ‘loans against gold jewellery’ sustained robust credit growth, ‘housing’ witnessed steady growth while ‘credit card outstanding’ growth decreased.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee recovers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-recovers/1669328</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669328</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 92.0400 per Dollar on Friday (30 January 2026), versus its previous close of 92.1500 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper corrects but still up around 7% this month]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-corrects-but-still-up-around-7-this-month/1669327</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669327</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures fell sharply today, giving up some of the recent gains in tune with other metals as the US dollar index edged up from its four-year low.

COMEX Copper futures fell sharply today, giving up some of the recent gains in tune with other metals as the US dollar index edged up from its four-year low. Rising LME Copper inventories, which hit around seven and half month high in last session, also weighed on the counter on the last session of the month. Copper is down 2% at $6.07 per pound. The metal is still up around 7% this month. Equities were mostly mixed. In Asia, Shanghai Composite index lost around 1% while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index dipped 2%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index eased marginally. European stocks moved up modestly. The US stocks saw volatile moves in last session. The Dow edged up 0.1% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR briefly hits Rs 92 per dollar before edging higher at close; All Eyes on Union Budget ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-briefly-hits-rs-92-per-dollar-before-edging-higher-at-close-all-eyes-on-union-budget/1669291</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669291</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee on Friday hit its record low of 92.02 before ending slightly higher at 91.90 against the US dollar, amid a firm American currency and volatile geopolitical cues.

The Indian rupee on Friday hit its record low of 92.02 before ending slightly higher at 91.90 against the US dollar, amid a firm American currency and volatile geopolitical cues. Sustained withdrawal of foreign funds and a negative trend in domestic equities weighed on investor sentiment. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 91.89 and gained ground, touching 91.82 against the greenback during intraday trade. The currency touched its lowest-ever level of 92.02 against the dollar. Indian shares ended lower on Friday, with tariff worries, speculation about a potential hawkish Federal Reserve chair appointment and caution ahead of the Union Budget keeping investors on edge. The benchmark BSE Sensex dropped 296.59 points, or 0.36 percent, to 82,269.78, pressured by a weak rupee and rising oil prices amid rising U.S.-Iran tensions. The broader NSE Nifty index slipped 98.25 points, or 0.39 percent, to 25,320.65.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Markets advance on RBI liquidity support, macro tailwinds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/markets-advance-on-rbi-liquidity-support-macro-tailwinds/1669292</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669292</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Benchmarks indices ended the week with modest gains, aided by positive sentiment around the India–EU Free Trade Agreement and supportive RBI liquidity measures, which helped improve market confidence.

The Benchmarks indices ended the week with modest gains, aided by positive sentiment around the India–EU Free Trade Agreement and supportive RBI liquidity measures, which helped improve market confidence. Better macro cues, including strong industrial output data and an improved fiscal outlook flagged in the Economic Survey, underpinned the domestic growth narrative. However, upside was capped by a sharp slide in the rupee to record lows against the dollar and persistent global geopolitical concerns, keeping broader markets mixed amid stock-specific action. In the week ended on Friday, 30 January 2026, the S&P BSE Sensex added 732.08 points or 0.89% to settle at 82,269.70. The Nifty 50 index jumped 272 points or 1.08% to settle at 25,320.65. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.09% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 1.25%. The rupee on Friday (30 January 2026) hit its record low of 92.02 before ending a tad higher at 91.97 against the U.S. dollar, amid a firm American currency and volatile geopolitical cues. Weekly Index Movement: Indian stock market was shut on Monday, 26 January 2026, for Republic Day. Benchmark equity indices closed with modest gains on Tuesday. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 319.78 points or 0.39% to 81,857.48. The Nifty 50 index added 126.75 points or 0.51% to 25,175.40. The domestic equities ended higher on Wednesday. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 487.20 points, or 0.60%, to 82,344.68, while the Nifty 50 gained 167.35 points, or 0.66%, to settle at 25,342.75. The key equity benchmarks ended with modest gains on Thursday. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 221.69 points or 0.27% to 82,566.37. The Nifty 50 index added 76.15 points or 0.30% to 25,418.90. The key equity benchmarks ended with modest cuts on Friday. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 296.59 points or 0.36% to 82,269.78. The Nifty 50 index lost 98.25 points or 0.39% to 25,320.65. RBI Liquidity Measures: The Reserve Bank of India on Friday announced a set of liquidity-enhancing measures to ease conditions in the banking system. These include a Rs 25,000 crore 90-day variable rate repo operation on January 30, a $10 billion USD/INR buy-sell swap auction with a three-year tenor on February 4, and open market purchases of government securities worth Rs 1 lakh crore in two equal tranches on February 5 and February 12. The RBI said it will continue to closely monitor liquidity and market conditions and act as needed to ensure orderly system liquidity. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union on January 27, 2026, concluded a landmark Free Trade Agreement at the 16th India-EU Summit, marking a major milestone in bilateral economic ties between the world's 4th and 2nd largest economies, together accounting for about 25% of global GDP. The pact grants preferential market access to over 99% of Indian exports to the EU, with labour-intensive sectors such as textiles, leather, gems and jewellery, marine products and engineering goods set to benefit, while safeguarding sensitive areas like dairy and key agricultural products. The agreement delivers calibrated auto liberalisation, ambitious access in services, and a structured mobility framework to support skilled and semi-skilled Indian professionals. It also addresses non-tariff barriers, CBAM-related cooperation, digital trade, MSMEs, and future technologies including AI and clean energy. With India-EU goods trade at Rs 11.5 lakh crore and services trade at Rs 7.2 lakh crore in 2024-25, the FTA is expected to significantly boost exports, jobs, investment, and India’s integration into global value chains, laying the foundation for inclusive, resilient and future-ready growth. Indian Politics: Ajit Pawar, NCP chief and Maharashtra’s Deputy Chief Minister, died in a plane crash near Baramati on Wednesday while travelling from Mumbai. Four others, including the pilot and his security personnel, were also killed. The small aircraft, a Learjet 45 operated by VSR, crashed during a landing attempt near Baramati airport about 45 minutes after takeoff, as Pawar was on his way to attend public meetings ahead of the local body polls. The 66-year-old leader was the nephew of Sharad Pawar and the cousin of Supriya Sule, both of whom were in Delhi and later arrived in Baramati. Economic Survey 2025-2026: The Economic Survey 2025-26, tabled in Parliament on January 29 ahead of the February 1 Union Budget, highlighted both improving macro fundamentals and a clear shift in India’s export strategy as exporters steadily reduce their reliance on the US amid tariff-related uncertainties. The survey noted that while the India-US trade agreement remains under discussion, export data for April to November FY26 show a pivot towards West Asia, Europe, Africa, and parts of Asia to sustain growth. Sectors such as gems and jewelry, marine products, auto components, and textiles saw weaker demand from the US, but this was offset by stronger shipments to alternative markets, while pharmaceuticals remained resilient with healthy growth led by Africa, Latin America and Europe. On the broader economy, the survey said the fiscal deficit has sharply improved from 9.2% of GDP in FY21 to 4.8% in FY25 and is budgeted at 4.4% in FY26, while real GDP growth for FY26 is estimated at a robust 7.4%, driven largely by domestic demand. Looking ahead, the Indian economy is expected to grow 6.8%-7.2% in FY27, supported by strong macro fundamentals and ongoing regulatory reforms, underscoring a combination of internal strength and strategic diversification on the global trade front. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signaling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. India's fiscal deficit for April to December, or the first nine months of this fiscal year, was at Rs 8.55 lakh crore, equivalent to 54.5% of annual estimates, narrowing from the previous year's 56.7%. The government aims to narrow the fiscal gap to 4.4% of GDP in this financial year from 4.8% a year earlier. Stocks in Spotlight: Asian Paints tumbled 10.12%. The company's consolidated net profit declined 4.55% to Rs 1,059.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,110.48 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26. Axis Bank jumped 8.74%. The bank reported a 2.94% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 6,489.57 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 6,303.77 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26. IndusInd Bank rose 0.16%. The bank reported 88.5% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 161.16 crore on 13.67% fall in total income to Rs 13,079.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shriram Finance added 1.65%. The NBFC’s standalone net profit declined 29.36% to Rs 2,521.67 crore on a 13.88% increase in total income to Rs 12,191.58 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Consumer Products fell 1.35%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 37.91% to Rs 384.61 crore on a 15.04% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5,112 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Godrej Consumer Products tumbled 6.71%. The company's consolidated net profit remained flat at Rs 497.91 crore in Q3 FY26, even as net sales increased 8.8% year-on-year to Rs 4,079.47 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Ultratech Cement advanced 2.8%. The company reported a 26.92% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,725.40 crore on 22.78% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 21,829.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Electronics (BEL) surged 9.54%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 20.81% to Rs 1,590.06 crore on 23.72% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,121.98 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company’s order book position stood at Rs 73,015 crore as of 1 January 2026. Maruti Suzuki India (MSIL) fell 5.61%. The car major reported a 4.08% YoY rise in net profit to Rs 3,879.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,726.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 29.2% YoY to Rs 47,534.4 crore, driven by a sharp recovery in the Indian car market led by the small car segment. Larsen & Toubro added 5.03%. The company reported a 17.78% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 2,832.08 crore on 8.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 37,902.84 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. SBI Cards and Payment Services fell 2.27%. The company reported 45% jump in net profit to Rs 557 crore on a 12% increase in total income to Rs 5,353 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Cards-in-force grew by 8% to 2.18 crore as of Q3 FY26 as against 2.02 crore as of Q3 FY25. New accounts volume stood at 864K in Q3 FY26 as compared to 1,175K in Q3 FY25. Nestle India added 2.95%. The company reported a 46.24% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 1,018.06 crore on 18.56% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 5,667.04 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Motors rose 2.04%. The company’s net profit declined 48% YoY to Rs 705 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,355 crore a year ago. Sequentially, it returned to profit from a loss of Rs 867 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue rose 16.2% YoY to Rs 21,732 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 18,697 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, revenue increased 17.5% QoQ from Rs 18,491 crore. ITC shed 0.39%. The company reported 5.6% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 4934.80 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5016.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose by 6.2% year-on-year to Rs 17857.56 crore during the period under review. Gillette India advanced 10.42%. The company reported a 36.91% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 172.46 crore on a 15.24% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 790 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Market: Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. The central bank is widely expected to keep its benchmark interest rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%, but traders will be seeking hints on longer-term changes to monetary policy. Tokyo CPI in Japan decreased to 1.50% in January from 2 percent in December of 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Budget and Monetary Policy to steer market sentiment]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-budget-and-monetary-policy-to-steer-market-sentiment/1669258</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669258</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equities start the first full week of February on mixed footing after a volatile final week in January.

Indian equities start the first full week of February on mixed footing after a volatile final week in January. The benchmark indices swung sharply; the Sensex settled 296 points lower and the Nifty slipped below 25,350, pressured by profit-taking and a record-weak rupee near a three-year low as foreign outflows persisted. The India–EU free trade agreement, a landmark pact encompassing nearly one-third of global trade, marks a meaningful step toward deepening India’s integration into global value chains, potentially improving export competitiveness and supporting medium-term earnings visibility across key sectors. Further, the Economic Survey projected India’s FY27 GDP to expand 6.8–7.2%, reinforcing long-term growth narratives. With the Union Budget now imminent, investors should monitor policy cues, crude price volatility and FII activity, favouring quality large-caps and export-linked sectors while navigating short-term risk-off phases. In India, the India Union Budget for 2026-27 would be announced on Sunday (01 February 2026). On Monday (02 February 2026), the HSBC Manufacturing PMI Final for January 2026 would be released. The HSBC India Manufacturing PMI rose to 56.8 in January 2026 from 55.0 in December, marking the strongest improvement in operating conditions in three months, according to preliminary estimates. On Wednesday (04 February 2026), the HSBC Services PMI Final and the HSBC Composite PMI Final for the month of January would be released. The HSBC India Services PMI increased to 59.3 in January 2026 from a final reading of 58.0 in December 2025, which marked the softest expansion in 11 months. The HSBC India Composite PMI rose to 59.5 in January 2026 from December’s 11-month low of 57.8, flash data showed. The reading was well above the long-run average, driven by stronger growth in both manufacturing and services. On Friday (06 February 2026), the RBI would be announce its interest rate decision through the release of the latest monetary policy. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) lowered its key repo rate by 25 basis points to 5.25% during its December 2025 meeting, amid confidence in a softer inflation outlook. The RBI has now cut rates by a total of 125 basis points since the beginning of the year, bringing the repo rate to its lowest level since July 2022. In China, the NBS Manufacturing PMI and the NBS Non-Manufacturing PMI for the month of January would be released on Saturday (31 January 2026). China’s official NBS Manufacturing PMI unexpectedly rose to 50.1 in December 2025, surpassing both November’s reading of 49.2. The official NBS Non-Manufacturing PMI for China rose to 50.2 in December 2025 from 49.5 in the prior month, marking the highest level since August. On Monday (02 February 2026), the RatingDog Manufacturing PMI for January 2026 would be released. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI unexpectedly increased to 50.1 in December 2025 from November’s four-month low of 49.9. On Wednesday (04 February 2026), the RatingDog Services PMI for January 2026 would be announced. The RatingDog China General Services PMI edged down to 52.0 in December 2025 from 52.1 in November. In the United States, the ISM Manufacturing PMI for January 2026 would be announced on Monday (02 February 2026). The ISM Manufacturing PMI for the US fell for a third consecutive month to 47.9 in December 2025, the lowest level since October 2024, compared to 48.2 in November. Tuesday (03 February 2026) would see the release of the JOLTs Job Openings data for December 2025. Job openings in the US fell by 303,000 to 7.146 million in November 2025, the lowest since September 2024. On Wednesday (04 February 2026), the ISM Services PMI for the month of January would be made public. The ISM Services PMI for the US increased for a third consecutive month to 54.4 in December 2025 from 52.6 in November, The figures pertaining to the changes in the API Crude Oil Stock for the period ended on January 30 would also be released on the same day. US crude oil inventories fell by 0.25 million barrels in the week ended January 23rd, 2025, reversing a 3.04 million-barrel build in the prior week. The Initial Jobless Claims data for the period ending on January 31 would be made public on Thursday (05 February 2026). Initial jobless claims in the US inched lower by 1,000 to 209,000 from the upwardly revised value in the previous week. Lastly, on Friday (06 February 2026), the Non-Farm Payrolls data for January 2026 would be released. The US economy added 50K payrolls in December 2025, less than a downwardly revised 56K in November. The Unemployment Rate for the month of January would be also be announced on the same day. The US unemployment rate edged down to 4.4% in December 2025, from a revised 4.5% in November, which had marked the highest level since October 2021. Friday would also see the release of the preliminary reading for the Michigan Consumer Sentiment for February 2026. The University of Michigan’s consumer sentiment index was revised up to 56.4 in January 2026, from a preliminary 54.0 and December’s 52.9.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's energy strategy is anchored in diversification, resilience and forward-looking transitions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-energy-strategy-is-anchored-in-diversification-resilience-and-forward-looking-transitions/1669238</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669238</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India has demonstrated strong preparedness to navigate sustained geopolitical volatility in global energy markets and will continue to occupy centre stage in international energy discourse, Union Minister for Petroleum and Natural Gas Hardeep Singh Puri said at the Closing Ceremony of India Energy Week (IEW) 2026.

India has demonstrated strong preparedness to navigate sustained geopolitical volatility in global energy markets and will continue to occupy centre stage in international energy discourse, Union Minister for Petroleum and Natural Gas Hardeep Singh Puri said at the Closing Ceremony of India Energy Week (IEW) 2026. The event was organised in Goa from 27th January to 30th January 2026. Puri emphasised that India’s energy strategy is anchored in diversification, resilience and forward-looking transitions. Highlighting India’s global standing, he noted that the country is today the third-largest energy consumer, fourth-largest refiner and among the top exporters of petroleum products. The Union Minister also emphasised the government’s push on compressed biogas (CBG), green hydrogen and indigenous clean-energy technologies, alongside continued investments in conventional fuels. Addressing concerns around consumer impact during global price shocks, the Minister said that India has successfully insulated its citizens from volatility. Global turmoil has never been passed on to the consumer. India today has among the lowest energy prices in the world, and uninterrupted supply has been maintained even during crises, he said.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/steel-long-pipes-in-crude-oil-factory-during-sunset-picture_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices retreat after 3-day rise on mixed global cues, Budget caution]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-retreat-after-3-day-rise-on-mixed-global-cues-budget-caution/1669219</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669219</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The benchmark equity indices Sensex and Nifty slipped on Friday, snapping a three-day rally, as weak global cues and caution ahead of the Union Budget on February 1 weighed on sentiment.

The benchmark equity indices Sensex and Nifty slipped on Friday, snapping a three-day rally, as weak global cues and caution ahead of the Union Budget on February 1 weighed on sentiment. Fresh foreign fund outflows added to the pressure. Investors also remained watchful of rupee movements, ongoing Q3 earnings and geopolitical developments. Reflecting the cautious mood, the Nifty closed below the 25,350 level, dragged down by losses in metal, IT and private banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 296.59 points or 0.36% to 82,269.78. The Nifty 50 index lost 98.25 points or 0.39% to 25,320.65. In the past three consecutive trading session, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.26% and 1.48%, respectively. Hindalco Industries (down 5.98%), Tata Steel (down 4.81%) and ICICI Bank (down 1.92%) were major Nifty drags. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.09% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 1.25%. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.14% to 13.37. India's April-December Fiscal Deficit India's fiscal deficit for April to December, or the first nine months of this fiscal year, was at Rs 8.55 lakh crore, equivalent to 54.5% of annual estimates, narrowing from the previous year's 56.7%. The government aims to narrow the fiscal gap to 4.4% of GDP in this financial year from 4.8% a year earlier. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.13% to 6.690 as compared with the previous close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9700 compared with its close of 91.9950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement tanked 4.29% to Rs 162,352. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.50% to 96.64. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.64% to 4.255. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement rose 63 cents or 0.89% to $70.08 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 333 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European indices advanced on Friday, as international relations and corporate earnings remained in focus. Most Asian indices ended lower, led by declines in technology stocks, after a weak overnight finish on Wall Street dampened risk appetite. Investors also weighed Tokyo inflation data, which kept expectations of further Bank of Japan policy tightening in focus, while U.S. President Donald Trump said he would announce his choice for the next Federal Reserve chair on Friday. Tokyo CPI in Japan decreased to 1.50% in January from 2% in December of 2025. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index slipped 0.13% to close at 6,969.01, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 0.72% to end at 23,685.12. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.11%, or 55.96 points, and settled at 49,071.56. Stocks in Spotlight: The Nifty Metal index tumbled 5.21% to 11,827.55. The index rose 8.71% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Zinc fell 12.47%, Vedanta declined 11.27%, and Hindustan Copper dropped 11.07%, leading losses in the metals pack. National Aluminium Company slid 10.69%, while Hindalco Industries lost 5.98%. Tata Steel ended 4.81% lower, NMDC slipped 4.26%, and Steel Authority of India declined 3.94%. Jindal Steel & Power shed 2.97%, Lloyds Metals & Energy fell 2.77%, and JSW Steel eased 1.88%. Welspun Corp was down 1.77%, while APL Apollo Tubes slipped 0.41%. Tata Motors (CV) slipped 2.54% after the company reported its Q3 FY26 performance, which was weighed down by exceptional losses during the quarter. On a consolidated basis, net profit declined 48% YoY to Rs 705 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,355 crore a year ago. Sequentially, it returned to profit from a loss of Rs 867 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue rose 16.2% YoY to Rs 21,732 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 18,697 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, revenue increased 17.5% QoQ from Rs 18,491 crore. Dabur India shed 0.57%. The company reported a 7.3% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 553.61 crore on a 6.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3,558.65 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ITC rose 1.11% after the company reported 5.6% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 4934.80 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5016.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose by 6.2% year-on-year to Rs 17857.56 crore during the period under review. Colgate-Palmolive (India) added 0.39%. The company reported a marginal 0.3% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 323.9 crore, while revenue from operations rose 1.4% to Rs 1,472.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. MTAR Technologies jumped 7% after the company announced a strong set of unaudited consolidated results for the third quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit jumped 117.3% YoY to Rs 34.7 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 16.0 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, profit after tax surged 717.2% from Rs 4.2 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations rose 59.3% YoY to Rs 278.0 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 174.5 crore a year ago. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue more than doubled, rising 105.0% QoQ from Rs 135.6 crore in Q2 FY26. Allied Blenders and Distillers (ABD) rallied 6.58% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 10.91% to Rs 63.74 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 57.47 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased by 2.98% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,002.98 crore in Q3 FY26. Nippon Life India Asset Management advanced 1.30% after its consolidated net profit jumped 36.74% to Rs 403.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 295.36 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income jumped 29.38% to Rs 780.55 crore in the third quarter of FY26, as against Rs 603.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Cupid gained 2.88% after the company reported 196.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 32.83 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 11.08 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 101.70% YoY to Rs 93.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Blue Star jumped 5.33%. The company reported 39.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 80.55 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 132.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased by 4.2% to Rs 2,925.31 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as compared to Rs 2807.36 crore during the same period in the previous year. One 97 Communications slipped 2.71%. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 225 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 208 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations during the period under review increased by 20.02% YoY to Rs 2,194 crore, driven by industry-leading customer monetization. Strides Pharma Science surged 8.41% after its consolidated operational profit after tax rose 38.6% YoY to Rs 128.2 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 92.5 crore a year ago. On a sequential basis, operational PAT declined 8.6% QoQ from Rs 140.3 crore. Revenue increased 3.6% YoY to Rs 1,194.6 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 1,153.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, revenue declined 2.1% QoQ from Rs 1,220.8 crore. Revenue was impacted by low offtake in the institutional business and flattish US operations. Swiggy tanked 4.98% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 1,065 crore in Q3 FY26, widening from a net loss of Rs 799 crore in Q3 FY25. Despite the loss, the company recorded strong top-line growth, with revenue from operations rising 53.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,148 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. TD Power Systems surged 8.23% after the company reported a 25.4% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 56.32 crore on a 26.4% rise in net sales to Rs 442.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Syrma SGS Technology jumped 4.91% after the company reported a strong set of consolidated numbers for Q3 FY26. On a consolidated basis, net profit surged 108.1% YoY to Rs 110.3 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 53.0 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, profit after tax jumped 66.3% QoQ from Rs 66.3 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations climbed 45.4% YoY to Rs 1,264.2 crore, up from Rs 869.2 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue increased 10.3% QoQ from Rs 1,145.9 crore in Q2 FY26. Gillette India surged 5.83% after the company reported a 36.91% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 172.46 crore on a 15.24% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 790 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) added 0.34%. The company said that it has secured a domestic contract from Pawan Hans for the supply of 10 Dhruv NG helicopters, along with associated spares and accessories.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1669240</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669240</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,425, a premium of 104.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,320.65 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,425, a premium of 104.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,320.65 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index fell 98.25 points or 0.39% to 25,320.65. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 1.96% to 13.63. Vedanta, Hindustan Zinc and Dixon Technologies (India) were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Voltas records over 35% YoY fall in Q3 PAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/voltas-records-over-35-yoy-fall-in-q3-pat/1669126</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669126</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income for the period under review was Rs 3,120 crore, down 1.4% YoY.

Total income for the period under review was Rs 3,120 crore, down 1.4% YoY. Profit before tax stood at Rs 116 crore in Q3 FY26, down by 39.3% from Rs 191 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Voltas stated that the management had stayed firmly focused on strengthening market leadership in the cooling segment, sharpening its competitive edge through disciplined network expansion, precise micro level market targeting, stronger channel readiness, and more impactful retail and digital activation across priority markets. At the same time, the diversified portfolio spanning Electro Mechanical Projects and Services and Engineering Products provided resilience and business continuity, reinforcing Voltas’ steady transformation into a full stack, consumer durable and engineering projects and services company. Mukundan Menon C P, managing director, Voltas, said, “In Q3, the Room Air Conditioner business remained the anchor of our overall performance, navigating inherent seasonality and the impact of a shorter second summer through stronger channel momentum, improved product mix, and the benefit of the GST rate reduction. With refreshed product lineups, sharper pricing architecture, and focused cost optimisation, Voltas is entering the upcoming season with heightened readiness, stronger execution capability, and a more efficient operating base. Built on this solid foundation, we are well positioned to further strengthen our leadership in cooling while accelerating the growth of our diversified portfolio across Home Appliances and Engineering Project Solutions.” Voltas, a part of the Tata Group, is a premier air conditioning and engineering solutions provider, projects specialist, and one of the leading players in the consumer durables category. The scrip had declined 1.24% to end at Rs 1330.50 on the BSE today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Voltas_2244231105_597.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 297 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,350 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-297-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25350-mark/1669122</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669122</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with modest losses on Friday, snapping a three-day gaining streak, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026.

The key equity benchmarks ended with modest losses on Friday, snapping a three-day gaining streak, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments. The Nifty settled below the 25,350 marks. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 296.59 points or 0.36% to 82,269.78. The Nifty 50 index lost 98.25 points or 0.39% to 25,320.65. In the past three consecutive trading session, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.26% and 1.48%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.09% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 1.25%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.96% to 13.63. The rupee on Friday (30 January 2026) hit its record low of 92.02 before ending a tad higher at 91.97 against the U.S. dollar, amid a firm American currency and volatile geopolitical cues. Among the sectoral indices, the Media index (up 1.85%), the Nifty FMCG index (up 1.37%) and the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 1.08%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Metal index (down 5.21%), the Nifty IT index (down 0.91%) and the Nifty Private Bank index (down 0.63%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. India's April-December Fiscal Deficit: India's fiscal deficit for April to December, or the first nine months of this fiscal year, was at Rs 8.55 lakh crore, equivalent to 54.5% of annual estimates, narrowing from the previous year's 56.7%. The government aims to narrow the fiscal gap to 4.4% of GDP in this financial year from 4.8% a year earlier. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.13% to 6.690 as compared with the previous close of 6.695. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9700 compared with its close of 91.9950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement tanked 4.29% to Rs 162,352. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.50% to 96.64. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.64% to 4.255. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement rose 63 cents or 0.89% to $70.08 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Friday, as international relations and corporate earnings remained in focus. Most Asian markets ended lower, led by declines in technology stocks, after a weak overnight finish on Wall Street dampened risk appetite. Investors also weighed Tokyo inflation data, which kept expectations of further Bank of Japan policy tightening in focus, while U.S. President Donald Trump said he would announce his choice for the next Federal Reserve chair on Friday. Tokyo CPI in Japan decreased to 1.50 percent in January from 2 percent in December of 2025. Speaking at the premiere of Melania, a film about first lady Melania Trump, he said the five-month search to replace current chair Jerome Powell was nearing its conclusion. The process for selecting Powell’s replacement began in September with an 11-candidate field that included past and current Fed officials, economists, and Wall Street investment professionals. Trump also endorsed a Senate deal to fund the vast majority of the federal government through the remainder of the fiscal year, easing near-term political uncertainty for investors. Senators clinched a deal with just over a day until a partial government shutdown. They agreed to remove funding for the Department of Homeland Security from the package and pass the other five bills, while DHS will be funded by a stopgap. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index slipped 0.13% to close at 6,969.01, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 0.72% to end at 23,685.12. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.11%, or 55.96 points, and settled at 49,071.56.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-mutual-funds-picture-id157281690_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index registers a drop of 5.21%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-registers-a-drop-of-521/1669119</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669119</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index closed down 5.21% at 11827.55 today.

Nifty Metal index closed down 5.21% at 11827.55 today. The index has added 6.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Hindustan Zinc Ltd dropped 12.12%, Vedanta Ltd fell 11.07% and National Aluminium Company Ltd shed 10.12%. The Nifty Metal index has increased 43.00% over last one year compared to the 8.91% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Commodities index has slid 2.13% and Nifty Media index increased 1.85% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has declined 0.39% to close at 25320.65 while the SENSEX has slid 0.36% to close at 82269.78 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market snaps three-day winning streak; Nifty ends below 25,350 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-snaps-three-day-winning-streak-nifty-ends-below-25350-mark/1669118</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669118</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices ended with modest losses on Friday, snapping a three-day gaining streak, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026.

The domestic equity indices ended with modest losses on Friday, snapping a three-day gaining streak, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments. The Nifty settled below the 25,350 mark. Metal, IT and oil & gas shares declined, while media, FMCG and realty shares edged lower. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 296.59 points or 0.36% to 82,269.78. The Nifty 50 index lost 98.25 points or 0.39% to 25,320.65. In the past three consecutive trading session, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.26% and 1.48%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE MidCap Select Index rose 0.10% and the S&P BSE SmallCap Select Index slipped 0.09%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,424 shares rose and 1,782 shares fell. A total of 166 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, advanced 1.96% to 13.63. India's April-December Fiscal Deficit India's fiscal deficit for April to December, or the first nine months of this fiscal year, was at Rs 8.55 lakh crore, equivalent to 54.5% of annual estimates, narrowing from the previous year's 56.7%. The government aims to narrow the fiscal gap to 4.4% of GDP in this financial year from 4.8% a year earlier. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index tumbled 5.21% to 11,827.55. The index rallied 8.71% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Zinc (down 12.53%), Vedanta (down 11.67%), Hindustan Copper (down 11.17%), National Aluminium Company (down 11.01%), Hindalco Industries (down 6.41%), Tata Steel (down 4.62%), NMDC (down 4.37%), Steel Authority of India (down 4.12%), Jindal Steel (down 2.86%) and Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 2.74%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Motors (CV) slipped 2.24% after the company reported its Q3 FY26 performance, which was weighed down by exceptional losses during the quarter. On a consolidated basis, net profit declined 48% YoY to Rs 705 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,355 crore a year ago. Sequentially, it returned to profit from a loss of Rs 867 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue rose 16.2% YoY to Rs 21,732 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 18,697 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, revenue increased 17.5% QoQ from Rs 18,491 crore. Dabur India shed 0.37%. The company reported a 7.3% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 553.61 crore on a 6.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3,558.65 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ITC rose 1.18% after the company reported 5.6% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 4934.80 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5016.72 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose by 6.2% year-on-year to Rs 17857.56 crore during the period under review. Colgate-Palmolive (India) added 0.16%. The company reported a marginal 0.3% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 323.9 crore, while revenue from operations rose 1.4% to Rs 1,472.9 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. MTAR Technologies jumped 6.90% after the company announced a strong set of unaudited consolidated results for the third quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit jumped 117.3% YoY to Rs 34.7 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 16.0 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, profit after tax surged 717.2% from Rs 4.2 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations rose 59.3% YoY to Rs 278.0 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 174.5 crore a year ago. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue more than doubled, rising 105.0% QoQ from Rs 135.6 crore in Q2 FY26. Allied Blenders and Distillers (ABD) rallied 5.58% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 10.91% to Rs 63.74 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 57.47 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased by 2.98% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,002.98 crore in Q3 FY26. Nippon Life India Asset Management advanced 2.33% after its consolidated net profit jumped 36.74% to Rs 403.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 295.36 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income jumped 29.38% to Rs 780.55 crore in the third quarter of FY26, as against Rs 603.30 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Cupid gained 4.04% after the company reported 196.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 32.83 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 11.08 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 101.70% YoY to Rs 93.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Blue Star jumped 4.88%. The company reported 39.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 80.55 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 132.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased by 4.2% to Rs 2,925.31 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as compared to Rs 2807.36 crore during the same period in the previous year. One 97 Communications slipped 2.60%. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 225 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 208 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations during the period under review increased by 20.02% YoY to Rs 2,194 crore Swiggy tanked 5.59% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 1,065 crore in Q3 FY26, widening from a net loss of Rs 799 crore in Q3 FY25. Despite the loss, the company recorded strong top-line growth, with revenue from operations rising 53.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,148 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. TD Power Systems surged 7.40% after the company reported a 25.4% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 56.32 crore on a 26.4% rise in net sales to Rs 442.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Syrma SGS Technology jumped 4.89% after the company reported a strong set of consolidated numbers for Q3 FY26. On a consolidated basis, net profit surged 108.1% YoY to Rs 110.3 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 53.0 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, profit after tax jumped 66.3% QoQ from Rs 66.3 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations climbed 45.4% YoY to Rs 1,264.2 crore, up from Rs 869.2 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue increased 10.3% QoQ from Rs 1,145.9 crore in Q2 FY26. Gillette India surged 5.87% after the company reported a 36.91% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 172.46 crore on a 15.24% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 790 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) added 0.34%. The company said that it has secured a domestic contract from Pawan Hans for the supply of 10 Dhruv NG helicopters, along with associated spares and accessories. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Friday, as international relations and corporate earnings remained in focus. Most Asian markets ended lower, led by declines in technology stocks, after a weak overnight finish on Wall Street dampened risk appetite. Investors also weighed Tokyo inflation data, which kept expectations of further Bank of Japan policy tightening in focus, while U.S. President Donald Trump said he would announce his choice for the next Federal Reserve chair on Friday. Tokyo CPI in Japan decreased to 1.50 percent in January from 2 percent in December of 2025. Speaking at the premiere of Melania, a film about first lady Melania Trump, he said the five-month search to replace current chair Jerome Powell was nearing its conclusion. The process for selecting Powell’s replacement began in September with an 11-candidate field that included past and current Fed officials, economists, and Wall Street investment professionals. Trump also endorsed a Senate deal to fund the vast majority of the federal government through the remainder of the fiscal year, easing near-term political uncertainty for investors. Senators clinched a deal with just over a day until a partial government shutdown. They agreed to remove funding for the Department of Homeland Security from the package and pass the other five bills, while DHS will be funded by a stopgap. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 index slipped 0.13% to close at 6,969.01, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 0.72% to end at 23,685.12. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.11%, or 55.96 points, and settled at 49,071.56.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nestle India gains as Q3 PAT jumps 46% YoY to Rs 1,018 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nestle-india-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-46-yoy-to-rs-1018-cr/1669097</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669097</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) rallied 26.65% to Rs 1,168.07 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 922.26 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax (PBT) rallied 26.65% to Rs 1,168.07 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 922.26 crore in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, revenue from domestic sales stood at Rs 5,402.6 crore, up 18.32% compared with Rs 4,566.05 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from export sales jumped 22.86% YoY to Rs 240.92 crore in Q3 FY26. During Q3 FY26, the company reported strong business momentum across channels. E-commerce, particularly quick commerce, witnessed accelerated growth, supported by sustained on-off platform demand generation. The organised trade channel continued to deliver broad-based growth across categories, aided by festive-season activations and the scale-up of new product launches. In the out-of-home (OOH) segment, Duo Gusto, its hot and cold beverage solution—saw robust machine deployments across quick service restaurants, educational institutions and corporate offices. The export business posted high double-digit growth, driven by strong demand across product categories, with coffee continuing to perform well. The company expanded its product portfolio in Thailand and Papua New Guinea through the launch of new SKUs of MUNCH wafer chocolates, while in the B2B segment it added new customers for Instant Tea, further strengthening its market presence. On the domestic front, product groups delivered a strong performance in Q3 FY26, led by broad-based volume growth across categories. In the prepared dishes and cooking aids segment, MAGGI Noodles posted double-digit volume growth, supported by a new thematic campaign, “Me & Maggi, So Good Together”, aimed at driving urban consumption, accelerating rural penetration through an optimised price-pack portfolio, and improving traction in the value-added range, including the new spicy variants and Double Masala. Masala-ae-Magic continued its strong momentum, aided by efforts to expand household penetration and usage frequency. In milk products and nutrition, MILKMAID sustained its strong growth trajectory, while EVERYDAY showed recovery across key geographies. Toddler milk products delivered a healthy performance and reported market share gains during the quarter. The confectionery segment recorded robust growth, with KITKAT posting high double-digit volume growth, particularly in rural markets, while MUNCH continued its double-digit growth momentum. MILKYBAR also delivered a strong performance. During the quarter, the company launched several festive packs, including KITKAT Celebreak and Goldenbreak, while variants such as KITKAT Delights Salted Caramel and Hazelnut, KITKAT Dark Sharebag and KITKAT Duo continued to perform well. In powdered and liquid beverages, NESCAFÉ CLASSIC, NESCAFÉ SUNRISE and NESCAFÉ GOLD maintained strong momentum, helping bring over 4.1 million households into the coffee category in 2025. NESCAFÉ Ready-to-Drink cold coffee also recorded strong growth during the quarter. On the commodity front, milk prices have remained firm despite the flush season, supported by robust demand. Edible oil prices continue to stay elevated and are expected to trade sideways during the first half of calendar year 2026. The upcoming wheat harvest in April 2026 is expected to be healthy, while coffee prices have stabilised at levels lower than last year, aided by favourable crop yields in Vietnam and India. Manish Tiwary, chairman and managing director (MD) of Nestlé India, said, “the company reported robust, broad-based volume-led sales growth of 18.5% during the quarter, resulting in its highest-ever quarterly turnover of Rs 5,643.5 crore and the strongest volume growth in nearly five years. EBITDA margin stood at 21.3%, while consumer-focused media and advertising spend increased 42% year-on-year. The performance was driven by capacity expansion, brand investments and market recovery following GST benefits. Tiwary said 2025 marked a landmark year for the company, recording the highest absolute and percentage reach gains outside the COVID period, led by strong rural expansion and best-in-class urban performance. All four product groups delivered positive volume-led growth, with three witnessing robust double-digit growth. Confectionery was the fastest-growing segment, supported by higher advertising spends, expanded store presence, premiumisation and quick commerce-led in-home penetration. Powdered and liquid beverages recorded double-digit growth for the 18th consecutive quarter, while prepared dishes and cooking aids posted strong double-digit value growth on accelerated volumes. Milk products and nutrition delivered mid-single-digit growth, with improving trends in consumer-facing channels. The pet food business reported strong double-digit growth, aided by expansion of the PRO PLAN dog range, while Nespresso continued to gain momentum in the premium segment. All business channels reported strong double-digit growth. Nestlé Professional delivered robust growth driven by out-of-home expansion across beverage vending solutions, confectionery and MAGGI Coconut Milk Powder. General trade saw a sharp acceleration, led by rural markets, supported by deeper technology adoption, including DMS at sub-distributor levels. E-commerce continued to grow strongly on the back of new launches, better platform availability and festive activations. Looking ahead, Tiwary said the company remains focused on bold innovation, consumer-centricity, operational excellence and leveraging automation and technology to drive efficiencies and long-term value creation.” The company has approved, in principle, investments in two special purpose vehicles (SPVs) with Adani Green Energy Ltd and Radiance Renewables, subject to customary closing conditions, for setting up captive renewable energy power plants. Under the arrangement, the company will invest up to 26% in the equity capital of each SPV and will consume at least 51% of the annual power generated by each project, enabling access to cost-effective green energy for its manufacturing facilities. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs 7 per equity share of face value Rs 1 each for the financial year 2025–26. The interim dividend will be paid on or after 26 February 2026, to shareholders whose names appear in the register of members or in the register of beneficial owners maintained by the depositories as on the record date of 6 February 2026, as previously intimated to the stock exchanges. Nestle India is a subsidiary of Nestle which is a Swiss MNC. The company operates in the Food segment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NestleIndia_49188289783_175.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Strides Pharma Science jumps after strong Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/strides-pharma-science-jumps-after-strong-q3-performance/1669095</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669095</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, profit after tax rose 131.14% YoY to Rs 208.12 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 90.04 crore a year ago.

On a consolidated basis, profit after tax rose 131.14% YoY to Rs 208.12 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 90.04 crore a year ago. On a sequential basis, PAT rose 58.24% QoQ from Rs 131.52 crore. Operational profit after tax rose 38.6% YoY to Rs 128.2 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 92.5 crore a year ago. On a sequential basis, operational PAT declined 8.6% QoQ from Rs 140.3 crore. Revenue increased 3.6% YoY to Rs 1,194.6 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 1,153.7 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, revenue declined 2.1% QoQ from Rs 1,220.8 crore. Revenue was impacted by low offtake in the institutional business and flattish US operations. Gross profit rose 8.6% YoY to Rs 731.7 crore from Rs 673.5 crore. Gross margin expanded sharply to 61.2%, an improvement of 280 bps YoY and 340 bps QoQ. EBITDA increased 12.2% YoY to Rs 235.9 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 210.3 crore, while rising 1.9% QoQ. EBITDA margin improved to 19.8%, up 160 bps YoY and 80 bps sequentially. Ex-US market revenue stood at $64 million, registering a strong 20% YoY growth. Growth was led by other regulated markets and growth markets, which helped offset weak institutional demand and flat US performance. Management reiterated continued investments in sustainable long-term growth and announced the appointment of Peter Hardwick as CEO of the North America business. Strides Pharma Science is a Bengaluru-headquartered global pharmaceutical company focused on regulated and emerging markets, with manufacturing facilities across India, Italy, Kenya and the US, and a presence in over 100 countries.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StridesPharma_63459406134_16996.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[South Indian Bank Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/south-indian-bank-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1669092</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669092</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd, Hindustan Copper Ltd, Vedanta Ltd and National Aluminium Company Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 30 January 2026.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd, Hindustan Copper Ltd, Vedanta Ltd and National Aluminium Company Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 30 January 2026. South Indian Bank Ltd lost 15.04% to Rs 37.61 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 158.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 30.68 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Zinc Ltd tumbled 11.49% to Rs 633.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 33 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12.64 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Copper Ltd crashed 10.59% to Rs 678.8. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 127.5 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 50.37 lakh shares in the past one month. Vedanta Ltd corrected 10.00% to Rs 689.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 21.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12.49 lakh shares in the past one month. National Aluminium Company Ltd plummeted 9.09% to Rs 389.95. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 31.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13.58 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SouthIndBank_65437939_6263.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Gold tumbles around 4%, crashes under $5200 per ounce]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-gold-tumbles-around-4-crashes-under-5200-per-ounce/1669089</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669089</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Gold futures melted today, sliding around 4% amid speculations the US Federal Reserve might receive a more hawkish chair.

COMEX Gold futures melted today, sliding around 4% amid speculations the US Federal Reserve might receive a more hawkish chair. Hefty profit selling was seen after the counter hit a fresh record high of $5626 per ounce in last session. The metal is still on track for its greatest monthly gain since 1982 as investors rushed to the safe haven amid persisting geopolitical and economic concerns. COMEX Gold futures are currently trading at $5151 per ounce, down 3.80% on the day. Gold has rallied around 80% in last one month. Latest data is reflecting some concerns over retail buying as total global gold jewellery fabrication demand dropped around 19% on year to 1638 tonnes in 2025. MCX Gold is also witnessing intense volatility after opening sharply lower and currently trades down 6% at Rs 172925 per 10 grams. Intraday gains above Rs 180000 per 10 grams mark earlier in the day evaporated quickly.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/california-software-company-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-losers-in-b-group/1669087</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669087</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Meera Industries Ltd, Alacrity Securities Ltd, Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd and Plaza Wires Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 January 2026.

Meera Industries Ltd, Alacrity Securities Ltd, Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd and Plaza Wires Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 30 January 2026. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup crashed 14.82% to Rs 3.62 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 25797 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1589 shares in the past one month. Meera Industries Ltd tumbled 14.00% to Rs 81. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 69081 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 46608 shares in the past one month. Alacrity Securities Ltd lost 9.98% to Rs 49. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15882 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21243 shares in the past one month. Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd slipped 8.05% to Rs 23.3. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 11 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1980 shares in the past one month. Plaza Wires Ltd pared 7.76% to Rs 40.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6405 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5835 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with modest losses; Oil & gas share slides]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-modest-losses-oil-gas-share-slides/1669082</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669082</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks trimmed some losses and traded with modest declines in mid-afternoon trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026.

The headline equity benchmarks trimmed some losses and traded with modest declines in mid-afternoon trade, tracking weak global cues, as investors remained cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026, scheduled to be presented on 1 February 2026. Market participants are closely monitoring the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments for fresh direction. Investor focus is also on quarterly results due later today from key companies such as Bajaj Auto, NTPC, Power Grid Corporation of India, Nestlé India, and Ambuja Cements. Reflecting the subdued sentiment, the Nifty slipped below the 25,300 level during morning trade. Metal, IT and oil & gas shares declined, while media, FMCG and realty shares advanced. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 272.19 points or 0.33% to 82,286.02. The Nifty 50 index lost 87.35 points or 0.34% to 25,330.45. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap select index slipped 0.14% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap select index fell 0.19%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,422 shares rose and 1,704 shares fell. A total of 171 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, advanced 2.97% to 13.77. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index fell 0.63% to 11,780.85. The index jumped 4.84% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 2.10%), Petronet LNG (down 1.84%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 1.7%), Oil India (down 1.59%), Indraprastha Gas (down 1.52%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 1.02%), Gujarat State Petronet (down 0.51%), GAIL (India) (down 0.44%), Mahanagar Gas (down 0.33%) and Indian Oil Corporation (down 0.32%) declined. On the other hand, Aegis Logistics (up 5.77%), Gujarat Gas (up 0.67%) and Reliance Industries (up 0.36%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.09% to 6.693 as compared with the previous close of 6.699. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9300 compared with its close of 91.9950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement dropped 3.78% to Rs 1,62,999. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.23% to 96.36. The United States 10-year bond yield gained 1.14% to 4.276. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement lost $1.01 or 1.45% to $68.67 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Cupid surged 7.84% after the company reported a 196.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 32.83 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 11.08 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 101.70% YoY to Rs 93.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. TD Power Systems zoomed 9.29% after the company reported a 25.4% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 56.32 crore on a 26.4% rise in net sales to Rs 442.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>