<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:48:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prime Minister highlights transformative role of AI across diverse sectors]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prime-minister-highlights-transformative-role-of-ai-across-diverse-sectors/1678059</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678059</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi today welcomed the world leaders, captains of industry, innovators, policymakers, researchers, and technology enthusiasts from across the globe to the AI Impact Summit at Bharat Mandapam, New Delhi.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi today welcomed the world leaders, captains of industry, innovators, policymakers, researchers, and technology enthusiasts from across the globe to the AI Impact Summit at Bharat Mandapam, New Delhi. The Summit, themed “Sarvajana Hitaya, Sarvajana Sukhaya — Welfare for All, Happiness for All”, reflects India’s commitment to harnessing Artificial Intelligence for human-centric progress and inclusive development. The Prime Minister highlighted the transformative role of AI across diverse sectors including healthcare, education, agriculture, governance, and enterprise. He expressed confidence that the deliberations at the Summit will enrich global discourse on innovation, collaboration, and responsible use of AI, shaping a future that is progressive, innovative, and opportunity-driven. Prime Minister Modi underscored India’s leadership in the global AI transformation, powered by the strength of its 1.4 billion people, robust digital public infrastructure, vibrant startup ecosystem, and cutting-edge research. He emphasized that India’s strides in AI reflect both ambition and responsibility, positioning the nation at the forefront of technological advancement.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-using-tablet-computer-with-magnifying-glass-pic_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brainbees Solutions Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brainbees-solutions-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678056</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678056</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps (India) Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd and PTC India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 16 February 2026.

Shakti Pumps (India) Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd and PTC India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 16 February 2026. Brainbees Solutions Ltd lost 11.21% to Rs 239.5 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.88 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 99845 shares in the past one month. Shakti Pumps (India) Ltd tumbled 10.30% to Rs 574.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62944 shares in the past one month. Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd crashed 9.93% to Rs 358. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 81235 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19745 shares in the past one month. Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd pared 9.13% to Rs 151.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 73176 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 40848 shares in the past one month. PTC India Ltd dropped 7.49% to Rs 171.1. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.56 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrainbeesSolutionsLtd_65573979_68149.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude oil sees mild selling pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-oil-sees-mild-selling-pressure/1678057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678057</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures hovered below $63 per barrel in early electronic trading on Monday as markets closely monitored a second round of US-Iran nuclear talks scheduled in Geneva.

WTI crude oil futures hovered below $63 per barrel in early electronic trading on Monday as markets closely monitored a second round of US-Iran nuclear talks scheduled in Geneva. Hopes that renewed diplomacy could ease geopolitical risks have kept traders cautious, limiting upside momentum. Oil prices weakened further last week after comments from US President Donald Trump raised expectations of a possible deal with Tehran within the next month. Brent crude slipped around 0.5% on the week, while WTI lost about 1%, reflecting reduced risk premiums. Beyond geopolitics, prices remain pressured by ample global supply. Reports suggest some OPEC+ members see scope to resume supply hikes as early as April, while the International Energy Agency reaffirmed expectations of a sizeable oil surplus in 2026 and trimmed its demand growth outlook.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold finds support from cooling inflation, Fed bets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-finds-support-from-cooling-inflation-fed-bets/1678054</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678054</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures recouped earlier losses to trade near $5,030 per ounce, finding support from a softer US dollar amid holiday-thinned trading.

Gold futures recouped earlier losses to trade near $5,030 per ounce, finding support from a softer US dollar amid holiday-thinned trading. The dollar index hovered below 97 as subdued US inflation data reinforced expectations that the Federal Reserve may begin easing policy later this year. US headline inflation slowed to 2.4% last month, helping gold secure a second consecutive weekly gain and underpinning medium-term rate-cut expectations. In domestic trade, April gold futures on the MCX slipped below Rs 155,000 per 10 grams, easing by Rs 441. Investor focus now shifts to the release of FOMC meeting minutes, the US advance GDP estimate, and PCE inflation data for clearer signals on the timing of policy easing. Geopolitical developments, including renewed US-Iran nuclear talks and negotiations aimed at ending the war in Ukraine, also remain firmly in focus.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Arkade Developers signs cluster redevelopment deal worth Rs 700-cr GDV ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/arkade-developers-signs-cluster-redevelopment-deal-worth-rs-700-cr-gdv/1678052</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678052</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project spans a total plot area of approximately 6,553 square metres and is planned as a large-scale cluster redevelopment with an estimated gross development value (GDV) of around Rs 700 crore.

The project spans a total plot area of approximately 6,553 square metres and is planned as a large-scale cluster redevelopment with an estimated gross development value (GDV) of around Rs 700 crore. Strategically situated along SV Road, the project offers strong connectivity to key business districts, social infrastructure, and major transport corridors in Mumbai’s western suburbs. Under the proposed development, Arkade Developers will deliver a modern residential project aligned with contemporary urban living standards, while upgrading lifestyle amenities and infrastructure for existing society members. The development further strengthens the company’s presence in the western suburbs, a key focus market. This follows the recent registration of a development agreement for a redevelopment project in Goregaon West, spanning 4,640.60 square metres with a projected GDV of Rs 350 crore. With the addition of the Malad West project, the company continues to expand its redevelopment pipeline across Western Mumbai, particularly in the Goregaon–Malad micro market. Amit Jain, chairman & managing director, Arkade Developers said “Cluster redevelopment remains a core growth driver for Arkade Developers, and this project at Malad West reinforces our commitment to transforming aging housing stock into futureready residential communities. Shree Rani Sati Nagar’s strategic location and scale make it a landmark opportunity, and we are confident of creating long-term value for residents, stakeholders, and homebuyers.” Arkade Developers is a real estate development company concentrating on the development of premium aspirational lifestyle residential premises in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India’s commercial capital. The company is engaged in the development of new projects (development/construction of residential premises on land acquired by the company) and redevelopment of existing premises. The company's consolidated net profit tumbled 19.54% to Rs 40.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 45.81 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 12.42% year-on-year to Rs 196.73 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter shed 0.33% to Rs 121.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArkadeDevelopersLtd_19074284_91895.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Delphi World Money Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/delphi-world-money-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678050</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678050</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sarthak Metals Ltd, Next Mediaworks Ltd, TIL Ltd and Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 16 February 2026.

Sarthak Metals Ltd, Next Mediaworks Ltd, TIL Ltd and Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 16 February 2026. Delphi World Money Ltd crashed 14.58% to Rs 14.35 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.65 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 38165 shares in the past one month. Sarthak Metals Ltd lost 12.98% to Rs 74.84. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1844 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1727 shares in the past one month. Next Mediaworks Ltd tumbled 12.56% to Rs 5.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 200 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 996 shares in the past one month. TIL Ltd plummeted 12.52% to Rs 226.45. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 16478 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1519 shares in the past one month. Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Ltd fell 12.06% to Rs 794.55. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 22085 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3649 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WeizmannFor_53863006980_41315.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Texmaco Rail & Engineering bags Rs 23-cr order from South Western Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/texmaco-rail-engineering-bags-rs-23-cr-order-from-south-western-railway/1678051</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678051</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves comprehensive annual maintenance and breakdown restoration of Overhead Equipment (OHE) and power supply installations across the Mysore Division, covering 1,046 track kilometres (TKM) of electrification infrastructure and associated electrical assets.

The order involves comprehensive annual maintenance and breakdown restoration of Overhead Equipment (OHE) and power supply installations across the Mysore Division, covering 1,046 track kilometres (TKM) of electrification infrastructure and associated electrical assets. The contract is to be executed within 24 months from the date of issuance of the Letter of Acceptance. The company said that neither the promoter nor promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not fall under related party transactions. Texmaco Rail & Engineering (TEXMACO) is a listed company and part of the Adventz Group. Texmaco is a key player in the railway and infrastructure sector. It operates across three business segments: Freight Cars, Rail Infrastructure & Green Energy, and Infrastructure – Electrical. The company reported a 44.65% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 42.27 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 76.38 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 21.45% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,041.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of Texmaco Rail & Engineering fell 1.81% to Rs 111.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TexmacoRail_96355740994_27419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CarTrade Tech jumps after unveiling multi-agent AI ecosystem]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cartrade-tech-jumps-after-unveiling-multi-agent-ai-ecosystem/1678048</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678048</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said it will deploy a fleet of specialised AI agents across its core brands, including CarWale, BikeWale, OLX India, and Shriram Automall India.

The company said it will deploy a fleet of specialised AI agents across its core brands, including CarWale, BikeWale, OLX India, and Shriram Automall India. These AI agents will manage end-to-end digital interactions such as vehicle discovery, pricing recommendations, trade-ins, loan approvals, listing assistance, buyer-seller matchmaking, bidding and transaction support. On its consumer platforms CarWale and BikeWale, the AI-powered "Sales Agent" will guide users through the full retail journey, from discovery to financing. On OLX India, multiple AI agents will assist in pricing, matching buyers and sellers, and improving hyperlocal discovery. At Shriram Automall, AI-led buying and bidding tools will streamline auctions and cross-geography transactions. CarTrade Tech said each of CarWale, BikeWale and OLX India attracts over 150 million annual users, with nearly 95% of traffic generated organically, underscoring brand stickiness and network strength. The company plans to leverage over a decade of proprietary data to enhance transaction velocity and customer outcomes. Financially, the company highlighted a three-year revenue CAGR of 32% and a profit after tax CAGR of 83%. Consolidated total income has reached an annualised run rate of around Rs 1,000 crore in Q3 FY26, while the balance sheet remains strong with over Rs 1,145 crore in cash and minimal capital expenditure needs. The company said the AI-led transformation is designed to deepen engagement, improve conversion rates and unlock further operating leverage as the company moves into its next phase of growth. CarTrade Tech reported a 4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 61.52 crore on a 2.8% rise in total income from operations to Rs 228.38 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit and revenue jumped 35.12%, and total income rose 18.36% in Q3 FY26. CarTrade Tech is India's largest digital marketplace ecosystem, operating multiple platforms including CarWale, BikeWale, CarTrade, OLX India, Shriram Automall, CarTrade Exchange, and Adroit Auto. These platforms empower millions of users, including consumers, dealers, OEMs, and enterprises, to buy and sell vehicles, real estate, electronics, mobile phones, furniture, and more with ease and efficiency.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cartrade--Tech-Ltd_25528484_65036.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 394 pts; PSU bank shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-394-pts-psu-bank-shares-advance/1678046</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678046</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,600 level after hitting the day’s low of 25,372.70 in early trade. PSU Bank shares advanced after declining in the previous two trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 393.93 points or 0.48% to 83,020.69. The Nifty 50 index rose 150.15 points or 0.59% to 25,621.30. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.31% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.29%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,688 shares rose and 2,529 shares fell. A total of 185 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s wholesale price index (WPI) inflation increased to 1.81% in January 2026 compared with 0.83% in December 2025. The positive rate of inflation in January 2026 was due to an increase in prices of the manufacture of basic metals, other manufacturing, non-food articles, food articles, and textiles, among others. Food inflation picked up to 1.41% in January after remaining flat at 0.00% in December. India’s foreign exchange reserves fell to $717.6 billion as of February 6, 2026, dropping by $6.71 billion, data from the Reserve Bank of India showed. Meanwhile, data showed a dip in foreign currency assets (FCAs), which declined by $7.66 billion to $570.05 billion during the week. Gold holdings also recorded a sharp drop by $14.2 billion to $123.47 billion. Meanwhile, Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) decreased by $132 million to $18.82 billion. India’s reserve tranche position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) edged down by $32 million to $4.71 billion. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index rose 1.09% to 9,266.55. The index rose 0.18% over the previous two trading sessions. Canara Bank (up 2.14%), Bank of India (up 2.13%), Bank of Baroda (up 1.51%), Indian Overseas Bank (up 1.15%), Punjab National Bank (up 0.82%), Indian Bank (up 0.76%), Union Bank of India (up 0.69%), Central Bank of India (up 0.62%), UCO Bank (up 0.6%) and Punjab & Sind Bank (up 0.44%) rose. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.04% to 6.674 compared with the previous session close of 6.677. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6150 compared with its close of 90.6650 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.30% to Rs 155,435. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 96.96. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.25% to 4.042. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement shed 15 cents or 0.22% to $67.60 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Precision Wires India soared 15.39% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 98.89% to Rs 37.69 crore on 36.55% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1336.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. KFin Technologies rallied 3.86% after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 2.02% to Rs 91.99 crore on 27.88% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 370.87 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Natco Pharma Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-natco-pharma-ltd-counter/1678045</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678045</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, RHI Magnesita India Ltd, Brainbees Solutions Ltd, Inox Wind Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 16 February 2026.

Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, RHI Magnesita India Ltd, Brainbees Solutions Ltd, Inox Wind Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 16 February 2026. Natco Pharma Ltd witnessed volume of 188.67 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 30.19 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.25 lakh shares. The stock increased 9.68% to Rs.903.60. Volumes stood at 4.52 lakh shares in the last session. Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd registered volume of 22.18 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 21.84 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.02 lakh shares. The stock rose 6.35% to Rs.480.00. Volumes stood at 70716 shares in the last session. RHI Magnesita India Ltd registered volume of 13.51 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.47 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.43 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.88% to Rs.457.95. Volumes stood at 1.13 lakh shares in the last session. Brainbees Solutions Ltd clocked volume of 77.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.68 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10.10 lakh shares. The stock lost 10.49% to Rs.241.50. Volumes stood at 10.2 lakh shares in the last session. Inox Wind Ltd notched up volume of 456.78 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.18 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 73.91 lakh shares. The stock slipped 3.03% to Rs.103.16. Volumes stood at 78.58 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NatcoPharma_90826076038_4684.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siyaram Recycling Industries secures Rs 2-cr order from Charbhuja Impex]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siyaram-recycling-industries-secures-rs-2-cr-order-from-charbhuja-impex/1678047</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678047</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company stated that the order will be executed within six months.

The company stated that the order will be executed within six months. It further clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group members have any interest in the awarding entity. The company also confirmed that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Siyaram Recycling Industries is primarily engaged in the recycling of brass scrap. On a full-year basis, the company's net profit jumped 93.8% to Rs 14.57 crore on a 23.9% rise in net sales to Rs 511.56 crore in FY25 over FY24. The counter slipped 2.86% to Rs 51 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiyaramRecyclingIndustriesLtd_80297349_92151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India wholesale price inflation rises 1.81% in January]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-wholesale-price-inflation-rises-181-in-january/1678043</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678043</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's wholesale prices increased in January to hit the highest level in ten months, official data revealed on Monday.

India's wholesale prices increased in January to hit the highest level in ten months, official data revealed on Monday. The wholesale price index, or WPI, rose 1.81 percent year-over-year in January, faster than the 0.83 percent rise in December. Further, this was the fastest growth since March 2025, when prices had risen more than 2.0 percent. The annual price growth in manufactured products accelerated to 2.86 percent from 1.82 percent. Food prices showed an increase of 1.41 percent after remaining flat in December, and inflation based on primary articles quickened to 2.21 percent from 0.21 percent. Meanwhile, the decline in costs for fuel and power deepened to 4.01 percent from 2.31 percent. On a monthly basis, wholesale prices rose at a stable rate of 0.51 percent.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Precision Wires hits record high after Q3 PAT climbs 99% YoY to Rs 38 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/precision-wires-hits-record-high-after-q3-pat-climbs-99-yoy-to-rs-38-cr/1678037</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678037</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) surged 108.25% YoY to Rs 52.23 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) surged 108.25% YoY to Rs 52.23 crore during the quarter. Total expenses rose 35.33% YoY to Rs 1,295.36 crore in Q3 FY26. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 1,294.23 crore (up 41.3% YoY), employee benefit expenses was at Rs 14.32 crore (up 12.93% YoY) while finance cost was at Rs 16.06 crore (up 56.07% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved availing of a new unsecured working capital facility from a CSB Bank for an aggregate amount of Rs 100 crore. Precision Wires India is engaged in the manufacturing of enamelled round and rectangular copper winding wires, continuously transposed conductors (CTC) and paper/mica/nomex insulated copper conductors (PICC). These products are primarily used in the electrical and electronics industries. The counter hit an all-time high at Rs 306 in intraday today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PrecWiresI_58863061203_2400.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex spurts 317 pts; realty shares outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-spurts-317-pts-realty-shares-outperforms/1678030</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678030</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,550 mark. Realty, private bank and pharma shared advanced while auto, media and IT shares declined. At 13:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 317.07 points or 0.39% to 82,945.23. The Nifty 50 index added 111.60 points or 0.43% to 25,579.50. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.39% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.11%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,688 shares rose and 2,471 shares fell. A total of 211 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s wholesale price index (WPI) inflation increased to 1.81% in January 2026 compared with 0.83% in December 2025. The positive rate of inflation in January 2026 was due to an increase in prices of the manufacture of basic metals, other manufacturing, non-food articles, food articles and textiles, among others. Food inflation picked up to 1.41% in January after remaining flat at 0.00% in December. Gainers & Losers: Power Grid Corporation of India (up 4.37%), Coal India (up 3.42%), HDFC Bank (up 2.53%), Adani Enterprises (up 2.08%) and Axis Bank (up 1.96%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Coal India (down 2.34%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 1.88%), Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (down 1.41%), HCL Technologies (down 1.30%) and ITC (down 1.26%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Alkem Laboratories added 1.58% after the company has informed that the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) has completed a pre-approval inspection (PAI) at the manufacturing facility of Enzene Biosciences in India (Enzene), a subsidiary of the company in India. KFin Technologies rallied 4.70 after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 2.02% to Rs 91.99 crore on 27.88% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 370.87 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Desco Infratech rallied 3.37% after it has received significant purchase orders in the power and solar infrastructure segments totaling Rs 40.43 crore. GK Energy locked into a 5% upper circuit after the company reported a 57.74% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 58.83 crore on a 43.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 460.20 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets opened higher on Monday as investors digest the key points from this year’s Munich Security Conference. Most Asian shares traded higher amid thin trading due to the Lunar New Year holiday, while weak economic data from Japan weighed on sentiment in that market. Markets in China, South Korea, Taiwan, and the United States were closed, keeping activity in currencies, commodities, and bond markets largely subdued. Japan reported that its economy grew just 0.1% on an annualized basis in the December quarter, much lower than expectations, mainly due to lower government spending. The weak data highlights the challenges facing Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and may strengthen the case for additional government spending to support growth. Wall Street markets were mostly steady on Friday after January inflation data came in largely in line with expectations. The S&P 500 ended flat at 6,836.17 points. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.2%, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average edged up 0.1% to 49,500.93 points. Data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that consumer prices rose 0.2% in January compared to the previous month and increased 2.4% compared to a year earlier. The inflation numbers offered only limited support to stocks, as hopes of lower interest rates were offset by ongoing concerns about the impact of artificial intelligence on businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HCL Technologies Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hcl-technologies-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1678031</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678031</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HCL Technologies Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

HCL Technologies Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1453.3, down 0.13% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.38% on the day, quoting at 25567.95. The Sensex is at 82893.76, up 0.32%.HCL Technologies Ltd has lost around 15.35% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which HCL Technologies Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 16.62% in last one month and is currently quoting at 32681.5, down 0.75% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 15.24 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 30.67 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1450.6, down 0.43% on the day. HCL Technologies Ltd tumbled 15.01% in last one year as compared to a 11.36% rally in NIFTY and a 21.03% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 32.17 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HCLTechnologies_63631997_5656.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mphasis Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mphasis-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1678032</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678032</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mphasis Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Mphasis Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2440.1, down 0.74% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.38% on the day, quoting at 25567.95. The Sensex is at 82893.76, up 0.32%.Mphasis Ltd has eased around 15.56% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Mphasis Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 16.62% in last one month and is currently quoting at 32681.5, down 0.75% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.09 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.78 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2445.2, down 0.44% on the day. Mphasis Ltd tumbled 5.84% in last one year as compared to a 11.36% rally in NIFTY and a 21.03% fall in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 32.86 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Mphasis_88855176_3361.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hathway-cable-datacom-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1678033</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678033</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 11.05, down 1.69% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.38% on the day, quoting at 25567.95. The Sensex is at 82893.76, up 0.32%.Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd has lost around 7.3% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 4.75% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1462.8, down 0.85% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 11.7 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 27.98 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 27.37 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HathwayCable_63160375018_20659.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen slips as Japan Q4 growth misses expectations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-slips-as-japan-q4-growth-misses-expectations/1678027</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678027</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The yen eased toward 153 per dollar, trimming last week’s gains after Japan’s Q4 GDP rose just 0.1% QoQ, well below expectations and underscoring weak domestic demand.

The yen eased toward 153 per dollar, trimming last week’s gains after Japan’s Q4 GDP rose just 0.1% QoQ, well below expectations and underscoring weak domestic demand. Consumer spending increased only marginally as elevated inflation continued to weigh on households. Despite the pullback, the yen remains supported by optimism around Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s fiscal expansion plans, expectations of further rate hikes by the Bank of Japan, and lingering currency intervention risks. A softer dollar, after benign US inflation reinforced rate-cut bets for the Federal Reserve, helped cap losses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siemens-energy-india-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1678025</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678025</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Siemens Energy India Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2810, up 2.55% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.33% on the day, quoting at 25554. The Sensex is at 82870.82, up 0.3%. Siemens Energy India Ltd has gained around 21.28% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Siemens Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 6.11% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35709.9, up 1.38% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 7.17 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.65 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 88.24 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiemensEnergyIndiaLtd_11731431_93274.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd soars 4.69%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/torrent-pharmaceuticals-ltd-soars-469/1678026</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678026</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 4269.3, up 4.69% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.33% on the day, quoting at 25554. The Sensex is at 82870.82, up 0.3%. Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd has risen around 4.47% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.09% in last one month and is currently quoting at 22194.9, up 0.82% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 12.03 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.05 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 4229, up 4.71% on the day. Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd is up 38.7% in last one year as compared to a 11.3% spurt in NIFTY and a 6.17% spurt in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 64.61 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TorrentPharma_35676110126_3616.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>