<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:57:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Japan yen stabilizes near 155.6 on policy caution signals  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/japan-yen-stabilizes-near-1556-on-policy-caution-signals/1679445</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679445</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen bounced back toward 155.6 per dollar on Wednesday after sliding in the previous session, as comments from Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi signaling concern over further rate hikes reinforced expectations of a cautious Bank of Japan.

The Japanese yen bounced back toward 155.6 per dollar on Wednesday after sliding in the previous session, as comments from Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi signaling concern over further rate hikes reinforced expectations of a cautious Bank of Japan. The yen also drew support from a weaker US dollar, with the dollar index slipping below 97.6 after President Donald Trump offered no change to tariff policy in his State of the Union address. Markets remain alert to trade developments, especially after the US Supreme Court struck down tariffs imposed under emergency powers, keeping currency sentiment sensitive to policy clarity.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Secmark Consultancy Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/secmark-consultancy-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1679443</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679443</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jindal Poly Films Ltd, Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd, Sumeet Industries Ltd and A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 25 February 2026.

Jindal Poly Films Ltd, Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd, Sumeet Industries Ltd and A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 25 February 2026. Secmark Consultancy Ltd soared 19.97% to Rs 121.05 at 11:59 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 3418 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 381 shares in the past one month. Jindal Poly Films Ltd surged 11.98% to Rs 618.15. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 48384 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5184 shares in the past one month. Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd spiked 10.00% to Rs 97.02. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 456 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 850 shares in the past one month. Sumeet Industries Ltd spurt 10.00% to Rs 24.43. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 3807 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8855 shares in the past one month. A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd jumped 9.96% to Rs 17.44. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 58538 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 29409 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SecMarkConsultancyLtd._72779962_75094.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concord Biotech Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concord-biotech-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1679437</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679437</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jai Balaji Industries Ltd, TVS Holdings Ltd, Usha Martin Ltd and Hero MotoCorp Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 25 February 2026.

Jai Balaji Industries Ltd, TVS Holdings Ltd, Usha Martin Ltd and Hero MotoCorp Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 25 February 2026. Concord Biotech Ltd spiked 11.18% to Rs 1198.6 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 30016 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18992 shares in the past one month. Jai Balaji Industries Ltd soared 10.48% to Rs 67.17. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 10.05 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 57591 shares in the past one month. TVS Holdings Ltd surged 6.45% to Rs 15234.15. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 941 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 400 shares in the past one month. Usha Martin Ltd advanced 6.00% to Rs 430.85. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.97 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18724 shares in the past one month. Hero MotoCorp Ltd gained 5.68% to Rs 5822.8. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 19750 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16758 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ConcordBiotechLtd_67563462_72610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yashhtej Industries (India) lists at 20% discount on BSE; hits lower circuit ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yashhtej-industries-india-lists-at-20-discount-on-bse-hits-lower-circuit/1679438</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679438</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 88, a 20% discount to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 88, a 20% discount to the issue price. The stock was locked in a 5% lower circuit from the listing price. It touched a high of Rs 88 and a low of Rs 83.60, with around 0.77 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Yashhtej Industries (India) IPO was subscribed 1.35 times. The issue opened for bidding on 18 February 2026 and it closed on 20 February 2025. The price of the IPO was fixed at Rs 110 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 80,79,600 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 65% from 100% Pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for capital expenditures, funding of working capital requirements and for general corporate purpose. Yashhtej Industries (India) is engaged in the business of manufacturing and processing soybean crude oil through the solvent extraction process, along with the production of Soybean De-Oiled Cake (DOC). DOC, also known as soya meal, is the protein-rich solid residue left after oil extraction and is widely used in the animal feed industry due to its high nutritional value. The company operates primarily in the B2B segment, supplying soybean crude oil to customers involved in refining activities for edible oil production. In addition to its core agro-processing operations, the company has diversified into solar power generation and supply, strengthening its sustainability focus and operational efficiency. Yashhtej Industries benefits from automated manufacturing processes, an in-house laboratory for stringent quality checks, customization capabilities in DOC offerings, and access to government incentives. The company is also moving towards forward integration into the edible soybean oil segment, enhancing its value chain presence. As of 30 September 2025, the company had 91 permanent employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 191.15 crore and net profit of Rs 7.25 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-investment-entrepreneur-trading-concept-pictu_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PGIM India Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pgim-india-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1679434</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679434</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PGIM India Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

PGIM India Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Akhil Dhar has been appointed as Fund Manager and Credit Analyst – Fixed Income with effect from February 25, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Mr. Akhil Dhar Age: 34 years Designation: Fund Manager and Credit Analyst – Fixed Income Qualification: PGDBM (Finance) and B.E (Electrical) .

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex gains 518 pts; metal shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-gains-518-pts-metal-shares-advance/1679433</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679433</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The frontline equity benchmarks traded with substantial gains in the mid-morning trade, supported by a recovery in technology stocks following the previous session’s sharp selloff that had dragged the indices lower.

The frontline equity benchmarks traded with substantial gains in the mid-morning trade, supported by a recovery in technology stocks following the previous session’s sharp selloff that had dragged the indices lower. The Nifty traded above the 25,600 level. Metal extended gains for the second consecutive trading session. At 11:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, surged 518 points or 0.63% to 82,744.85. The Nifty 50 index gained 181.30 points or 0.71% to 25,605.95. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index jumped 0.66% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rallied 0.54%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,232 shares rose and 1,567 shares fell. A total of 217 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Omnitech Engineering received bids for 3,29,868 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.02 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026 and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 35,81,248 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.63 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 4,64,04,000 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 4.38 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 1,09,03,774 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.50 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index surged 2.55% to 12,381.75. The index rallied 3.50% in two consecutive trading sessions. Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 4.97%), Vedanta (up 4.86%), National Aluminium Company (up 4.05%), Steel Authority of India (up 3.58%), Tata Steel (up 3.32%), Hindustan Zinc (up 2.75%), Hindalco Industries (up 2.20%), Hindustan Copper (up 2%), Jindal Steel (up 1.80%) and Welspun Corp (up 1.56%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) added 1.74% after the company said its Power Transmission & Distribution (PT&D) vertical has secured ‘major’ EPC orders to establish electricity grid system elements in India and overseas. Schaeffler India rallied 5.36% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 31.54% to Rs 322.36 crore on 26.53% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 2643.06 crore in Q4 CY2025 over Q4 CY2024. Global Markets: Asian markets edged higher with South Korea and Japan stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gaudium IVF and Women Health IPO ends with 7.27 times subscription]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gaudium-ivf-and-women-health-ipo-ends-with-727-times-subscription/1679432</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679432</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 10,63,50,489 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer.

The initial public offer (IPO) of Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 10,63,50,489 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 7.27 times. The Non-Institutional Investors category was subscribed 14.05 times, the Retail Individual Investors category was subscribed 7.60 times and the Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB) category was subscribed 1.62 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it closed on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 189 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The IPO comprised a fresh issue of 1,13,92,500 equity shares, worth up to Rs 90 crore, and an offer for sale of 9,493,700 equity shares, aggregating up to Rs 75 crore, by Dr. Manika Khanna. The objectives for the fresh issue include Rs 50 crore for funding capital expenditure towards the establishment of new IVF centers, Rs 20 crore for repayment and prepayment of certain outstanding loans, and the remaining amount for general corporate purposes. The promoters and promoter group hold an aggregate of 6,13,85,084 equity shares, aggregating to 99.99% of the pre-offer issued and paid-up equity share capital. Their post-IPO shareholding is expected to be around 71.29%. Ahead of the IPO of Gaudium IVF and Women Health on 19 February 2026, the company raised Rs 49.50 crore from anchor investors by allotting 62.65 lakh shares at Rs 79 each to 4 anchor investors. Gaudium IVF and Women Health (est. 2015) is an India-based fertility chain operating 30+ centers under a hub-and-spoke model. It offers IVF, ICSI, IUI, fertility preservation, and related gynecology services. IVF contributes approximately 69% of revenue, with a success rate of 58.74% and average revenue per patient of Rs 2.58 lakh. The company plans to add 19 new centers over FY26–FY28 to expand its footprint. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 4.28 crore and income from operations of Rs 49.50 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/USD holds above 1.3500 mark, tepid economic cues can gains]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpusd-holds-above-13500-mark-tepid-economic-cues-can-gains/1679429</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679429</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound is attempting to hold above 1.3500 mark though tepid economic cues and lax equities are capping the currency.

British Pound is attempting to hold above 1.3500 mark though tepid economic cues and lax equities are capping the currency. The GBP/USD pair has moved up from four-week low near 1.3430 mark in last week. Gains have been moderate but the tendency of the counter to sustain above 1.3500 level is turning supportive as it nears one-week high. The pair currently trades at 1.3518, up 0.12% on the day. Meanwhile, UK retailers reported a sharp decline in sales in February due to poor weather conditions, the Distributive Trades Survey results from the Confederation of British Industry showed on Tuesday. The retail sales balance eased to -43 percent in February from -17 percent in January. This can likely cap advances for the GBP/USD pair. On NSE, GBP/INR futures are currently quoting at 122.95, up 0.25% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PGIM Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pgim-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1679428</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679428</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PGIM Mutual Fund has announced change in Fund Manager of the following schemes with effect from: 25 February, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager of the Schemes: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) PGIM India Overnight Fund Mr.

PGIM Mutual Fund has announced change in Fund Manager of the following schemes with effect from: 25 February, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager of the Schemes: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) PGIM India Overnight Fund Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Sandeep Devan Mr. Puneet Pal PGIM India Liquid Fund Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Akhil Dhar PGIM India Ultra Short Term Fund Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Akhil Dhar PGIM India Money Market Fund Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Akhil Dhar PGIM India Dynamic Bond Fund Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Akhil Dhar PGIM India Corporate Bond Fund Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Akhil Dhar PGIM India Gilt Fund Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Akhil Dhar PGIM India CRISIL IBX Gilt Index - Apr 2028 Fund Mr. Puneet Pal Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Sandeep Devan Mr. Puneet Pal PGIM India Large Cap Fund Mr. A. Anandha Mr. Vivek Sharma Mr. Vinay Paharia Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. A. Anandha Mr. Vivek Sharma Mr. Vinay Paharia Mr. Akhil Dhar PGIM India ELSS Tax Saver Fund Mr. Vivek Sharma Mr. Utsav Mehta Mr. Vinay Paharia Mr. Bhupesh Kalyani Mr. Vivek Sharma Mr. Utsav Mehta Mr. Vinay Paharia Mr. Akhil Dhar

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[First round of negotiations for India-Israel Free Trade Agreement commence]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/first-round-of-negotiations-for-india-israel-free-trade-agreement-commence/1679426</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679426</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Commerce & Industry has stated that the first round of negotiations for the India-Israel Free Trade Agreement (FTA) commenced on 23 February 2026 in New Delhi, and is scheduled to take place until 26 February 2026.

Ministry of Commerce & Industry has stated that the first round of negotiations for the India-Israel Free Trade Agreement (FTA) commenced on 23 February 2026 in New Delhi, and is scheduled to take place until 26 February 2026. The Terms of Reference (ToR) was signed in November 2025 establishing a structured framework for discussions on identified areas to enhance trade, and economic cooperation. Total merchandise trade between the two countries stood at USD 3.62 billion in FY 2024-2025. India and Israel share complementarities across several sectors, and the FTA will be a catalyst to further enhance the bilateral trade by providing certainty and predictability to businesses, including MSMEs. During this round, technical experts from both sides will engage in sessions covering various aspects of FTA such as trade in goods, trade in services, rules of origin, sanitary and phytosanitary measures, technical barriers to trade, customs procedure and trade facilitation, intellectual property rights, among others.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-markets-currency-trading-concept-picture-id609801990_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Premier Energies Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-premier-energies-ltd-counter/1679424</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679424</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Communications Ltd, Usha Martin Ltd, Schaeffler India Ltd, Waaree Energies Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 25 February 2026.

Tata Communications Ltd, Usha Martin Ltd, Schaeffler India Ltd, Waaree Energies Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 25 February 2026. Premier Energies Ltd notched up volume of 5.6 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 10.35 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 54106 shares. The stock slipped 5.32% to Rs.736.40. Volumes stood at 66214 shares in the last session. Tata Communications Ltd notched up volume of 71499 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.85 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7258 shares. The stock slipped 1.36% to Rs.1,597.10. Volumes stood at 5950 shares in the last session. Usha Martin Ltd saw volume of 2 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.75 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 20544 shares. The stock increased 7.15% to Rs.435.50. Volumes stood at 7045 shares in the last session. Schaeffler India Ltd clocked volume of 42533 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.73 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4371 shares. The stock gained 4.05% to Rs.4,247.80. Volumes stood at 10232 shares in the last session. Waaree Energies Ltd saw volume of 5.68 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.12 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 69936 shares. The stock dropped 10.59% to Rs.2,704.95. Volumes stood at 1.74 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PremierEnergiesLtd_39693029_76751.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India and Gulf Cooperation Council sign joint statement on India–GCC free trade agreement ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-and-gulf-cooperation-council-sign-joint-statement-on-indiagcc-free-trade-agreement/1679425</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679425</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Joint Statement on the India-GCC Free Trade Agreement (FTA) was signed between Piyush Goyal, Union Minister of Commerce and Industry and His Excellency Jasem Mohamed Albudaiwi, Secretary General of the Gulf Cooperation Council on 24th February 2026 in New Delhi formally launching negotiations for a comprehensive and mutually beneficial agreement.

The Joint Statement on the India-GCC Free Trade Agreement (FTA) was signed between Piyush Goyal, Union Minister of Commerce and Industry and His Excellency Jasem Mohamed Albudaiwi, Secretary General of the Gulf Cooperation Council on 24th February 2026 in New Delhi formally launching negotiations for a comprehensive and mutually beneficial agreement. Piyush Goyal emphasized that the Statement along with the Terms of Reference (ToR) for FTA which were signed on 5thFebruary, 2026, mark a significant milestone in the relationship between India and GCC countries. He underscored that the relationship which is deeply rooted in shared history and cultural linkages, would get further impetus from a broad-based and mutually beneficial FTA. Jasem Mohamed Albudaiwi emphasized that FTA will serve as an important tool to further strengthen trade and investment ties between India and GCC countries by infusing predictability and certainty for businesses. The FTA holds significant potential to unlock and expand trade with an important region, with which India has longstanding historical ties in trade and commerce. GCC is India's largest trading partner bloc with bilateral trade reachingUSD 178.56 billion (Exports: USD 56.87 billion; Imports: USD 121.68 billion) in FY 2024-25, accounting for 15.42% of India’s global trade. In the last five years, India’s trade with the GCC has expanded steadily, registering an annual average growth rate of 15.3 per cent.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/hands-people-woman-girl_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Larsen & Toubro gains after PT&D arm bags major EPC orders in India, Overseas]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/larsen-toubro-gains-after-ptd-arm-bags-major-epc-orders-in-india-overseas/1679423</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679423</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order has been classified as 'major,' indicating a value in the range of Rs 5,000 crore to Rs 10,000 crore.

The order has been classified as 'major,' indicating a value in the range of Rs 5,000 crore to Rs 10,000 crore. In India, the PT&D arm has bagged an order for the design, supply and construction of two 220 kV Gas Insulated Substations in the Durgapur–Raniganj–Asansol industrial belt of West Bengal. The scope includes associated transmission line segments featuring advanced conductors and multi-circuit towers. These grid modernisation projects are aimed at ensuring a stable voltage profile and enhancing the reliability of power networks supporting infrastructure and industrial growth in the region. In the Middle East, the business vertical has won turnkey orders from key utilities for the construction of five substations and over 250 km of transmission lines across three countries. The projects involve systems of up to 500 kV. One of the contracts also includes the supply and installation of a 400 kV underground cable system. The company said that amid rising power demand, evolving energy mix and security-driven initiatives, grid investments have emerged as high-priority areas globally. The latest wins underscore continued customer confidence in L&T’s capabilities to deliver large-scale grid infrastructure projects in a safe, sustainable and timely manner. L&T is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services, operating across multiple geographies. On a consolidated basis, L&T's net profit declined 4.27% year-on-year to Rs 3,215.11 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 10.48% to Rs 71,449.70 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India is building bridges of trade, trust and transformation and enjoys preferential trade access to nearly two-thirds of global trade:  Piyush Goyal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-is-building-bridges-of-trade-trust-and-transformation-and-enjoys-preferential-trade-access-to-nearly-two-thirds-of-global-trade-piyush-goyal/1679421</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679421</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Minister of Commerce and Industry Shri Piyush Goyal said that at a time when the world is grappling with uncertainty, India is building “bridges of trade, trust and transformation,” and now enjoys preferential trade access to nearly two-thirds of global trade owing to a series of high-quality free trade agreements (FTAs) concluded under the leadership of Prime Minister Narendra Modi.

Union Minister of Commerce and Industry Shri Piyush Goyal said that at a time when the world is grappling with uncertainty, India is building “bridges of trade, trust and transformation,” and now enjoys preferential trade access to nearly two-thirds of global trade owing to a series of high-quality free trade agreements (FTAs) concluded under the leadership of Prime Minister Narendra Modi. Goyal highlighted the rapid pace of trade engagement, noting that within a span of six hours the Minister had engaged in three FTA-related discussions. India signed a joint statement launching FTA negotiations with the six-nation bloc of the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) in the Middle East. Shortly thereafter, Goyal met the Israeli negotiating team to advance discussions on finalising an FTA. The Minister said that he will also hold discussions with the Chilean counterpart to conclude a new-age FTA that will provide India greater access to critical minerals. He further informed that the Prime Minister of Canada is expected to visit India shortly, and both sides are hopeful of finalising the terms of reference and launching FTA negotiations with Canada later this week. The Minister described this strategic network of FTAs as part of India’s approach to de-risking through diversified trade partnerships, calling it unprecedented in scale and ambition.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378254__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cabinet approves Minimum Support Prices for Raw Jute by Rs 275 per quintal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cabinet-approves-minimum-support-prices-for-raw-jute-by-rs-275-per-quintal/1679422</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679422</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs has approved Minimum Support Prices (MSP) of Raw Jute for Marketing season 2026-27.

The Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs has approved Minimum Support Prices (MSP) of Raw Jute for Marketing season 2026-27. The MSP of Raw Jute (TD-3 grade) has been fixed at Rs 5925 per quintal for 2026-27 season. This would ensure a return of 61.8 percent over the all India weighted average cost of production. The announced MSP of raw jute for Marketing season 2026-27 is in line with the principle of fixing MSP at a level of at least 1.5 times all India weighted average cost of production as announced by the Government in the Budget 2018-19. The MSP of Raw Jute for Marketing season 2026-27 is an increase of Rs 275 per quintal over the previous Marketing season 2025-26. Government has increased MSP of Raw jute from Rs 2400 per quintal in 2014-15 to Rs 5925 per quintal in 2026-27, registering an increase of Rs 3525 per quintal (2.5 times).

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs approves three projects of Ministry of Railways with total cost of Rs 9072 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cabinet-committee-on-economic-affairs-approves-three-projects-of-ministry-of-railways-with-total-cost-of-rs-9072-crore/1679416</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679416</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs has approved three projects of Ministry of Railways with total cost of Rs.

The Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs has approved three projects of Ministry of Railways with total cost of Rs. 9,072 crore (approx.). These projects include: Gondia – Jabalpur Doubling, Punarakh - Kiul 3rd and 4th line and Gamharia - Chandil 3rd and 4th line. The 3 (three) projects covering 8 Districts across the states of Maharashtra, Madhya Pradesh, Bihar and Jharkhand will increase the existing network of Indian Railways by about 307 Kms. The proposed multi-tracking project will enhance connectivity to approx. 5,407 villages, which are having a population of about 98 lakhs. The increased line capacity will significantly enhance mobility, resulting in improved operational efficiency and service reliability for Indian Railways. These multi-tracking proposals are poised to streamline operations and alleviate congestion. The projects are planned on PM-Gati Shakti National Master Plan with focus on enhancing multi-modal connectivity & logistic efficiency through integrated planning and stakeholder consultations. These projects will provide seamless connectivity for movement of people, goods, and services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/not-used-railway-3-1368776_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DSP MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under four schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dsp-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-four-schemes/1679420</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679420</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

DSP Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs. per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: DSP Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.220000 DSP Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.220000 DSP Multi Asset Allocation Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.800000 DSP Healthcare Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.900000 DSP Healthcare Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 2.100000 DSP Quant Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.500000 DSP Quant Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.500000 DSP Arbitrage Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.600000 DSP Arbitrage Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.600000 DSP Large & Mid Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 3.200000 DSP Large & Mid Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 9.300000 DSP Multicap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.800000 DSP Multicap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.000000 DSP Income Plus Arbitrage Omni FoF – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.900000 DSP Income Plus Arbitrage Omni FoF – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.900000

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,600 level; IT shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25600-level-it-shares-rally/1679415</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679415</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major gains in the morning trade, supported by a recovery in technology stocks following the previous session’s sharp selloff that had dragged the indices lower.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major gains in the morning trade, supported by a recovery in technology stocks following the previous session’s sharp selloff that had dragged the indices lower. The Nifty traded above the 25,600 level. IT shares advanced after declining in the past five consecutive trading sessions. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, surged 650.09 points or 0.79% to 82,876.01. The Nifty 50 index gained 213.55 points or 0.83% to 25,638. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 0.63% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 0.65%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,307 shares rose and 1,253 shares fell. A total of 220 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index surged 2.87% to 30,916.35. The index tumbled 9.13% in the past five consecutive trading sessions. Mphasis (up 3.67%), Infosys (up 2.83%), LTIMindtree (up 2.77%), HCL Technologies (up 2.70%), Tech Mahindra (up 2.36%), Tata Consultancy Services (up 2.26%), Persistent Systems (up 2.09%), Coforge (up 1.95%), Wipro (up 1.92%) and Oracle Financial Services Software (up 1.80%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Lupin rose 0.51%. The company said that it has received approval from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) for Brivaracetam oral solution 10 mg/mL. Biocon added 0.22%. The company said that it has received approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (U.S. FDA) for its complex formulation Liraglutide Injection.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finance-background-picture-id625756386_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Schaeffler India climbs after Q4 PAT jumps 31% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/schaeffler-india-climbs-after-q4-pat-jumps-31-yoy/1679414</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679414</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 31.51% YoY to Rs 445.46 crore in Q4 CY25.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 31.51% YoY to Rs 445.46 crore in Q4 CY25. Total expenses increased 26.04% YoY to Rs 2,243.65 crore in Q4 CY2025. Cost of material consumed was Rs 1,105.75 core (up 43.9% YoY) and employee benefit expenses added up to Rs 162.93 crore (up 32.9% YoY) during the period under review. On full year basis (CY2025), the company’s standalone net profit increased by 22.36% YoY to Rs 1,196.25 crore in CY2025. Net sales rose by 16.3% to Rs 9,395.32 crore in CY2025 from Rs 8,076.29 crore in CY2024. Harsha Kadam, managing director and chief executive officer, said: "I am happy to share that we continued our growth trajectory aided by strong performance across our domestic and intercompany exports business. Strong demand traction in the automotive industry riding on the back of the GST reforms in September and our continued trajectory of business wins in all our divisions, aided growth. Our strategic focus on localization and capital efficiency contributed to enhancing our quality of earnings while navigating changes in the regulatory environment related to labor code." Schaeffler India provides precision engineering solutions, delivering high-precision components and systems for engine, transmission, and chassis applications, along with rolling and plain bearing solutions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SchaefflerIndia_19536550509_446.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zelio E-Mobility rises after commissioning new manufacturing facility in Cuttack]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zelio-e-mobility-rises-after-commissioning-new-manufacturing-facility-in-cuttack/1679410</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679410</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The decision to set up a new unit in this region follows from the strong demand and customer acceptance received in Odisha and West Bengal.

The decision to set up a new unit in this region follows from the strong demand and customer acceptance received in Odisha and West Bengal. Theses areas have emerged as high-growth markets for the company. The new facility is expected to reduce delivery timelines currently extending up to a week from the Hisar facility and also strengthen dealer support across Eastern and Southern India. Prior to this new facility, Zelio’s total installed capacity stood at 72,000 units per annum. The newly commissioned Odisha facility would contribute 60,000 units per annum to the company’s production capacity. Additionally, the existing Hisar plant’s capacity has been enhanced from 72,000 units to 1,20,000 units per annum. The capacity increase at Hisar was achieved through process-level optimisation, installation of extended conveyor systems, and addition of machinery. The company has invested under Rs 3 crore in the Odisha facility. The plant is operational and is expected to contribute to revenue immediately. Over FY26–FY27, the Odisha plant is projected to contribute a significant share to overall revenues, the company stated. Kunal Arya, managing director, Zelio E-Mobility, said: “Eastern India has emerged as one of our strongest growth regions, with customers showing exceptional trust in our products. Setting up the Cuttack facility brings us closer to our riders and dealers, enabling faster deliveries, lower logistics costs and improved serviceability.” Zelio E-Mobility is a rapidly expanding electric two-wheeler and three-wheeler manufacturer.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZelioE-MobilityLtd_33924160_95333.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>