<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:33:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jindal Saw Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jindal-saw-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1665597</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665597</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[JSW Infrastructure Ltd, Refex Industries Ltd, CG Power & Industrial Solutions Ltd and Sequent Scientific Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalSaw_11729026871_965.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index net speculative shorts near 6-month low ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-net-speculative-shorts-near-6-month-low/1665595</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665595</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[US dollar index net speculative shorts near 6-month low 

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-42338__340_stock_exchange.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slides 573 pts; realty shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slides-573-pts-realty-shares-tumble/1665593</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665593</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sensex slides 573 pts; realty shares tumble

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Q3 PAT climbs 11% YoY to Rs 18,564 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-bank-q3-pat-climbs-11-yoy-to-rs-18564-cr/1665588</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665588</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 11.05% YoY to Rs 24,259.94 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 11.05% YoY to Rs 24,259.94 crore during the quarter. Net interest income (NII) (interest earned less interest expended) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 grew by 6.4% to Rs 32,620 crore from Rs 30,650 crore for the quarter ended 31st December 2024. Operating profit before provisions and contingencies stood at Rs 27,097.80 crore as on 31st December 2025, registering the growth of 8.39% compared with 25,000.40 crore as on 31st December 2024. Operating expenses for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 were Rs 18,770 crore as on 3st December 2025. Operating expenses excluding the estimated impact of Rs 800 crore for employee benefits under the New Labour Code were Rs 17,970 crore, as against Rs 17,110 crore during the corresponding quarter of the previous year. The core cost-to-income ratio for the quarter was at 39.2%. Provisions and contingencies for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 were Rs 2,840 crore (after release of contingent provisions of Rs 1,040 crore primarily in respect of a large borrower group fulfilling certain conditions). The bank's average deposits were Rs 27,52,400 crore for the 31st December 2025, registering a growth of 12.2% over Rs 24,52,800 crore for the 31st December 2024, and 1.5% over Rs 27,10,500 crore for the 30th September 2025. Gross advance jumped 11.9% to Rs 28,44,600 crore as on 31st December 2025, recording the growth of 11.9% over 31st December 2024. Retail loans grew by 6.9%, small and mid-market enterprises loans grew by 17.2% and corporate and other wholesale loans grew by 10.3%. Overseas advances constituted 1.7% of total advances. Gross non-performing assets (GNNPA) stood at 1.24% as on 31st December 2025 unchanged from 1.24% as of 30 September 2025, and improved from 1.42% as of 31 December 2024. Net non-performing assets (NNPA) remained stable at 0.42% as of 31 December 2025, compared with 0.42% as of 30 September 2025, and declined from 0.46% as of 31 December 2024. The bank's total capital adequacy ratio (CAR) as per Basel Ill guidelines was at 19.9% as on 31st December 2025 (20.0% as on 31st December 2024) as against a regulatory requirement of 11.9%. Tier 1 CAR was at 17.8% and common equity tier 1 capital ratio was at 17.4% as of 31st December 2025. Risk-weighted Assets were at Rs 28,80,800 crore as on 31st December 2025. HDFC Bank is India's largest private sector lender. As of 31st December 2025, the bank's distribution network was at 9,616 branches and 21,176 ATMs across 4,170 cities/ towns as against 9,143 branches and 21,049 ATMs across 4,101 cities/ towns as of December 31, 2024. The counter declined 0.88% to settle at Rs 923 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCBank_24534281400_4987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian economy continues to demonstrate resilience and momentum, says SEBI Chair]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-economy-continues-to-demonstrate-resilience-and-momentum-says-sebi-chair/1665584</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665584</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tuhin Kanta Pandey, Chairman, SEBI, has noted in a speech highlighted India’s economic strength.

Tuhin Kanta Pandey, Chairman, SEBI, has noted in a speech highlighted India’s economic strength. The latest GDP estimates project real growth of around 7.4% for 2025–26, following 6.5% growth in 2024–25. India now stands as the fourth-largest economy globally. At a time when many economies are contending with weak growth, high debt, and persistent uncertainty, India continues to demonstrate resilience and momentum. This performance rests on deliberate structural choices — investment in physical, digital and social infrastructure; reforms in taxation and sustained efforts towards improving ease of doing business. But a less discussed, yet equally powerful, transformation has been unfolding alongside: the growing centrality of capital markets in financing India’s development. He also noted that capital markets have become structural pillars of the financial architecture. Over the past ten years, equity and debt markets together have facilitated average annual issuances of about Rs 9.6 lakh crore. This is capital that has flowed into highways and ports, into renewable energy and semiconductors, into manufacturing corridors, startups, MSMEs, banks, and fintech platforms. Between Apr-Dec of FY26, companies have already raised more than Rs 3.8 trillion in equity, while corporate bond issuances have reached nearly Rs 6.8 trillion in the first nine months alone.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Bank edges lower as Q3 profit drops over 4% on higher provisions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-bank-edges-lower-as-q3-profit-drops-over-4-on-higher-provisions/1665587</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665587</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26.

Net interest income (NII) increased by 7.7% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 21,932 crore in Q3 FY26. Net interest margin was 4.30% in Q3 FY26 as against 4.25% in Q3 FY25. Non-interest income added up to Rs 7,525 crore (up 12.4% YoY) and fee income aggregated to Rs 6,180 crore (up 6.3% YoY) during the period under review. Operating expenses increased by 13.2% YoY to Rs 11,944 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 10,552 crore in Q3 FY25. This includes Rs 145 crore of provisions on an estimated basis pursuant to the new Labour Codes. There was a treasury loss of Rs 157 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared to gain of Rs 371 crore in Q3 FY25, primarily reflecting market movements. Provisions (excluding provision for tax) were Rs 2,556 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 1,227 crore in Q3 FY25. Following its annual supervisory review, RBI has directed the Bank to make a standard asset provision of Rs 1,283 crore in respect of a portfolio of agricultural priority sector credit facilities wherein the terms of the facilities were found to be not fully compliant with the regulatory requirements for classification as agricultural priority sector lending. "There is no change in asset classification or in the terms and conditions applicable to the borrowers or in the repayment behaviour of borrowers as per these terms. This additional standard asset provision will continue until the loans are repaid or renewed in conformity with the PSL classification guidelines,” the bank said in a statement. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 14,800 crore, up by _ % from Rs 15,660 crore in Q3 FY25. Total advances increased by 11.5% YoY to Rs 14,66,154 crore as on 31 December 2025. Total period-end deposits increased by 9.2% YoY to Rs 16,59,611 crore as on 31 December 2025. With the addition of 402 branches during 9M-2026, the Bank had a network of 7,385 branches and 11,983 ATMs & cash recycling machines as on 31 December 2025. The gross NPA ratio was 1.53% as on at 31 December 2025 compared to 1.96% as on 31 December 2024. The net NPA ratio was 0.37% as on 31 December 2025 compared to 0.42% as on 31 December 2024. The bank has written-off gross NPAs amounting to Rs 2,046 crore in Q3-2026. The provisioning coverage ratio on non-performing loans was 75.4% as on 31 December 2025. As on 31 December 2025, the bank held total provisions, other than specific provisions on fund-based outstanding to borrowers classified as non-performing, amounting to Rs 22,657 crore or 1.5% of loans. The bank’s total capital adequacy ratio as on 31 December 2025 was 17.34% and CET-1 ratio was 16.46% as compared to the minimum regulatory requirements of 11.70% and 8.20%, respectively. The bank’s consolidated profit after tax was Rs 12,538 crore in Q3 FY26 compared to Rs 12,883 crore in Q3-2025, down 2.68% YoY. Consolidated assets grew by 8.8% YoY to Rs 27,53,471 crore as on 31 December 2025. ICICI Bank (IBL) is a systemically important private sector bank in India. With a presence in banking, insurance, asset management, investment banking and private equity, the ICICI Group is a large player in the Indian financial system.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIBank_93786457618_5418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI issues Foreign Exchange Management -Export and Import of Goods and Services Regulations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-issues-foreign-exchange-management--export-and-import-of-goods-and-services-regulations/1665582</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665582</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India has issued the Foreign Exchange Management (Export and Import of Goods and Services) Regulations, 2026 and Directions on Export and Import of Goods and Services, which shall come into force from October 01, 2026.

The Reserve Bank of India has issued the Foreign Exchange Management (Export and Import of Goods and Services) Regulations, 2026 and Directions on Export and Import of Goods and Services, which shall come into force from October 01, 2026. The regulations are primarily principle based and intended to promote ease of doing business, especially for small exporters and importers. They are also intended to empower Authorised Dealers to provide quicker and more efficient service to their customers. These regulations and directions have been issued after examining and suitably including feedback received from stakeholders on the draft regulations and draft directions published on the Bank’s website vide Press Release dated July 02, 2024 and Press Release April 04, 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Netweb Tech jumps after Q3 PAT climbs over two-fold to Rs 73-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/netweb-tech-jumps-after-q3-pat-climbs-over-two-fold-to-rs-73-cr/1665583</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665583</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 98.06 crore during the quarter, registering the growth of 144.48% compared with Rs 40.11 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year.

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 98.06 crore during the quarter, registering the growth of 144.48% compared with Rs 40.11 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Operating EBITDA jumped 127.1% YoY to Rs 97.95 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA margin reduced 75 bps to 12.2% in Q3 FY26 from 12.9% in Q3 FY25. On segmental front, revenue from AI Systems accounted for around 64.2% of Q3 FY26 revenue. Sanjay Lodha, chairman and managing director, Netweb Technologies said: “Netweb delivers a record-breaking quarter, achieving its highest-ever income and profit. We are pleased to announce that Netweb has delivered a record quarter, achieving its highest-ever income and profit. During the quarter, Netweb successfully executed a large strategic order valued at Rs 450.39 crore, reaffirming its position as India’s largest OEM in high-end computing solutions. As communicated earlier, this implementation is of national significance, aimed at strengthening India’s AI compute infrastructure. With this, the AI Systems contribution to revenue stood at 64.2% in Q3 FY26 and 47.6% in 9M FY26. We would also like to emphasize that alongside the accelerated growth in AI, our other two core segments, HPC and Private Cloud, are also witnessing strong and sustained demand. Netweb’s continued focus on its three strategic growth pillars: HPC, Private Cloud, and AI Systems is enabling us to capitalize on strong industry tailwinds. Supported by these core strengths, we continue to remain technology leader in the High-End Computing Systems (HCS) space.” Netweb Technologies is India’s leading high-end computing solutions (HCS) provider, with fully integrated design and manufacturing capabilities. Netweb’s HCS offering comprises HPC, Private cloud and HCI, AI systems and enterprise workstations, High performance storage (HPS) and Data Centre Servers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NetwebTechnologiesIndiaLtd_73333970_78854.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra EPC gains as Q3 PAT jumps 2% YoY to Rs 6 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-epc-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-2-yoy-to-rs-6-cr/1665581</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665581</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rallied 14.75% to Rs 93.47 crore in Q3 FY26, against Rs 81.45 crore posted in the same quarter last year.

Revenue from operations rallied 14.75% to Rs 93.47 crore in Q3 FY26, against Rs 81.45 crore posted in the same quarter last year. Total expenses increased 15.61% to Rs 84.48 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 73.07 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 44.52 crore (up 14.62% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were Rs 8.23 crore (up 6.05% YoY) during the period under review. Profit before tax was at Rs 8.74 crore in Q3 FY26, up 2.46% as against Rs 8.53 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Mahindra EPC Irrigation is in the business of micro irrigation systems, viz., drip and sprinklers, agricultural pumps, greenhouses, and landscape products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EPCInds_53518955692_2786.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Jindal Saw Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-jindal-saw-ltd-counter/1665579</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665579</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Triveni Turbine Ltd, Tech Mahindra Ltd, Jubilant Pharmova Ltd, Wipro Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 19 January 2026.

Triveni Turbine Ltd, Tech Mahindra Ltd, Jubilant Pharmova Ltd, Wipro Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 19 January 2026. Jindal Saw Ltd clocked volume of 25.33 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 22.18 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.14 lakh shares. The stock gained 11.66% to Rs.172.90. Volumes stood at 2.04 lakh shares in the last session. Triveni Turbine Ltd recorded volume of 7.53 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 13.83 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 54468 shares. The stock lost 3.14% to Rs.487.35. Volumes stood at 36384 shares in the last session. Tech Mahindra Ltd witnessed volume of 9.27 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.29 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.47 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.38% to Rs.1,727.00. Volumes stood at 1.8 lakh shares in the last session. Jubilant Pharmova Ltd notched up volume of 24138 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.65 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4273 shares. The stock slipped 3.12% to Rs.1,013.95. Volumes stood at 3198 shares in the last session. Wipro Ltd notched up volume of 16.94 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.53 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.06 lakh shares. The stock slipped 6.45% to Rs.250.00. Volumes stood at 5.29 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalSaw_11729026871_965.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Defrail Technologies rings the bell with a sprint]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-defrail-technologies-rings-the-bell-with-a-sprint/1665578</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665578</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 95, a premium of 28.38% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 95, a premium of 28.38% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently down 3.07% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 99.75 and a low of Rs 90.25. About 8.02 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Defrail Technologies' was subscribed 98.19 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 January 2026 and it closed on 13 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 70 to Rs 74 per share. The IPO comprised a fresh issue of 18,60,800 equity shares, with about 94,400 equity shares reserved for subscription by the market maker to the issue. The company intends to utilise the net proceeds for purchase of equipment/machineries, purchase and installation of solar panel and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Defrail Technologies on 8 January 2026, raised Rs 3.84 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 5.18 lakh shares at Rs 74 each to 3 anchor investors. Defrail Technologies is engaged in the manufacturing of rubber parts and components, including rubber hoses and assemblies, rubber profiles and beadings, and rubber moulded parts. Its products have diverse applications across various industries such as automotive, railways, and defence. The company assists clients in selecting the appropriate products for their specific applications and also provides design and customization options based on the intended use. As of 30 November 2025, the company had a total workforce of 298 individuals, including workers. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 39.08 crore and net profit of Rs 1.51 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DefrailTechnologiesLtd_30555918_95995.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves rise marginally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-rise-marginally/1665575</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665575</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's forex reserves rose by USD 392 million to USD 687.19 billion during the week ended January 9, the Reserve Bank of India said on Friday.

India's forex reserves rose by USD 392 million to USD 687.19 billion during the week ended January 9, the Reserve Bank of India said on Friday. In the previous reporting week, the overall kitty had dropped by USD 9.809 billion to USD 686.80 billion. For the week ended January 9, foreign currency assets, a major component of reserves, dipped by USD 1.124 billion to USD 550.866 billion. Value of the gold reserves jumped by USD 1.568 billion to USD 112.83 billion during the week while Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) were down by USD 39 million to USD 18.739 billion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growing-from-coin-jar-picture-id622446130_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty below 25,550; media shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-below-25550-media-shares-decline/1665571</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665571</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in morning trade, pressured by renewed worries over a potential escalation in global trade tensions and a mixed set of earnings from heavyweight companies.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in morning trade, pressured by renewed worries over a potential escalation in global trade tensions and a mixed set of earnings from heavyweight companies. The Nifty traded below the 25,550 mark. Media stocks witnessed selling pressure for the second consecutive trading session. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 623.26 points or 0.75% to 82,947.09. The Nifty 50 index lost 168.90 points or 0.66% to 25,506.35. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.43% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.80%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,229 shares rose and 2,536 shares fell. A total of 238 shares were unchanged. Result Today: LTIMindtree (down 0.45%), Punjab National Bank (up 1.32%), Tata Capital (down 0.07%), Aarti Surfactants (up 0.08%), Bharat Heavy Electricals (up 0.62%), Ceat (up 1.50%), Hatsun Agro Product (up 1.98%), Havells India (up 0.39%), Hindustan Zinc (up 2.30%), Indian Railway Finance Corporation (down 0.70%), Oberoi Realty (up 1.63%), Apollo Techno Industries (up 5.28%), and Atlanta Electricals (down 0.64%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. New Listing: Shares of Bharat Coking Coal were currently trading at Rs 42.61 at 10:20 IST on the BSE, representing a premium of 85.26% as compared with the issue price of Rs 23. The stock debuted at Rs 45.21, marking a premium of 96.57% to the issue price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 45.21 and a low of 40.17. On the BSE, over 592.08 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 1.13% to 1,394.55. The index dropped 1.48% in the past two trading sessions. Prime Focus (down 3.03%), Sun TV Network (down 2.46%), Tips Music (down 2.41%), PVR Inox (down 2.17%) and Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 1.66%), Nazara Technologies (down 1.15%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 0.95%), Saregama India (down 0.62%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 0.55%) fell. Stocks in Spotlight: Sobha fell 2.11% after the company reported a 28.85% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 154.28 crore on 22.95% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 943.11 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. CG Power and Industrial Solutions soared 7.14% after it has secured a landmark order worth Rs 900 crore ($99.2 million) from Tallgrass Integrated Logistics Solutions LLC, USA, for a large-scale data centre project in the United States.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Coking Coal makes blockbuster debut on listing day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-coking-coal-makes-blockbuster-debut-on-listing-day/1665568</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665568</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock debuted at Rs 45.21, marking a premium of 96.57% to the issue price.

The stock debuted at Rs 45.21, marking a premium of 96.57% to the issue price. So far, the stock has hit a high of 45.21 and a low of 40.17. On the BSE, over 5.79 crore shares of the company were traded in the counter so far. The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 50,95,55,58,000 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 146.87 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 January 2026, and it closed on 13 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. The offer had been a pure offer-for-sale (OFS) of up to 46.57 crore equity shares of face value Rs 10 each by Coal India. At the upper price band of Rs 23 per equity share, Coal India had raised Rs 1,071 crore. The IPO had included a reservation of up to 2.32 crore equity shares for eligible employees and up to 4.66 crore shares for eligible shareholders of Coal India under the shareholder reservation portion. Ahead of the IPO of Bharat Coking Coal on 8 January 2026, the company raised Rs 273.13 crore from anchor investors by allotting 11.87 crore shares at Rs 23 each to 15 anchor investors. Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) produces coking coal, non-coking coal, and washed coal. BCCL is India's largest producer of coking coal and operates primarily in the Jharia coalfields of Jharkhand and the Raniganj coalfields of West Bengal. It is the wholly owned subsidiary of Coal India and was conferred with Mini Ratna status in 2014. The primary product is coking coal, catering to the steel and power industries. BCCL had an estimated coking coal reserve of approximately 7,910 million tonnes (mt) as of 01 April 2024. It accounted for 58.50% of the total domestic coking coal production in India in FY 2025. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 123.88 crore and sales of Rs 5,659 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatCokingCoalLtd_73867136_12380.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JK Cement slips as Q3 PAT tanks 9% YoY to Rs 174 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jk-cement-slips-as-q3-pat-tanks-9-yoy-to-rs-174-cr/1665569</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665569</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 18.18% to Rs 3,463.07 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,930.28 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

However, revenue from operations rose 18.18% to Rs 3,463.07 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,930.28 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 268.28 crore, down by 3.93% from Rs 279.26 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA rose 13% YoY to Rs 558 crore, while the EBITDA margin reduced to 16.5% in Q3 FY26. JK Cement is one of India’s leading manufacturers of grey cement and one of the leading white cement manufacturers in the world. The company is engaged in the manufacturing and selling of cement and allied products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JKCements_26301288730_17136.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Invesco India Mutual Fund Change in Minimum Application Amount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/invesco-india-mutual-fund-change-in-minimum-application-amount/1665567</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665567</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Invesco India Mutual Fund announces that the Minimum Application Amount for Invesco India Business Cycle Fund, Invesco India Flexi Cap Fund, Invesco India Large & Mid Cap Fund, Invesco India Midcap Fund, Invesco India Smallcap Fund, Invesco India Multi Asset Allocation Fund with effect from January 20, 2026.

Invesco India Mutual Fund announces that the Minimum Application Amount for Invesco India Business Cycle Fund, Invesco India Flexi Cap Fund, Invesco India Large & Mid Cap Fund, Invesco India Midcap Fund, Invesco India Smallcap Fund, Invesco India Multi Asset Allocation Fund with effect from January 20, 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name(s) Existing Minimum Application Amount Revised Minimum Application Amount Invesco India Business Cycle Fund Invesco India Flexi Cap Fund Invesco India Large & Mid Cap Fund Invesco India Midcap Fund Invesco India Smallcap Fund Invesco India Multi Asset Allocation Fund For Purchase / Additional Purchase - Rs. 1,000/- per application and in multiples of Re. 1/- thereafter. For Switch-in - Rs. 1,000/- per application and in multiples of Re. 0.01/- thereafter For Purchase / Additional Purchase - Rs. 100/- per application and in multiples of Re. 1/- thereafter. For Switch-in - Rs. 100/- per application and in multiples of Re. 0.01/- thereafter

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sobha slides after Q3 PAT drops 29% YoY to Rs 154 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sobha-slides-after-q3-pat-drops-29-yoy-to-rs-154-cr/1665558</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665558</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) fell 30.31% YoY to Rs 205.34 crore in Q3 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) fell 30.31% YoY to Rs 205.34 crore in Q3 December 2025. Sales value stood at Rs 2,115 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 52% YoY and 11% QoQ. Average price realization stood was Rs 15,436 per square feet (Sq.Ft.). On nine month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 88.69% to Rs 101.57 crore on 14.46% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3,202.66 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Jagadish Nangineni, managing director, Sobha said, “The first nine months of FY26 have been truly exceptional for SOBHA, with our real estate sales reaching an all-time high of Rs 6,097 crore. This remarkable achievement is a testament to the enduring trust of our customers and the dedication of our aligned teams across every function and business vertical. We are confident that this strong momentum will sustain, fueled by our planned new project launches in a resilient Indian macroeconomic environment, even as we navigate heightened geopolitical volatility. A significant milestone this period was our entry into the vibrant Mumbai market with the launch of SOBHA Inizio, expanding our real estate presence to 13 cities across India. In Q3, we completed 915 homes, taking cumulative deliveries for the first nine months to 2,100 homes. While procedural delays in securing Occupancy Certificates (OCs) have temporarily moderated quarterly profitability, we remain fully confident in accelerating project completions moving forward, which will drive substantial improvements in our P&L performance. With gross debt at a prudent Rs 910 crore and a negative net debt, our robust balance sheet uniquely equips us to capitalize on emerging opportunities while effectively managing the inherent cyclicality of residential real estate." Sobha is the real estate brand in the country that offers international quality homes, and commercial and contractual projects delivered on time, through its backward integration model.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Sobha_16954596303_27443.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CG Power spurts on bagging Rs 900-cr US data centre order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cg-power-spurts-on-bagging-rs-900-cr-us-data-centre-order/1665545</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665545</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order marks CG Power’s entry into the global data centre segment, one of the fastest-growing infrastructure verticals, and is the largest single order ever won by the company.

The order marks CG Power’s entry into the global data centre segment, one of the fastest-growing infrastructure verticals, and is the largest single order ever won by the company. It is a direct export order for the supply of power transformers. Under the contract, CG Power will design and supply high-capacity power transformers engineered to meet the stringent reliability, efficiency and uptime requirements of hyperscale data centre applications. The execution of the order is scheduled over a delivery period of 12 to 20 months. The supplies will be made on an FAS Mumbai Port basis, in line with Incoterms® 2020, the company said in a statement. Amar Kaul, Global CEO & MD, said: “This landmark order from Tallgrass is a strategic platform win for CG and marks our entry into the rapidly growing global data center vertical. It validates our capability to deliver globally benchmarked, mission-critical technology solutions from India, and reinforces our position as a trusted global partner in applications where reliability and performance are non-negotiable. The global shift toward cloud computing, AI, and digital infrastructure is fundamentally reshaping the power demand. We believe this win opens up a significant long-term opportunity pipeline in global data center projects, aligned with our global growth and margin-accretive expansion strategy.” CG Power & Industrial Solutions is a global enterprise providing end-to-end solutions to utilities, industries and consumers for the management and application of efficient and sustainable electrical energy. It offers products, services and solutions in two main business segments, viz. Power Systems and Industrial Systems. The company's consolidated net profit rose 29.76% to Rs 286.72 crore on a 21.14% increase in revenue to Rs 2,922.79 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CGPowerIndu_42121517029_125.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR seen recovering slightly amid dollar weakness overseas]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-seen-recovering-slightly-amid-dollar-weakness-overseas/1665543</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665543</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee is seen recovering some lost momentum from around record lows in opening trades on Monday tracking weakness in dollar overseas.

The Indian rupee is seen recovering some lost momentum from around record lows in opening trades on Monday tracking weakness in dollar overseas. Decline in international oil prices also supported the counter although lower start to domestic equities is likely limit gains. INR opened at Rs 90.68 per dollar and slipped to a low of 90.73 so far during the day. On Friday, rupee ended at Rs 90.78 per dollar. Tariff concerns soured investors' appetite for riskier assets as the European Union is reportedly preparing to strike the U.S. with a hefty set of tariffs worth €93bn ($107.71bn) after Donald Trump threatened to impose a 10 percent tariff on goods from eight European countries starting Feb. 1, rising to 25 percent in June unless there's a deal for a "purchase of Greenland". The dollar index was under pressure under 99 mark.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers drift lower in early trade; FMCG shares advance; VIX jumps 6.04%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-drift-lower-in-early-trade-fmcg-shares-advance-vix-jumps-604/1665541</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665541</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in early trade, pressured by renewed worries over a potential escalation in global trade tensions and a mixed set of earnings from heavyweight companies.

The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in early trade, pressured by renewed worries over a potential escalation in global trade tensions and a mixed set of earnings from heavyweight companies. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. FMCG and consumer durables shares advanced while all other index traded in red on the NSE. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 384.78 points or 0.46% to 83,193.96. The Nifty 50 index fell 125.30 points or 0.50% to 25,563.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.21% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.82%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,108 shares rose and 2,097 shares fell. A total of 236 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 6.04% to 12.06. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 4,346.13 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,935.31 crore in the Indian equity market on 16 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Reliance Industries (RIL) fell 1.28%. The company has reported 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. L&T Finance fell 1.77%. The company has reported 18% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 739 crore on a 18% increase in total income to Rs 2,920 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Yes Bank shed 0.64%. The company has reported a sharp improvement in its Q3 FY26 performance, with net profit surging 55.4% YoY to Rs 952 crore, driven by strong operating income, lower credit costs. Net interest income stood at Rs 2,466 crore, up 10.9% YoY and 7.2% QoQ, aided by a reduction in the cost of funds. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.47% to 6.678 compared with previous session close of 6.647. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7300 compared with its close of 90.7875 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 1.38% to Rs 144,487. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.20% to 99.19. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.17% to 4.240. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 8 cents or 0.12% to $64.21 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market mostly slipped Monday, as investors assessed threats from the Trump administration toward Greenland over the weekend, as well as key economic data from China out Monday. Over the weekend, U.S. President Donald Trump and European leaders exchanged tense rhetoric over the Arctic territory, with Trump threatening tariffs on eight European countries and demanding control of Greenland, which is part of Denmark. European leaders responded by calling the threats “completely wrong” and “unacceptable.” In Asia, China released its fourth-quarter GDP numbers, along with December figures for retail sales, urban investment and industrial output. China’s economic growth slowed to its weakest pace in nearly three years in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, though full-year growth matched Beijing’s target despite growing trade frictions with the U.S. and a prolonged real estate slump. Gross domestic product grew 4.5% in the October-to-December period, data from the National Statistics Bureau showed Monday. That marked a slowdown from 4.8% in the third quarter and was the weakest reading since the first quarter of 2023, when growth also came in at 4.5%. The full-year economic output came in at 5%, meeting the official target of around 5%. On Friday in the U.S., the S&P 500 ended just below the flatline and posted a losing week, while the Nasdaq Composite also inched down 0.06%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.17%. The three major indexes hit their session lows after Trump said in the White House on Friday that he’d rather have National Economic Council Director Kevin Hassett stay in his current role and that he might not be chosen to become the next U.S. Fed chair. Hassett has been seen as the more market-friendly option to replace current Fed chair than the new frontrunner nominee, former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, and is expected to be more willing to keep rates low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>