<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NHPC board clears over Rs 5,000-cr hydropower projects in J&K]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nhpc-board-clears-over-rs-5000-cr-hydropower-projects-in-jk/1679014</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679014</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The board cleared the implementation of Uri-I Stage-II hydro electric (HE) Project (240 MW) at an estimated completion cost of Rs 2,708.95 crore.

The board cleared the implementation of Uri-I Stage-II hydro electric (HE) Project (240 MW) at an estimated completion cost of Rs 2,708.95 crore. The project cost includes Rs 264.31 crore for IDC and grant of Rs 26.20 crore for enabling infrastructure. The construction start date has been considered as March 1, 2026. In addition, the board also approved an investment proposal of Dulhasti Stage-II HE Project (260 MW) at a completion cost of Rs 2,993.96 crore including Rs 289.06 crore for IDC and Rs 245.00 crore for enabling infrastructure, with construction also slated to commence from 1 March 2026. Both investments are subject to the signing of implementation agreement between NHPC and Government of Jammu & Kashmir / JKSPDC & other requisite approvals, if any. NHPC, a Navratna Ratna public sector utility, is the Government of India’s flagship hydroelectric generation company. The company is primarily involved in the generation and sale of bulk power to various power utilities. Its other business includes providing project management/construction contracts/consultancy assignment services and trading of power. The company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 320.60 crore in Q3 FY26, down 2.89% as against Rs 330.13 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income declined 4.74% year-on-year to Rs 2,492.83 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The scrip rose 0.08% to settle at Rs 74.43 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NHPCLtd_36439171799_12584.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India Ratings upgrades ratings of Wheels India to 'A+' with 'stable' outlook]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-ratings-upgrades-ratings-of-wheels-india-to-a-with-stable-outlook/1679011</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679011</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘IND A1’.

The agency has affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘IND A1’. India Ratings and Research stated that the upgrade reflects a notable improvement in WIL’s EBITDA margins, and thus credit metrics at the consolidated level during FY25–9MFY26, supported by sustained revenue diversification and working capital efficiencies. The agency expects this positive momentum to continue over the near to medium term, driven by higher contributions from margin-accretive segments and ongoing cost-optimisation initiatives undertaken by the company. India Ratings further said that a significant improvement in the profitability along with improving profitability from newer segments, while maintaining the gross working capital cycle, and net adjusted leverage reducing below 2.5x, all on a consolidated and sustained basis, could lead to a positive rating action. However, a decline in the profitability margins and/or a stretch in the gross working capital cycle, leading to net adjusted leverage exceeding 3.5x, and deterioration in the liquidity position, could lead to a negative rating action. Wheels India manufactures steel and aluminium wheel rims across the automotive (except two-wheeler), tractor and earth mover segments. It caters to both the domestic and overseas markets. The company also has a presence in air suspension systems for luxury buses in India, supplies fabricated and machined parts for windmills, and produces bogie frame and bogie bolsters for the Indian Railways. The company had reported 44.05% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 36.07 crore on a 21.92% increase in revenue to Rs 1,371.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip had declined 2.03% to end at Rs 899.25 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WheelsIndia_63910222667_609.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WeWork India proposes to add 3,100 desks in Bengaluru by Sept'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wework-india-proposes-to-add-3100-desks-in-bengaluru-by-sept26/1679005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679005</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s existing capacity comprises of 1,21,638 desks, with a utilization rate of 83%.

The company’s existing capacity comprises of 1,21,638 desks, with a utilization rate of 83%. With this new lease deed, the company expects to add a total of 3,100 desks before September 2026. The total cost for the proposed capacity addition is Rs 42 crore, which would be funded either through debt or internal accruals. WeWork India is one of India’s leading premium flexible workspace operators. Since its inception, WeWork India has expanded across 8 cities in Chennai, New Delhi, Gurugram, Noida, Mumbai, Bengaluru, Pune, and Hyderabad, with 73 operational centres spanning 8.2 million square feet (as of December 2025). The company had reported a consolidated net profit of 16.70 crore in the quarter ended December 2025 as against net loss of Rs 83.25 crore during the previous quarter ended December 2024. Sales rose 28.97% to Rs 634.11 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip had declined 1.56% to end at Rs 531.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WeworkIndiaManagementLtd_48346151_76903.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1679002</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679002</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 24 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 24 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) in the following scheme. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit. Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 0.10 per unit

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/invesco-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1679000</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679000</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund has announced that Mr.

Invesco Mutual Fund has announced that Mr. Munesh Khanna has been appointed as an Associate Director with effect from February 17, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Mr. Munesh Khanna Age: 63 years Designation: (Associate Director) Qualification: B.Com., C.A.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gulf Oil Lubricants renews multi-year pact with Mahindra & Mahindra]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gulf-oil-lubricants-renews-multi-year-pact-with-mahindra-mahindra/1678985</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678985</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The renewal reinforces a strategic alliance that began in 2011 with a co-branded initiative alongside Mahindra Automotive and expanded into the Tractors Division in 2014.

The renewal reinforces a strategic alliance that began in 2011 with a co-branded initiative alongside Mahindra Automotive and expanded into the Tractors Division in 2014. Over the past 12 years, the partnership has evolved into one of Gulf Oil's most enduring OEM relationships. The collaboration has been consistently strengthened through investments in digital initiatives, efficient supply chain management, and impactful joint marketing campaigns, delivering growth and value for all stakeholders. Ravi Chawla, managing director & CEO, Gulf Oil Lubricants India, said: “Our renewed partnership with Mahindra Tractors is a testament to the strength of our alliance and the shared values that drive it. In line with our long-term philosophy of partnership for growth, we have, over the past decade, consistently delivered reliable performance and service excellence, adding sustained value to Mahindra & Mahindra.” Gulf Oil Lubricants India (GOLIL), part of the Hinduja Group and Gulf Oil International, is a leading player in India's lubricant market offering a comprehensive product portfolio in automotive and industrial lubricants. The company had reported 21.77% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 76.13 crore despite a 10.56% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,017.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.95% to currently trade at Rs 1081.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GulfOilLubric_49865113351_45765.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>