<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI decides to conduct operations to inject liquidity into the banking system]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-decides-to-conduct-operations-to-inject-liquidity-into-the-banking-system/1661723</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661723</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated today that on a review of current liquidity, it has decided to conduct the operations to inject liquidity into the banking system.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated today that on a review of current liquidity, it has decided to conduct the operations to inject liquidity into the banking system. It includes OMO purchase auctions of Government of India securities for an aggregate amount of Rs 2,00,000 crore in four tranches of Rs 50,000 crore each to be held on December 29, 2025, January 05, 2026, January 12, 2026, and January 22, 2026 and USD/INR Buy/Sell Swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of 3 years to be held on January 13, 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee fights back]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-fights-back/1661722</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661722</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 89.6750 per Dollar on Tuesday (23 December 2025), vewrsus its previous close of 89.7500 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper stays in demand amid steady equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-stays-in-demand-amid-steady-equities/1661721</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661721</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures saw excellent gains after breaking above $5.50 per pound.

COMEX Copper futures saw excellent gains after breaking above $5.50 per pound. The red metal currently trades up 1% at $5.56 per pound amid firm equities. Asian markets extended gains in steady moves on Tuesday in the backdrop of renewed optimism around AI-related shares that boosted equities on Wall Street yesterday. China's Shanghai Composite Index added 0.07% and neared two-week high. The Japanese benchmark Nikkei 225 gained 0.06% on the day. There has been a sizable drop in LME Copper inventories this week, providing a decent impetus to the commodity as it lingers around five-month high. MCX Copper trades at Rs 1155 per kg, up 1.90% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR consolidates around three-week high as dollar wobbles]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-consolidates-around-three-week-high-as-dollar-wobbles/1661718</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661718</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee held steady against the US dollar, consolidating near three-week high.

Indian Rupee held steady against the US dollar, consolidating near three-week high. Stable undertone in equities and weakness in the US dollar index offered decent support to the INR and it added 5 paise to 89.63 per US dollar. Overall mood remains choppy for the local currency but it managed to see a good intraday upswing after testing lows of 89.85 per US dollar. Meanwhile, the US dollar index was under stress after falling under 98 mark in last session. On NSE, USD/INR futures shed marginally by 0.07% on the day to close at 89.67 after hitting highs above 89.90 in intraday moves.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-currency-trading-concept-picture-id504246822_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality subscribed 2.67 times ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-kidney-and-super-speciality-subscribed-267-times/1661714</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661714</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 3,53,62,816 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (23 December 2025).

Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 3,53,62,816 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (23 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 2.67 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. The IPO comprises fresh issue of equity shares, aggregating up to Rs 250.8 crore. The objectives of the fresh issue are to utilize Rs 77 crore towards the acquisition of Parekh’s Hospital in Ahmedabad; Rs 12.4 crore will be used for part-payment of the purchase consideration for the already acquired Ashwini Medical Centre; Rs 10.78 crore is earmarked for the acquisition of additional shareholding in the subsidiary, Harmony Medicare, located in Bharuch; Rs 30.09 crore towards funding its capital expenditure requirements; Rs 6.82 crore will be utilized for the purchase of robotics equipment for Gujarat Kidney & Super Specialty Hospital in Vadodara; Rs 1.2 crore will be used for the repayment and/or prepayment of certain outstanding borrowings; and the remaining proceeds will be used for general corporate purposes. The promoters are Dr. Pragnesh Yashwantsinh Bharpoda, Dr. Bhartiben Pragnesh Bharpoda, Dr. Yashwantsingh Motisinh Bharpoda and Anitaben Yashwantsinh Bharpoda. The promoters and promoter group hold an aggregate of 5,63,33,900 equity shares, aggregating to 99.1% of the pre-offer issued and paid-up equity share capital. Their post IPO shareholding is expected to be around 71.45%. Ahead of the IPO, Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality on 22 December 2025, the company raised Rs 100.01 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 87.73 lakh shares at Rs 114 each to 10 anchor investors. Gujarat Kidney & Super Speciality specializes in providing multispeciality healthcare services, including secondary and tertiary care, across multiple locations in Gujarat, India. The company operates seven multispeciality hospitals and four pharmacies with a total bed capacity of 490 beds, an approved capacity of 455 beds, and an operational capacity of 340 beds. Comprehensive medical care is provided across a range of specialty and super-specialty services. Treatment is offered across areas such as internal medicine, general surgery, nephrology, urology, cardiology, and orthopedics, while also focusing on advanced super-specialty care including renal transplantation, vascular surgery, and hematology among others. Healthcare services are categorized as secondary services, which are surgical services, and tertiary Services, which are super speciality surgical services. Central, state and local government bodies contributed 5.46% to its revenue, Insurers through third party administrators 13.9%, and Self-payers and others 80.64% in Q1 FY2026. For the three month ended 30 June 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 4.84 crore and income from operations of Rs 15.26 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks close flat as expiry volatility caps gains]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-close-flat-as-expiry-volatility-caps-gains/1661712</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661712</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Benchmark equity indices ended Tuesday’s session largely flat as volatility persisted around the weekly expiry of Nifty futures.

Benchmark equity indices ended Tuesday’s session largely flat as volatility persisted around the weekly expiry of Nifty futures. The market opened lower and hovered around the flat line for most of the session. Mild selling pressure emerged toward the close, though the Nifty still managed to eke out marginal gains. Metal and chemical shares were in demand while IT, PSU banks and healthcare stocks witnessed selling. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. Sentiment found support from a firmer rupee and improving global cues. Expectations of interest-rate cuts by the U.S. Federal Reserve early next year also helped steady investor confidence. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 42.64 points or 0.05% to 85,524.84. The Nifty 50 index rose 4.75 points or 0.02% to 26,177.15. Shriram Finance (up 2.42%), ITC (up 1.53%) and HDFC Bank (up 0.94%) supported the Nifty today. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rallied 0.38%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,292 shares rose and 1,892 shares fell. A total of 198 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tumbled 3.07% to 9.38. Economy: The Index of Eight Core Industries rose 1.8% year-on-year in November, driven by higher output of cement, steel, fertilisers and coal. Cement production grew 14.5%, fertilisers 5.6%, steel 6.1% and coal 2.1%, while crude oil output fell 3.2% and natural gas production declined 2.5%. The index tracks eight sectors that together account for over 40% of the weight in the Index of Industrial Production. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.19% to 6.656 compared with previous session close of 6.669. In the foreign exchange market, the partially convertible rupee traded flat at 89.6850 compared with the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 1.06% to Rs 138,188. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.39% to 97.57. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.53% to 4.147. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 3 cents or 0.05% to $62.10 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European markets declined on Tuesday as investors awaited Spain’s final GDP data, due later in the day. Provisional figures released last month showed year-on-year growth of 2.8%. Most Asian market ended higher, after AI trade lifted major Wall Street indexes overnight. Nvidia shares rose more than 1% after media reports said that the company was looking to start shipments of its H200 chips to China by mid-February. Singapore's inflation in November remained steady at 1.2%. Core inflation in the city-state, which strips out prices of private transport and accommodation, also came in at 1.2%, compared to expectations of 1.3%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 gained 0.64%, posting its third positive day in a row. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.47%, and the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.52%. New Listing: Shares of KSH International settled at Rs 354.55 on the BSE, a discount of 7.67% compared with the issue price of Rs 384. The stock debuted at Rs 370 on the BSE, a discount of 3.65% over the issue price. The stock has hit a high of Rs 370 and a low of Rs 350.05. On the BSE, 5.72 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Stocks in Spotlight: Shares of ACC slipped 1.21%, while Ambuja Cements climbed 1.25% and Orient Cement surged 4.18% after Ambuja Cements unveiled a major consolidation plan. In a regulatory filing, Ambuja said its board has approved schemes to amalgamate ACC and Orient Cement into Ambuja Cements. The move will create a single pan-India cement platform. Under the proposed share swap, Ambuja will issue 328 equity shares of face value Rs 2 each for every 100 ACC shares of face value Rs 10 each. Orient Cement shareholders will receive 33 Ambuja shares of face value Rs 2 each for every 100 shares of Orient Cement with face value Re 1. Belrise Industries surged 6.18% after the company announced a strategic agreement with Israel-based Plasan Sasa. Under the agreement, the two companies will jointly identify and pursue defence-related business opportunities in India. IRB Infrastructure Developers rose 1.59% after its associate, IRB Infrastructure Trust, emerged as the preferred bidder for a highway asset under the toll-operate-transfer (TOT) model. Sunita Tools rose 2.13% after the company announced a strategic memorandum of understanding with a Middle East-based partner to support an upcoming defence order. Shakti Pumps India rose 2.72% after the company received a Letter of Empanelment/Award worth Rs 356.77 crore from the Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company (MSEDCL) for the supply of off-grid solar water pumping systems. RITES jumped 4.06% after it has won an international order worth $35.2 million from Ndalama Capital, South Africa for the supply and commissioning of in-service Cape gauge ALCO diesel-electric locomotives on a CIF basis. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.30%. The company announced that its Hydrocarbon Onshore business vertical (L&T Onshore) has secured a major engineering, procurement, construction and commissioning (EPCC) order from Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL). Puravankara zoomed 7.96% after it has acquired a 53.5-acre land parcel in Anekal Taluk, Bengaluru, with a potential gross development value of over Rs 4,800 crore. Antony Waste Handling Cell surged 5.94% after the company announced that its arm, Antony Lara Enviro Solutions, has secured a contract worth Rs 329.45 crore for the development of a mixed solid waste processing plant in Maharashtra. IPO Update: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 3,50,35,904 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:36 IST on Tuesday (23 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 2.65 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty December futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-december-futures-trade-at-premium/1661711</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661711</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 30 December 2025 futures closed at 26,202.10, a premium of 24.95 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,177.15 in the cash market.

The Nifty 30 December 2025 futures closed at 26,202.10, a premium of 24.95 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,177.15 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index advanced 4.75 points or 0.02% to 26,177.15. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 3.07% to 9.38. HDFC Bank, Axis Bank and Reliance Industries were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The December 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 30 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends sideways; VIX slides 3.07%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-sideways-vix-slides-307/1661710</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661710</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity indices ended the session sideways, reflecting a lack of clear direction in the market.

The headline equity indices ended the session sideways, reflecting a lack of clear direction in the market. Volatility was driven by the weekly expiry of Nifty futures, which impacted intraday trading activity. Investors remained cautious, tracking movements in the rupee, foreign institutional investor (FII) activity, ongoing IPO developments, and global cues. Nifty settles above the 26,150 mark. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 42.64 points or 0.05% to 85,524.84. The Nifty 50 index rose 4.75 points or 0.02% to 26,177.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rallied 0.38%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tumbled 3.07% to 9.38. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Media index (up 0.80%), the Metal index (up 0.54%) and the Nifty Chemical (up 0.53%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 0.80%), the PSU Bank index (down 0.34%) and the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.24%), underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: The combined Index of Eight Core Industries (ICI) increased by 1.8% (provisional) in November, 2025 as compared to the Index in November, 2024. The production of Cement, Steel, Fertilizer and Coal recorded positive growth in November, 2025. Coal production rose 2.1% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Crude oil output declined 3.2% year-on-year, while natural gas production fell 2.5% during the same period. Petroleum refinery production also slipped 0.9% in November 2025 over a year ago. Steel production increased 6.1% year-on-year, cement output surged 14.5%, while electricity generation declined 2.2% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Fertilizer production increased by 5.6% YoY in November 2025. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.19% to 6.656 compared with previous session close of 6.669. In the foreign exchange market, the partially convertible rupee traded flat at 89.6850 compared with the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 1.06% to Rs 138,188. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.39% to 97.57. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.53% to 4.147. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 3 cents or 0.05% to $62.10 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Tuesday as investors awaited Spain’s final GDP data, due later in the day. Provisional figures released last month showed year-on-year growth of 2.8%. Most Asian market ended higher, after AI trade lifted major Wall Street indexes overnight. Nvidia shares rose more than 1% after media reports said that the company was looking to start shipments of its H200 chips to China by mid-February. In Southeast Asia, Singapore's inflation in November remained steady at 1.2%. Core inflation in the city-state, which strips out prices of private transport and accommodation, also came in at 1.2%, compared to expectations of 1.3%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 gained 0.64%, posting its third positive day in a row. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.47%, and the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.52%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers end sideways; media shares rally  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-end-sideways-media-shares-rally/1661705</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661705</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended near flat line today.

The key equity indices ended near flat line today. Investors will keep track a crucial economic data including US GDP data, scheduled later this week. Further, market participants will closely monitor rupee movement, FII activity, ongoing IPO activity, and global cues. The Nifty settled above the 26,150 mark. Media, metal and FMCG shares advanced and IT, PSU Bank and Pharma stocks declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 42.64 points or 0.05% to 85,524.84. The Nifty 50 index gained 4.75 points or 0.02% to 26,177.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index surged 0.38% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.08%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,293 shares rose and 1,889 shares fell. A total of 200 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tumbled 3.07% to 9.38. IPO Update: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 3,38,15,808 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Tuesday (23 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 2.56 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. New Listing: Shares of KSH International ended at Rs 354.55, representing a discount of 7.67% as compared with the issue price of Rs 384. The stock debuted at Rs 370 on the BSE, exhibiting a discount of 3.65% over the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 370 and a low of 350.05. On the BSE, over 5.72 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Economy: The combined Index of Eight Core Industries (ICI) increased by 1.8% (provisional) in November, 2025 as compared to the Index in November, 2024. The production of Cement, Steel, Fertilizer and Coal recorded positive growth in November, 2025. Coal production rose 2.1% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Crude oil output declined 3.2% year-on-year, while natural gas production fell 2.5% during the same period. Petroleum refinery production also slipped 0.9% in November 2025 over a year ago. Steel production increased 6.1% year-on-year, cement output surged 14.5%, while electricity generation declined 2.2% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Fertilizer production increased by 5.6% YoY in November 2025. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index climbed 0.80% to 1,413.60. The index jumped 1.46% for the four consecutive trading sessions. Nazara Technologies (up 5.25%), Network 18 Media & Investments (up 3.71%), Hathway Cable & Datacom (up 1.83%), Sun TV Network (up 1.8%), Prime Focus (up 1.59%) and D B Corp (up 0.81%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Shares of ACC slipped 1.21%, while Ambuja Cements climbed 1.25% and Orient Cement surged 4.18% after Ambuja Cements announced a major consolidation plan. In a regulatory filing, Ambuja said its board has approved schemes to amalgamate ACC and Orient Cement into Ambuja Cements. The move will create a single pan-India cement platform. Under the proposed share swap, Ambuja will issue 328 equity shares of face value Rs 2 each for every 100 ACC shares of face value Rs 10 each. Orient Cement shareholders will receive 33 Ambuja shares of face value Rs 2 each for every 100 shares of Orient Cement with face value Re 1. Shakti Pumps India rose 2.72% after the company received a Letter of Empanelment/Award worth Rs 356.77 crore from the Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company (MSEDCL) for the supply of off-grid solar water pumping systems. RITES jumped 4.06% after it has won an international order worth $35.2 million from Ndalama Capital, South Africa for the supply and commissioning of in-service Cape gauge ALCO diesel-electric locomotives on a CIF basis. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.28%. The company announced that its Hydrocarbon Onshore business vertical (L&T Onshore) has secured a major engineering, procurement, construction and commissioning (EPCC) order from Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL). Puravankara zoomed 7.96% after it has acquired a 53.5-acre land parcel in Anekal Taluk, Bengaluru, with a potential gross development value of over Rs 4,800 crore. Antony Waste Handling Cell surged 5.94% after the company announced that its arm, Antony Lara Enviro Solutions, has secured a contract worth Rs 329.45 crore for the development of a mixed solid waste processing plant in Maharashtra. Global Markets: Most European markets advanced on Tuesday as investors awaited Spain’s final GDP data, due later in the day. Provisional figures released last month showed year-on-year growth of 2.8%. Most Asian markets ended higher, after AI trade lifted major Wall Street indexes overnight. Nvidia shares rose more than 1% after media reports said that the company was looking to start shipments of its H200 chips to China by mid-February. In Southeast Asia, Singapore's inflation in November remained steady at 1.2%. Core inflation in the city-state, which strips out prices of private transport and accommodation, also came in at 1.2%, compared to expectations of 1.3%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 gained 0.64%, posting its third positive day in a row. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.47%, and the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.52%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty PSE Index gains 1.02%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-pse-index-gains-102/1661704</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661704</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty PSE index ended up 1.02% at 9738.05 today.

Nifty PSE index ended up 1.02% at 9738.05 today. The index has slipped 1.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, NMDC Ltd rose 3.83%, Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd added 3.76% and Coal India Ltd gained 3.66%. The Nifty PSE index has soared 1.00% over last one year compared to the 10.20% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty IT index has dropped 0.80% and Nifty Media index gained 0.80% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 recorded a gain of 0.02% to close at 26177.15 while the SENSEX has slid 0.05% to close at 85524.84 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-city-stock-market-data-and-charts-on-skyscrapers-b_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coforge Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coforge-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1661698</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661698</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cartrade Tech Ltd, Patel Engineering Ltd, Mrs Bectors Food Specialities Ltd and Cigniti Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 December 2025.

Cartrade Tech Ltd, Patel Engineering Ltd, Mrs Bectors Food Specialities Ltd and Cigniti Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 23 December 2025. Coforge Ltd tumbled 4.77% to Rs 1779 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 47976 shares in the past one month. Cartrade Tech Ltd crashed 4.76% to Rs 2763. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11662 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 93761 shares in the past one month. Patel Engineering Ltd lost 4.45% to Rs 30.04. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8.14 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21.31 lakh shares in the past one month. Mrs Bectors Food Specialities Ltd plummeted 4.30% to Rs 238.15. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 24740 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13672 shares in the past one month. Cigniti Technologies Ltd pared 4.05% to Rs 1750. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8700 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1379 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoforgeLtd_47640546_24978.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/USD hits three-month high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpusd-hits-three-month-high/1661699</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661699</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound surged today, adding to recent gains and breaking above 1.3500 mark as the sentiment around US dollar remained flat and risk appetite held up in year-end trades.

British Pound surged today, adding to recent gains and breaking above 1.3500 mark as the sentiment around US dollar remained flat and risk appetite held up in year-end trades. GBP/USD pair is currently around three-month high at 1.3516, up 0.45% on the day. Latest data showed that the UK was a net borrower from the rest of the world in Quarter 3 (July to Sept) 2025 of 1.6% of gross domestic product (GDP). This is the lowest UK current account deficit (including precious metals) since Quarter 4 (Oct to Dec) 2022. Excluding precious metals, the underlying current account deficit was 1.4% of GDP, its lowest since Quarter 4 2021. On NSE, GBP/INR futures are quoting at 121.31, up 0.55% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/globe-series-3-1425556_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IRB Infra gains after associate emerges preferred bidder for NHAI’s TOT-18 project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/irb-infra-gains-after-associate-emerges-preferred-bidder-for-nhais-tot-18-project/1661697</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661697</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said IRB Infrastructure Trust has been selected as the preferred bidder for NHAI's TOT-18 concession.

The company said IRB Infrastructure Trust has been selected as the preferred bidder for NHAI's TOT-18 concession. The project involves tolling, operation, maintenance and transfer of the 74.5 km Chandikhole-Bhadrak section of NH-16 in Odisha. The trust will make an upfront concession fee payment of Rs 3,087 crore to National Highways Authority of India after achieving financial closure. The concession period is 20 years and is revenue-linked. Tolling and operations are expected to commence from the appointed date, with annual tariff revision set at a fixed 3% plus 40% of the wholesale price index. IRB Infrastructure Developers will act as the project manager for the concession. The project marks the group’s entry into its 13th Indian state and its second project in eastern India, following its West Bengal asset on NH-19. The company said the order book is expected to increase by about Rs 1,600 crore with this project. The TOT-18 asset is part of the Golden Quadrilateral network and further strengthens IRB Group’s presence in the TOT segment. IRB Infrastructure Developers is India’s first Integrated multi-national transport infrastructure developer in roads & highways segment. As the largest integrated private toll roads and highways infrastructure developer in India, IRB has an asset base of approx. Rs 94,000 crore in 13 States across the parent company and two InvITs. The company reported a 41% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.82 crore on a 10.42% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 1,751.02 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IRBInfraDevl_42061995161_28365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sri Havisha Hospitality & Infrastructure Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sri-havisha-hospitality-infrastructure-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1661696</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661696</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Meesho Ltd, Vinny Overseas Ltd and SRM Contractors Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 December 2025.

California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup, Meesho Ltd, Vinny Overseas Ltd and SRM Contractors Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 23 December 2025. Sri Havisha Hospitality & Infrastructure Ltd tumbled 10.66% to Rs 1.76 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2964 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5053 shares in the past one month. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup crashed 9.58% to Rs 4.34. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2231 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5017 shares in the past one month. Meesho Ltd lost 8.19% to Rs 185.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 94.01 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 159.06 lakh shares in the past one month. Vinny Overseas Ltd shed 6.38% to Rs 1.32. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 46878 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.15 lakh shares in the past one month. SRM Contractors Ltd slipped 6.08% to Rs 521.65. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 17528 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7357 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SriHavishaHospitalityInfrastru_79235314_5516.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade in positive terrain; IT shares drop]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-in-positive-terrain-it-shares-drop/1661695</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661695</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in mid-afternoon trade, buoyed by encouraging eight core industries data.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate gains in mid-afternoon trade, buoyed by encouraging eight core industries data. Traders will closely monitoring rupee movement, FII activity, ongoing IPO activity, and global cues. The Nifty traded above the 26,200 level. IT shares declined after gaining over the past four consecutive trading sessions. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 103.12 points or 0.12% to 85,670.60. The Nifty 50 index added 48 points or 0.18% to 26,220.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.10% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.34%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 2,292 shares rose and 1,803 shares fell. A total of 211 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 1.80% to 9.50. Economy: The combined Index of Eight Core Industries (ICI) increased by 1.8% (provisional) in November, 2025 as compared to the Index in November, 2024. The production of Cement, Steel, Fertilizer and Coal recorded positive growth in November, 2025. Coal production rose 2.1% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Crude oil output declined 3.2% year-on-year, while natural gas production fell 2.5% during the same period. Petroleum refinery production also slipped 0.9% in November 2025 over a year ago. Steel production increased 6.1% year-on-year, cement output surged 14.5%, while electricity generation declined 2.2% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Fertilizer production increased by 5.6% YoY in November 2025. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 0.73% to 39,200.35. The Index rallied 3.75% in the past four consecutive trading sessions. Coforge (down 4.37%), Infosys (down 1.25%), Persistent Systems (down 1.12%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 0.8%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.69%), Wipro (down 0.37%), Tech Mahindra (down 0.26%), LTIMindtree (down 0.14%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.06% to 6.673 compared with previous session close of 6.669. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.7350 compared with its close of 89.6700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 1.22% to Rs 138,416. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.26% to 98.01. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.53% to 4.147. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement fell 4 cents or 0.06% to $62.03 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Soma Papers & Industries was locked in 5% upper circuit after the company announced that its subsidiary KS Smart Solutions has been awarded a project worth Rs 172.65 crore by the School Education Department, Government of Punjab. Vardhman Special Steels rose 0.48%. The company said that it has approved an investment of Rs 475 crore to set up a new Steel forging and machining manufacturing facility in Ludhiana. Belrise Industries surged 6.15% after the company announced a strategic agreement with Israel-based Plasan Sasa. In a regulatory filing, Belrise said it entered into an exclusive teaming and strategic agreement with Plasan Sasa on 18 December 2025. The agreement is valid for three years and will be subject to annual performance reviews based on mutually agreed key performance indicators.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-akums-drugs-pharmaceuticals-ltd-counter/1661693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661693</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rites Ltd, Alok Industries Ltd, Ircon International Ltd, Jupiter Wagons Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 23 December 2025.

Rites Ltd, Alok Industries Ltd, Ircon International Ltd, Jupiter Wagons Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 23 December 2025. Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd recorded volume of 35.95 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 32.26 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.11 lakh shares. The stock gained 2.14% to Rs.452.65. Volumes stood at 3.12 lakh shares in the last session. Rites Ltd notched up volume of 81.47 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 20.57 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.96 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.76% to Rs.243.67. Volumes stood at 12.95 lakh shares in the last session. Alok Industries Ltd witnessed volume of 404.9 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 17.71 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 22.86 lakh shares. The stock increased 5.36% to Rs.16.90. Volumes stood at 26.45 lakh shares in the last session. Ircon International Ltd recorded volume of 468.84 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.01 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 31.23 lakh shares. The stock gained 8.48% to Rs.170.10. Volumes stood at 64.32 lakh shares in the last session. Jupiter Wagons Ltd witnessed volume of 1124.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.54 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 89.68 lakh shares. The stock increased 9.50% to Rs.339.95. Volumes stood at 741.29 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AkumDrugsPharmaceuticalsLtd_36614148_34484.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Domestic banking system liquidity remained largely in surplus, says RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/domestic-banking-system-liquidity-remained-largely-in-surplus-says-rbi/1661692</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661692</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its latest monthly update that banking system liquidity remained largely in surplus during the second half of November and December (up to 19th).

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its latest monthly update that banking system liquidity remained largely in surplus during the second half of November and December (up to 19th). Temporary increases in government cash balances due to GST related payments and an increase in currency-in-circulation led to some decline in system liquidity during the second half of November. The last tranche of CRR reduction, effective November 29, 2025 improved liquidity conditions till mid-December. System liquidity turned into deficit in the second half of December (up to 19th) on account of buildup in government cash balances due to advance tax payments. To offset the transient liquidity tightness, the Reserve Bank conducted variable rate repo auctions. With the aim of injecting durable liquidity into the system, the Reserve Bank conducted open market operation (OMO) purchases of government securities amounting to Rs 1 lakh crore and 3-year USD/INR Buy/Sell swaps of USD 5 billion in December.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/concept-money-tree-on-grass-picture-id462171033_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India, New&#8239;Zealand Conclude FTA Talks to Boost Trade, Investments and Export Diversification]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-new8239zealand-conclude-fta-talks-to-boost-trade-investments-and-export-diversification/1661687</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661687</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The free trade agreement (FTA) between India and New Zealand will help diversify exports, and attract investments in areas like agriculture.

The free trade agreement (FTA) between India and New Zealand will help diversify exports, and attract investments in areas like agriculture. The conclusion of negotiations for the pact was announced on December 22. It is likely to be signed and implemented next year. India and New Zealand mentioned that they have concluded talks on a free trade deal that will give India tariff-free access to the island nation's markets, bring in USD 20 billion of investment over the next 15 years and help double bilateral trade in goods and services the next five years to 5 billion USD.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/gold-2048293__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with small gains; media shares advance; VIX slides 1.70%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-small-gains-media-shares-advance-vix-slides-170/1661685</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661685</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded near the flatline with some positive points in the afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded near the flatline with some positive points in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above 26,150 mark. Media, metal and financial services shares advanced while IT, pharma and consumer durables shares declined. At 13:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex rose 9.14 points or 0.01% to 85,576.62. The Nifty 50 index advanced 18.85 points or 0.07% to 26,191. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.05% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.33%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,267 shares rose and 1,784 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. Economy: The combined Index of Eight Core Industries (ICI) increased by 1.8% (provisional) in November, 2025 as compared to the Index in November, 2024. The production of Cement, Steel, Fertilizer and Coal recorded positive growth in November, 2025. Coal production rose 2.1% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Crude oil output declined 3.2% year-on-year, while natural gas production fell 2.5% during the same period. Petroleum refinery production also slipped 0.9% in November 2025 over a year ago. Steel production increased 6.1% year-on-year, cement output surged 14.5%, while electricity generation declined 2.2% in November 2025 compared with November 2024. Fertilizer production increased by 5.6% YoY in November 2025. Gainers & Losers: Coal India (up 3.70%), Shriram Finance (up 2.17%), UltraTech Cement (up 1.60%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 1.42%) and Power Grid Corporation of India (up 1.26%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Infosys (down 1.42%), Bharti Airtel (down 0.96%), Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (down 0.68%), Bajaj Auto (down 0.68%) and Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.64%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Shakti Pumps India rose 3.92% after the company received a Letter of Empanelment/Award worth Rs 356.77 crore from the Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company (MSEDCL) for the supply of off-grid solar water pumping systems. RITES added 5.68% after it has won an international order worth $35.2 million from Ndalama Capital, South Africa for the supply and commissioning of in-service Cape gauge ALCO diesel-electric locomotives on a CIF basis. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) rose 0.28%. The company announced that its Hydrocarbon Onshore business vertical (L&T Onshore) has secured a major engineering, procurement, construction and commissioning (EPCC) order from Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL). Puravankara zoomed 14.97% after it has acquired a 53.5-acre land parcel in Anekal Taluk, Bengaluru, with a potential gross development value of over Rs 4,800 crore. Antony Waste Handling Cell surged 7.47% after the company announced that its arm, Antony Lara Enviro Solutions, has secured a contract worth Rs 329.45 crore for the development of a mixed solid waste processing plant in Maharashtra. IPO Update: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 2,97,04,704 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 13:15 IST on Tuesday (23 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 2.25 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. Global Markets: European markets opened lower open on Tuesday, extending losses into a second day after hitting record highs last week. Asia market traded higher, after AI trade lifted major Wall Street indexes overnight. Nvidia shares rose more than 1% after media reports said that the company was looking to start shipments of its H200 chips to China by mid-February. In Southeast Asia, Singapore will release its November inflation reading, with media reports stating that the city-state’s inflation rate is expected to have climbed to its highest in 2025. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 gained 0.64%, posting its third positive day in a row. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 0.47%, and the Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.52%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Soma Papers hits the roof after subsidiary bags contract worth Rs 173 crore in Punjab]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/soma-papers-hits-the-roof-after-subsidiary-bags-contract-worth-rs-173-crore-in-punjab/1661686</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661686</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves the deployment and commissioning of IT infrastructure across government educational institutions in the State of Punjab, comprising 23,846 mid-level desktop computing systems and 23,207 line-interactive UPS systems, along with associated installation and system readiness activities at designated locations.

The project involves the deployment and commissioning of IT infrastructure across government educational institutions in the State of Punjab, comprising 23,846 mid-level desktop computing systems and 23,207 line-interactive UPS systems, along with associated installation and system readiness activities at designated locations. Under the project, KS Smart is responsible for supply, installation, configuration, commissioning and warranty support of the systems in accordance with the technical specifications, statutory requirements and government procurement guidelines. The project follows an OEM-verified framework with traceable device identification, configuration integrity and prescribed quality standards. Through this engagement, KS Smart will support the State’s digital education initiatives by enabling reliable, standardized and scalable computing infrastructure across schools. The project has to be completed by April 2026. KS Smart Solutions is a wholly owned subsidiary of Soma Papers & Industries. Soma Papers & Industries manufactures and markets coated papers & boards, fluorescent papers and self-copy papers. The company exports fluorescent papers to southeast Asian countries. They have also started selling copier paper under the brand 'Soma'.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SomaPapers_52077839009_3028.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>