<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JD Cables bags Rs 9 crore cable supply order in Bihar & Jharkhand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jd-cables-bags-rs-9-crore-cable-supply-order-in-bihar-jharkhand/1662179</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662179</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract entails the manufacture and supply of 831 km of cables across Bihar and Jharkhand, covering a wide range of products such as Aerial Bunched XLPE Cable, LT XLPE AB Cable, and Control Cable, including manufacturing, testing, and delivery.

The contract entails the manufacture and supply of 831 km of cables across Bihar and Jharkhand, covering a wide range of products such as Aerial Bunched XLPE Cable, LT XLPE AB Cable, and Control Cable, including manufacturing, testing, and delivery. JD Cables is engaged in the manufacturing of cables and conductors that cater to the power transmission and distribution sector. The company’s standalone net profit surged 384.1% to Rs 22.17 crore in FY25, driven by a 148.5% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 250.33 crore, compared with FY24. Shares of JD Cables rose 0.64% to Rs 206 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JDCablesLtd_48912059_95607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge higher in early trade; breadth positive]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-positive/1662180</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662180</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded with minor gains in early trade, supported by positive global markets cues.

The key equity barometers traded with minor gains in early trade, supported by positive global markets cues. The Nifty traded above the 26,100 level. Metal, auto and private bank shares advanced while media, FMCG and pharma stocks declined. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 22.05 points or 0.03% to 85,072.33. The Nifty 50 index added 11.60 points or 0.04% to 26,056.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.03% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.03%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,479 shares rose and 1,683 shares fell. A total of 223 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 317.56 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,772.56 crore in the Indian equity market on 24 December 2025, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Suzlon Energy rose 0.43%. The company announced that Vivek Srivastava has resigned as chief executive officer (CEO) of the WTG Division, effective December 26. 2025. Diamond Power Infrastructure advanced 0.82%. The company said that it has received a letter of intent from Hild Projects, an EPC contractor, for the supply of power cables worth Rs 66.18 crore. Avantel added 0.09%. The company has received a contract worth Rs 4.16 crore from the Ministry of Defence, Headquarters Naval Aviation, for CAMC of Satcom equipment. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.14% to 6.569 as compared with the previous close of 6.560. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9400 compared with its close of 89.9000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.24% to Rs 1,40.187. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 97.99. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.10% to 4.135. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 63 cents or 1.04% to $61.27 a barrel. Global Markets: Most Asian markets advanced on Monday as investors kicked off the final trading week of the year. Prices of spot silver rose to a fresh record high of above $80 per ounce before pulling back sharply to $77. Silver’s recent surge was driven by speculative buying and lingering supply tightness, said experts. Media report further stated silver’s rally this year reflects a depletion of freely traded inventory, amplifying price moves as demand increases. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 reached a new high and posted weekly gains as traders came back from the Christmas holiday. The broad market index closed down 0.03% to end at 6,929.94. At its high, the S&P 500 was up 0.2%, reaching 6,945.77. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.09% and closed at 23,593.10. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 20.19 points, or 0.04%, and settled at 48,710.97.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd Spikes 1.61%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-ltd-spikes-161/1662177</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662177</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd rose 1.61% today to trade at Rs 647.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd rose 1.61% today to trade at Rs 647. The BSE Metal index is up 0.76% to quote at 35930.97. The index is up 5.33 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Steel Authority of India Ltd increased 1.44% and National Aluminium Company Ltd added 1.16% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 23.05 % over last one year compared to the 8.01% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Zinc Ltd has added 33.28% over last one month compared to 5.33% gain in BSE Metal index and 0.82% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 93746 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 7.51 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 656.25 on 29 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 378.65 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank Slips 1.41%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/punjab-national-bank-slips-141/1662178</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662178</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Punjab National Bank fell 1.41% today to trade at Rs 118.65.

Punjab National Bank fell 1.41% today to trade at Rs 118.65. The BSE BANKEX index is down 0.18% to quote at 65873.63. The index is down 1.6 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, IndusInd Bank Ltd decreased 0.39% and Axis Bank Ltd lost 0.31% on the day. The BSE BANKEX index went up 13.15 % over last one year compared to the 8.01% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Punjab National Bank has lost 4.7% over last one month compared to 1.6% fall in BSE BANKEX index and 0.82% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1.12 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 9.51 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 127.8 on 02 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 85.5 on 04 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PunjabNatlBank_67799088412_7855.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR recovers slightly above Rs 90/$ mark in opening trades ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-recovers-slightly-above-rs-90-mark-in-opening-trades/1662174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662174</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee registered a mild pullback after sustained weakness beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark in past few days.

The Indian rupee registered a mild pullback after sustained weakness beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark in past few days. INR opened at Rs 89.95 per dollar and rebounded to a high of 89.89 so far during the day. Weakness in dollar overseas and positive cues from equities is keeping the counter supported. US dollar edged below 98 on Monday, trading sideways near its lowest level since early October as holiday-thinned trading continued and markets priced in rate cuts next year. On Friday, rupee depreciated 19 paise to close at 89.90 against the US dollar tracking a negative trend in domestic equities and foreign fund outflows. Indian shares ended lower despite firm cues from global markets. The benchmark BSE Sensex dropped 367.25 points, or 0.43%, to 85,041.45 as trading resumed after a holiday on Thursday for Christmas. The broader NSE Nifty index fell 99.80 points, or 0.38%, to 26,042.30.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Avantel bags Rs 4-crore defence order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/avantel-bags-rs-4-crore-defence-order/1662172</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662172</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract is scheduled to be executed by 1 January 2028.

The contract is scheduled to be executed by 1 January 2028. The company said the order carries a performance bank guarantee requirement of 5% as per the terms and conditions. It added that the contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related-party transactions, with neither the promoters nor promoter group entities having any interest in the awarding authority. Avantel is engaged in the business of designing, developing, and maintaining wireless and satellite communication products, defence electronics, radar systems, and the development of network management software applications for its customers, mainly from the aerospace and defence sectors. The company’s consolidated net profit tanked 81.39% to Rs 4.26 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 22.89 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 28.42% year on year to Rs 55.41 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Avantel rose 0.25% to close at Rs 160.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Avantel_19473582893_20881.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests flat opening for equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-flat-opening-for-equities/1662166</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662166</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 14.00 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 14.00 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 317.56 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,772.56 crore in the Indian equity market on 24 December 2025, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 24,148.33 crore so far in December. This follows their cash sales of Rs 17,500.31 crore in November and Rs 2,346.89 crore in October. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Monday as investors kicked off the final trading week of the year. Prices of spot silver rose to a fresh record high of above $80 per ounce before pulling back sharply to $77. Silver’s recent surge was driven by speculative buying and lingering supply tightness, said experts. Media report further stated silver’s rally this year reflects a depletion of freely traded inventory, amplifying price moves as demand increases. On Friday stateside, the S&P 500 reached a new high and posted weekly gains as traders came back from the Christmas holiday. The broad market index closed down 0.03% to end at 6,929.94. At its high, the S&P 500 was up 0.2%, reaching 6,945.77. The Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.09% and closed at 23,593.10. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 20.19 points, or 0.04%, and settled at 48,710.97. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks slipped into the red on Tuesday, as profit booking in a holiday-shortened week and relentless FII selling sapped investor confidence. The Nifty closed below the 26,050 mark, pulled down by losses in IT and auto stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 367.25 points or 0.43% to 85,041.45. The Nifty 50 index lost 99.80 points or 0.38% to 26,042.30.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Coforge, Vedanta, Suzlon Energy, Solarworld Energy Solutions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-coforge-vedanta-suzlon-energy-solarworld-energy-solutions/1662162</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662162</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Monday, 29 December 2025.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Monday, 29 December 2025. Key Events to Watch The government is slated to release the Index of Industrial Production (IIP) data for November, which will offer cues on industrial activity. The Supreme Court of India is scheduled to hear a matter related to the definition of the Aravalli Hills. S. Krishnan, Secretary, Ministry of Electronics & IT, will brief the media on the upcoming India AI Impact Summit 2026. Stocks to Watch: Coforge announced that it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire a 100% stake in Encora from Advent International, Warburg Pincus, and other minority shareholders for Rs 17,032.6 crore. The enterprise value of the transaction stands at $2.35 billion. The board approved raising up to $550 million through a qualified institutional placement (QIP) to repay Encora’s term loan. Vedanta said that it has been declared the successful bidder for the Depo Graphite–Vanadium block under the critical mineral auctions. The company said the development will strengthen its critical minerals portfolio. Suzlon Energy announced that Vivek Srivastava has resigned as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of the WTG Division, effective December 26. Diamond Power Infrastructure said that it has received a letter of intent from Hild Projects, an EPC contractor, for the supply of power cables worth Rs 66.18 crore. Avantel informed that it has received a contract worth Rs 4.16 crore from the Ministry of Defence, Headquarters Naval Aviation, for CAMC of Satcom equipment. Solarworld Energy Solutions said that it has received a letter of award from NTPC Renewable Energy for an EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project valued at Rs 725.33 crore. Vikran Engineering announced that it has accepted letters of award from MP Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of grid-connected solar PV-based power plants with an aggregate capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Monarch Surveyors secures Rs 3-cr contract from Western Railway]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/monarch-surveyors-secures-rs-3-cr-contract-from-western-railway/1662161</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662161</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves carrying out pre- and post-tamping track measurement surveys using the Trimble Gedo Vorsys trolley system.

The contract involves carrying out pre- and post-tamping track measurement surveys using the Trimble Gedo Vorsys trolley system. The project aims to support accurate track geometry assessment and improve rail infrastructure maintenance. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and will be executed in India. The company clarified that the transaction does not fall under related party transactions, and that the promoters or promoter group entities have no interest in the awarded contract. The deal has been entered into at arm’s length. The work will commence immediately as per the letter of acceptance, with completion timelines governed by the terms of the contract. The project is subject to receipt of necessary approvals from relevant governmental authorities. The contract will be executed on a cash consideration basis, with a total value of Rs 3,29,89,898.40. No shareholding or control is being acquired as part of the transaction. Monarch Surveyors and Engineering Consultants are engaged in the business to provide comprehensive consultancy services under Concept to Commissioning of infrastructure projects which includes Survey, design and technical supervision for roads, railways, metros, town planning, geospatial, mapping, land acquisition, water, transmission Line, pipelines and other civil engineering sectors. Our objective is to create consistent value for our clients by delivering uncompromising quality of services at optimum cost through continuous improvement in elemental technologies of this field, maintaining integrity and design processes which fosters excellence in all the aspects of our operations. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 16.1% to Rs 34.83 crore on a 10.5% rise in revenue to Rs 154.14 crore in FY25 compared with FY24. The counter fell 1.59% to end at Rs 210 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MonarchSurveyorsandEngineeringConsultantsLimited_26476128_94045.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>