<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:27:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Current state of Indian economy provides ground for optimism going forward, says RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/current-state-of-indian-economy-provides-ground-for-optimism-going-forward-says-rbi/1666412</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666412</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that amidst the global uncertainties, the current state of the Indian economy provides ground for optimism going forward.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that amidst the global uncertainties, the current state of the Indian economy provides ground for optimism going forward. The GDP growth estimates for 2025-26 indicate that India will remain the fastest-growing major economy in the world. India has made significant efforts to diversify and strengthen its exports, aiming to mitigate external sector risks. The country is currently engaged in trade negotiations with 14 countries or groups, representing nearly 50 nations, including the European Union, Gulf Cooperation Council countries, and the United States. The month of December saw India concluding trade negotiations with New Zealand and Oman. The year 2025 also witnessed major economic reforms, including the rationalisation of tax structures, implementation of labour codes for labour market reforms, and financial sector deregulation, all of which are expected to strengthen the growth prospects.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/growth-951606__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI says softening in cereal prices continues]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-says-softening-in-cereal-prices-continues/1666411</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666411</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that food prices remained in deflation for the fourth consecutive month, though the rate of deflation eased.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that food prices remained in deflation for the fourth consecutive month, though the rate of deflation eased. Within food group, prices declined for cereals, pulses, spices, and vegetables on a y-o-y basis. High-frequency food price data for January so far (up to 19th) point towards a softening in cereal prices. Among pulses, a broad-based moderation in prices is observed across gram, moong and tur/arhar dal. Within edible oils, sunflower oil and groundnut oil prices increased. Within vegetables, onion prices picked up while potato prices eased further.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[High-frequency indicators of industrial activity remained strong in December, says RBI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/high-frequency-indicators-of-industrial-activity-remained-strong-in-december-says-rbi/1666410</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666410</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that in November, growth in industrial activity, as measured by the year-on-year (y-o-y) change in the Index of Industrial Production (IIP), jumped to a 25-month high, primarily driven by a robust manufacturing growth.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that in November, growth in industrial activity, as measured by the year-on-year (y-o-y) change in the Index of Industrial Production (IIP), jumped to a 25-month high, primarily driven by a robust manufacturing growth. Mining sector also rebounded after two consecutive months of contraction. The index of eight core industries posted a four-month high growth in December, led by strong growth in steel and cement and turnaround in electricity generation. High-frequency indicators of industrial activity remained strong in December. Automobile production experienced accelerated growth across segments in December, underpinned by a healthy booking pipeline driven by policy support, including income tax relief, GST rationalisation, and easier financing conditions. Tractor production also surged in view of buoyant sales propelled by improved cash flows from strong kharif output. Electricity generation, which had contracted for two consecutive months, recovered in December. The manufacturing PMI remained in expansion despite some deceleration due to slower expansion in new orders and output.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-1203161_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Advance estimates of GDP reflect resilience of Indian economy, demand conditions upbeat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/advance-estimates-of-gdp-reflect-resilience-of-indian-economy-demand-conditions-upbeat/1666392</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666392</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that the first advance estimates of gross domestic product (GDP) for 2025-26 reflected the resilience of the Indian economy, driven by domestic factors - private final consumption expenditure (PFCE) and fixed investment - amidst a challenging external environment.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has stated in its monthly update today that the first advance estimates of gross domestic product (GDP) for 2025-26 reflected the resilience of the Indian economy, driven by domestic factors - private final consumption expenditure (PFCE) and fixed investment - amidst a challenging external environment. A strong rebound in the manufacturing sector and continued buoyancy in services is expected to boost growth in gross value added (GVA). High-frequency indicators for December suggest continued buoyancy in growth impulses. Demand conditions remained upbeat, underpinned by a resurgence in rural demand and a gradual recovery in urban demand. On the demand side, PFCE and fixed investment were the key growth drivers. On the supply side, a strong rebound in the manufacturing sector and continued buoyancy in services boosted GVA growth. High-frequency indicators for December suggest a continued buoyancy in growth impulses. Demand conditions remained upbeat, underpinned by a resurgence in rural demand and a gradual recovery in urban demand.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id4664857_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee Tanks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-tanks/1666390</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666390</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 91.6700 per Dollar on Wednesday (21 January 2025), versus its previous close of 91.0150 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies IPO subscribed 60%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shadowfax-technologies-ipo-subscribed-60/1666389</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666389</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 5,33,05,920 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Wednesday (21 January 2026).

Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 5,33,05,920 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Wednesday (21 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.60 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 January 2026 and it will close on 22 January 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. The Rs 1,907 crore IPO comprises a fresh issue of 80.6 million equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,000 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 73.2 million equity shares worth up to Rs 907.27 crore. Existing investors—Flipkart India, Eight Roads Investments Mauritius II, International Finance Corporation, Qualcomm Asia Pacific, Nokia Growth Partners, NewQuest Asia Fund and Miare Asset—will offload part of their holdings through the OFS. Shadowfax plans to utilize Rs 423.43 crore from the net proceeds of the fresh issue to enhance network infrastructure capacity, Rs 138.64 crore towards lease payments for new first-mile, last-mile and sort centers, and Rs 88.57 crore for branding, marketing and communication initiatives. The balance will be used for unidentified inorganic acquisitions and general corporate purposes. Shadowfax Technologies is a leading Indian logistics and 3PL player providing e-commerce, D2C, quick commerce and hyperlocal delivery services. It operates a nationwide network covering over 14,700 pin codes and serves major clients such as Flipkart, Meesho, Swiggy, Zomato, Blinkit and Nykaa. The company is among the fastest-growing large-scale logistics providers, with rising market share and strong order growth. Ahead of the IPO of Shadowfax Technologies on 19 January 2026, the company raised Rs 856.02 crore from anchor investors by allotting 6.90 crore shares at Rs 124 each to 39 anchor investors. For the three months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 21.04 crore and sales of Rs 1,805.64 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper holds steady amid stressed equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-holds-steady-amid-stressed-equities/1666387</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666387</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures held up steady today though weak equities capped gains.

COMEX Copper futures held up steady today though weak equities capped gains. The metal currently trades at $5.84 per pound, up 0.85% on the day after some stability emerged in the counter following recent losses. However, bulk of the gains are due to steady global growth forecast amid tepid US dollar as equities are under stress. In Asia, Shanghai Composite index edged up marginally while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index added 0.37%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index eased 0.41% amid sustained selling pressure. European stocks stayed cautious. German DAX shed around half a percent. The US stocks slumped amid renewed concerns about a trade war between the US and Europe over President Donald Trump's efforts to take control of Greenland. The Dow lost 1.8%; the Nasdaq plummeted 2.4% and the S&P 500 tumbled 2.1%. MCX Copper futures gained sharply, breaking above Rs 1300 per kg and currently trade at Rs 1304.50 per kg, up 1.50% on the day as the Indian Rupee tanked to a fresh record low against the US dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-petrochemical-plant-equipment-picture-id627839_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eternal Q3 PAT jumps 73% YoY to Rs 102-cr; CEO Deepinder Goyal resigns ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eternal-q3-pat-jumps-73-yoy-to-rs-102-cr-ceo-deepinder-goyal-resigns/1666384</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666384</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 37.1% YoY to Rs 170 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 37.1% YoY to Rs 170 crore during the quarter. Adjusted revenue grew 190% YoY (19% QoQ) to Rs 16,692 crore, However, on a like-for-like basis, growth was 64% YoY, with the difference largely reflecting the accounting shift to inventory ownership in quick commerce, under which revenue now includes the full value of goods sold rather than only marketplace commissions. Adjusted EBITDA stood at Rs 364 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 27.72% compared with Rs 285 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. In food delivery business, adjusted revenue increased 26.5% YoY to Rs 3,053 crore in Q3 FY26. Net order value (NOV) jumped 16.6% YoY to Rs 9,846 crore during the quarter. In his letter to shareholders, Deepinder Goyal attributed the stronger growth primarily to a modest improvement in the demand environment, especially during the second half of the quarter which led to higher app opens and consequently higher-than-expected order volumes. Growth was also supported by the full-quarter impact of the reduction in the minimum order value for free delivery on Gold orders to Rs 99 from Rs 199, which boosted ordering frequency among more budget-conscious customers. The company expects year-on-year growth to gradually move closer to 20% over time. In quick commerce business, adjusted revenue surged 776.1% YoY to Rs 12,256 crore in Q3 FY26, On a like-for-like (LFL) basis, quick commerce revenue grew 153% YoY (13% QoQ) in Q3FY26. NOV soared 120.9% YoY to Rs 13,300 crore during the quarter. The company, however, fell short of its store rollout guidance by around 70 stores against a target of 2,100 stores for the quarter. This was primarily due to extended pollution-related restrictions in its largest city, which slowed construction and store fit-outs for several weeks and continue to remain in effect. During Diwali and surrounding weeks, the operations team had to prioritise managing record order volumes over opening new stores. The company stated that the stores not opened in Q3 will be commissioned in Q4 and reaffirmed that it remains on track to reach 3,000 stores by March 2027. Going-out NOV grew 20% YoY whereas Adjusted EBITDA margin (as a % of NOV) declined to -4.7% resulting in an Adjusted EBITDA loss of Rs 121 crore in the quarter as against Rs 63 crore in Q2FY26, driven by continued investments in category creation. The company expects losses to reduce from here sequentially towards breakeven in the next 4-6 quarters. As mentioned earlier, it thinks District can become a $3 billion NOV business with 5% Adjusted EBITDA margin by FY30. Hyperpure, the restaurant supply business continued to grow steadily at 33% YoY (7% QoQ) with total Adjusted EBITDA margin turning positive for the first time resulting in an Adjusted EBITDA profit of Rs 1 crore as compared to loss of Rs 5 crore in the previous quarter. Meanwhile, the company’s board accepted the resignation of Deepinder Goyal, managing director & chief executive officer, with effect from 1 February 2026. Following this, the board approved the appointment of Albinder Singh Dhindsa (currently, CEO of Blinkit) as chief executive officer with effect from 1 February 2026. Eternal, an Indian multinational technology company, is the parent company of Zomato, Blinkit, District and Hyperpure. The scrip rallied 4.98% to settle at Rs 283.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EternalLtd_13706833_68117.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty slide for third session amid global jitters]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-slide-for-third-session-amid-global-jitters/1666379</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666379</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equities extended losses for a third straight session on Wednesday as global shocks and weak earnings hit risk appetite.

Domestic equities extended losses for a third straight session on Wednesday as global shocks and weak earnings hit risk appetite. The Sensex fell over 1,000 points intraday, while the Nifty 50 slipped below 25,000 for the first time since October. Selling was broad-based, with IT, chemicals and consumer durables under sharp pressure. Banking and financial stocks stayed weak, while defensive sectors offered limited support. Equities were weighed down by renewed global uncertainty after President Donald Trump’s remarks on Greenland, soft domestic earnings, a record-low rupee, and continued foreign investor selling. The S&P BSE Sensex dropped 270.84 points or 0.33% to 81,909.63. The Nifty 50 index lost 75 points or 0.30% to 25,157.50. In three trading sessions, the Sensex slipped 1.99% while the Nifty declined 2.09%. ICICI Bank (down 2.10%), HDFC Bank (down 1.10%) and Larsen & Toubro (down 1.06%) were major Nifty drags today. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.80%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,437 shares rose and 2,831 shares fell. A total of 142 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 8.24% to 13.78. The Indian rupee fell to a record low of 91.19 against the US dollar on Wednesday, pressured by a stronger greenback as fresh tariff threats from US President Donald Trump over Greenland fueled global risk aversion. World Economic Forum: At the 56th World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos, the Adani Group on Wednesday outlined a $66 billion investment blueprint for Maharashtra, spanning aviation, clean energy, urban infrastructure, digital platforms and advanced manufacturing, positioning itself as a long-term partner in the state’s infrastructure-led growth agenda. U.S. President Donald Trump arrived in Davos on Wednesday (21 January 2026) for high-level engagements with European leaders, with his renewed push on Greenland adding to tensions within the transatlantic alliance. Meanwhile, European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, in a special address on Tuesday (20 January 2026), said the European Union is close to finalizing a landmark trade agreement with India. She described the pact as "the mother of all deals," noting it could create a market encompassing nearly two billion people, or about one-fourth of global GDP. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.16% to 6.662 as compared with the previous close of 6.673. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6850 compared with its close of 90.9700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement jumped 4.69% to Rs 1,57,619. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.05% to 98.49. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.33% to 4.281. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement lost 43 cents or 0.66% to $64.49 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares traded lower on Wednesday as investors awaited U.S. President Donald Trump’s address at the World Economic Forum later in the day. Most Asian shares ended lower, while gold jumped to a record high level after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on countries resisting the transfer of Greenland to the United States. Spot gold prices rose over 1% to an all-time high of $4,813 per ounce as investors rushed into safe haven assets. On Saturday, Trump said that exports from eight European countries would face tariffs of 10% from Feb. 1, rising to 25% by June 1 if talks fail to deliver U.S. control of mineral-rich Greenland. He also threatened to slap 200% tariffs on French wine and champagne, following reports that President Emmanuel Macron was unwilling to join his proposed “Board of Peace.” Trump further criticized the U.K., calling its plan to transfer sovereignty of the Chagos Islands, which is home to a joint U.K.-U.S. military base, to Mauritius an “act of great stupidity,” citing the move as further justification for acquiring Greenland on national security grounds. European leaders have labeled President Donald Trump's latest tariff threats "unacceptable" and are reportedly weighing retaliatory measures. France is said to be urging the European Union to deploy its strongest economic response tool, the so-called Anti-Coercion Instrument. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 870.74 points, or 1.76%, to end the session at 48,488.59. The S&P 500 dipped 2.06% to settle at 6,796.86. The Nasdaq Composite slid 2.39%, closing at 22,954.32. It was the worst session since October for all three major averages. U.S. Treasury yields spiked and the U.S. dollar declined as Trump’s threat caused a flight from U.S. assets. New Listing: Shares of Amagi Media Labs ended at Rs 348 on the BSE, a discount of 3.60% as compared with the issue price of Rs 361. The stock debuted at Rs 317, a discount of 12.19% to the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 357.50 and a low of 317. On the BSE, over 18.97 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Stocks in Spotlight: Persistent Systems declined 1.57% after the company reported a 6.79% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 439.4 crore despite of 5.52% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3778.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. IndiaMart InterMESH jumped 5.73% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 55.62% to Rs 188.3 crore on a 13.35% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 401.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shoppers Stop tanked 5.86% after the company’s standalone profit slipped 74.14% to Rs 12.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 48.78 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations marginally rose 0.71% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,320.85 crore in Q3 FY26. SRF tumbled 6.56%. The company reported a 59.60% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 432.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 271.08 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations rose 6.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 3,712.53 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Rallis India rose 2.34%. The company’s standalone net profit tanked 81.81% to Rs 2 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 11 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 19.34% year on year (YoY) to Rs 623 crore in Q3 FY26, driven primarily by strong volume growth across businesses. KPI Green Energy fell 1.77%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 47.73% to Rs 125.80 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 85.15 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 676 crore, up 45% year-on-year from Rs 466 crore in Q3 FY25, driven by accelerated project execution and strong performance across key business segments. Vikram Solar tumbled 8.52% after the company reported a 25.2% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 96.1 crore on a 0.36% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,105.95 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Supreme Petrochem rose 1.62%. The company’s standalone net profit fell 57.74% to Rs 30.15 crore on a 10% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,264.69 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. K.P. Energy fell 1.70%. The company reported a 56.68% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 41.35 crore on a 62.83% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 344.96 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 5,30,88,480 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:45 IST on Wednesday (21 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.60 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR tumbles to settle at new record low of Rs 91.70 amid risk-off sentiment in global markets; Nifty drags under 25K]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-tumbles-to-settle-at-new-record-low-of-rs-9170-amid-risk-off-sentiment-in-global-markets-nifty-drags-under-25k/1666362</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666362</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee crashed 73 paise to close at an all-time low of 91.70 (provisional) against the American currency on Wednesday, pressured by persistent foreign fund outflow amid heightened uncertainty and risk-off sentiment in global markets.

The Indian rupee crashed 73 paise to close at an all-time low of 91.70 (provisional) against the American currency on Wednesday, pressured by persistent foreign fund outflow amid heightened uncertainty and risk-off sentiment in global markets. The local unit recorded its previous all-time low of 91.14 on December 16, 2025, and so far this month, the local unit has fallen by 1.50 per cent. The depreciation in the local unit can be attributed to heightened geopolitical uncertainty. Rising tensions in Europe over the Greenland issue and potential tariffs are denting investor sentiment. Domestic shares extended a bruising selloff into a third straight session on Wednesday as risk aversion gripped financial markets on the back of rising bond yields and U.S. President Donald Trump's renewed push to acquire Greenland. The BSE Sensex tumbled more than 850 points before recovering some lost ground to end the session down 270.84 points, or 0.33 percent at 81,909.63, extending losses for a third day. The broader NSE Nifty index ended down 75 points, or 0.30 percent, at 25,157.50, after hitting a low of 24,919.80 earlier.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at a premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-a-premium/1666361</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666361</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,190, a premium of 32.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,157.50 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,190, a premium of 32.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,157.50 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index lost 75 points or 0.30% to 25,157.50. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 8.24% to 13.78. HDFC Bank, Infosys and Eternal were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices ends with moderate losses; Nifty settles below 25,200 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-ends-with-moderate-losses-nifty-settles-below-25200-level/1666357</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666357</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today, extending losses for the third consecutive session, amid persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings and lingering global trade and geopolitical concerns.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today, extending losses for the third consecutive session, amid persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings and lingering global trade and geopolitical concerns. A sharp rise in the India VIX signalled heightened volatility as investors stayed on the sidelines ahead of key Q3 earnings and cues from the World Economic Forum. The Nifty settled below the 25,200 level. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 270.84 points or 0.33% to 81,909.63. The Nifty 50 index lost 75 points or 0.30% to 25,157.50. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex slipped 1.99% while the Nifty declined 2.09%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.80%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 8.24% to 13.78. The Indian rupee fell to a record low of 91.19 against the US dollar on Wednesday, pressured by a stronger greenback as fresh tariff threats from US President Donald Trump over Greenland fueled global risk aversion. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Metal index (up 0.57%), the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 0.27%) and the Nifty Auto (down 0.29%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Chemical index (down 2.12%), Nifty Consumer Durables index (down 1.66%) and the Nifty PSU Bank index (down 1.01%) and the underperformed the Nifty 50 index. World Economic Forum: At the 56th World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos, the Adani Group on Wednesday outlined a $66 billion investment blueprint for Maharashtra, spanning aviation, clean energy, urban infrastructure, digital platforms and advanced manufacturing, positioning itself as a long-term partner in the state’s infrastructure-led growth agenda. U.S. President Donald Trump arrived in Davos on Wednesday (January 21, 2026) for high-level engagements with European leaders, with his renewed push on Greenland adding to tensions within the transatlantic alliance. Meanwhile, European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, in a special address on Tuesday (January 20, 2026), said the European Union is close to finalizing a landmark trade agreement with India. She described the pact as “the mother of all deals,” noting it could create a market encompassing nearly two billion people, or about one-fourth of global GDP. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.16% to 6.662 as compared with the previous close of 6.673. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6850 compared with its close of 90.9700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement jumped 4.69% to Rs 1,57,619. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.05% to 98.49. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.33% to 4.281. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement lost 43 cents or 0.66% to $64.49 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares traded lower on Wednesday as investors awaited U.S. President Donald Trump’s address at the World Economic Forum later in the day. Most Asian markets ended lower, while gold jumped to a record high level after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on countries resisting the transfer of Greenland to the United States. Spot gold prices rose over 1% to an all-time high of $4,813 per ounce as investors rushed into safe haven assets. On Saturday, Trump said that exports from eight European countries would face tariffs of 10% from Feb. 1, rising to 25% by June 1 if talks fail to deliver U.S. control of mineral-rich Greenland. He also threatened to slap 200% tariffs on French wine and champagne, following reports that President Emmanuel Macron was unwilling to join his proposed “Board of Peace.” Trump further criticized the U.K., calling its plan to transfer sovereignty of the Chagos Islands, which is home to a joint U.K.-U.S. military base, to Mauritius an “act of great stupidity,” citing the move as further justification for acquiring Greenland on national security grounds. European leaders have labeled President Donald Trump’s latest tariff threats “unacceptable” and are reportedly weighing retaliatory measures. France is said to be urging the European Union to deploy its strongest economic response tool, the so-called Anti-Coercion Instrument. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 870.74 points, or 1.76%, to end the session at 48,488.59. The S&P 500 dipped 2.06% to settle at 6,796.86. The Nasdaq Composite slid 2.39%, closing at 22,954.32. It was the worst session since October for all three major averages. U.S. Treasury yields spiked and the U.S. dollar declined as Trump’s threat caused a flight from U.S. assets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Bank Index falls 1.02%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-bank-index-falls-102/1666354</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666354</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Bank index closed down 1.02% at 58800.3 today.

Nifty Bank index closed down 1.02% at 58800.3 today. The index has slipped 1.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, ICICI Bank Ltd dropped 1.95%, Canara Bank slipped 1.90% and Union Bank of India fell 1.86%. The Nifty Bank index has soared 21.00% over last one year compared to the 9.26% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index has dropped 1.01% and Nifty Financial Services index is down 0.87% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 is down 0.30% to close at 25157.5 while the SENSEX has slid 0.33% to close at 81909.63 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-1071758__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 271 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,200 level; VIX spurts 8.24%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-271-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25200-level-vix-spurts-824/1666355</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666355</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts today, extending losses for the third consecutive session, amid persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings and lingering global trade and geopolitical concerns.

The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts today, extending losses for the third consecutive session, amid persistent foreign fund outflows, uneven corporate earnings and lingering global trade and geopolitical concerns. A sharp rise in the India VIX signalled heightened volatility as investors stayed on the sidelines ahead of key Q3 earnings and cues from the World Economic Forum. The Nifty settled below the 25,200 level. Consumer durables, PSU bank and private bank stocks declined, while metal and oil & gas advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 270.84 points or 0.33% to 81,909.63. The Nifty 50 index lost 75 points or 0.30% to 25,157.50. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex slipped 1.99% while the Nifty declined 2.09%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 1.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.80%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,439 shares rose and 2,831 shares fell. A total of 122 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 8.24% to 13.78. The Indian rupee fell to a record low of 91.6850 against the US dollar on Wednesday, pressured by a stronger greenback as fresh tariff threats from US President Donald Trump over Greenland fueled global risk aversion. World Economic Forum: At the 56th World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos, the Adani Group on Wednesday outlined a $66 billion investment blueprint for Maharashtra, spanning aviation, clean energy, urban infrastructure, digital platforms and advanced manufacturing, positioning itself as a long-term partner in the state’s infrastructure-led growth agenda. U.S. President Donald Trump arrived in Davos on Wednesday (January 21, 2026) for high-level engagements with European leaders, with his renewed push on Greenland adding to tensions within the transatlantic alliance. Meanwhile, European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, in a special address on Tuesday (January 20, 2026), said the European Union is close to finalizing a landmark trade agreement with India. She described the pact as “the mother of all deals,” noting it could create a market encompassing nearly two billion people, or about one-fourth of global GDP. New Listing: Shares of Amagi Media Labs ended at Rs 348 on the BSE, representing a discount of 3.60% as compared with the issue price of Rs 361. The stock debuted at Rs 317, a discount of 12.19% to the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 357.50 and a low of 317. On the BSE, over 18.97 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 5,21,19,480 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Wednesday (21 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.59 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index fell 1.66% to 34,740. The index dropped 9.38% in the nine consecutive trading sessions. Kalyan Jewellers India (down 12.68%), Amber Enterprises India (down 4.02%), PG Electroplast (down 3.34%), Voltas (down 2.32%), Havells India (down 2.23%), Blue Star (down 1.99%), Dixon Technologies (India) (down 1.49%), Bata India (down 0.74%), Kajaria Ceramics (down 0.72%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (down 0.6%) tumbled. Stocks in Spotlight: Persistent Systems declined 1.57% after the company reported a 6.79% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 439.4 crore despite of 5.52% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3778.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. IndiaMart InterMESH jumped 5.73% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 55.62% to Rs 188.3 crore on a 13.35% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 401.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shoppers Stop tanked 5.86% after the company’s standalone profit slipped 74.14% to Rs 12.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 48.78 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations marginally rose 0.71% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,320.85 crore in Q3 FY26. United Spirits rose 0.47%. The company’s standalone net profit increased 11.83% to Rs 529 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 473 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding net excise duty) jumped 7.31% to Rs 3,683 crore in Q3 December 2025, driven by solid performance in the top half of the portfolio, partly offset by the adverse policy-led impact in Maharashtra and lapping the one-time retail pipeline fill in Andhra Pradesh in the prior year comparative. Rallis India rose 2.34%. The company’s standalone net profit tanked 81.81% to Rs 2 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 11 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 19.34% year on year (YoY) to Rs 623 crore in Q3 FY26, driven primarily by strong volume growth across businesses. KPI Green Energy fell 1.77%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 47.73% to Rs 125.80 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 85.15 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 676 crore, up 45% year-on-year from Rs 466 crore in Q3 FY25, driven by accelerated project execution and strong performance across key business segments. Supreme Industries shed 0.77%. The company’s consolidated net profit slipped 17.97% to Rs 153.37 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 186.97 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 7.05% year on year (YoY) to Rs 2,686.94 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. AU Small Finance Bank (SFB) shed 0.68%. The company reported a 26.34% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 667.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 528.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Cyient DLM shed 0.75%. The company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 65.06% to Rs 11.23 crore on a 2.35% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 303.34 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Vikram Solar tumbled 8.52% after the company reported a 25.2% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 96.1 crore on a 0.36% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,105.95 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Supreme Petrochem rose 1.62%. The company’s standalone net profit fell 57.74% to Rs 30.15 crore on a 10% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 1,264.69 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. K.P. Energy fell 1.70%. The company reported a 56.68% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 41.35 crore on a 62.83% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 344.96 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. SRF tumbled 6.56%. The company reported a 59.60% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 432.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 271.08 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations rose 6.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 3,712.53 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: European shares traded lower on Wednesday as investors awaited U.S. President Donald Trump’s address at the World Economic Forum later in the day. Most Asian markets ended lower, while gold jumped to a record high level after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on countries resisting the transfer of Greenland to the United States. Spot gold prices rose over 1% to an all-time high of $4,813 per ounce as investors rushed into safe haven assets. On Saturday, Trump said that exports from eight European countries would face tariffs of 10% from Feb. 1, rising to 25% by June 1 if talks fail to deliver U.S. control of mineral-rich Greenland. He also threatened to slap 200% tariffs on French wine and champagne, following reports that President Emmanuel Macron was unwilling to join his proposed “Board of Peace.” Trump further criticized the U.K., calling its plan to transfer sovereignty of the Chagos Islands, which is home to a joint U.K.-U.S. military base, to Mauritius an “act of great stupidity,” citing the move as further justification for acquiring Greenland on national security grounds. European leaders have labeled President Donald Trump’s latest tariff threats “unacceptable” and are reportedly weighing retaliatory measures. France is said to be urging the European Union to deploy its strongest economic response tool, the so-called Anti-Coercion Instrument. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 870.74 points, or 1.76%, to end the session at 48,488.59. The S&P 500 dipped 2.06% to settle at 6,796.86. The Nasdaq Composite slid 2.39%, closing at 22,954.32. It was the worst session since October for all three major averages. U.S. Treasury yields spiked and the U.S. dollar declined as Trump’s threat caused a flight from U.S. assets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rajratan Global gains after Q3 PAT climbs 122% YoY to Rs 21 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rajratan-global-gains-after-q3-pat-climbs-122-yoy-to-rs-21-crore/1666352</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666352</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[During the quarter, profit before tax (PBT) climbed 116.36% to Rs 26.70 crore, compared with Rs 12.34 crore in Q3 FY25.

During the quarter, profit before tax (PBT) climbed 116.36% to Rs 26.70 crore, compared with Rs 12.34 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 33.39% to Rs 275.36 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 206.43 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of material consumed stood at Rs 175.07 crore (up 23% YoY), employee benefit expenses were Rs 13.85 crore (down 18.78% YoY) and finance costs stood at Rs 7.23 crore (down 8.13% YoY) during the period under review. Meanwhile, the board of directors, at its meeting held on Wednesday, 21 January 2026, approved the reappointment of Yashovardhan Chordia as chief executive officer & deputy managing director of the company, liable to retire by rotation, for a period of three years with effect from 21 April 2026 to 20 April 2029 (both days inclusive), subject to the approval of the shareholders. Rajratan Global Wire is engaged in the manufacturing of bead wire, a high-carbon steel wire utilized in the production of tires.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RajratanGlobal_26706945406_4364.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ministry of Power announces new draft National Electricity Policy 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ministry-of-power-announces-new-draft-national-electricity-policy-2026/1666349</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666349</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Ministry of Power announced the release of a new “Draft National Electricity Policy (NEP) 2026”.

The Ministry of Power announced the release of a new “Draft National Electricity Policy (NEP) 2026”. The Draft NEP 2026 aims to transform the power sector for meeting the vision of Viksit Bharat @2047. The policy, once finalised, intends to replace the existing NEP which was notified in 2005. The first National Electricity Policy, notified in February 2005, addressed fundamental challenges of the power sector, including demand–supply deficits, limited access to electricity, and inadequate infrastructure. Since then, India’s power sector has witnessed transformational progress. Installed generation capacity has increased fourfold with significant private sector participation; universal electrification was achieved by March 2021; a unified national grid became operational in December 2013; and per capita electricity consumption reached 1,460 kWh in 2024–25. Power markets and exchanges have improved flexibility and efficiency in power procurement across the country. In spite of these achievements, persistent challenges remain, particularly in the distribution segment like high accumulated losses and outstanding debt. Tariffs in several segments remain non–cost reflective, and high cross-subsidisation has resulted in elevated industrial tariffs, adversely affecting the global competitiveness of Indian industry. Against this backdrop, the Draft NEP 2026 sets ambitious yet necessary goals. The Policy targets per capita electricity consumption of 2,000 kWh by 2030 and over 4,000 kWh by 2047. It also aligns with India’s climate commitments, including reduction of emissions intensity by 45 percent below 2005 levels by 2030 and achievement of net-zero emissions by 2070, necessitating a decisive shift towards low-carbon energy pathways.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-1043552_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold boosted by Greenland tensions and tariff threats]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-boosted-by-greenland-tensions-and-tariff-threats/1666340</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666340</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold extended its strong rally toward $4,900 per ounce in early electronic trade, scaling a fresh record as escalating tensions over Greenland and President Trump’s tariff threats against eight European nations intensified safe-haven demand.

Gold extended its strong rally toward $4,900 per ounce in early electronic trade, scaling a fresh record as escalating tensions over Greenland and President Trump’s tariff threats against eight European nations intensified safe-haven demand. Further support came from a softer US dollar, with the dollar index slipping near 98.5 for a third straight session amid waning confidence in US assets. On the domestic front, MCX February gold futures surged nearly 5% to trade around ₹1,57,650 per 10 grams, while investors now await the delayed US PCE inflation data later this week for clearer signals on the Federal Reserve’s rate outlook.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Govt approves continuation of Atal Pension Yojana till 2030-31]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/govt-approves-continuation-of-atal-pension-yojana-till-2030-31/1666337</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666337</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Union Cabinet on Wednesday approved continuation of government's flagship Atal Pension Yojana (APY) up to financial year 2030-31 along with extension of funding support for promotional and developmental activities and gap funding.

The Union Cabinet on Wednesday approved continuation of government's flagship Atal Pension Yojana (APY) up to financial year 2030-31 along with extension of funding support for promotional and developmental activities and gap funding. APY was launched on May 9, 2015 with the objective of providing old-age income security to workers in the unorganised sector. As of January 19, 2026, over 8.66 crore subscribers have been enrolled under APY.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/tightening-up-on-savings-picture-id477424223_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kalyan-jewellers-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1666335</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666335</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Inox Green Energy Services Ltd, SRF Ltd, Shoppers Stop Ltd and The Anup Engineering Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 21 January 2026.

Inox Green Energy Services Ltd, SRF Ltd, Shoppers Stop Ltd and The Anup Engineering Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 21 January 2026. Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd lost 10.85% to Rs 402.6 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 24.11 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.82 lakh shares in the past one month. Inox Green Energy Services Ltd crashed 10.04% to Rs 155.9. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.23 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53131 shares in the past one month. SRF Ltd tumbled 6.71% to Rs 2680.25. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 41263 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 30103 shares in the past one month. Shoppers Stop Ltd pared 6.64% to Rs 340.05. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 86914 shares in the past one month. The Anup Engineering Ltd slipped 6.28% to Rs 1845.7. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1909 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1131 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KalyanJewellersIndia_46056464.1248805_42402.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME GRE Renew Enertech enters Dalal Street on a softer note]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-gre-renew-enertech-enters-dalal-street-on-a-softer-note/1666336</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666336</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 96, a discount of 8.57% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 96, a discount of 8.57% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its lower limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 99 and a low of Rs 91.20. About 9.26 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. GRE Renew Enertech's IPO was subscribed 15.43 times. The issue opened for bidding on 13 January 2026 and it closed on 16 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was set at Rs 100 to Rs 105 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 37,68,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilised the net proceeds for setting up of 7.20 MW (AC) / 9.99 MW (DC) ground mounted solar power plant and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, GRE Renew Enertech 12 January 2025, raised Rs 11.15 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 10.62 lakh shares at Rs 105 each to 9 anchor investors. GRE Renew Enertech provides solar energy solutions to industrial and commercial customers through two operating models: CAPEX and RESCO. Under the CAPEX model, customers fund the project while the company handles engineering, procurement, construction and operations. Under the RESCO model, GRE Renew Enertech develops, owns and operates solar projects, supplying power to consumers at pre-agreed tariffs while retaining ownership of the assets, including rooftop installations and proposed ground-mounted projects. The company is planning to develop a 7.20 MW (AC) or 9.99 MW (DC) ground-mounted solar power project as part of its expansion under the RESCO model. As of 30 September 2025, the company had employed 48 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 43.80 crore and net profit of Rs 4 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GRERenewEnertechLtd_52580340_65238.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>