<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:27:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shakti Pumps India rises after bagging Rs 170-cr order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shakti-pumps-india-rises-after-bagging-rs-170-cr-order/1662625</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662625</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order is for the supply of 4,840 stand-alone off-grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems (SPWPS) across the state of Madhya Pradesh under Component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme.

According to an exchange filing, the order is for the supply of 4,840 stand-alone off-grid DC solar photovoltaic water pumping systems (SPWPS) across the state of Madhya Pradesh under Component-B of the PM-KUSUM scheme. The total value of the order for the 4,840 pumps is approximately Rs 170.25 crore. The company stated that the order will be executed within 120 days. It also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Shakti Pumps (India) manufactures solar pumps, energy-efficient stainless-steel submersible pumps, pressure booster pumps, pump motors, and other products. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 10.56% to Rs 90.71 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Rs 101.42 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5% YoY to Rs 666.35 crore in Q2 Sept 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShaktiPumps_14702424257_6580.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Admach Systems wobbles on debut before stabilising]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-admach-systems-wobbles-on-debut-before-stabilising/1662624</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662624</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 191.20, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 191.20, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 200.75 and a low of Rs 191.20. About 9.29 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Admach Systems' IPO was subscribed 3.95 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 December 2025 and it closed on 26 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 227 to Rs 239 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 17,82,600 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for funding of capital expenditure requirements of company towards purchase of new machinery & installation cost thereon, funding working capital requirements of company and for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Admach Systems Polymers on 22 December 2025, raised Rs 5.03 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 2.10 lakh shares at Rs 239 per share to 4 anchor investors. Admach Systems designs, manufactures, and supplies customized special-purpose machines and automation systems for the steel, automobile, food, tooling, and engineering industries. With a production capacity of 100 units per year and 100% utilization in FY 2024–25, the company offers solutions like Black Bar handling, Bar Chamfering and Straightening, Bright Bar processing, Grinding, and Super Finishing. Headquartered in Pune, Maharashtra, Admach Systems delivers innovative, efficient, and high-quality engineering solutions to clients in India and abroad. As of 31 March 2025, the company had 58 full-time employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 23.04 crore and net profit of Rs 3.01 crore for the period ended 30 June 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdmachSystemsLtd_98065190_95795.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Bai-Kakaji Polymers struggles to hold ground after modest listing]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-bai-kakaji-polymers-struggles-to-hold-ground-after-modest-listing/1662621</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662621</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 190, a premium of 2.15% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 190, a premium of 2.15% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently down 4.97% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 192 and a low of Rs 180.50. About 27.56 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Bai-Kakaji Polymers' IPO was subscribed 5.38 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 December 2025 and it closed on 26 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 177 to Rs 186 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 56,54,400 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 73.55% from 100% Pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for repayment & pre-payment, in full or part, of borrowing availed by company, funding capital expenditure for the installation of additional plant & machinery, funding capital expenditure for setting up a solar power project and for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Bai-Kakaji Polymers on 22 December 2025, raised Rs 29.90 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 16.08 lakh shares at Rs 186 per share to 14 anchor investor. Bai-Kakaji Polymers is an Indian manufacturer and trader of plastic and polymer products, producing plastic granules, PET preforms, caps, and closures mainly used in packaged water, beverages, juices, and dairy. It operates four manufacturing units in Latur, Maharashtra, spread over 33,000 square metres, and uses advanced molding and quality-testing machinery to ensure consistent, high-quality output. As of 30 September 2025, the company had 359 full-time employees across various levels of the organization. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 162.11 crore and a net profit of Rs 12.81 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Bai-KakajiPolymersLtd_95669652_95606.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade in positive terrain; PSU bank shares climb ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-in-positive-terrain-psu-bank-shares-climb/1662622</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662622</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade.

The key equity barometers traded with modest gains in mid-morning trade. Trading sentiment stayed positive amid thin year-end volumes and absence of strong domestic triggers. The Nifty scaled above the 26,050 mark. PSU Bank shares rallied in the three consecutive trading sessions. At 11:26 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 274.61 points or 0.32% to 84,946.70. The Nifty 50 index jumped 116.20 points or 0.45% to 26,055.05. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.75%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.82%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,634 shares rose and 1,200 shares fell. A total of 219 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU bank index rallied 1.57% to 8,563.65. The index jumped 3.33% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Punjab & Sind Bank (up 3.37%), Indian Bank (up 2.67%), Bank of Maharashtra (up 2.63%), Canara Bank (up 2.09%), UCO Bank (up 1.94%), Union Bank of India (up 1.94%), Punjab National Bank (up 1.93%), Bank of India (up 1.53%), Bank of Baroda (up 1.28%) and Indian Overseas Bank (up 1.17%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: ZF Steering Gear India surged 5.34% after the company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Drivesys Systems, has secured a significant order worth Rs 151 crore for its renewable energy business. Power Grid Corporation of India rose 1.54% after the company said that it has declared a successful bidder for the 2,000 MWh battery energy storage project. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on the holiday-shortened and final trading day of the year. Markets in Hong Kong and Australia will close early for the holidays, while Japan and South Korea are shut for the day. China’s economy ended the year on a slightly less gloomy note, as factory activity expanded in December for the first time since March, beating expectations, according to official data released Wednesday. The official manufacturing purchasing managers index rose to 50.1 in December, higher than 49.2 reading that was recorded in November. A reading above 50 indicates expansion. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 fell modestly, notching a third consecutive losing session. The broad market index lost 0.14% and closed at 6,896.24, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.24% and settled at 23,419.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.20% and ended at 48,367.06. The three major averages have slumped to start the week, dragged down by losses in tech. Nvidia posted back-to-back losing sessions, as did another AI stock Palantir Technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TRAI releases framework for the sale of foreign service providers’ SIM and eSIM cards]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/trai-releases-framework-for-the-sale-of-foreign-service-providers-sim-and-esim-cards/1662620</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662620</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) has released recommendations on establishing a regulatory framework for the sale of foreign telecom service providers’ SIM and eSIM cards used in machine-to-machine (M2M) and Internet of Things (IoT) devices meant exclusively for export.

Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) has released recommendations on establishing a regulatory framework for the sale of foreign telecom service providers’ SIM and eSIM cards used in machine-to-machine (M2M) and Internet of Things (IoT) devices meant exclusively for export. This is primarily aimed at unlocking India’s export potential in connected devices while ensuring regulatory clarity, national security, and ease of doing business. The proposed framework introduces a dedicated category called the International M2M SIM Service Authorisation, designed specifically to regulate the sale of foreign telecom service providers’ SIM and eSIM cards for export-oriented M2M and IoT devices. TRAI has recommended that this authorisation be included under auxiliary service authorisations in its earlier framework dated September 18, 2024, and under miscellaneous service authorisations in the Department of Telecommunications’ draft rules under Section 3(1)(a) of the Act.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/mobile-phone-android-apps-phone-163065_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Samco Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/samco-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1662619</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662619</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Samco Mutual Fund has that Mr.

Samco Mutual Fund has that Mr. Sachin Shetty, Head – Operations, has been redesignated as Chief Operating Officer (COO) and Key Personnel of Samco Asset Management Private Limited with effect from December 23, 2025. Details of Mr. Sachin Shetty Age: 41 years Designation: Chief Operating Officer (COO) Qualification: MBA & B.COM

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Royal Orchid Hotels launches Regenta Z Vadodara in Gujarat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/royal-orchid-hotels-launches-regenta-z-vadodara-in-gujarat/1662618</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662618</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The property marks the group’s fourth hotel in the city, following Royal Orchid Central, Regenta Inn, and Regenta Fairlark, underscoring its strategy to expand in high-growth urban markets through specialized brand architecture.

The property marks the group’s fourth hotel in the city, following Royal Orchid Central, Regenta Inn, and Regenta Fairlark, underscoring its strategy to expand in high-growth urban markets through specialized brand architecture. Regenta Z is a newly introduced brand aimed at Gen Z and millennial travelers, offering a digital-first, modern hospitality experience at an affordable price point. Strategically located in Alkapuri, one of Vadodara’s upscale residential and commercial neighbourhoods, the hotel offers easy access to key locations — just 1 km from Vadodara Railway Station and central bus stand, and 7 km from Vadodara International Airport. It also serves as a convenient transit point for tourists visiting the Statue of Unity, 86 km away. The property features 36 rooms, including two studio suites, blending modern design with functional comfort. Amenities include Burgundy Cafe, an in-house dining option serving global cuisines, and the 900 sq. ft. Orchid Meeting Room, ideal for corporate and social events. Commenting on the launch, Arjun Baljee, President, Royal Orchid Hotels, said, “The launch of Regenta Z Vadodara is a significant step in our '2030 expansion roadmap' as we introduce our first Gen Z-focused brand in Gujarat. Vadodara is a city of rich cultural heritage and rapid industrial growth. By adding a fourth property here, we are ensuring that we cater to every segment of traveller—from luxury seekers to the value-conscious modern explorer. We are committed to providing the same warmth and genuine hospitality that the Royal Orchid brand is known for, now in a more youthful and energetic format.” Representing the ownership, the Suryavanshi family stated, “We are thrilled to collaborate with Royal Orchid Hotels to introduce a high-quality hospitality experience in Vadodara. This property has been crafted to offer a blend of modern elegance and comfort that aligns perfectly with the upscale character of Alkapuri. We look forward to welcoming travellers, families, and business professionals to a stay that is both enriching and memorable, serving as a gateway to the city's landmarks and the Statue of Unity.” Royal Orchid Hotels operates and manages hotels/resorts and provides related services through its portfolio of hotel properties. The company’s consolidated net profit dropped 42.9% to Rs 4.28 crore on a 12.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 79.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Royal Orchid Hotels fell 0.25% to currently trade at Rs 417.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RoyalOrchHotel_11218221105_22048.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WhiteOak Capital Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/whiteoak-capital-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1662617</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662617</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WhiteOak Capital Mutual Fund has that Mr.

WhiteOak Capital Mutual Fund has that Mr. Avinash Sonker has been appointed as Head – Information Technology (IT) of WhiteOak Capital Asset Management Limited effective January 01, 2026. Details of Mr. Avinash Sonker Age: 47 years Designation: Associate Director & Head IT Qualification: Computer Science Engineering

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India slaps three-year import duty on some steel products from China]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-slaps-three-year-import-duty-on-some-steel-products-from-china/1662611</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662611</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India has slapped a three-year import duty of 11-12% on some steel products, as per an order issued by the finance ministry to curb the inflow of low-priced steel from China.

India has slapped a three-year import duty of 11-12% on some steel products, as per an order issued by the finance ministry to curb the inflow of low-priced steel from China. As per the order published in the official government gazette, the tariff will be set at 12% in the first year and then reduced to 11.5% in the second year and further cut to 11% in the third year. The “recent, sudden, sharp, and significant increase in imports of subject goods into India has caused and threatens to cause serious injury to the domestic industry/producers of subject goods”, the order noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/colorful-infographic-chart-of-businessrelated-elements-pict_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Zydus Wellness Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-zydus-wellness-ltd-counter/1662608</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662608</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Swan Corp Ltd, Blue Star Ltd, Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd, JSW Steel Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 31 December 2025.

Swan Corp Ltd, Blue Star Ltd, Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd, JSW Steel Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 31 December 2025. Zydus Wellness Ltd clocked volume of 1.42 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 23.71 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5997 shares. The stock gained 6.92% to Rs.453.20. Volumes stood at 9454 shares in the last session. Swan Corp Ltd registered volume of 15.06 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 20 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 75337 shares. The stock rose 0.35% to Rs.472.55. Volumes stood at 37452 shares in the last session. Blue Star Ltd saw volume of 1.45 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.79 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 16554 shares. The stock increased 0.74% to Rs.1,720.40. Volumes stood at 51332 shares in the last session. Deepak Fertilisers & Petrochemicals Corp Ltd registered volume of 71875 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.57 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 15740 shares. The stock rose 5.97% to Rs.1,278.65. Volumes stood at 13153 shares in the last session. JSW Steel Ltd registered volume of 2.21 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.04 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 54656 shares. The stock rose 4.94% to Rs.1,166.55. Volumes stood at 79882 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZydusWellness_96134066137_6367.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s Industrial Output Rebounds 6.7% in November 2025, Driven by Manufacturing and Energy Growth]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-industrial-output-rebounds-67-in-november-2025-driven-by-manufacturing-and-energy-growth/1662605</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662605</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's industrial production rose 6.7% in November 2025 after achieving two consecutive yearly declines.

India's industrial production rose 6.7% in November 2025 after achieving two consecutive yearly declines. The strength of growth came from greater investment in manufactured goods, increasing use of energy generation capacity, the continuing ability of major industrialised sectors There's an increase for each key sub-sector, including automotive manufacturing, electrical equipment production and textile production. In addition, manufacturing output increased at an accelerated pace due to improved production of both consumer and capital goods. Mining and electricity producing facilities Continued to increase their output, contributing positively to the overall Industrial Production Index (IIP). Thus, the reversals of the declines in production numbers show the extent to which we can expect that there will be an overall increase in economic activity across most of the economy. There was an increase in production numbers for both the consumer and investment related sectors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/world-economy-3513561__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mach Conferences jumps on securing Rs 92-crore Punjab pilgrimage order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mach-conferences-jumps-on-securing-rs-92-crore-punjab-pilgrimage-order/1662603</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662603</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the end-to-end execution of a 2-night, 3-day pilgrimage program for approximately 185,000 Yatris, which is expected to be completed within the next six months.

The order involves the end-to-end execution of a 2-night, 3-day pilgrimage program for approximately 185,000 Yatris, which is expected to be completed within the next six months. Mach Conferences and Events offers solutions for organizing corporate conferences, training programs, and incentive events. On a full-year basis, the company's net profit declined 45.9% to Rs 14.17 crore on a 0.6% drop in revenue to Rs 235.75 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MachConferencesEventsLtd_59976383_93342.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Apollo Techno Industries drills into Dalal Street with a steady debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-apollo-techno-industries-drills-into-dalal-street-with-a-steady-debut/1662612</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662612</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 145, a premium of 11.54% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 145, a premium of 11.54% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently down 2.07% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 149 and a low of Rs 140. About 18.06 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Apollo Techno Industries' IPO was subscribed 47.15 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 December 2025 and it closed on 26 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 123 to Rs 130 per share. The IPO comprised a fresh issue of 36,89,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds to meet working capital requirements for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Apollo Techno Industries on 22 December 2025, raised Rs 13.65 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 10.50 lakh shares at Rs 130 per share to 11 anchor investors. Apollo Techno Industries is a construction technology manufacturer focused on trenchless and foundation equipment, offering drilling rigs and spare parts backed by an in-house design team. It serves domestic and international markets with refurbishment and sustainable solutions, emphasising customer relationships and growth in key Indian regions while delivering efficient, environmentally friendly drilling technologies for infrastructure and deep excavation projects. As of 30 June 2025, the company had 154 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 24.54 crore and a net profit of Rs 1.08 crore for the period ended 30 June 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/APOLLOTECHNOINDUSTRIESLIMITED_63872010_82923.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR slips as recent slide in local equities weighs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-slips-as-recent-slide-in-local-equities-weighs/1662598</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662598</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee slipped today, giving up steady gains seen in last session.

Indian rupee slipped today, giving up steady gains seen in last session. Local equities have been falling recently and the benchmark NIFTY50 index tested around one and half week low in last session. INR has moved mostly lower and is on track to decline around 6% this year and is not far from record lows against the US dollar. Overall mood is cautious trades in global fx markets around year-end though there is a modest uptick in the US dollar index. INR slipped amid these cues and also eyed the Indian government monthly finances data. INR currently trades down 15 paise at 89.90 per US dollar. On NSE, USD/INR futures edged up 0.06% to 90.32.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ZF Steering Gear India jumps after bagging Rs 151-cr order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zf-steering-gear-india-jumps-after-bagging-rs-151-cr-order/1662590</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662590</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order was received from a leading Indian business conglomerate.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order was received from a leading Indian business conglomerate. However, the name of the customer has not been disclosed to protect commercial confidentiality and avoid any potential impact on future business opportunities. ZF Steering Gear India confirmed that the counterparty is a credible and well-established entity. The order involves the manufacturing and supply of machined aluminium parts. Pricing for the order is on a CIF basis and is linked to base metal prices declared by NALCO. The company stated that the order will be executed over a period of 15 months. It also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity, and the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions under applicable regulatory norms. ZF Steering Gear (India) is engaged in the business of production & assembling of steering systems for vehicles, buses and tractors. On the financial front, the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 0.39 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 1.72 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 8.4% year-on-year to Rs 120.56 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZFSteering_63694674382_619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hsbc-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1662596</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662596</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026.

HSBC Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 01 January 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) Revised Fund Manager(s) HSBC Overnight Fund • Mr. Abhishek Iyer and • Mr. Mahesh Chhabria • Mr. Abhishek Iyer and • Mr. Rahul Totla HSBC Liquid Fund • Mr. Abhishek Iyer and • Mr. Mahesh Chhabria • Mr. Abhishek Iyer and • Mr. Rahul Totla HSBC Ultra Short Duration Fund • Mr. Mahesh Chhabria and • Mr. Abhishek Iyer • Mr. Mahesh Chhabria and • Mr. Rahul Totla

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prime Minister calls for mission-mode reforms across diverse sector to sustain long-term growth]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prime-minister-calls-for-mission-mode-reforms-across-diverse-sector-to-sustain-long-term-growth/1662578</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662578</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi interacted with a group of eminent economists and experts at NITI Aayog, yesterday.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi interacted with a group of eminent economists and experts at NITI Aayog, yesterday. The Theme of the interaction was ‘Aatmanirbharta and Structural Transformation: Agenda for Viksit Bharat’. Addressing the gathering, Prime Minister highlighted the core pillars for India’s journey toward 2047. The Prime Minister noted that the vision of a developed India by 2047 has transcended government policy to become a genuine mass aspiration. This shift is evident in the evolving patterns of education, consumption, and global mobility, necessitating enhanced institutional capacity and proactive infrastructure planning to meet the needs of an increasingly aspirational society. Prime Minister further stressed the need for mission-mode reforms to build global capability and attain global integration. To sustain long-term growth, Prime Minister called for mission-mode reforms across diverse sectors. He stressed that India’s policymaking and budgeting must remain anchored with vision for 2047. He also spoke about the need for ensuring that the nation remains a vital hub for the global workforce and international markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 26,000 level; metal shares shine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-26000-level-metal-shares-shine/1662569</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662569</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices continued to trade in positive territory with moderate gains in morning trade.

The key equity indices continued to trade in positive territory with moderate gains in morning trade. Trading sentiment stayed positive amid thin year-end volumes and absence of strong domestic triggers. The Nifty traded above the 26,000 level. Metal shares extended their rally into a third straight session. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 166.92 points or 0.20% to 84,842.00. The Nifty 50 index rose 66.15 points or 0.26% to 26,007.00. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.55% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 0.71%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,552 shares rose and 1,081 shares fell. A total of 219 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index jumped 1.46% to 11,168.60. The index jumped 3.52% for third consecutive trading session. JSW Steel (up 4.77%), Jindal Steel (up 3.23%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (up 2.44%), Steel Authority of India (up 2.33%), Tata Steel (up 1.64%), Welspun Corp (up 1.05%), Jindal Stainless (up 1.04%), APL Apollo Tubes (up 0.89%), Adani Enterprises (up 0.31%) and National Aluminium Company (up 0.13%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Premier Energies added 0.45% after it has secured new orders worth Rs 2,307.30 crore during the third quarter of FY26, with execution scheduled across FY27 and FY28. Ahasolar Technologies spurted 7.48% after the company has received a contract from CIL Rajasthan Akshay Urja for providing owner’s engineering and project management consultancy (OEPMC) services for an 875 MW solar photovoltaic power project. Apollo Micro Systems jumped 4.20% after the company’s step- down subsidiary IDL Explosives bagged supply contracts worth approximately Rs 421 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Dhara Rail Projects steams out of the station with a strong debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-dhara-rail-projects-steams-out-of-the-station-with-a-strong-debut/1662572</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662572</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock listed at Rs 150, a 19.05% premium to the IPO price, and is currently up 0.53% over the listing price.

The stock listed at Rs 150, a 19.05% premium to the IPO price, and is currently up 0.53% over the listing price. It touched a high of Rs 155 and a low of Rs 142.60, with 20.95 lakh shares traded on the exchange. Dhara Rail Projects' IPO was subscribed 103.99 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 December 2025 and it closed on 26 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 120 to Rs 126 per share. The IPO comprised a fresh issue of 39,84,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter group shareholding diluted to 72.36% from 98.33% pre-issue. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for repayment or pre-payment, in full or part, of borrowing availed by the company, to meet working capital requirements of the company and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Dhara Rail Projects on 22 December 2025, raised Rs 14.27 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 11.33 lakh shares at Rs 126 per share to 8 anchor investors. Dhara Rail Projects undertakes contractual railway projects focused on maintenance, repair, and electrical services for railway rolling stock. Its activities include annual maintenance and repair of train lighting systems, including those on Vande Bharat trains, maintenance of OHE vehicles, power car equipment and HVAC systems, as well as supply, installation, testing and commissioning of electrical equipment. The company executes work for the Ministry of Railways through competitive tenders and arrangements with original equipment manufacturers. As of 31 October 2025, the company employed 1,019 full-time employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 28.37 crore and net profit of Rs 7.06 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DharaRailProjectsLtd_94401522_95939.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Grid rises after emerging as successful bidder for 2,000 MWh battery storage]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-grid-rises-after-emerging-as-successful-bidder-for-2000-mwh-battery-storage/1662551</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662551</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project entails the selection of battery energy storage developers for setting up a cumulative capacity of 2,000 MWh, structured as 1,000 MW with a two-hour storage duration, for on-demand usage.

The project entails the selection of battery energy storage developers for setting up a cumulative capacity of 2,000 MWh, structured as 1,000 MW with a two-hour storage duration, for on-demand usage. The project will be implemented under the build-own-operate (BOO) model and is supported by Viability Gap Funding through the Power System Development Fund. As part of the mandate, PowerGrid will set up a 150 MW/300 MWh standalone battery energy storage system at the 400/220 kV substation at Kalikiri in Chittoor district, Andhra Pradesh. The facility will be located at a selected APTRANSCO substation and is aimed at enhancing grid flexibility and reliability. The letter of award was received by PowerGrid on 29 December 2025. The battery energy storage system is expected to support on-demand power requirements and improve the integration of renewable energy into the grid, while also strengthening the overall transmission infrastructure in Andhra Pradesh. The Power Grid Corporation of India was established by the Government of India (GoI) as the central transmission utility of India. The company is a 'Maharatna' firm under the Ministry of Power, GoI. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 5.98% to Rs 3,566.08 crore despite a 1.76% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,147.59 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerGridCorpn_89479008350_5455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>