<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Embassy Developments Ltd Spikes 4.7%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/embassy-developments-ltd-spikes-47/1663711</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663711</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Embassy Developments Ltd rose 4.7% today to trade at Rs 68.8.

Embassy Developments Ltd rose 4.7% today to trade at Rs 68.8. The BSE Realty index is up 0.13% to quote at 7075.76. The index is up 4.73 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Anant Raj Ltd increased 0.26% and Oberoi Realty Ltd added 0.21% on the day. The BSE Realty index went down 11.86 % over last one year compared to the 8.48% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Embassy Developments Ltd has lost 2.04% over last one month compared to 4.73% gain in BSE Realty index and 0.13% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1.01 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 4.07 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 163.7 on 21 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 55.8 on 05 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndbullRealEst_49523889882_27800.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Balkrishna Industries Ltd Slips 0.81%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/balkrishna-industries-ltd-slips-081/1663712</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663712</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Balkrishna Industries Ltd fell 0.81% today to trade at Rs 2382.95.

Balkrishna Industries Ltd fell 0.81% today to trade at Rs 2382.95. The BSE Auto index is down 0.32% to quote at 63447.64. The index is up 4.06 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Maruti Suzuki India Ltd decreased 0.62% and Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd lost 0.62% on the day. The BSE Auto index went up 20.24 % over last one year compared to the 8.48% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Balkrishna Industries Ltd has added 2.54% over last one month compared to 4.06% gain in BSE Auto index and 0.13% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 17 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 4249 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2915.75 on 01 Feb 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 2157.2 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BalkrishnaInds_9898029362_55.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR slips from one-week high but stays afloat Rs 90 per dollar mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-slips-from-one-week-high-but-stays-afloat-rs-90-per-dollar-mark/1663708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663708</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee edged lower from a one-week high in opening trades on Thursday but manages to stay afloat Rs 90 per dollar mark.

The Indian rupee edged lower from a one-week high in opening trades on Thursday but manages to stay afloat Rs 90 per dollar mark. INR opened at Rs 89.96 per dollar and fell to a low of 89.97 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee rose 31 paise to close at 89.87 against the US dollar, on falling international global crude oil prices. Besides, possible intervention by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) may also have supported the counter, although muted local equities capped upside. Indian shares ended slightly lower on Wednesday to extend losses for a third day running as rising geopolitical tensions and tariff-related concerns overshadowed investor optimism around the earnings outlook. The benchmark S&P/BSE Sensex dropped 102.20 points, or 0.12 percent, to 84,961.14, while the broader NSE Nifty index ended down 37.95 points, or 0.14 percent, at 26,140.75.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IRB Infra gains as toll collections climb 12% YoY to Rs 754 cr in Dec’25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/irb-infra-gains-as-toll-collections-climb-12-yoy-to-rs-754-cr-in-dec25/1663707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663707</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Amitabh Murarka, Dy.

Amitabh Murarka, Dy. CEO of the IRB Infra, said, “IRB Group continues to see strong and consistent traffic growth, driving robust toll revenue growth for the month of December 2025, supported by healthy GDP expansion.” He further said. “The consistently strong growth trend reflects underlying buoyancy that is here to stay, and with nationwide economic activity picking up along with revenue from new TOTs and completed BOT assets coming on stream in the coming months, we expect toll revenue momentum to accelerate even further.” IRB is India's first integrated multinational transport infrastructure developer in the roads & highways segment. The company has a strong track record of constructing, tolling, operating, and maintaining around 19,000 lane kms pan-India in its existence of more than 25 years in India. The company reported a 41% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.82 crore on a 10.42% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 1,751.02 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IRBInfraDevl_42061995161_28365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty indicates negative opening for key benchmarks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-indicates-negative-opening-for-key-benchmarks/1663696</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663696</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 48.50 points, indicating a negative opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were down 48.50 points, indicating a negative opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,527.71 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,889.32 crore in the Indian equity market on 07 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 4,650.39 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia-Pacific markets traded mixed Thursday after Wall Street closed lower amid rising geopolitical tensions and comments from U.S. President Donald Trump. U.S. defense stocks fell after Trump said he “will not permit” defense companies to issue dividends or stock buybacks until they address his complaints about the industry, including executive pay packages and production issues. In U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day winning streak, falling 466 points, or 0.94%, to close at 48,996.08. The S&P 500 declined 23.89 points or 0.34% to end at 6,920.93, while the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite edged up 37.10 points or 0.16% to close at 23,584.28. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks ended lower on Wednesday, extending losses for a third consecutive session, as persistent selling pressure in heavyweight stocks weighed on sentiment. The Nifty ended below the 26,150 level amid mixed global cues, following geopolitical concerns linked to developments in Venezuela. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 120.20 points or 0.12% to 84,961.14. The Nifty 50 index dropped 37.95 points or 0.14% to 26,140.75. In three consecutive sessions, the Sensex declined 0.93% while the Nifty fell 0.71%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Gland Pharma, Angel One, Tata Steel, Meesho, Swaraj Engines]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-gland-pharma-angel-one-tata-steel-meesho-swaraj-engines/1663693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663693</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India(SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 8 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India(SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&O trading on 8 January 2026. Stocks to Watch: Gland Pharma has received an approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) filed for Olopatadine Hydrochloride Ophthalmic Solution. The said drug is indicated for the treatment of ocular itching associated with allergic conjunctivitis. Angel One is scheduled to meet on Thursday, 15 January, 2026 to consider sub-division/split of existing equity shares having face value of Rs 10 each, fully paid up. Tata Steel’s India crude steel production stood at 6.34 million tons in Q3 FY26, up 12% QoQ and YoY, primarily aided by higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities. Meesho’s general manager- business, Megha Agarwal has tendered her resignation with effect from 7 January 2026. Following her exit, Milan Partani, General Manager - User Growth and Content Commerce will now assume the role of General Manager – Commerce Platform. Swaraj Engines received a warning letter from BSE and National Stock Exchange of India (NSE) for non-compliance with Regulation 21 (3A) of SEBI Listing Regulations, wherein only one meeting of the Risk Management Committee was held during the financial year 2024-25. Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) has signed a non-binding MoU with the Chhattisgarh government to provide financial assistance of up to Rs 1 lakh crore over five years for housing and infrastructure projects.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zaggle Prepaid inks pact with Cubastion Consulting]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zaggle-prepaid-inks-pact-with-cubastion-consulting/1663692</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663692</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As part of the agreement, Zaggle will provide a facility for the procurement and leasing of mobile phones to employees of Cubastion Consulting through its Employee Purchase Programme.

As part of the agreement, Zaggle will provide a facility for the procurement and leasing of mobile phones to employees of Cubastion Consulting through its Employee Purchase Programme. The agreement will remain effective until terminated in accordance with the terms specified therein. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entities, and both contracts do not qualify as related-party transactions under applicable regulatory norms. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services (Zaggle) is a leading player in spend management, with a differentiated value proposition and diversified user base. The company operates in the business-to-business-to-customer segment. It is one of the largest numbers of issued prepaid cards in India in partnership with its banking partners. Additionally, the company has a diversified portfolio of software as a service (SaaS) products, including tax and payroll software, and a wide touchpoint reach. The company’s standalone net profit surged 79.1% to Rs 33.24 crore on a 42.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 430.98 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter shed 0.36% to Rs 336.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZagglePrepaidOceanServicesLtd_95613182_78337.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>