<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1679274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679274</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Axis Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The quantum of dividend (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Axis Arbitrage Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.05 Axis Arbitrage Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.05 AXIS Equity Savings Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.09 AXIS Equity Savings Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.09 AXIS Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – & Regular Plan Monthly IDCW Option: 0.10 AXIS Multi Asset Allocation Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.15 AXIS Multi Asset Allocation Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.15

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/citurgia-biochemicals-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1679272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679272</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Krishival Foods Ltd Partly Paidup, Regaal Resources Ltd, Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Ltd and Filatex Fashions Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 February 2026.

Krishival Foods Ltd Partly Paidup, Regaal Resources Ltd, Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Ltd and Filatex Fashions Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 February 2026. Citurgia Biochemicals Ltd soared 20.00% to Rs 88.2 at 24-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 219 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 912 shares in the past one month. Krishival Foods Ltd Partly Paidup spiked 15.25% to Rs 130. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 602 shares in the past one month. Regaal Resources Ltd surged 13.09% to Rs 70. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 16.14 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 29109 shares in the past one month. Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Ltd spurt 10.24% to Rs 453.35. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 4048 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3916 shares in the past one month. Filatex Fashions Ltd added 9.09% to Rs 0.24. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 315.62 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 130.67 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CiturgiaBiochem_55686104813_115.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Fractal Industries lists at 6% premium on BSE; hits lower circuit]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fractal-industries-lists-at-6-premium-on-bse-hits-lower-circuit/1679271</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679271</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 229, a 6.01% premium to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 229, a 6.01% premium to the issue price. The stock was locked in a 5% lower circuit from the listing price. It touched a high of Rs 229 and a low of Rs 217.55, with around 9.99 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Fractal Industries’ IPO was subscribed 5.13 times. The issue opened for bidding on 16 February 2026 and it closed on 18 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 205 to Rs 216 per share. The IPO comprised a fresh issue of 22,68,600 equity shares. The promoter and promoter group shareholding diluted to 69.07% from 97.15% pre-issue. The company intends to utilise the net proceeds for funding working capital requirements and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Fractal Industries on Friday, 13 February 2026, raised Rs 13.93 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 6.45 lakh shares at Rs 216 each to 6 anchor investors. Fractal Industries is engaged in the designing, sourcing and manufacturing of garments, along with providing end-to-end warehousing and supply chain solutions for e-commerce platforms such as Myntra, Ajio and similar marketplaces. With a pan-India presence, the company operates as a full-service garment manufacturer and technology-driven supply chain partner, focusing on fast-moving, high-quality apparel for online marketplaces. The company integrates agile design-to-delivery manufacturing, scalable production capabilities, stringent quality control and data-driven supply chain management to help brands and private labels accelerate speed-to-market, improve margins and enhance customer satisfaction. In addition to manufacturing, Fractal Industries offers integrated warehousing and fulfilment solutions that enable apparel brands and e-commerce partners to streamline and optimise their operations. Its manufacturing unit is located in Mumbai, while warehouses are strategically located in Gujarat, Maharashtra, Haryana, West Bengal and Karnataka. The company also provides a range of value-added services, including a product management system, data analytics, integrated logistics management, an order management system (OMS), inventory and returns management, order anomaly detection and multi-channel sales enablement. As of 30 September 2025, the company had 45 permanent employees and 38 labours on a contract basis. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 47.30 crore and net profit of Rs 6.78 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FRACTALINDUSTRIESLIMITED_79971641_96158.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/thangamayil-jewellery-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1679268</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679268</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Fine Organic Industries Ltd, Natco Pharma Ltd, Apollo Micro Systems Ltd and Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 February 2026.

Fine Organic Industries Ltd, Natco Pharma Ltd, Apollo Micro Systems Ltd and Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 February 2026. Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd spiked 4.92% to Rs 3771.5 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 12753 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9643 shares in the past one month. Fine Organic Industries Ltd soared 4.66% to Rs 4862.5. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 7484 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 941 shares in the past one month. Natco Pharma Ltd surged 4.63% to Rs 934.55. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 6.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.53 lakh shares in the past one month. Apollo Micro Systems Ltd added 4.34% to Rs 240.55. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.86 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.59 lakh shares in the past one month. Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd jumped 4.18% to Rs 110.9. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 12.05 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.05 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ThangamayilJew_68304331310_34920.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Altiva SIF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/altiva-sif-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1679270</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679270</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Altiva SIF has announced 18 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Altiva SIF has announced 18 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of distribution (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Altiva Hybrid Long-Short Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.05 Altiva Hybrid Long-Short Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.05

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LIC Mutual Fund announces change in face value under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lic-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-face-value-under-its-scheme/1679267</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679267</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[LIC Mutual Fund has announced change in Face Value under the following scheme, With effect from 06 March 2026.

LIC Mutual Fund has announced change in Face Value under the following scheme, With effect from 06 March 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Face Value Scheme Name Existing Provisions Revised Provisions LIC MF Gold Exchange Traded Fund Face Value Rs. 100/- Creation Unit size 1,000 units Face Value Rs. 1/- Creation Unit size 1,20,000 units

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Silver Touch Tech bags contract from FSSAI to upgrade portal and applications]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/silver-touch-tech-bags-contract-from-fssai-to-upgrade-portal-and-applications/1679266</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679266</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI) is the apex food regulatory authority under the Ministry of Health & Family Welfare, Government of India, responsible for protecting and promoting public health through regulation and supervision of food safety.

The Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI) is the apex food regulatory authority under the Ministry of Health & Family Welfare, Government of India, responsible for protecting and promoting public health through regulation and supervision of food safety. Under the current mandate, the company will be as Managed Service Provider (MSP) for application development, enhancement, operations & maintenance of FSSAI portals and applications. The scope of work includes development of new portals and mobile applications (Android & iOS), enhancement of existing portals and dashboards, microservices-based architecture upgrades, cloud-based deployment and management, API integrations with external ministries/departments, payment gateway integrations and the development of multilingual AI-enabled chatbot. Additionally, the engagement covers database management and architecture enhancement, implementation of document compression system capable of handling over 40 TB data and ongoing operations & maintenance with defined service-level agreements (SLAs). Minesh V. Doshi, executive director, Silver Touch Technologies, said: “The order strengthens the Company’s position in large-scale Government digital transformation programs and reinforces its capabilities in enterprise portal development, cloud-native architecture, cybersecurity compliance, and mission-critical system management. “ Silver Touch Technologies a leading provider of end-to-end IT solutions with deep expertise in e-Governance, secure digital platforms, and large-scale public sector programs. The company leverages cloud, AI, automation, analytics, and open-source technologies to support large-scale, mission-critical programs for government and enterprise customers in India and globally. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 109.3% to Rs 11.01 crore on 30.9% jump in net sales to Rs 95.73 crore in Q3 December 2025 compared with Q3 December 2024. The counter fell 2.66% to Rs 1,415.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SilverTouchTechnologiesLtd_8102135951_71656.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shilpa Medicare's biopharma subsidiary inks licensing agreement with SteinCares for Latin America]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shilpa-medicares-biopharma-subsidiary-inks-licensing-agreement-with-steincares-for-latin-america/1679273</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679273</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SteinCares is a leading specialty pharmaceutical company dedicated to expanding patient access to innovative and cost-effective treatments across Latin America.

SteinCares is a leading specialty pharmaceutical company dedicated to expanding patient access to innovative and cost-effective treatments across Latin America. Shilpa Biologicals is a fully integrated biopharmaceutical company with a therapeutic focus on immunology, oncology, and ophthalmics. As a hybrid CDMO/pharma company, Shilpa offers both development and manufacturing services alongside ready-to-license novel formulations. Under the agreement, SteinCares will hold exclusive rights to register, commercialize, and distribute the biosimilar across the region while Shilpa Biologicals will complete product development and provide long-term commercial manufacturing from its facility in Dharwad, India. The partnership brings together Shilpa Biologicals’ expertise in biologics development and high-quality commercial manufacturing with SteinCares’ integrated regional platform, combining regulatory capabilities, market access, and deep understanding of Latin American healthcare systems. Shilpa Medicare is a manufacturer of API, formulation, and development services. The company's consolidated net profit jumped 40.28% to Rs 44.58 crore on a 28.32% increase in revenue to Rs 409.73 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip fell 1.33% to currently trade at Rs 322.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShilpaMedicare_71228849681_5031.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty traded below 25,550 marks; realty shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-traded-below-25550-marks-realty-shares-decline/1679261</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679261</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The frontline equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in the mid-morning trade, dragged down by heavy selling in index heavyweight Bharti Airtel and weakness across IT stocks.

The frontline equity benchmarks traded with significant losses in the mid-morning trade, dragged down by heavy selling in index heavyweight Bharti Airtel and weakness across IT stocks. Investor sentiment remained subdued after U.S. President Donald Trump’s renewed tariff threats rattled global markets, while the expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE added to the volatility in mid-morning trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,550 mark. Realty shares extended losses for the second consecutive trading session. At 11:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 730.32 points or 0.88% to 82,564.34. The Nifty 50 index fell 196.70 points or 0.76% to 25,516.05. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.49% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.77%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,284 shares rose and 2,512 shares fell. A total of 214 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 1,91,552 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.03 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 23,79,168 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.22 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 80,99,812 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.37 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 1.10% to 810.10. The index declined 1.29% in two consecutive trading sessions. SignatureGlobal India (down 3.36%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 1.94%), Brigade Enterprises (down 1.46%), Godrej Properties (down 1.42%), DLF (down 1.28%), Anant Raj (down 1.13%), Lodha Developers (down 1.04%), Sobha (down 0.93%) and Phoenix Mills (down 0.54%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.82%. The company said its Heavy Civil Infrastructure (HCI) and Heavy Engineering (HE) verticals have jointly secured a ‘significant’ order from the Department of Atomic Energy for the LIGO India Observatory in Maharashtra. Samvardhana Motherson International slipped 0.04%. The company announced that it has launched a manufacturing facility in Sanand, Gujarat, dedicated to producing cutting-edge exterior lighting systems. Global Markets: Asian markets traded mixed on Tuesday as investors weighed renewed tariff threats from U.S. President Donald Trump and concerns that artificial intelligence could disrupt software companies. Trump posted on Truth Social Monday that any country that wants to “play games” with the Supreme Court decision “will be met with a much higher tariff.” The comments followed a Supreme Court decision Friday striking down tariffs enacted under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act. In response, Trump said he would impose a 15% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act. Investors in Asia were also assessing China’s loan prime rate (LPR) decision. China’s central bank on Tuesday kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged at 3% for the one-year LPR and 3.5% for the five-year LPR. Overnight on Wall Street, U.S. equities tumbled on Monday as investors grappled with persistent fears around artificial intelligence disruptions to various industries and President Donald Trump’s decision to raise his global tariffs. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 821.91 points, or 1.66%, to close at 48,804.06, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.13% and ended at 22,627.27. The S&P 500 shed 1.04% and closed at 6,837.75, putting it into the red once again for 2026. The 30-stock Dow was dragged down by IBM shares, which declined 13% on the heels of Anthropic outlining new programming capabilities for its Claude Code product. Software stocks such as Microsoft and CrowdStrike were under pressure yet again as AI disruption worries hovered over the market. However, software hasn’t been the only sector to be hit due to AI fears recently: Stocks linked to trucking and logistics, commercial real estate and financial services have similarly suffered losses this month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Nifty Midcap 150 Momentum 50 ETF announces Extension of NFO period]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-nifty-midcap-150-momentum-50-etf-announces-extension-of-nfo-period/1679259</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679259</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBI Mutual Fund has announced that New Fund Offer (NFO) Period of the Scheme has been modified as follows: Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Name of the Scheme Existing closing date of NFO Revised closing date of NFO SBI Nifty Midcap 150 Momentum 50 ETF February 24, 2026 February 27, 2026

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CARE Ratings upgrades ratings of KSH International to 'A/A1']]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/care-ratings-upgrades-ratings-of-ksh-international-to-aa1/1679257</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679257</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has also upgraded the company’s short term rating to ‘CARE A1’ from ‘CARE A2’.

The agency has also upgraded the company’s short term rating to ‘CARE A1’ from ‘CARE A2’. CARE Ratings stated that upgrade in ratings assigned to bank facilities of KSH International factors in substantial improvement in the scale of operations and profitability in FY25 and 9M FY26 and strengthening of capital structure post the fund raising by way of initial public offer (IPO). Growth was supported by sustained demand from key end-user industries and higher realisation. Ratings upgrade also considers successful commissioning of the greenfield project without cost overrun. CARE Ratings expects KSH to sustain revenue growth while maintaining profitability levels supported by capacity enhancement. The ratings continue to derive strength from long-track record of operations, experienced promoter group, established and diversified customer base and KSH’s healthy market position in the copper windings wire industry. These strengths are partially offset by modest profitability, exposure to raw material price volatility, working capital intensive operations and end-user concentration in revenue. KSH International manufactures insulated copper conductors, which include CTC, paper insulated copper conductors (PICC), wrapped and enamelled rectangular copper/aluminium magnet winding wires and other specialty conductors. As on 31 December 2025, KSH had manufacturing capacity of 43,445 MTPA. The scrip fell 1.34% to currently trade at Rs 367.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KSHInternationalLtd_52946873_39206.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Brahmaputra Infrastructure hits the roof after emerging L-1 for Rs 397-Cr NH-458 project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/brahmaputra-infrastructure-hits-the-roof-after-emerging-l-1-for-rs-397-cr-nh-458-project/1679256</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679256</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project entails widening the Raipur–Jassakhera stretch (Km 0.000 to Km 29.770) of NH-458 in Rajasthan under the EPC (engineering, procurement, and construction) model.

The project entails widening the Raipur–Jassakhera stretch (Km 0.000 to Km 29.770) of NH-458 in Rajasthan under the EPC (engineering, procurement, and construction) model. The total contract value is Rs 397 crore, with a scheduled execution period of 30 months. The scope of work includes converting the highway to a two-lane configuration, constructing paved shoulders, multiple bridges, and ancillary road works such as drains and culverts. The project aligns with Brahmaputra Infrastructure’s core EPC operations, particularly in road and transportation infrastructure. With this award, Brahmaputra Infrastructure’s total order book, including joint operations, now stands at approximately Rs 1,500 crore. The current order book provides multi-year revenue visibility, underpinned by the Company’s historical execution cycle. Most of its projects are government infrastructure contracts, which typically feature structured milestone-based payments. On its outlook, the company continues to actively participate in government infrastructure tenders and expects transportation and public works spending to remain a key driver of future opportunities. With a strong order book and ongoing project execution, Brahmaputra Infrastructure remains focused on timely delivery, cost control, and project completion. Brahmaputra Infrastructure is a versatile construction company with a significant presence in sectors like highways & roads, buildings, bridges/flyovers, airports, tunnels, and other civil construction works. On a consolidated basis, Brahmaputra Infrastructure reported a net profit of Rs 15.12 crore in Q3 December 2025, a surge of 4,625% from Rs 0.32 crore in Q3 December 2024. Net sales rose 212% year-on-year to Rs 91.98 crore during the same period.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BrahmaputraInf_89782917235_28067.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T bags ‘significant’ order for LIGO India Observatory in Maharashtra]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-bags-significant-order-for-ligo-india-observatory-in-maharashtra/1679251</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679251</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order has been classified as 'significant,' indicating a value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore.

The order has been classified as 'significant,' indicating a value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore. The project involves engineering, procurement, and construction of vibration-sensitive, high-precision civil infrastructure, along with manufacturing and installation of an ultra-high vacuum-compatible 8-km beam tube and critical vacuum equipment. The scope also includes integration of mechanical, electrical, HVAC, fire protection, vacuum control, and monitoring systems, along with support utilities. The LIGO (Laser Interferometer Gravitational Wave Observatory) facility will be developed at Aundha in Hingoli district, Maharashtra, with a completion timeline of 48 months. L&T is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services, operating across multiple geographies. On a consolidated basis, L&T's net profit declined 4.27% year-on-year to Rs 3,215.11 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 10.48% to Rs 71,449.70 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Aegis Logistics Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-aegis-logistics-ltd-counter/1679249</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679249</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GE Vernova T&D India Ltd, Fine Organic Industries Ltd, Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd, LIC Housing Finance Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 24 February 2026.

GE Vernova T&D India Ltd, Fine Organic Industries Ltd, Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd, LIC Housing Finance Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 24 February 2026. Aegis Logistics Ltd saw volume of 8.44 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 90.11 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 9363 shares. The stock increased 1.68% to Rs.715.00. Volumes stood at 8641 shares in the last session. GE Vernova T&D India Ltd saw volume of 2.03 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 11.18 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 18186 shares. The stock increased 0.15% to Rs.3,716.45. Volumes stood at 18237 shares in the last session. Fine Organic Industries Ltd recorded volume of 6765 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.57 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 789 shares. The stock gained 4.87% to Rs.4,872.05. Volumes stood at 923 shares in the last session. Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd witnessed volume of 9.74 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.9 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.65 lakh shares. The stock increased 4.70% to Rs.111.45. Volumes stood at 4.98 lakh shares in the last session. LIC Housing Finance Ltd notched up volume of 3.6 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 5.11 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 70353 shares. The stock rose 0.67% to Rs.528.00. Volumes stood at 40834 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisLogistics_61348536029_9.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India remains among the fastest -growing major economies, says SEBI Chair]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-remains-among-the-fastest--growing-major-economies-says-sebi-chair/1679246</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679246</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India remains among the fastest -growing major economies and is on a trajectory to becoming the world's third-largest economy.

India remains among the fastest -growing major economies and is on a trajectory to becoming the world's third-largest economy. This growth will also power a rise in the number of affluent investors- investors who seek professionally managed investment solutions beyond standardised products, stated Tuhin Kanta Pandey, Chairman, SEBI in a speech made at PMS Conclave. The Portfolio Management Services or PMS industry has seen strong growth. Non -EPFO/PF AUM has risen from about Rs 5 trillion in FY 2020 - 21 to about Rs 10.5 trillion, as on January 31, 2026, implying a CAGR of 17%. Total clients, as on January 31, 2026, are about 2 .15 lakh, an almost 50% increase from 2022. The number of registered portfolio managers has also increased from 361 to 501 over the same broad period.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1679247</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679247</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of distribution (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: HDFC Dividend Yield Fund – Regular Plan - IDCW Option & Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 1.50 each. HDFC ELSS Tax Saver – Regular Plan - IDCW Option & Direct Plan - IDCW Option: 7.00 each.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sigma Advanced Systems hits the roof on bagging Rs 100-cr order from Ministry of Defence]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sigma-advanced-systems-hits-the-roof-on-bagging-rs-100-cr-order-from-ministry-of-defence/1679245</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679245</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contracts are linked to ongoing strategic programmes spanning missile systems, naval platforms and airborne applications.

The contracts are linked to ongoing strategic programmes spanning missile systems, naval platforms and airborne applications. The company will supply built-to-spec systems, control electronics and actuation solutions under these orders. The scope includes work on Surface-to-Air Missile (SAM) programmes supporting next-generation air defence platforms, as well as anti-tank missile programmes involving critical electronics and flight control systems. Sigma will also contribute to new-generation anti-radiation missile programmes through precision guidance systems and provide advanced actuation solutions for underwater naval weapon platforms. In addition, the company will support rotary-wing avionics programmes with onboard flight data acquisition systems. The orders will be executed for leading defence PSUs and research laboratories, including Bharat Dynamics, Hindustan Aeronautics, and establishments under the Defence Research and Development Organisation. The company said the order wins reflect sustained customer confidence amid long qualification cycles and stringent reliability standards in the defence sector. Commenting on the development, Sunil Kalidindi, chief executive officer (CEO) of Sigma Advanced Systems, said: “These orders demonstrate the continued confidence of India’s defence ecosystem in Sigma’s engineering, manufacturing capabilities, and ability to deliver complex systems for mission-critical applications. Sigma remains committed to strengthening indigenous defence capability through reliable delivery, technology depth, and sustained programme support.” Sigma Microsystems is engaged in providing Embedded system solutions, with hardware and software, backed by its sound expertise in microprocessors, digital signal processors, VLSI designs and real-time systems. The company offers embedded modules and sub-stations, test benches and ATE, embedded boards, bus based boards and other related products. The company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 1.02 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net profit of Rs 7.30 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations zoomed 667.65% to Rs 145.70 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 18.98 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Samvardhana Motherson establishes automotive lighting facility in Gujarat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/samvardhana-motherson-establishes-automotive-lighting-facility-in-gujarat/1679243</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679243</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The facility has been set up under a strategic joint venture with Marelli, namely Marelli Motherson Automotive Lighting India (MMLI).

The facility has been set up under a strategic joint venture with Marelli, namely Marelli Motherson Automotive Lighting India (MMLI). The joint venture strengthens the group’s capabilities in automotive component manufacturing. MMLI is a 50:50 partnership between Samvardhana Motherson International and Marelli Europe S.p.A. The new automotive lighting facility spans 8,200 square meters and utilises the latest technologies to serve the rising demand for premium lighting solutions. It is the first facility in India capable of manufacturing edge-to-edge single-piece long lighting parts, powered by high-tonnage multi-colour moulding machines (2,000T to 2,700T). Laksh Vaaman Sehgal, vice chairman, Motherson, said: "The inauguration of our cutting-edge automotive lighting plant underscores Motherson’s unwavering commitment to innovation, excellence, and customer-centricity. This strategic investment strengthens our ability to deliver advanced, future-ready lighting solutions while meeting the evolving needs of our customers. We deeply appreciate the trust and support of our customers, which has been instrumental in achieving this significant milestone.” Frank Huber, president of Marelli’s Lighting business, said, “Our new facility in Sanand is a key milestone in bringing advanced lighting technologies to our customers in India. Together with our partner Motherson, we are uniting global innovation with strong local manufacturing capabilities to deliver cutting-edge solutions for the Indian market. Our joint venture continues to be a great success—built on Marelli’s global technology leadership, Motherson’s great infrastructure, execution excellence and deep customer relationships on the subcontinent, and the significant autonomy both partners have entrusted to the MMLI team since its establishment in 2008.” Samvardhana Motherson International (SAMIL) is one of the world’s leading specialized automotive component manufacturing companies for OEMs. It is currently the largest auto ancillary in India and is ranked among the top 15 automotive suppliers worldwide. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 16.5% to Rs 1023.70 crore on 14.5% increase in net sales to Rs 31,185.29 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.31% to Rs 130.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MothersonSumi_60777480057_2966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1679244</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679244</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Union Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The quantum of dividend (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Union Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.17 Union Balanced Advantage Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.17 Union Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.15 Union Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.15

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bandhan MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bandhan-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1679240</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679240</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Bandhan Mutual Fund has announced 26 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs. per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Bandhan Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.146 Bandhan Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.167 Bandhan Equity Savings Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.055 Bandhan Equity Savings Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.058 Bandhan Arbitrage Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.0528 Bandhan Arbitrage Fund – Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: 0.0531 Bandhan Conservative Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.0570 Bandhan Conservative Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.0671

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>