<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:17:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee Loses]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-loses/1662714</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662714</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed weaker at 90.1500 per Dollar on Wednesday (31 December 2025), versus its previous close of 90.0925 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Total government receipts stood at Rs 19 lakh crore in first eight months of current fiscal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/total-government-receipts-stood-at-rs-19-lakh-crore-in-first-eight-months-of-current-fiscal/1662713</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662713</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Latest official data showed that India's fiscal deficit for April to November, or the first eight months of current fiscal year FY26, stood at Rs 9.76 lakh crore, equivalent to 62.3% of annual estimates, marking a rise from the previous year's 52.5%.

Latest official data showed that India's fiscal deficit for April to November, or the first eight months of current fiscal year FY26, stood at Rs 9.76 lakh crore, equivalent to 62.3% of annual estimates, marking a rise from the previous year's 52.5%. Total government receipts stood at Rs 19 lakh crore, while total expenditure stood at Rs 29.25 lakh crore. Total receipts in the year-earlier period was at 59.1% of estimate, while expenditure stood at 56.9%. Data showed that revenue receipts stood at Rs 19.10 lakh crore, of which tax revenue was Rs 13.93 lakh crore and non-tax revenue was Rs 5.16 lakh crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks snap four-day losing streak, Nifty ends near 26,130 mark ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-snap-four-day-losing-streak-nifty-ends-near-26130-mark/1662710</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662710</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity indices rebounded on Wednesday, with the Sensex and Nifty breaking a four-session losing streak on the year’s final trading day.

Domestic equity indices rebounded on Wednesday, with the Sensex and Nifty breaking a four-session losing streak on the year’s final trading day. Bargain hunting lifted benchmarks despite continued foreign fund outflows. The Nifty closed near the 26,130 mark, driven by strength in energy and consumer durables stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 545.52 points or 0.64% to 85,220.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 190.75 points or 0.74% to 26,129.60. The 50 unit index slipped 0.91% in the past four sessions. JSW Steel (up 4.88%), Reliance Industries (up 1.9%) and Titan Company (up 1.86%) boosted the Nifty today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 1.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.19%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,799 shares rose and 1,413 shares fell. A total of 169 shares were unchanged. In 2025, the Sensex advanced 9.06%, while the Nifty 50 rose 10.51% and the Bank Nifty gained 17.15%. The broader S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 1.1% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index was up 6.62%. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.02% to 6.577 as compared with the previous close of 6.576. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8850 compared with its close of 89.7500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement fell 0.82% to Rs 135,542. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.13% to 98.37. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.44% to 4.111. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement rose 11 cents or 0.18% to $61.44 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares declined on Wednesday. Markets will operate for a half-day on Wednesday and will remain closed on Thursday for the New Year's Day holiday before reopening on Friday. Asian indices ended lower on the holiday-shortened final trading day of the year. Hong Kong and Australia will close early for the holidays, while Japan and South Korea remained closed for the day. China’s economy ended the year on a slightly less gloomy note, as factory activity expanded in December for the first time since March, beating expectations, according to official data released Wednesday. The official manufacturing purchasing managers index rose to 50.1 in December, higher than the 49.2 reading that was recorded in November. A reading above 50 indicates expansion. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 fell modestly, notching a third consecutive losing session. The broad market index lost 0.14% and closed at 6,896.24, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.24% and settled at 23,419.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.20% and ended at 48,367.06. The three major averages have slumped to start the week, dragged down by losses in tech. Nvidia posted back-to-back losing sessions, as did another AI stock Palantir Technologies. Stocks in Spotlight: The Nifty Oil & Gas index jumped 2.66% to 12,231.20. The index declined 1.13% in the past four trading sessions. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation rose 6.56%, followed by Gujarat Gas at 5.63% and Gujarat State Petronet at 4.26%. Bharat Petroleum Corporation gained 3.78%, Oil India advanced 3.29%, and Indian Oil Corporation climbed 2.95%. Oil and Natural Gas Corporation added 2.46%, while Mahanagar Gas rose 2.22%. Castrol India gained 2.09%, Aegis Logistics moved up 2.00%, and Reliance Industries advanced 1.90%. Indraprastha Gas rose 1.76%, Petronet LNG added 1.52%, GAIL India increased 0.80%, and Adani Total Gas edged up 0.35%. Shares of leading steelmakers moved higher after the government imposed a three-year safeguard duty of up to 12% on select steel imports, boosting hopes of stronger pricing support for domestic producers. JSW Steel advanced 4.89%, while Jindal Steel jumped 2.75%. Tata Steel climbed 2.45% and Jindal Stainless rose 0.15%. Waaree Energies shed 0.52%. The company announced that it has secured an order to supply 1,500 MW of solar modules (1,000 MW DCR and 500 MW non-DCR) from a renowned power sector customer. Shakti Pumps India rallied 3.45% after the company announced that it has secured a new work order worth Rs 170.25 crore from Madhya Pradesh Urja Vikas Nigam. ZF Steering Gear India surged 8.62% after the company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Drivesys Systems, has secured a significant order worth Rs 151 crore for its renewable energy business. Power Grid Corporation of India rose 1.63% after the company said that it has declared a successful bidder for the 2,000 MWh battery energy storage project. Premier Energies declined 1.23%. The company has secured new orders worth Rs 2,307.30 crore during the third quarter of FY26, with execution scheduled across FY27 and FY28. Ahasolar Technologies surged 7.71% after the company has received a contract from CIL Rajasthan Akshay Urja for providing owner’s engineering and project management consultancy (OEPMC) services for an 875 MW solar photovoltaic power project. Apollo Micro Systems jumped 4.79% after the company’s step- down subsidiary IDL Explosives bagged supply contracts worth approximately Rs 421 crore. RITES gained 2.13% after the company has received a Letter of Award for the supply of in-service Cape gauge diesel-electric locomotives from Berhard Development Corporation, Zimbabwe. The order is valued at $3.6 million.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance infuses Rs 500-cr into Muthoot Money ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/muthoot-finance-infuses-rs-500-cr-into-muthoot-money/1662709</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662709</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The subsidiary has allotted 3,25,139 equity shares to Muthoot Finance.

The subsidiary has allotted 3,25,139 equity shares to Muthoot Finance. This capital infusion is intended to strengthen Muthoot Money’s capital base and improve its capital adequacy ratio. The funds raised through the rights issue will be utilized for funding the business, general corporate purposes and for repayment of existing loans. Muthoot Finance provides gold loans secured against gold jewellery, helping individuals and small businesses access essential short-term liquidity. Additionally, through its subsidiaries, the company offers a range of financial services, including personal and business loans, insurance distribution, and money transfer services. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 90.4% to Rs 2,420.63 crore on 47.9% increase in total income to Rs 7,332.59 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip rose 0.35% to settle at Rs 3,813.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MuthootFinance_48499437395_24769.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1662705</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662705</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2025 futures closed at 26,304.80, a premium of 175.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,129.60 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2025 futures closed at 26,304.80, a premium of 175.2 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,129.60 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index surged 190.75 points or 0.74% to 26,129.60. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 2.09% to 9.48. Vodafone Idea, Indus Towers and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Non-food bank credit rises 11.40% on year, personal loans segment clocks surge of nearly 13%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/non-food-bank-credit-rises-1140-on-year-personal-loans-segment-clocks-surge-of-nearly-13/1662704</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662704</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released sectoral deployment of bank credit for the month of November 2025, collected from 41 select scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) which together account for about 95 per cent of the total non-food credit by all SCBs.

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has released sectoral deployment of bank credit for the month of November 2025, collected from 41 select scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) which together account for about 95 per cent of the total non-food credit by all SCBs. On a year-on-year (y-o-y) basis, non-food bank credit grew by 11.4 per cent as on the fortnight ended November 28, 2025, compared to 10.6 per cent during the corresponding fortnight of the previous year (i.e., November 29, 2024). RBI noted that credit to agriculture and allied activities registered a y-o-y growth of 8.7 per cent (15.3 per cent in the corresponding fortnight of the previous year). Credit to industry recorded a y-o-y growth of 9.6 per cent, compared with 8.3 per cent in the corresponding fortnight of last year. Credit to ‘Micro and Small’ and ‘Medium’ industries continued to exhibit double-digit expansion. Among major industries, outstanding credit to ‘infrastructure’, ‘all engineering’, ‘textiles’ and ‘petroleum, coal products and nuclear fuels’ registered buoyant y-o-y growth. Credit to services sector registered a growth rate of 11.7 per cent y-o-y (12.8 per cent in the corresponding fortnight of the previous year). Growth in segments such as ‘non-banking financial companies’ (NBFCs) and ‘computer software’ improved. Segments such as ‘trade’ and ‘commercial real estate’ also registered healthy growth, albeit with a marginal deceleration. Credit to personal loans segment recorded a y-o-y growth of 12.8 per cent, as compared with 13.4 per cent a year ago. While segments such as ‘vehicle loans’ and ‘loans against gold jewellery’ sustained steady credit growth, ‘housing’ and ‘credit card outstanding’ witnessed moderation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/euro-seem-money-finance_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR tumbles around 6% in 2025]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-tumbles-around-6-in-2025/1662703</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662703</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee eased today, ending the year on a tepid note.

Indian rupee eased today, ending the year on a tepid note. INR has moved mostly lower and is on track to decline around 6% this year and is not far from record lows against the US dollar. Overall mood is cautious as trades in global fx markets around year-end though there is a modest uptick in the US dollar index. INR slipped amid these cues and also eyed the Indian government monthly finances data. INR shed 13 paise at 89.88 per US dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 546 pts higher in 2025’s final session; Nifty ends above 26,100 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-546-pts-higher-in-2025s-final-session-nifty-ends-above-26100-level/1662702</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662702</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended the final trading session of the year on a strong note amid robust trading activity, as investor sentiment remained upbeat ahead of the new year.

The key equity barometers ended the final trading session of the year on a strong note amid robust trading activity, as investor sentiment remained upbeat ahead of the new year. The Nifty settled above the 26,100 level, with investors turning their focus to the upcoming corporate earnings season. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, advanced 545.52 points or 0.64% to 85,220.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 190.75 points or 0.74% to 26,129.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 1.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.19%. The market breadth was strong. Over the past year, the Sensex advanced 9.06%, while the Nifty 50 rose 10.51% and the Bank Nifty gained 17.15%. Broader markets posted modest gains, with the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index up 1.1% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index higher by 6.62%. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 2.66%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 1.56%) and the Nifty Media index (up 1.50%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 0.30%), the Nifty Healthcare index (up 0.67%) and the Nifty Bank index (up 0.69%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.02% to 6.577 as compared with the previous close of 6.576. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8850 compared with its close of 89.7500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement fell 0.82% to Rs 135,542. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.13% to 98.37. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.44% to 4.111. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement rose 11 cents or 0.18% to $61.44 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares advanced on Wednesday. Markets will operate for a half-day on Wednesday and will remain closed on Thursday for the New Year’s Day holiday before reopening on Friday. Asian markets ended mixed on the holiday-shortened final trading day of the year. Hong Kong and Australia will close early for the holidays, while Japan and South Korea remained closed for the day. China’s economy ended the year on a slightly less gloomy note, as factory activity expanded in December for the first time since March, beating expectations, according to official data released Wednesday. The official manufacturing purchasing managers index rose to 50.1 in December, higher than the 49.2 reading that was recorded in November. A reading above 50 indicates expansion. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 fell modestly, notching a third consecutive losing session. The broad market index lost 0.14% and closed at 6,896.24, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.24% and settled at 23,419.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.20% and ended at 48,367.06. The three major averages have slumped to start the week, dragged down by losses in tech. Nvidia posted back-to-back losing sessions, as did another AI stock Palantir Technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty PSE Index records a surge of 1.77%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-pse-index-records-a-surge-of-177/1662693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662693</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty PSE index ended up 1.77% at 9853.65 today.

Nifty PSE index ended up 1.77% at 9853.65 today. The index has added 1.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd jumped 6.46%, Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd rose 3.92% and Oil India Ltd added 3.14%. The Nifty PSE index has increased 3.00% over last one year compared to the 10.51% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Commodities index increased 1.61% and Nifty Media index gained 1.50% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 increased 0.74% to close at 26129.6 while the SENSEX witnessed a rise of 0.64% to close at 85220.6 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-background-design-picture-id511195524_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices wrap up year with solid gains; oil & gas shares climb]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-wrap-up-year-with-solid-gains-oil-gas-shares-climb/1662694</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662694</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended the last trading day of the year with substantial gains, as robust trading activity reflected optimism for the year ahead.

The key equity barometers ended the last trading day of the year with substantial gains, as robust trading activity reflected optimism for the year ahead. The Nifty closed above 25,100, snapping a four-day losing streak, while the Sensex bounced back after five straight days of losses. Investors focused on the upcoming corporate earnings season. Barring IT, all sectoral indices on the NSE ended in the green, led by gains in oil & gas, consumer durables and metal stocks. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 545.52 points or 0.64% to 85,220.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 190.75 points or 0.74% to 26,129.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index climbed 1.01% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index jumped 1.19%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,801 shares rose and 1,410 shares fell. A total of 170 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index jumped 2.66% to 12,231.20. The index declined 1.13% in the past four trading sessions. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (up 6.55%), Gujarat Gas (up 5.19%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (up 3.91%), Gujarat State Petronet (up 3.87%) and Oil India (up 3.21%), Indian Oil Corporation (up 3.05%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (up 2.5%), Mahanagar Gas (up 2.21%), Castrol India (up 1.98%) and Aegis Logistics (up 1.96%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Waaree Energies shed 0.52%. The company announced that it has secured an order to supply 1,500 MW of solar modules (1,000 MW DCR and 500 MW non-DCR) from a renowned power sector customer. Shakti Pumps India rallied 3.45% after the company announced that it has secured a new work order worth Rs 170.25 crore from Madhya Pradesh Urja Vikas Nigam. ZF Steering Gear India surged 8.62% after the company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Drivesys Systems, has secured a significant order worth Rs 151 crore for its renewable energy business. Power Grid Corporation of India rose 1.63% after the company said that it has declared a successful bidder for the 2,000 MWh battery energy storage project. Premier Energies declined 1.23%. The company has secured new orders worth Rs 2,307.30 crore during the third quarter of FY26, with execution scheduled across FY27 and FY28. Ahasolar Technologies surged 7.71% after the company has received a contract from CIL Rajasthan Akshay Urja for providing owner’s engineering and project management consultancy (OEPMC) services for an 875 MW solar photovoltaic power project. Apollo Micro Systems jumped 4.79% after the company’s step- down subsidiary IDL Explosives bagged supply contracts worth approximately Rs 421 crore. RITES gained 2.13% after the company has received a Letter of Award for the supply of in-service Cape gauge diesel-electric locomotives from Berhard Development Corporation, Zimbabwe. The order is valued at $3.6 million. Global Markets: Most European shares advanced on Wednesday. Markets will operate for a half-day on Wednesday and will remain closed on Thursday for the New Year’s Day holiday, before reopening on Friday. In Asia, markets ended mixed on the holiday-shortened final trading day of the year. Hong Kong and Australia will close early for the holidays, while Japan and South Korea remained closed for the day. China’s economy ended the year on a slightly less gloomy note, as factory activity expanded in December for the first time since March, beating expectations, according to official data released Wednesday. The official manufacturing purchasing managers index rose to 50.1 in December, higher than 49.2 reading that was recorded in November. A reading above 50 indicates expansion. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 fell modestly, notching a third consecutive losing session. The broad market index lost 0.14% and closed at 6,896.24, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.24% and settled at 23,419.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.20% and ended at 48,367.06. The three major averages have slumped to start the week, dragged down by losses in tech. Nvidia posted back-to-back losing sessions, as did another AI stock Palantir Technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI releases Financial Stability Report (FSR) highlighting resilience of the Indian financial system and risks to financial stability]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-releases-financial-stability-report-fsr-highlighting-resilience-of-the-indian-financial-system-and-risks-to-financial-stability/1662695</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662695</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank released the December 2025 edition of the Financial Stability Report (FSR), which reflects the collective assessment of the Sub-Committee of the Financial Stability and Development Council (FSDC) on the resilience of the Indian financial system and risks to financial stability.

The Reserve Bank released the December 2025 edition of the Financial Stability Report (FSR), which reflects the collective assessment of the Sub-Committee of the Financial Stability and Development Council (FSDC) on the resilience of the Indian financial system and risks to financial stability. Global economy has been resilient, supported by fiscal measures, front-loaded trade, and strong AI-related investment. However, downside risks persist due to still elevated uncertainty, high public debt, and the risk of a disorderly market correction. Global financial markets appear strong on the surface but show growing underlying vulnerabilities. Sharp rise in equities and other risk assets, the expanding role of non-bank financial intermediaries and their deepening interconnectedness with banks, and the growth of stablecoins all heighten global financial system fragilities. Despite an uncertain and challenging global economic backdrop, the Indian economy continues to grow strongly, underpinned by robust domestic demand, benign inflation, and prudent macroeconomic policies. The domestic financial system remains robust and resilient, bolstered by strong balance sheets, easy financial conditions, and low financial market volatility. Nonetheless, there are near-term risks from external uncertainties - geopolitical and trade related. The health of the scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) remains sound with strong capital and liquidity buffers, improved asset quality and robust profitability. Macro stress test results affirm the resilience of SCBs to withstand losses under hypothetical adverse scenarios and maintain capital buffers well above the regulatory minimum. Stress tests also confirm the resilience of mutual funds and clearing corporations. Non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) remain robust supported by strong capital buffers, solid earnings, and improving asset quality. The insurance sector continues to display balance sheet resilience and the consolidated solvency ratio remained above the minimum threshold limit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Satin Creditcare Network to consider fundraising via NCDs on January 5]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/satin-creditcare-network-to-consider-fundraising-via-ncds-on-january-5/1662690</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662690</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the company will consider raising funds through the issuance of listed secured or unsecured non-convertible debentures (NCDs) on a private placement basis at the meeting.

According to an exchange filing, the company will consider raising funds through the issuance of listed secured or unsecured non-convertible debentures (NCDs) on a private placement basis at the meeting. Satin Creditcare Network is a leading microfinance institution (MFI) in the country. The company offers a bouquet of financial products in the non-MFI segment, comprising loans to MSMEs and affordable housing loans. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 19% to Rs 53.16 crore on a 20.6% rise in total income to Rs 792.80 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter rose 0.17% to Rs 143.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SatinCreditcare_84494064_16093.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold glitters, up around 65% this year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-glitters-up-around-65-this-year/1662689</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662689</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Gold futures saw selling pressure yesterday amid heavy volatility.

COMEX Gold futures saw selling pressure yesterday amid heavy volatility. The US dollar index edged up a bit after the minutes of the Federal Reserve's latest monetary policy meeting revealed participants expressed a "range of views" about the restrictiveness of the Fed's current monetary policy stance. Some participants also felt it would likely be appropriate to keep rates unchanged for "some time" following the quarter point rate cut at the December meeting. The metal had tested near two-week low on Monday amid an across-the-board tumble in metals. The precious metal currently quotes at $4344 per ounce, down around 1% on the day but is up around 65% this year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/forex-markets-currency-trading-concept-picture-id609801990_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kirloskar Ferrous edges higher after ICRA reaffirms ratings at 'AA/A1+']]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kirloskar-ferrous-edges-higher-after-icra-reaffirms-ratings-at-aaa1/1662687</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662687</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘[ICRA] A1+’.

The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘[ICRA] A1+’. ICRA stated that the ratings favourably factor in the established position of Kirloskar Ferrous Industries (KFIL) in the foundry-grade pig iron and ferrous castings businesses. Despite commodity headwinds, the company’s financial performance continues to remain comfortable as reflected in the healthy operating profits reported in FY2025 and H1 of FY2026. The company is a part of the reputed Pune-based Kirloskar Group, which has a proven management track record. The ratings derive comfort from the backward integration achieved at KFIL‘s manufacturing plant through coke oven plant, captive power generation, pulverized coal injection (PCI) plant which leads to substantial cost savings. Besides, the commencement of operations at the Bharath iron ore mine has partially reduced reliance on external iron ore purchases, resulting in cost savings. The ratings factor in KFIL’s established relationships with large original equipment manufacturers (OEMs). ICRA notes the high customer concentration in the castings segment, though it derives comfort from the fact that KFIL is the single source supplier in most of these cases, which leads to customer retention and repeat orders. The ratings also derive comfort from the comfortable consolidated financial profile of KFIL, marked by healthy credit metrics. Despite the large capex plans going forward, ICRA expects KFIL’s comfortable credit metrics to sustain going forward given the healthy cash generation expected which will limit dependence on debt. The ratings are constrained by the vulnerability of the company’s operating profit margin (OPM) to fluctuating raw material prices, given the commoditised nature of the pig iron business. The ratings are constrained by the casting division’s exposure to the inherent demand cyclicality in the key end-user segments (both commercial vehicle and tractor segments). Kirloskar Ferrous Industries (KFIL) is part of Pune-based Kirloskar Group. KFIL manufactures pig iron, and ferrous castings such as cylinder blocks, cylinder heads, axles and transmission parts and different types of housings required in Automobile, Tractor and Diesel engine related industries.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KirlFerrous_92911245656_3511.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Steel shares spurt after govt slaps safeguard duty on steel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/steel-shares-spurt-after-govt-slaps-safeguard-duty-on-steel/1662685</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662685</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[JSW Steel surged 4.97%, Tata Steel added 2.50%, Jindal stainless rose 0.64%, Steel Authority of India (SAIL) climbed 4.15%, Jindal Steel rallied 3.33%.

JSW Steel surged 4.97%, Tata Steel added 2.50%, Jindal stainless rose 0.64%, Steel Authority of India (SAIL) climbed 4.15%, Jindal Steel rallied 3.33%. The duty on select non-alloy and alloy steel products will be set at 12% in the first year, before being reduced to 11.5% in the second year and further to 11% in the third year. Imports from certain developing countries are exempt, while shipments from China, Vietnam and Nepal will be subject to the levy. Specialty steel products, including stainless steel, are excluded. The safeguard measure is expected to support domestic steel prices and protect margins at a time when global steel prices remain subdued.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JSWSteel_59462548667_4764.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prostarm Info Systems to set up new UPS manufacturing unit in Gujarat]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prostarm-info-systems-to-set-up-new-ups-manufacturing-unit-in-gujarat/1662683</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662683</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the facility will produce UPS ranging from 1 KVA to 600 KVA.

According to an exchange filing, the facility will produce UPS ranging from 1 KVA to 600 KVA. Commercial production is expected to begin on or before May 2026, subject to the receipt of necessary approvals. The estimated capital expenditure for the project is Rs 6 crore, which includes plant and machinery, civil construction, infrastructure, and contingencies. The project will be financed through internal accruals and IPO proceeds, aimed at creating and strengthening the company’s manufacturing capacity. Prostram Info Systems is a power solutions provider specializing in UPS systems, inverters, lithium-ion battery packs, and solar EPC projects. The company designs, manufactures, and assembles products in-house and via partners in India and China. It serves sectors like healthcare, IT, defense, and energy through direct sales and a nationwide distributor network. The company operates three units in Maharashtra and has strengthened its tech capabilities through strategic acquisitions and licensing agreements. The company’s consolidated net profit tanked 40.5% to Rs 8.27 crore on a 33.1% fall in sales to Rs 65.92 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Q2 FY25. The counter rose 0.86% to Rs 181.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ProstarmInfo_11067685_73286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar index sees near double-digit correction in 2025]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-index-sees-near-double-digit-correction-in-2025/1662682</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662682</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar index has been sliding this year amid a resumption of interest rate cuts.

The US dollar index has been sliding this year amid a resumption of interest rate cuts. The index fell to around three and half year low in Sep-25 and has lost around 9.50% this year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/power-of-money-picture-id155389485_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hyundai Motor to raise prices by 0.6% for all models from Jan 01]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hyundai-motor-to-raise-prices-by-06-for-all-models-from-jan-01/1662684</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662684</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While the company continuously strives to optimize costs and minimize the impact on its customers, the company is constrained to pass on some of the increased costs to the market through this minor price increase.

While the company continuously strives to optimize costs and minimize the impact on its customers, the company is constrained to pass on some of the increased costs to the market through this minor price increase. The announcement was made during market hours today. Hyundai Motor India manufactures and sells passenger cars, along with vehicle parts and accessories. The company's consolidated net profit rose 14.31% to Rs 1,572.26 crore on a 1.15% increase in revenue to Rs 17,155.83 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip shed 0.20% to currently trade at Rs 2297.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HyundaiMotorIndiaLtd_73449848_16486.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Idea Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vodafone-idea-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1662676</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662676</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Navin Fluorine International Ltd, Asahi India Glass Ltd, Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd and Hindustan Copper Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 31 December 2025.

Navin Fluorine International Ltd, Asahi India Glass Ltd, Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd and Hindustan Copper Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 31 December 2025. Vodafone Idea Ltd tumbled 10.02% to Rs 10.86 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 2151.26 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 720.57 lakh shares in the past one month. Navin Fluorine International Ltd crashed 4.06% to Rs 5880. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6163 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6868 shares in the past one month. Asahi India Glass Ltd lost 3.08% to Rs 1003.25. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 7919 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7592 shares in the past one month. Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd slipped 2.67% to Rs 344.85. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.04 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Copper Ltd shed 2.60% to Rs 519.1. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 62.27 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 33.22 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VodafoneIdea_33393045864_23040.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waaree Renewable rises after bagging Rs 97-cr Solar EPC order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waaree-renewable-rises-after-bagging-rs-97-cr-solar-epc-order/1662678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662678</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the contract, the company will execute a 28.60 MWac / 39.80 MWp solar project on a turnkey basis.

Under the contract, the company will execute a 28.60 MWac / 39.80 MWp solar project on a turnkey basis. The project is scheduled to be completed during FY27, in line with the terms of the order. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not involve any related-party transaction. Additionally, the promoters and promoter group companies of Waaree Renewable Technologies do not have any interest in the awarding entity. This order further strengthens Waaree Renewable Technologies’ presence in the renewable energy EPC segment and underscores its growing execution capabilities in large-scale solar projects. Waaree Renewable Technologies, based in Mumbai, is a subsidiary of the Waaree Group and leads the group’s Solar EPC operations. In addition to engineering, procurement, and construction, the company develops, finances, builds, owns, and operates solar power projects as part of its long-term investment approach. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 117.2% to Rs 116.30 crore on 47.7% jump in net sales to Rs 774.78 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SangamRenewab_88718616710_42529.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>