<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:28:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sai-silks-kalamandir-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663221</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663221</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cupid Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, DCM Financial Services Ltd and SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 January 2026.

Cupid Ltd, Vivimed Labs Ltd, DCM Financial Services Ltd and SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 05 January 2026. Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd tumbled 11.59% to Rs 134.65 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.29 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 23961 shares in the past one month. Cupid Ltd crashed 10.12% to Rs 377.45. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 60.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7.56 lakh shares in the past one month. Vivimed Labs Ltd lost 9.95% to Rs 13.58. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15545 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9530 shares in the past one month. DCM Financial Services Ltd plummeted 9.14% to Rs 5.07. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 229 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3884 shares in the past one month. SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd slipped 7.80% to Rs 377.1. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 19791 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8088 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SaiSilksKalamandirLtd_62265977_34768.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of Baroda’s global advances jump 15% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-barodas-global-advances-jump-15-yoy-in-q3/1663222</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663222</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[During the quarter, the bank’s global business stood at Rs 28,90,661 crore, registering a growth of 12.22% YoY compared to Rs 25,75,943 crore recorded in Q3 FY25.

During the quarter, the bank’s global business stood at Rs 28,90,661 crore, registering a growth of 12.22% YoY compared to Rs 25,75,943 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Global deposits increased 10.25% YoY to Rs 15,46,749 crore, up from Rs 14,02,909 crore reported in the same period last year. Domestic advances stood at Rs 10,95,528 crore as of 31 December 2025, marking a YoY growth of 13.54%. Domestic deposits were at Rs 13,07,189 crore, reflecting an 11.13% YoY increase. Bank of Baroda is engaged in providing various services, such as personal banking, corporate banking, international banking, small and medium enterprise (SME) banking, rural banking, non-resident Indian (NRI) services and treasury services. Bank of Baroda reported an 8.2% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 4,809.39 crore on a 1.2% decline in total income to Rs 35,025.76 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The counter rose 0.31% to settle at Rs 306 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofBaroda_23609426771_5456.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 375 pts; oil & gas shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-375-pts-oil-gas-shares-decline/1663220</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663220</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses in the mid- afternoon trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with moderate losses in the mid- afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 26,250 mark. Oil & Gas shares declined after advancing for previous three consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 374.75 points or 0.44% to 85,392.93. The Nifty 50 index dropped 103.15 points or 0.39% to 26,225.40. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.23% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.09%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,607 shares rose and 2,568 shares fell. A total of 222 shares were unchanged. Gold surges over Rs 2k, silver shoots up by Rs 9,900 as US takes control in Venezuela: Gold and silver prices opened sharply higher on Monday, reflecting an intense global rush toward safe-haven assets after the United States’ dramatic intervention in Venezuela over the weekend. On the MCX, silver futures for March delivery surged by nearly Rs 10,000 per kg in early trade, while gold futures were also firmly up by over Rs 2,000/10 grams. With global investors seeking refuge in precious metals, both gold and silver continued their upward march in international and domestic markets. Spot silver surged 4.5% to $75.86 an ounce, while spot gold rose 1.5% to $4,395.35 per ounce, marking a fresh one-week high. U.S. gold futures for February delivery jumped 1.8% to $4,405.40. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Oil & Gas index declined 1.22% to 12,189.90. The index rose 2.30% in the previous three consecutive trading session. Oil India (down 2.32%), Indraprastha Gas (down 1.92%), Adani Total Gas (down 1.8%), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (down 1.78%), Indian Oil Corporation (down 1.78%), Oil & Natural Gas Corpn (down 1.64%), GAIL (India) (down 1.52%), Petronet LNG (down 1.48%), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (down 1.28%) and Mahanagar Gas (down 1.14%) declined. On the other hand, Aegis Logistics (up 1.03%), Gujarat Gas (up 0.91%) and Gujarat State Petronet (up 0.39%) added. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper added 0.57% to 6.647 compared with previous session close of 6.609. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2875 compared with its close of 90.2050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement added 1.54% to Rs 137,850. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.28% to 98.70. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.43% to 4.173. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 81 cents or 0.81% to $59.94 a barrel.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Netweb Technologies India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-netweb-technologies-india-ltd-counter/1663205</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663205</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd, Sobha Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd, SJVN Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 05 January 2026.

Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd, Sobha Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd, SJVN Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 05 January 2026. Netweb Technologies India Ltd clocked volume of 62.71 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 27.36 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.29 lakh shares. The stock gained 8.40% to Rs.3,278.00. Volumes stood at 2.94 lakh shares in the last session. Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd notched up volume of 18.03 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 17.17 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.05 lakh shares. The stock rose 3.52% to Rs.751.80. Volumes stood at 1.38 lakh shares in the last session. Sobha Ltd registered volume of 12.28 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.57 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.16 lakh shares. The stock rose 4.64% to Rs.1,559.80. Volumes stood at 59233 shares in the last session. Aegis Logistics Ltd witnessed volume of 14.76 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.08 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.46 lakh shares. The stock increased 1.16% to Rs.734.60. Volumes stood at 1.76 lakh shares in the last session. SJVN Ltd recorded volume of 817.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.1 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 134.12 lakh shares. The stock gained 5.00% to Rs.87.19. Volumes stood at 822.65 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NetwebTechnologiesIndiaLtd_73333970_78854.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sobha climbs after Q3 sales value surges 52% YoY in FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sobha-climbs-after-q3-sales-value-surges-52-yoy-in-fy26/1663207</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663207</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[New sales area stood at 13,70,340 square foot (sq.ft), registering the growth of 34.83% compared with 10,16,367 sq.ft in corresponding quarter last year.

New sales area stood at 13,70,340 square foot (sq.ft), registering the growth of 34.83% compared with 10,16,367 sq.ft in corresponding quarter last year. Average price realization increased 12.98% to Rs 15,436 per sq.ft compared with Rs 13,663 per sq.ft posted in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, the company launched three projects across three cities, with saleable area of 9,32,171 sq.ft, taking cumulative new launches for 9M of FY 2026 to 2.58 million sft. Sobha is the real estate brand in the country that offers international quality homes, and commercial and contractual projects delivered on time, through its backward integration model. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 178% to Rs 72.53 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 26.09 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales climbed 50.8% YoY to Rs 1,407.62 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Sobha_16954596303_27443.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold extends record run as US action in Venezuela shakes markets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-extends-record-run-as-us-action-in-venezuela-shakes-markets/1663203</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663203</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices jumped by more than $100 to around $4435 per ounce in Asian trading on Monday after a surprise US military operation in Venezuela led to the capture of President Nicolás Maduro, sparking fresh safe-haven demand.

Gold prices jumped by more than $100 to around $4435 per ounce in Asian trading on Monday after a surprise US military operation in Venezuela led to the capture of President Nicolás Maduro, sparking fresh safe-haven demand. The move adds to gold’s strong momentum after prices surged over 60% in 2025, hitting a record high of $4584 per ounce toward year-end. Broader precious metals also rallied sharply, with silver jumping over 7% to $76 per ounce and platinum climbing more than 5% to $2229.9 per ounce, as investors reacted to heightened geopolitical uncertainty and potential fallout for energy markets. Reflecting the global strength, MCX February gold futures rose 1.5% to ₹137749 per 10 grams. Looking ahead, market participants are also closely watching key US economic data this week, especially Friday’s non-farm payrolls report, for further clues on the direction of US interest rates.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts fall further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-fall-further/1663196</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663196</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a six high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown.

Large currency speculators reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a six high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) that began releasing delayed data following brief period of US shutdown. The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 41199 contracts in the data reported through December 23, 2025. This was a weekly drop of 7299 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Amber Enterprises rises after subsidiaries get ECMS approval]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/amber-enterprises-rises-after-subsidiaries-get-ecms-approval/1663193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663193</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said Ascent K Circuit and Shogini Technoarts have been granted formal approval under the ECMS.

The company said Ascent K Circuit and Shogini Technoarts have been granted formal approval under the ECMS. The approval was received on 2 January 2026, in the presence of Union Minister for Electronics and Information Technology Ashwini Vaishnaw and senior officials from the Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology. Amber said the approval is a key milestone for accelerating localisation of critical electronic components. It is expected to strengthen India’s electronics manufacturing services value chain and support the Atmanirbhar Bharat initiative. The company thanked the Government of India and MeitY for the approval. It reiterated its commitment to expanding domestic EMS manufacturing and building long term capabilities in electronics components. Amber Enterprises India manufactures complete room air conditioners, including window and split AC units, as well as air conditioning systems for railways, metro trains, buses, and defence. The company also produces critical AC components such as heat exchangers, condensers, sheet metal parts, motors, PCB assemblies, and moulded components, and supplies parts for other consumer durables and the automobile sector. On a consolidated basis, the company reported net loss of Rs 32.86 crore in Q2 September 2025 as against net profit of Rs 19.20 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales declined 2.24% YoY to Rs 1647.01 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AmberEnterprisesIndiaLtd_4767604800_45967.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Government Approves NBS Rates for Rabi 2025–26 to Promote Balanced Fertilizer Use and Ensure Timely Farmer Support]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/government-approves-nbs-rates-for-rabi-202526-to-promote-balanced-fertilizer-use-and-ensure-timely-farmer-support/1663192</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663192</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nutrient-Based Subsidy (NBS) Scheme of the Ministry of Chemicals and Fertilizers aims to promote the balanced use of essential nutrients, such as nitrogen, phosphorus, potassium, and sulphur, thereby helping farmers avoid over-dependence on any single fertilizer and maintain soil health while improving productivity.

The Nutrient-Based Subsidy (NBS) Scheme of the Ministry of Chemicals and Fertilizers aims to promote the balanced use of essential nutrients, such as nitrogen, phosphorus, potassium, and sulphur, thereby helping farmers avoid over-dependence on any single fertilizer and maintain soil health while improving productivity. It ensures that fertilizers are available to farmers on time and at affordable, subsidized prices which is vital for smooth crop planning. The scheme also fosters healthy competition among fertilizer companies, driving improvements in quality, innovations, and efficiency in the fertilizer market. By supporting the introduction of new and innovative fertilizers, including advanced and micro nutrient-enriched products, the NBS scheme helps modernize agricultural practices. Additionally, it focuses on rationalizing subsidies by aligning them with global price trends of fertilizers and raw materials, ensuring both farmer support and fiscal responsibility. The government approved the Nutrient-Based Subsidy (NBS) rates for Rabi 2025–26, effective from October 1, 2025 to March 31, 2026, covering Phosphatic and Potassic (P&K) fertilizers, including DAP and NPKS grades. The tentative budget requirement for Rabi 2025–26 is approximately Rs 37,952 crore, about Rs 736 crore higher than the budgetary requirement for the Kharif 2025 season.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/keyboard-338517__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PC Jeweller jumps on strong Q3 business update]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pc-jeweller-jumps-on-strong-q3-business-update/1663191</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663191</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The jewellery retailer said standalone revenue rose around 37% year on year in Q3 FY26, driven by robust demand during the ongoing festival and wedding season.

The jewellery retailer said standalone revenue rose around 37% year on year in Q3 FY26, driven by robust demand during the ongoing festival and wedding season. The company said consumer traction remained strong across its product portfolio, supporting healthy sales momentum during the quarter. During the quarter, PC Jeweller also received approval from the Government of Uttar Pradesh to be onboarded as a franchise brand under the CM Yuva Udyami Vikas Abhiyan scheme. The initiative aims to support trained goldsmith entrepreneurs by setting up 1,000 jewellery retail franchise units across rural and semi urban areas of the state. The company has signed a memorandum of understanding with the CM Yuva Mission under the state’s MSME and Export Promotion Department. PC Jeweller said the programme is expected to enhance its retail footprint while contributing to entrepreneurship, skill development, and local employment generation in Uttar Pradesh. The company also reiterated its focus on becoming debt free in the near future. Since executing a settlement agreement with banks in September 2024, PC Jeweller has reduced its outstanding debt by about 68%, it said. The financial numbers shared in the update are provisional and subject to limited review by the statutory auditor. PC Jeweller is engaged in the manufacture, retail, and export of jewellery. On a consolidated basis, net profit of PC Jeweller rose 17.14% to Rs 209.54 crore while net sales rose 63.43% to Rs 825.25 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PCJeweller_98607766370_33583.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 26,300 level; broader mrkt outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-26300-level-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1663190</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663190</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with small cuts in early-afternoon trade as investors balanced encouraging corporate updates against heightened geopolitical risks.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with small cuts in early-afternoon trade as investors balanced encouraging corporate updates against heightened geopolitical risks. Initial optimism driven by improving quarterly earnings was capped by caution over the potential fallout from reported U.S. military action in Venezuela. The Nifty traded below the 26,300 level. IT and oil & gas shares declined, while realty, consumer durables and media shares advanced. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 133.13 points or 0.16% to 85,628.88. The Nifty 50 index dropped 42.60 points or 0.16% to 26,286.05. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.11% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.10%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,735 shares rose and 2,397 shares fell. A total of 214 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. Gainers & Losers: Bharat Electronics (up 2.94%), Nestle India (up 3.03%), Eicher Motors (up 1.77%), Asian Paints (up 1.75%) and UltraTech Cement (up 1.64%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Infosys (down 1.95%), HCL Technologies (down 1.93%), HDFC Bank (down 1.92%), Wipro (down 1.82%) and Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (down 1.21%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Corona Remedies added 2.23% after it reported a 21.75% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 52.32 crore on 15.05% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 361.13 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. NIBE surged 4.72% after it secured a domestic defence contract worth Rs 292.69 crore from the Indian Army under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. Jammu & Kashmir Bank added 0.64%. The bank's gross advances jumped 17.26% to Rs 1,16,247.92 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 99,133.35 crore as of 31 December 2024. Bank of Maharashtra rose 0.45%. The bank reported a 15.30% year-on-year (YoY) increase in total deposits to Rs 3,21,695 crore as of 31st December 2025, compared with Rs 2,79,007 crore as of 31st December 2024. Global Markets: European shares opened mixed on Monday as global markets reacted to the U.S.-led overthrow of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Asian market began the first full trading week of 2026 on a stronger note after the U.S. said it had attacked Venezuela and captured President Nicolas Maduro over the weekend. Oil prices edged lower as markets weighed the potential impact of geopolitical tensions. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. Oil prices fell after the escalation involving the oil-rich nation. Brent crude prices slipped more than 1% earlier before paring losses and were last trading 0.25% lower, while the West Texas Intermediate crude prices fell 0.4%. On Friday stateside, the first trading day of 2026, the S&P 500 closed slightly higher as gains in semiconductor names kept the index afloat. The benchmark closed up 0.19% at 6,858.47, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.03% to finish at 23,235.63. The two had been solidly positive earlier in the day, with the S&P 500 and the tech-heavy Nasdaq trading higher by 0.7% and 1.5% at their peaks, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GST collection up 6% on year in Dec-25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gst-collection-up-6-on-year-in-dec-25/1663187</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663187</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Goods and Service Tax or GST collections for December 2025 came at Rs.1,74,550 crores, marking a modest rise of 2.52% on month.

Goods and Service Tax or GST collections for December 2025 came at Rs.1,74,550 crores, marking a modest rise of 2.52% on month. The GST collections for December 2025 have increased compared to the previous financial year, showing a stable tax base and sustained compliance levels. Year-on-year data indicates that December 2025 collections are up by 6.1% than those of December 2024. Key components include CGST at Rs.34,289 crores, SGST at Rs.41,368 crores, IGST at Rs.98,894 crores, and Cess at Rs.4,238 crores. Refunds processed in December 2025 total Rs.28,980 crores, data showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd spurts 2.27%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/patanjali-foods-ltd-spurts-227/1663185</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663185</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Patanjali Foods Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 569.65, up 2.27% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.65. The Sensex is at 85736.3, down 0.03%. Patanjali Foods Ltd has risen around 3.98% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Patanjali Foods Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 2.16% in last one month and is currently quoting at 53078.8, up 0.54% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 10.76 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 29.03 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 573, up 2.34% on the day. Patanjali Foods Ltd is down 7.99% in last one year as compared to a 11.51% spurt in NIFTY and a 5.91% spurt in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 42.53 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RuchiSoyaInds_47333195530_704.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd spurts 3.25%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-copper-ltd-spurts-325/1663186</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663186</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Hindustan Copper Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 559.5, up 3.25% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.65. The Sensex is at 85736.3, down 0.03%. Hindustan Copper Ltd has risen around 53.92% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Hindustan Copper Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 13.28% in last one month and is currently quoting at 11421.85, up 0.59% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 361.45 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 456.49 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 91.41 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindCopper_52829551966_3898.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[State Bank of India spurts 1.11%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/state-bank-of-india-spurts-111-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1663170</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663170</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[State Bank of India gained for a fifth straight session today.

State Bank of India gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1010, up 1.11% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.05. The Sensex is at 85709.92, down 0.06%. State Bank of India has gained around 5.6% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which State Bank of India is a constituent, has gained around 1.64% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60150.95, up 0.1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 59.03 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 67.04 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1013.05, up 0.66% on the day. State Bank of India is up 30.09% in last one year as compared to a 11.5% jump in NIFTY and a 20.6% jump in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 12.93 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StBkofIndia_57185891_1375.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of Baroda gains for fifth session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-baroda-gains-for-fifth-session/1663171</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663171</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bank of Baroda is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

Bank of Baroda is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 306.95, up 0.62% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.05. The Sensex is at 85709.92, down 0.06%. Bank of Baroda has added around 7.63% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Bank of Baroda is a constituent, has added around 1.64% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60150.95, up 0.1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 116.59 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 71.92 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 308, up 0.36% on the day. Bank of Baroda is up 34.65% in last one year as compared to a 11.5% gain in NIFTY and a 20.6% gain in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 8.2 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofBaroda_23609426771_5456.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IndusInd Bank Ltd spurts 0.29%, gains for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indusind-bank-ltd-spurts-029-gains-for-five-straight-sessions/1663172</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663172</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IndusInd Bank Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

IndusInd Bank Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 905.05, up 0.29% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.05. The Sensex is at 85709.92, down 0.06%. IndusInd Bank Ltd has added around 7.56% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which IndusInd Bank Ltd is a constituent, has added around 1.64% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60150.95, up 0.1% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 12.78 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 32 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 908.8, up 0.38% on the day. IndusInd Bank Ltd is down 6.7% in last one year as compared to a 11.5% gain in NIFTY and a 20.6% gain in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndusIndBankLtd_64968625_5531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki India Ltd spurts 1.8%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-spurts-18-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1663173</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663173</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki India Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Maruti Suzuki India Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 17266, up 1.8% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.05. The Sensex is at 85709.92, down 0.06%. Maruti Suzuki India Ltd has gained around 6.67% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 5.25% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28803.65, up 0.84% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.93 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.06 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 17320, up 1.8% on the day. Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is up 46.87% in last one year as compared to a 11.5% jump in NIFTY and a 23.69% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 37.44 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MarutiSuzuki_13596837192_5496.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd soars 1.55%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-ltd-soars-155-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1663174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663174</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 6025, up 1.55% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.05. The Sensex is at 85709.92, down 0.06%. Hero MotoCorp Ltd has dropped around 2.3% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Hero MotoCorp Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 5.25% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28803.65, up 0.84% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 4.66 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.93 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 6058, up 1.51% on the day. Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up 43.36% in last one year as compared to a 11.5% spurt in NIFTY and a 23.69% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 24.71 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Uno Minda Ltd spurts 1.26%, gains for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uno-minda-ltd-spurts-126-gains-for-fifth-straight-session/1663175</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663175</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Uno Minda Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Uno Minda Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1337.8, up 1.26% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 26333.05. The Sensex is at 85709.92, down 0.06%. Uno Minda Ltd has gained around 6.33% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Uno Minda Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 5.25% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28803.65, up 0.84% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.46 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 5.59 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1342.5, up 0.95% on the day. Uno Minda Ltd is up 25.72% in last one year as compared to a 11.5% jump in NIFTY and a 23.69% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 80.35 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MindaInds_25112038741_12295.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>