<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:43:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Edutech shares gain as FM targets services sector growth & jobs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/edutech-shares-gain-as-fm-targets-services-sector-growth-jobs/1670007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670007</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of education-to-employment and enterprise companies jumped after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the setting up of a High-Powered “Education to Employment and Enterprise” Standing Committee.

Shares of education-to-employment and enterprise companies jumped after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the setting up of a High-Powered “Education to Employment and Enterprise” Standing Committee. The panel will recommend measures to strengthen the services sector as a core driver of India’s growth and global competitiveness. Shares of Virtual Global Education surged 6.38%, Physicswallah gained 2.64%, Career Point Edutech rose 1.28%, Zee Learn added 0.78%, and Aptech advanced 0.59%. In her statement, the Finance Minister said the committee will prioritise areas to optimise growth, employment, and exports. It will also assess the impact of emerging technologies, including artificial intelligence, on jobs and skill requirements, and propose measures to prepare the workforce accordingly. The initiative is aimed at positioning India as a global leader in services, targeting a 10% share of the global services market by 2047.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's fiscal deficit to be 4.3% of GDP for FY27]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-fiscal-deficit-to-be-43-of-gdp-for-fy27/1670006</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670006</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Finance Minister announced that India's Fiscal deficit retained at 4.3% of GDP for FY27.

The Finance Minister announced that India's Fiscal deficit retained at 4.3% of GDP for FY27. Finance Minister sets debt to GDP ratio for FY27 at 55.6 percent in Budget. Gross market borrowing estimated at 17.2 lakh crore, higher than estimates. Gross borrowing for FY27 proposed at Rs 17.2 trillion compared to compared to Rs 14.8 trillion in FY26. Net borrowing for FY27 pegged at Rs 11.7 trillion, a small rise from Rs 11.2 trillion in FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/global-business-growth-picture-id518037359_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Individuals residing abroad to be permitted equity investments in listed Indian firms: FM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/individuals-residing-abroad-to-be-permitted-equity-investments-in-listed-indian-firms-fm/1670004</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670004</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman said individual persons residing outside India (PROI) will be permitted equity investments in listed Indian companies through a portfolio investment scheme.

Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman said individual persons residing outside India (PROI) will be permitted equity investments in listed Indian companies through a portfolio investment scheme. She also proposed raising investment limit for PROIs to 10 per cent from 5 per cent. The finance minister also proposed making framework with suitable access to funds and derivatives on corporate bond indices.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Railway stocks gains after budget push; Govt proposes seven high-speed rail corridors]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railway-stocks-gains-after-budget-push-govt-proposes-seven-high-speed-rail-corridors/1670001</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670001</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of railway-related companies traded higher after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in the Union Budget 2026, proposed the development of seven high-speed rail corridors, signaling a strong push to modernize India’s rail infrastructure and enhance long-distance mobility.

Shares of railway-related companies traded higher after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in the Union Budget 2026, proposed the development of seven high-speed rail corridors, signaling a strong push to modernize India’s rail infrastructure and enhance long-distance mobility. Quadrant Future Tek (up 2.59%), Jupiter Wagons (up 1.24%), IRFC (up 1.10%), RITES (up 1.20%), and RailTel (up 1.08%) edged higher. The proposed corridors include Mumbai–Pune, Hyderabad–Pune, Hyderabad–Bengaluru, Chennai–Bengaluru, Delhi–Varanasi, and Varanasi–Siliguri, aimed at improving intercity connectivity, reducing travel time, and supporting economic activity across key urban and industrial clusters. The announcements were made during Sitharaman’s ninth consecutive Union Budget presentation in the Lok Sabha.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Easy Trip Planners Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/easy-trip-planners-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1669997</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669997</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shilpa Medicare Ltd, Global Health Ltd, PNC Infratech Ltd and RattanIndia Power Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 01 February 2026.

Shilpa Medicare Ltd, Global Health Ltd, PNC Infratech Ltd and RattanIndia Power Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 01 February 2026. Easy Trip Planners Ltd spiked 8.12% to Rs 6.79 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 6.02 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9.86 lakh shares in the past one month. Shilpa Medicare Ltd surged 7.09% to Rs 310.5. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.84 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9958 shares in the past one month. Global Health Ltd soared 5.82% to Rs 1116.45. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 12552 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10062 shares in the past one month. PNC Infratech Ltd added 5.65% to Rs 229. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 80853 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13406 shares in the past one month. RattanIndia Power Ltd advanced 5.52% to Rs 8.98. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 31.07 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16.07 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EasyTripPlanners_83237855.6888425_74649.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cargo stocks rally after FM proposes new dedicated freight corridor]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cargo-stocks-rally-after-fm-proposes-new-dedicated-freight-corridor/1669998</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669998</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Finance Minister also announced an increase in public capital expenditure to Rs 12.2 lakh crore in FY27 and the creation of an Infrastructure Risk Guarantee Fund to support infrastructure development.

The Finance Minister also announced an increase in public capital expenditure to Rs 12.2 lakh crore in FY27 and the creation of an Infrastructure Risk Guarantee Fund to support infrastructure development. Sitharaman said, “I propose to establish new dedicated freight corridors connecting Dankuni in the East to Surat in the West and operationalise 20 new national waterways over the next five years.” Following these announcements, logistics and cargo-related stocks rallied on the bourses. Container Corporation of India rose up to 2.99%, Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone gained 0.87%, JSW Infrastructure climbed 2.69%, Shipping Corporation of India advanced 3.24%, Allcargo Logistics added 1.63% and Delhivery rose 1.37%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[REC, Power Finance rise after Union Budget outlays proposal to overhaul power finance institutions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rec-power-finance-rise-after-union-budget-outlays-proposal-to-overhaul-power-finance-institutions/1669990</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669990</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of REC and Power Finance Corp rose after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced proposals to restructure both companies.

Shares of REC and Power Finance Corp rose after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced proposals to restructure both companies. REC (up 3.13%) and Power Finance Corporation (up 3.08%) edged higher in trade. In her latest Budget speech, the FM announced significant restructuring plans for two major power sector financial institutions. The proposed overhaul will target Power Finance Corporation and REC, marking a key policy initiative in the government's power sector strategy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM announced enhanced focus and support to SMEs and textiles]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-announced-enhanced-focus-and-support-to-smes-and-textiles/1669982</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669982</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Budget for FY27 proposes Rs 10,000 crore fund for SME growth to create champions among MSMEs.

Union Budget for FY27 proposes Rs 10,000 crore fund for SME growth to create champions among MSMEs. The FM proposes a three-pronged approach to help MSMEs grow - equity support via MSME growth fund. FM also proposes to top up self-reliant Indian Fund with Rs 2,000 crore. FM announces textile labour incentive scheme and national handloom and handicrafts programme and setting up mega textile parks in challenge mode. Mega textile parks will be set up to enhance scale, efficiency and competitiveness in the sector. FM proposes scheme to strengthen khadi and handicrafts textiles and said Mahatma Gandhi Gram Swaraj Initiative to be launched.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade higher; metal shares decline for 2-day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-higher-metal-shares-decline-for-2-day/1669981</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669981</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with modest gains amid the ongoing Budget 2026 proceedings.

The key equity indices traded with modest gains amid the ongoing Budget 2026 proceedings. Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to do so. Reform-oriented announcements by the finance minister boosted investor sentiment. Metal shares skid as gold and silver prices slide; index plunges for a second consecutive session. At 11:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex rose 314.85 points or 0.38% to 82,529.21. The Nifty 50 index added 62.80 points or 0.21% to 25,372.25. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index rose 0.05% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index declined 0.19%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,443 shares rose and 1,319 shares fell. A total of 210 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 2.56% to 13.98. MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 5.06% to Rs 1,42,075, while MCX Silver futures for the same settlement declined 8.09% to Rs 2,68,295. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index declined 1.88% to 11,604.85. The index tumbled 7% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Copper (down 10.93%), Hindustan Zinc (down 9.26%), National Aluminium Company (down 8.47%), Hindalco Industries (down 3.97%) and Jindal Stainless (down 2.56%), Vedanta (down 2.27%), NMDC (down 0.17%), Tata Steel (down 0.07%), Adani Enterprises (down 0.07%) declined. Union Budget 2026 Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman is presenting her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to deliver nine budgets in a row. She said Budget 2026–27 was prepared at Kartavya Bhavan and was being presented amid a challenging global environment where trade and multilateralism have become increasingly important. Reflecting on the government’s record, she said India’s economic trajectory over the past 12 years has been marked by fiscal discipline, moderate inflation and sustained growth, even during periods of global uncertainty and disruption. Outlining the policy roadmap, the finance minister proposed interventions across six broad areas, including scaling up manufacturing in strategic and frontier sectors, rejuvenating legacy industries, creating champion MSMEs, delivering a strong push to infrastructure, ensuring long-term security and stability, and developing city-centric economic regions. She said Aatmanirbharta has remained the guiding principle of policymaking, with a focus on building domestic manufacturing capacity, strengthening energy security and reducing critical import dependencies, while implementing reforms to support employment, agricultural productivity, household purchasing power and universal service delivery. These measures, she said, have helped sustain economic growth of around 7% and reduce poverty. Emphasising reform over rhetoric and people over populism, she said the government has pursued structural reforms, fiscal prudence and monetary stability, alongside a strong thrust on public investment. She also announced the Rs 10,000 crore Biopharma Shakti initiative over five years to develop India as a global biopharma manufacturing hub, including plans to expand NIPER institutions, build a nationwide network of clinical trial sites and strengthen the Central Drugs Standard Control Organisation to global standards. Continuing her speech, the finance minister said the government will launch ISM 2.0 to boost domestic production of equipment and materials, enable full-stack design based on Indian intellectual property, strengthen supply chains, and promote industry-led research, training and skill development. Stocks in Spotlight: NTPC rose 0.20% after the company reported an 8.27% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 5,597.05 crore, supported by a 1.72% rise in net sales to Rs 45,845.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. MPS rose 3.13% after the company said it has agreed to acquire a 100% stake in Unbound Medicine, marking its entry into the healthcare and medical information technology segment. Meesho fell 4.97% after the company's consolidated net loss widened to Rs 490.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 37.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter. Global Markets: On Friday, stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mining stocks advance after Govt announces push to rare earth sector in Union Budget ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mining-stocks-advance-after-govt-announces-push-to-rare-earth-sector-in-union-budget/1669977</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669977</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Union Budget 2026-27, which is currently being presented by the Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, has announced a proposal to develop a major rare earth corridor in the country.

The Union Budget 2026-27, which is currently being presented by the Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, has announced a proposal to develop a major rare earth corridor in the country. Shares of Permanent Magnets (up 9.02%), Maithan Alloys (up 3.86%), Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (up 3.74%), Orissa Minerals Development Company (up 2.16%) Mishra Dhatu Nigam (up 1.44%) and Indian Metals & Ferro Alloys (up 1.17%) edged higher. In her latest Budget speech, the FM said that a scheme for rare earth permanent magnets was launched in 2025 November. “We now propose to support the mineral-rich states of Odisha, Kerala, Andhra Pradesh and Tamil Nadu to establish dedicated rare earth corridors,” the FM said. The government is expanding its rare earth scheme to promote mining, processing, research and manufacturing.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Textile stocks rally as FM announces mega textile parks, integrated schemes in budget 2026–27]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/textile-stocks-rally-as-fm-announces-mega-textile-parks-integrated-schemes-in-budget-202627/1669973</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669973</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Textile stocks surged after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in Union Budget 2026–27, announced plans to set up mega textile parks aimed at promoting khadi, silk, and other textile segments.

Textile stocks surged after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in Union Budget 2026–27, announced plans to set up mega textile parks aimed at promoting khadi, silk, and other textile segments. The budget proposed the development of Rare Earth Corridors to strengthen mineral supply chains and support industrial growth. Shares of Gokaldas Exports jumped 5.09%, Pearl Global Industries gained 4.89%, Welspun Living rose 3.31%, Arvind advanced 3.32%, K.P.R. Mill climbed 3.06%, and Vardhman Textiles added 1.40%. The Finance Minister unveiled a slew of supportive measures for the textile sector, signalling the government’s intent to boost competitiveness and scale in one of India’s key manufacturing industries. The announcements come against the backdrop of former US President Donald Trump’s proposal to impose a 50% tariff, which could impact global textile trade. Market participants said the timing of the policy push is a proactive step to cushion the domestic textile industry amid evolving international trade dynamics. For the labour-intensive textile sector, the Finance Minister outlined an integrated five-part programme. The National Fibre Scheme aims to promote self-reliance in natural fibres such as silk, wool, and jute, as well as man-made and new-age fibres. The Textile Expansion and Employment Scheme seeks to modernise traditional clusters with capital support for machinery, technology upgradation, and common testing and certification centres. The National Handloom and Handicraft Programme will integrate and strengthen existing schemes to provide targeted support for weavers and artisans. The Text-ECON initiative will promote globally competitive and sustainable textiles and apparel, while SAMARTH 2.0 will modernise and upgrade the textile skilling ecosystem through collaboration with industry and academic institutions. The Finance Minister also proposed setting up mega textile parks in challenge mode, with a focus on value addition in technical textiles. Additionally, the Mahatma Gandhi Gram Swaraj initiative will strengthen handloom and handicrafts by enhancing global market linkages, branding, training, skilling, and quality processes. These measures are expected to benefit weavers, village industries, the One District One Product (ODOP) initiative, and rural youth, reinforcing India’s long-term strategy for sustainable growth in the textile sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Electronics manufacturing stocks rally after budget boost; Govt hikes outlay to Rs 40,000 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/electronics-manufacturing-stocks-rally-after-budget-boost-govt-hikes-outlay-to-rs-40000-cr/1669974</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669974</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of electronics manufacturing companies rallied after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in the Union Budget 2026, announced a Rs 40,000 crore allocation for the electronics components manufacturing scheme, significantly strengthening the outlook for India’s domestic electronics ecosystem.

Shares of electronics manufacturing companies rallied after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, in the Union Budget 2026, announced a Rs 40,000 crore allocation for the electronics components manufacturing scheme, significantly strengthening the outlook for India’s domestic electronics ecosystem. Dixon Technologies (up 4.26%), Amber Enterprises (up 5.59%), Syrma SGS Technology (up 4.07%), Kaynes Technology (up 3.73%), PG Electroplast (up 2.75%), Cyient DLM (up 1.04%), Avalon Technologies (up 3.25%), CG Power and Industrial Solutions (up 5.17%), and Amber Enterprises India (up 5.12%) edged higher. The rally was further supported by the government’s announcement of India Semiconductor Mission 2.0, aimed at strengthening semiconductor supply chains and promoting Indian stack IP-based semiconductors. The government proposed a sharp increase in the scheme outlay to Rs 40,000 crore from Rs 24,900 crore, underscoring its focus on scaling up domestic electronics manufacturing. The announcements were made during Sitharaman’s ninth consecutive Union Budget presentation in the Lok Sabha.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM announces CAPEX of Rs 12.02 lakh crore for FY27]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-announces-capex-of-rs-1202-lakh-crore-for-fy27/1669971</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669971</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India earmarks capex of Rs 12.02 lakh crore in FY27, Nirmala Sitharaman stated in her budget speech, keeping the overall momentum in infrastructure spending supported.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/colorful-infographic-chart-of-businessrelated-elements-pict_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GST collection rises 6.2% on year in Jan-26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gst-collection-rises-62-on-year-in-jan-26/1669970</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669970</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gross Goods and Services Tax (GST) revenue witnessed a 6.2% annualized increase in January 2026.

Gross Goods and Services Tax (GST) revenue witnessed a 6.2% annualized increase in January 2026. The total collections were Rs 1,93,384 crore, compared to Rs 1,82,094 crore in January 2025 after proportionately adjusting compensation cess amount of Rs 7,241 crore for a correct annualized comparison), according to government officials, who requested anonymity. The net GST collection in January 2026 after refunds was Rs 1,70,719 crore compared to Rs 1,58,701 crore in January 2025, marking 7.6% growth.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/concept-money-and-small-tree-in-jar-and-sunshine-picture-id_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's capex increased to Rs.12.2 lakh crore to continue infra growth momentum]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-capex-increased-to-rs122-lakh-crore-to-continue-infra-growth-momentum/1669969</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669969</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The FM announced capital expenditure to be increased to Rs 12.2 lakh crore to continue momentum in infrastructure spending.

The FM announced capital expenditure to be increased to Rs 12.2 lakh crore to continue momentum in infrastructure spending. FM proposes infrastructure risk guarantee fund for credit guarantee for lenders. India to establish new dedicated freight corridors. The FM proposes to recycle assets of CPSE by setting up dedicated REITs. FM proposes to operationalize 20 new waterways starting with one in Odisha. FM proposes developing seven high speed rail corridors between cities - Mumbai to Pune, Pune to Hyderabad, Hyderabad to Chennai, Delhi to Varanasi, Varanasi to Siliguri. Public capital expenditure has increased manifold, from Rs two lakh crore in 2014-15 to an allocation of Rs 11.2 lakh crore in BE 25-26. In this coming year, that is financial year 2026-27 Budget proposes to increase it to Rs 12.2 lakh crore, to continue the momentum.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-buildings-2-1210278_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pharma shares advance after Union Budget announces measures to promote domestic biopharma sector ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pharma-shares-advance-after-union-budget-announces-measures-to-promote-domestic-biopharma-sector/1669965</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669965</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Union Budget 2026-27, which is currently being presented by the Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, has announced significant measures to promote the biopharma sector in the country.

The Union Budget 2026-27, which is currently being presented by the Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, has announced significant measures to promote the biopharma sector in the country. The Nifty Pharma index added 0.51% to 21,824.80 while the benchmark Nifty 50 index gained 0.35% to 25,408.85. Among the pharma stocks, Biocon (up 2.10%), Sun Pharma (up 1.74%), Piramal Pharma (up 1.27%), Torrent Pharma (up 1.13%), Dr Reddys Labs (up 1.08%), Zydus Life (up 0.79%), Cipla (up 0.76%), Mankind Pharma (up 0.74%) and Glan Pharma (up 0.60%) advanced. In her latest Budget speech, the FM said that the BioPharma Strategy for Health Advancement through knowledge, technology and innovation will strengthen India’s digital ecosystem in healthcare. “India's digital disease burden is observed to be shifting towards non-communicable diseases like diabetes, cancer and autoimmune disorders. Biologic medicines are key to longevity and quality of life at affordable costs. To develop India as a global biopharma manufacturing hub, I proposed the Biopharma Shakti with an outlay of Rs 10,000 crores over the next five years. This will build the ecosystem. For domestic production of biologics and biosimilars, the strategy will include a biopharma-focused network with three new national institutes of pharmaceutical education and research, popularly known as NIPERS, and upgrading seven existing ones. It will also create a network of 1,000 accredited India clinical trials sites. We propose to strengthen the Central Drug Standard Control Organisation to meet global standards and approve timeframes through a dedicated scientific review and specialists,” the FM said.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM increases electronic components manufacturing scheme outlay to Rs. 40,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-increases-electronic-components-manufacturing-scheme-outlay-to-rs-40000-crore/1669966</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669966</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[FM has proposed Bio Pharma Shakti with a proposal of Rs 10,000 crore for next 5 years.

FM has proposed Bio Pharma Shakti with a proposal of Rs 10,000 crore for next 5 years. Futhermore, Electronic Components Manufacturing Scheme outlay increased to Rs 40,000 crore. The FM also announced Rare earth permanent scheme. Tamil Nadu to be supported for rare earth corridor among other states. The government has proposed to support states like Orissa, Kerala, Andhra, Tamil Nadu to establish critical mineral corridors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/mineral-oil-297487__340_crude_oil.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UPI transactions hit record high of Rs 28.33 lakh crore in January]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/upi-transactions-hit-record-high-of-rs-2833-lakh-crore-in-january/1669963</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669963</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Transactions through the popular Unified Payments Interface (UPI) touched a record Rs 28.33 lakh crore and 21.70 billion in value and volume terms, respectively, in January, according to data released by the National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI).

Transactions through the popular Unified Payments Interface (UPI) touched a record Rs 28.33 lakh crore and 21.70 billion in value and volume terms, respectively, in January, according to data released by the National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI). NPCI said the value of transactions was at Rs 27.97 lakh crore in December. On a month-on-month basis, the growth was 21 per cent in value terms.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pencil-1468274_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM proposes scheme for container manufacturing]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-proposes-scheme-for-container-manufacturing/1669960</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669960</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Finance Minister, Nirmala Sitharaman, proposed a scheme for container manufacturing.

The Finance Minister, Nirmala Sitharaman, proposed a scheme for container manufacturing. A scheme for enhancement of construction and infrastructure equipment, will be introduced to strengthen domestic manufacturing of high value and technologically advanced CIE. The container manufacturing scheme will have a outlay of Rs 10,000 crore over 5 years. FM proposes an integrated plan for labour intensive sector of textiles.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/ship-71423__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Timken India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-timken-india-ltd-counter/1669957</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669957</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Intellect Design Arena Ltd, Delhivery Ltd, NTPC Green Energy Ltd, Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 01 February 2026.

Intellect Design Arena Ltd, Delhivery Ltd, NTPC Green Energy Ltd, Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 01 February 2026. Timken India Ltd clocked volume of 41519 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 49.94 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 831 shares. The stock gained 1.37% to Rs.2,979.40. Volumes stood at 1506 shares in the last session. Intellect Design Arena Ltd registered volume of 40804 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 3.42 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 11927 shares. The stock slipped 7.01% to Rs.848.00. Volumes stood at 10190 shares in the last session. Delhivery Ltd saw volume of 5.43 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 2.53 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.15 lakh shares. The stock increased 1.36% to Rs.428.25. Volumes stood at 14.24 lakh shares in the last session. NTPC Green Energy Ltd saw volume of 9.53 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 2.15 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 4.43 lakh shares. The stock increased 4.12% to Rs.89.76. Volumes stood at 8.76 lakh shares in the last session. Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd saw volume of 6.39 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 1.71 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.74 lakh shares. The stock dropped 12.91% to Rs.2,198.90. Volumes stood at 4.75 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimkenIndia_38040425983_2226.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>