<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:43:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Safari Industries (India) Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/safari-industries-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1675880</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675880</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[KPIT Technologies Ltd, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Birlasoft Ltd and Ashapura Minechem Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 February 2026.

KPIT Technologies Ltd, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Birlasoft Ltd and Ashapura Minechem Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 12 February 2026. Safari Industries (India) Ltd crashed 6.93% to Rs 1840 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 11704 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1980 shares in the past one month. KPIT Technologies Ltd tumbled 6.66% to Rs 895.2. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62107 shares in the past one month. AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd lost 6.51% to Rs 360.95. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6543 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11698 shares in the past one month. Birlasoft Ltd slipped 6.16% to Rs 436.25. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.06 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 96252 shares in the past one month. Ashapura Minechem Ltd shed 6.16% to Rs 587.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 41881 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 66563 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SafariInds_98893928962_710.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian AI market expected to grow to US$131.31 billion by 2032 from US$7.63 billion in 2024]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-ai-market-expected-to-grow-to-us13131-billion-by-2032-from-us763-billion-in-2024/1675879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675879</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Government stated in a latest update that India is in the first group of AI-ready nations, with systematic progress across all five layers of the AI architecture applications, models, chips, infrastructure and energy.

Government stated in a latest update that India is in the first group of AI-ready nations, with systematic progress across all five layers of the AI architecture applications, models, chips, infrastructure and energy. The report published by CCI (Competition Commission of India) cites that the global market size of AI has increased from USD 103.6 billion in 2020 to USD 288.8 billion in 2024. During the same period, the AI market in India has expanded from USD 2.97 billion to USD 7.63 billion. The Indian AI market is expected to grow to USD 131.31 billion by 2032 at a CAGR of 42.2%. India’s rapid digital transformation is being underpinned by strong foundational infrastructure, with data centres and widespread internet connectivity emerging as critical enablers of cloud adoption, AI deployment, and data-driven governance across the country.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-1549702_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bullion dips below $5100; consolidation seen ahead]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bullion-dips-below-5100-consolidation-seen-ahead/1675881</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675881</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices lost steam and slipped below $5100 per ounce in the Asia electronic trades, with the metal seen consolidating in a narrow range after hitting historical highs of $ 5626.8 on January 29th.

Gold prices lost steam and slipped below $5100 per ounce in the Asia electronic trades, with the metal seen consolidating in a narrow range after hitting historical highs of $ 5626.8 on January 29th. The counter trimmed yesterday’s gains as investors pared back expectations for Federal Reserve policy easing. Strength in the US dollar post stronger-than-expected US labor market data that reduced the likelihood of near-term Federal Reserve rate cuts also pulled the yellow metal lower today. Data released Wednesday showed nonfarm payrolls increased by 130,000 in January, the largest gain in more than a year, while the unemployment rate unexpectedly declined to 4.3%. MCX April 2 delivery futures were down 0.3% at Rs 158211 per 10 grams. More losses can be expected in the yellow metal and other precious metals, following the consolidation phase going on post the historic highs attained late last month. Investors are now awaiting Friday’s US consumer price index report for further insights.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suryalakshmi-cotton-mills-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1675845</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675845</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Khandwala Securities Ltd, Unitech Ltd, Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd and Network People Services Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 February 2026.

Khandwala Securities Ltd, Unitech Ltd, Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd and Network People Services Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 12 February 2026. Suryalakshmi Cotton Mills Ltd crashed 16.31% to Rs 61 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1228 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 694 shares in the past one month. Khandwala Securities Ltd tumbled 11.71% to Rs 18.7. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1553 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5679 shares in the past one month. Unitech Ltd lost 10.58% to Rs 5.58. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 25.68 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.95 lakh shares in the past one month. Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd slipped 9.26% to Rs 332.75. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1942 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1071 shares in the past one month. Network People Services Technologies Ltd shed 8.75% to Rs 1252.95. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3320 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1083 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuryalakCott_55522786721_1952.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade with significant losses; media shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-with-significant-losses-media-shares-tumble/1675843</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675843</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking. Sentiment remained subdued due to the expiry of BSE derivatives contracts and FII selling, prompting a shift toward a risk-off approach. The Nifty hovered below the 25,850 mark. Oil & gas shares tumbled after rallying for four consecutive trading sessions. Media shares declined after advancing in the past three trading sessions. At 14:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 455.46 points or 0.54% to 83,772.58. The Nifty 50 index fell 127.90 points or 0.49% to 25,824.55. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.55% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.67%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,675 shares rose and 2,448 shares fell. A total of 187 shares were unchanged. Direct Tax Collection : The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index declined 1.13% to 1476.70. the index increased 7.4% in the past three trading sessions. Network 18 Media & Investments (down 2.96%), PVR Inox (down 2.86%), Saregama India (down 2.52%), Prime Focus (down 2.41%) and Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 1.97%) were the top losers. Among the other losers were Sun TV Network (down 1.48%), Tips Music (down 1.09%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 1.07%), D B Corp (down 0.84%) and Nazara Technologies (down 0.07%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper fell 0.01% to 6.709 compared with previous session close of 6.710. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6125 compared with its close of 90.7800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 0.42% to Rs 158,083. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.05% to 96.87. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.17% to 4.179. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 11 cents or 0.16% to $69.51 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Hindalco Industries shed 0.48%. The company said its wholly owned subsidiary Novelis Inc. has provided an update on the twin fire incidents at its Oswego plant in New York that occurred in September and November 2025. Novelis estimates the total free cash flow impact at $1.3-1.6 billion, which includes repair costs, operational downtime, working capital timing and other related expenses. The company said 70-80% of the free cash flow and adjusted EBITDA impact is expected to be recoverable through insurance, subject to policy terms, conditions and potential coverage disputes. No firm estimate for insurance recovery has been accrued at this stage. The Oswego hot mill is expected to restart by late Q2 calendar 2026. Meanwhile, Novelis reported its Q3 earnings. The Hindalco subsidiary reported a net loss attributable to common shareholders of $160 million, compared with a net income of $110 million in the prior year, Net sales rose 3% YoY to $4.2 billion. Jupiter Wagons slipped 3.60% after its consolidated net profit tanked 35.28% to Rs 62.99 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 97.33 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 13.54% YoY to Rs 890.36 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Bombay Dyeing & Manufacturing Company declined 2.32% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 9.85 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 70.06 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 21.9% year-on-year to Rs 324.02 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Abbott India Q3 PAT jumps 4% YoY to Rs 376 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/abbott-india-q3-pat-jumps-4-yoy-to-rs-376-cr/1675842</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675842</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 508.98 crore in Q3 FY26, up 4.38% year on year (YoY).

Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 508.98 crore in Q3 FY26, up 4.38% year on year (YoY). Total expenses increased 7.20% to Rs 1,284.82 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,198.44 crore posted in same quarter last year. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 147.31 crore (up 26.88% YoY), employee benefit expense was at Rs 196.07 crore (up 45.58% YoY) and finance cost was at Rs 5.48 crore (up 142.47% YoY) during the period under review. Abbott India is one of the leading multinational pharmaceutical companies in India and sells its products through independent distributors primarily within India. Shares of Abbott India fell 1.06% to currently trade at Rs 26,609.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AbbottIndia_90273760573_90.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IT stocks tumble as AI disruption fears deepen; Nifty IT down over 5%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/it-stocks-tumble-as-ai-disruption-fears-deepen-nifty-it-down-over-5/1675841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675841</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The sharp decline followed the launch of a new artificial intelligence tool by US-based startup Anthropic, which recently introduced a product tailored for corporate legal teams.

The sharp decline followed the launch of a new artificial intelligence tool by US-based startup Anthropic, which recently introduced a product tailored for corporate legal teams. The company, known for its Claude chatbot, said the tool can automate functions such as contract reviews, non-disclosure agreement triage, compliance workflows, legal brief preparation and standardised responses. The development intensified investor concerns about the potential impact of AI automation on outsourcing-driven business models. Among major IT stocks, Coforge declined 6.31%, Oracle Financial Services Software fell 5.65%, and LTIMindtree dropped 5.63%. Infosys lost 5.58%, while Tata Consultancy Services fell 5.39%. Tech Mahindra declined 5.30%, Persistent Systems slipped 4.87%, and Mphasis dropped 4.56%. Wipro fell 4.25%, while HCL Technologies declined 3.99%. The sector was also weighed down by stronger-than-expected US jobs data, which dampened expectations of near-term interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve and added to investor caution toward export-oriented technology stocks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude nears $65 per barrel in Asia]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-nears-65-per-barrel-in-asia/1675840</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675840</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil prices edged higher toward $65 per barrel in early electronic trade on Thursday, as rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran sparked fresh supply concerns.

Oil prices edged higher toward $65 per barrel in early electronic trade on Thursday, as rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran sparked fresh supply concerns. Markets remain alert to the risk of disruptions to Iranian output or key shipping routes amid heightened rhetoric from Washington. US President Donald Trump said talks with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu produced no definitive agreement on the Iran issue, though negotiations with Tehran would continue. Earlier this week, Trump said the US may consider deploying a second aircraft carrier to the Middle East if talks fail, even as indirect US-Iran discussions resumed in Oman. The timing of the next round of talks remains unclear. Meanwhile, OPEC kept its global oil demand growth forecasts unchanged at 1.38 million bpd for 2026 and 1.34 million bpd for 2027, while maintaining its non-OPEC supply outlook. Investors now await the IEA’s monthly report later in the day, which could again point to a global supply surplus. In the domestic market, MCX February crude oil futures slipped below Rs 5,900 per barrel, down 0.34%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-in-morning-picture-id637134984_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Godrej Agrovet Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-godrej-agrovet-ltd-counter/1675827</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675827</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finolex Industries Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd, SJVN Ltd, Elgi Equipments Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 12 February 2026.

Finolex Industries Ltd, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd, SJVN Ltd, Elgi Equipments Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 12 February 2026. Godrej Agrovet Ltd clocked volume of 62.29 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 24.43 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 2.55 lakh shares. The stock gained 8.82% to Rs.643.45. Volumes stood at 1.81 lakh shares in the last session. Finolex Industries Ltd saw volume of 80.81 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 21.72 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.72 lakh shares. The stock increased 6.10% to Rs.192.60. Volumes stood at 5.14 lakh shares in the last session. Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd registered volume of 43.26 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.9 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.72 lakh shares. The stock rose 3.65% to Rs.1,373.00. Volumes stood at 7 lakh shares in the last session. SJVN Ltd registered volume of 429.84 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.26 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 68.62 lakh shares. The stock rose 1.27% to Rs.78.36. Volumes stood at 268.63 lakh shares in the last session. Elgi Equipments Ltd saw volume of 36.68 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.39 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.81 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.49% to Rs.514.85. Volumes stood at 2.45 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejAgrovetLtd_16027601587_16166.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindalco updates on Novelis Oswego plant fire; estimates $1.3-1.6 bn cash flow impact]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindalco-updates-on-novelis-oswego-plant-fire-estimates-13-16-bn-cash-flow-impact/1675807</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675807</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Novelis estimates the total free cash flow impact at $1.3-1.6 billion, which includes repair costs, operational downtime, working capital timing and other related expenses.

Novelis estimates the total free cash flow impact at $1.3-1.6 billion, which includes repair costs, operational downtime, working capital timing and other related expenses. The company said 70-80% of the free cash flow and adjusted EBITDA impact is expected to be recoverable through insurance, subject to policy terms, conditions and potential coverage disputes. No firm estimate for insurance recovery has been accrued at this stage. The Oswego hot mill is expected to restart by late Q2 calendar 2026. Novelis said it is working with customers and leveraging its global operations and external suppliers to mitigate the impact during the restoration period. Meanwhile, Novelis reported its Q3 earnings. The Hindalco subsidiary reported a net loss attributable to common shareholders of $160 million, compared with a net income of $110 million in the prior year, largely due to the fires at its Oswego, US plant in September and November. Net sales rose 3% YoY to $4.2 billion. Production disruptions at Oswego led to rolled product shipments being about 72 kilotonnes lower than expected, resulting in an estimated pre-tax negative impact of $54 million on adjusted EBITDA and net loss. Overall, net loss was further weighed down by $327 million in pre-tax fire-related losses. Adjusted EBITDA stood at $348 million, down 5% YoY, impacted by an estimated $54 million hit from the Oswego fires and $34 million from tariffs. It received a $750 million equity infusion received from the parent company in December 2025 to support operations and recovery efforts. Novelis said underlying market fundamentals remain positive, with strong growth expected to continue in beverage packaging and favourable trends emerging in the scrap market. The company highlighted that controllable actions are driving improvements in adjusted EBITDA per tonne, supported by a cost-efficiency programme that is delivering positive results and a higher FY26 savings outlook, while its tariff mitigation plan remains on track. Novelis added that it is deploying full resources towards the recovery of the Oswego facility to minimise customer disruption, while also making significant progress on its ongoing US investment at Bay Minette. Hindalco Industries is the metals flagship company of the Aditya Birla Group. Hindalco is the world’s largest aluminium company by revenues and the world’s second-largest copper rod manufacturer (outside China). It operates across the value chain, from bauxite mining, alumina refining, coal mining, captive power plants and aluminium smelting to downstream rolling, extrusions, and foils. Along with its subsidiary Novelis, Hindalco is the global leader in flat-rolled products and the world’s largest recycler of aluminium. HIndalco will announce Q3 results later today, 12 February 2026. The company's consolidated net profit rose 21.30% to Rs 4,741 crore while revenue from operations grew 13.5% YoY to Rs 66,058 crore in Q2 September 2025. Shares of Hindalco Industries were down 0.41% at Rs 961.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindalcoInds_40254437488_252.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market under pressure; European mrkt advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-under-pressure-european-mrkt-advance/1675849</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675849</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking.

The key equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the mid-afternoon trade, weighed down by profit booking. Sentiment remained subdued due to the expiry of BSE derivatives contracts and FII selling, prompting a shift toward a risk-off approach. The Nifty traded below the 25,900 level. Barring consumer durables all the sectoral indices on the NSE were traded in red with IT, Oi& gas and Realty leading the fall. At 13:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 366.25 points or 0.43% to 83,867.39. The Nifty 50 index fell 93.30 points or 0.36% to 25,860.55. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 0.68% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.90%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,675 shares rose and 2,448 shares fell. A total of 187 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Bajaj Finance (up 2.32%), Eicher Motors (up 2.07%), Shirram Finance (up 1.75%), ICICI Bank (up 1.46%) and Trent (up 1.20%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Tech Mahindra (down 5.56%), Infosys (down 5.47%), TCS (down 5.45%), Wipro (down 4.46%) and HCl Technologies (down 4.34%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Direct Tax Collection : The central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. Stocks in Spotlight: SJVN rose 4.59% after the company reported a 50.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 224.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 149.03 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations surged 61.2% year-on-year to Rs 1,081.97 crore during the quarter under review, up from Rs 670.99 crore in the corresponding period last year. Zydus Lifesciences rose 2.25% after the company announced a settlement agreement with Astellas Pharma Inc. in relation to Myrbetriq (generic name: Mirabegron) in the United States. Lenskart Solutions surged 11.35% after the company reported 237.9% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 132.7 crore on a 37.4% rise in revenue to Rs 2,307.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Bombay Dyeing & Manufacturing Company declined 3.33% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 9.85 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 70.06 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 21.9% year-on-year to Rs 324.02 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global market: European market advanced as investors assessed another big batch of earnings reports. Most Asian market advanced on Thursday, buoyed by Japan’s post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Japanese stocks extending its post-election rally to fresh highs, fueled by renewed confidence in domestic politics and the ruling administration’s economic agenda. Media reports noted that Takaichi’s snap-election landslide gives her an unusually strong, multi-year mandate to execute policy, which they view as broadly supportive for Japan’s markets and corporate sector. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day win streak after a better-than-expected January jobs report. The blue-chip index lost 66.74 points, or 0.13%, and closed at 50,121.40. The S&P 500 was nearly flat at 6,941.47. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 0.16% to end at 23,066.47. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000. Strong labor market has reduced the odds for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The jobs report follows weaker-than-expected consumer data released on Tuesday. That report showed that consumer spending in December was flat, missing the 0.4% monthly gain expected from economists polled by Dow Jones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IDFC First Bank Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/idfc-first-bank-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1675804</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675804</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IDFC First Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

IDFC First Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 82.29, down 0.33% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 25851.6. The Sensex is at 83790.38, down 0.53%.IDFC First Bank Ltd has eased around 0.81% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which IDFC First Bank Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 2.09% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60745.35, up 0.13% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 80.65 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 253.99 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 82.44, down 0.35% on the day. IDFC First Bank Ltd jumped 33.83% in last one year as compared to a 12.25% rally in NIFTY and a 23.22% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 43.67 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDFCBank_27126132357_54759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[REC Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rec-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1675805</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675805</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[REC Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

REC Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 351.75, down 0.62% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.39% on the day, quoting at 25851.6. The Sensex is at 83790.38, down 0.53%.REC Ltd has lost around 4.13% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which REC Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 2.9% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28276.95, up 0.39% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 31.94 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 119.02 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 352.2, down 0.87% on the day. REC Ltd tumbled 14.13% in last one year as compared to a 12.25% rally in NIFTY and a 21.98% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 5.43 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RECLtd_11504702_18075.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jupiter Wagons slides as Q3 PAT slumps 35% YoY to Rs 63 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jupiter-wagons-slides-as-q3-pat-slumps-35-yoy-to-rs-63-cr/1675806</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675806</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 13.54% YoY to Rs 890.36 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations fell 13.54% YoY to Rs 890.36 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax declined 33.09% to Rs 86.82 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 129.60 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter last year. EBITDA stood at Rs 116 crore in Q3 FY26, down 22.4% YoY. EBITDA margin declined to 13% in Q3 FY26 as against 14.4% posted in Q3 FY25. As of 31st Decemeber 2025, the company's order book stands at Rs 5,041 crore. Vivek Lohia, Managing Director of Jupiter Wagons, said, “During Q3 FY26, the Company witnessed further improvement in performance with consolidated revenues of Rs 890 crore, representing a sequential growth of 13% quarter-on-quarter compared to Q2 and Consolidated EBITDA increasing by 11% QoQ to Rs 116 crore, reflecting stable execution and operational resilience despite ongoing industry headwinds. For the nine months ending December 2025, consolidated revenues were Rs 2,136 crore, with EBITDA of Rs 279 crore and Profit After Tax of Rs 139 crore. On the supply side, while wheelset supply has improved from its peak shortage in first few months of the year, Industry continues to face constraints in wheelsets supply chain affecting wagon production and dispatch cycles which is expected to continue for next few quarters till the time our integrated wheelsets plant commences operation, which is expected by end of year, thereby helping in securing steady supply and production levels. Despite these near-term challenges, Jupiter continues to maintain healthy order books, especially from private customers, underlining strong customer confidence. The policy environment remains supportive. The announcement of a new freight corridor in the Union Budget and railway ministry maintaining its procurement estimates at approx. 32,000 wagons reinforces the long-term demand for freight rolling stock and associated components. Within the railways segment, in addition to freight wagons, we continue to witness steady growth in our products like Wheelsets, Brake Discs, CMS Crossing etc, and are actively pursuing opportunities to enhance our share in the Passenger Segment In addition, recent positive developments towards strengthening trade agreements with the EU and the US are expected to open up sizeable export opportunities for Indian railway engineering products—particularly in high-value components such as wheelsets, brake discs, and allied systems—where we are well positioned to target European and other international market through our JVs, subsidiaries and global partnerships. Our commercial vehicle and container sales recorded healthy growth during the year and following the recent PLI announcement and Rs 10,000 Crore budgetary allocation, segment is well positioned for accelerated growth over the coming years. Jupiter, being one of the leading manufacturers for containers, is well positioned to benefit from these initiatives. Our wheelsets business is witnessing steady growth and has healthy orderbook for wheelsets and Axle supply across different applications - Freight wagons, LHB coaches, Metro applications, Vande Baharat train, etc. The Odisha railwheel facility—a key structural initiative aimed at addressing this constraint—is progressing as planned and is expected to commence production by year-end. This will materially enhance supply chain resilience and support higher throughput across both wagon and component manufacturing. Our Battery business, especially the Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) segment gained further traction, reflected in initial deployments and incremental additions to the order book. We have commissioned an additional cell-to-battery manufacturing line in Indore, thereby increasing our capacity to meet the growing demand opportunities. Looking ahead, Company is also preparing for a entry into the passenger rolling stock segment and is in advance stage of engagement with a leading European partner, further details of which shall be shared at an appropriate time. While near-term challenges persist due to supply chain constraints, our fundamentals remain strong. With healthy order book, policy tailwinds, diversified business and strategic capacity expansion underway we remain confident about the Company’s long term growth trajectory and are well placed to leverage opportunities across both domestic and global markets to scale our business and drive sustained, long-term value creation.” Jupiter Wagons (JWL) is a provider of comprehensive mobility solutions, with diverse offerings across Freight Wagons, Locomotives, Passenger Coaches (LHB), Braking Systems, Metro Coach, Commercial Vehicles, ISO Marine Containers, and products such as Couplers, Draft Gears, Bogies, and CMS Crossings, Brake Disc, Brake System, Wheels, Axles and Wheel sets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CommercialEng_80068172090_39220.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bombay Dyeing slumps on reporting dismal Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bombay-dyeing-slumps-on-reporting-dismal-q3-performance/1675801</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675801</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations declined 21.9% year-on-year to Rs 324.02 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations declined 21.9% year-on-year to Rs 324.02 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company reported a loss before tax of Rs 12.64 crore in Q3 FY26, as against a profit before tax of Rs 93.91 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses declined 11.17% year-on-year to Rs 362.43 crore during the quarter. The cost of raw materials fell 26.78% to Rs 204.10 crore, while employee benefit expenses surged 451.07% YoY to Rs 48.99 crore. Meanwhile, the company announced the resignation of Khiroda Jena, chief financial officer & chief risk officer (CFO & CRO) and key managerial personnel of the company, effective from the closure of business hours on 13 February, 2026. Bombay Dyeing & Manufacturing Company is currently engaged in the business of real estate development, polyester staple fiber, and retail (textiles).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BombayDyeing_52736991153_85.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LG Electronics India edges lower after weak Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lg-electronics-india-edges-lower-after-weak-q3-performance/1675800</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675800</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[EBITDA declined by 42.4% to Rs 196 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 340 crore in Q3 FY25.

EBITDA declined by 42.4% to Rs 196 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 340 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 151.69 crore, down by 52.7% from Rs 320.65 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Despite lower-than-expected post-festive demand, LGE India stated that it has managed to maintain market leadership across key categories. EBITDA margin declined due to combined effect of subdued sales impacting operating leverage, increased input costs in copper and aluminum and currency related headwinds. Hong Ju Jeon, managing director and chief sales and marketing officer, LG Electronics India, said: "LGE India has maintained #1 position across key B2C segments, despite a subdued last quarter affected by external factors. Anchored by strong fundamentals, focus on innovation and long-term stability, we have entered Q4 with renewed strength, validated by the positive response to our new BEE-rated portfolio. As summer approaches, we are poised to capture demand for compressor products through our two-track strategy — expanding both premium and ‘LG Essential’ lineups. We remain committed to scaling our high-margin AMC business and leveraging B2B infrastructure opportunities. The rationalization of US tariffs will further help accelerate our commitment to 'Make India Global,’ as we optimize production to serve both domestic needs and expand exports. Our third manufacturing plant, on track to being operational by end of year, will accelerate our 'Make India Global’ plans.” LG Electronics India, a subsidiary of South Korea-based LG Electronics, is one of India's leading consumer durables companies. It manufactures and sells a wide range of products, including TVs, refrigerators, washing machines, and air conditioners, serving both retail and institutional customers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LGElectronicsIndiaLtd_35129397_18787.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Britannia Industries Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/britannia-industries-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1675795</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675795</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Britannia Industries Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Britannia Industries Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 6125, up 1.76% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.42% on the day, quoting at 25844.8. The Sensex is at 83826.36, down 0.48%. Britannia Industries Ltd has gained around 3.5% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Britannia Industries Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1% in last one month and is currently quoting at 52152.1, down 0.2% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.79 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3.92 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 6150, up 1.83% on the day. Britannia Industries Ltd is up 25.29% in last one year as compared to a 12.22% jump in NIFTY and a 2.37% jump in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 62.94 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BritanniaInds_60979410361_93.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd spurts 0.81%, up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/muthoot-finance-ltd-spurts-081-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1675783</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675783</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

Muthoot Finance Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3964.9, up 0.81% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.42% on the day, quoting at 25844.45. The Sensex is at 83853.26, down 0.45%. Muthoot Finance Ltd has added around 0.98% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Muthoot Finance Ltd is a constituent, has added around 2.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28276.95, up 0.32% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.9 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.78 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3975.6, up 1.01% on the day. Muthoot Finance Ltd is up 71.06% in last one year as compared to a 12.21% gain in NIFTY and a 21.9% gain in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 21.74 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MuthootFinance_48499437395_24769.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd spurts 0.35%, gains for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-ltd-spurts-035-gains-for-fifth-straight-session/1675784</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675784</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vedanta Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Vedanta Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 703.6, up 0.35% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.42% on the day, quoting at 25844.45. The Sensex is at 83853.26, down 0.45%. Vedanta Ltd has gained around 10.42% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Metal index of which Vedanta Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 8.4% in last one month and is currently quoting at 12276.55, up 0.26% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 59.62 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 237.6 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 703.5, down 0.03% on the day. Vedanta Ltd is up 65.73% in last one year as compared to a 12.21% jump in NIFTY and a 47.65% jump in the Nifty Metal index. The PE of the stock is 54.65 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Garware Technical Fibres climbs after Q3 PAT rises 18% YoY to Rs 56 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/garware-technical-fibres-climbs-after-q3-pat-rises-18-yoy-to-rs-56-cr/1675782</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675782</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 21.75% YoY to Rs 75.40 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 21.75% YoY to Rs 75.40 crore during the quarter. Total expenses increased 10.71% to Rs 329.54 in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 297.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 98.71 crore (up 1.84% YoY), employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 58.46 crore (up 7.78% YoY) and processing and testing charges was at Rs 40.33 crore (up 24.63% YoY) during the period under review. On a nine month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 11.96% YoY to Rs 141.29 crore in 9M FY26. Revenue from operations fell 0.47% to Rs 1,102.37 crore in 9M FY26 compared with Rs 1,107.56 crore in 9M FY25. Vayu Garware, CMD, Garware Technical Fibres, said, “Our financial performance has come on track in Q3FY26 after a challenging Q2, driven by a one-time event which led to a significant decline in North European Salmon Aquaculture orders. Order flow is now normalized and we are working to ship and bill as much as possible in the rest of FY26. In this quarter, we saw good results in Chile, international value added ropes business and significant growth in domestic business. However, USA duties has impact on our profitability margins for Q3 and some impact will be seen in Q4 as well. We have worked closely to retain all our US customers. With recent announcements for relaxation in USA tariffs, going forward we expect to return back to original margins and ordering cycles in the coming quarters. The Geosynthetics business continues excellent growth momentum on profitability as well as ROCE. New product launched in Norway in Hi are receiving a very positive response from the market through good order flows from our largest customers. We are rolling out these products in other markets as well.” Garware Technical Fibres is a technical textiles company that provides customised solutions across global markets. It operates in segments such as sports, fisheries, aquaculture, shipping, agriculture, coated fabrics and geosynthetics, and is known for its applied innovation in these areas.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GarwareTech_67737855063_190.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>