<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:36:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Home First Finance Company India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679864</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679864</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Vesuvius India Ltd, CreditAccess Grameen Ltd and JK Tyre & Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 February 2026.

Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Vesuvius India Ltd, CreditAccess Grameen Ltd and JK Tyre & Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 February 2026. Home First Finance Company India Ltd tumbled 7.54% to Rs 1087.55 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.12 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17941 shares in the past one month. Vishal Mega Mart Ltd crashed 7.52% to Rs 118. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 128.18 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.33 lakh shares in the past one month. Vesuvius India Ltd lost 5.87% to Rs 503.55. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 32575 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 90454 shares in the past one month. CreditAccess Grameen Ltd shed 5.56% to Rs 1264.55. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.52 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 29300 shares in the past one month. JK Tyre & Industries Ltd plummeted 5.37% to Rs 502.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 89265 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.29 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HomeFirstFinanceCompanyIndiaLtd_56604898_71865.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Renaissance Global Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/renaissance-global-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679863</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679863</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Flexituff Ventures International Ltd, R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd, Shankar Lal Rampal Dye-Chem Ltd and Fino Payments Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 February 2026.

Flexituff Ventures International Ltd, R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd, Shankar Lal Rampal Dye-Chem Ltd and Fino Payments Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 February 2026. Renaissance Global Ltd crashed 17.70% to Rs 119.75 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 27.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.27 lakh shares in the past one month. Flexituff Ventures International Ltd lost 9.97% to Rs 8.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 7460 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2692 shares in the past one month. R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd tumbled 9.95% to Rs 70.6. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 32150 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5.55 lakh shares in the past one month. Shankar Lal Rampal Dye-Chem Ltd fell 9.62% to Rs 46.7. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4590 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3503 shares in the past one month. Fino Payments Bank Ltd corrected 9.49% to Rs 188.3. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 87017 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6901 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RenaissanceJew_35784122165_27346.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with significant losses; pharma shares drop]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-significant-losses-pharma-shares-drop/1679862</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679862</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Key Indian stock indices traded with major losses in mid-afternoon trade as investors remained cautious amid continued selling by foreign institutional investors (FII) and weak global cues.

Key Indian stock indices traded with major losses in mid-afternoon trade as investors remained cautious amid continued selling by foreign institutional investors (FII) and weak global cues. Geopolitical tensions escalated after Pakistan and Afghanistan declared open conflict, while US-Iran talks concluded without a resolution, adding to market uncertainty. The Nifty dropped below the 25,300 level. Pharma shares declined after advancing in the past five consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 577.35 points or 0.72% to 81,671.26. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 196.40 points or 0.78% to 25,298.90. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index declined 0.62% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 0.57%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,714 shares rose and 2,403 shares fell. A total of 170 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, advanced 2.56% to 13.40. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index fell 0.84% to 23,105.70. The index rallied 3.89% in the past five consecutive trading sessions. Piramal Pharma (down 3.03%), Dr Reddys Laboratories (down 2.31%), Alkem Laboratories (down 1.5%), Gland Pharma (down 1.43%), Zydus Lifesciences (down 1.41%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (down 1.31%), Mankind Pharma (down 1.17%), Torrent Pharmaceuticals (down 1.07%), J B Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals (down 0.86%) and Cipla (down 0.82%) declined. On the other hand, Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (up 1.37%), Aurobindo Pharma (up 1.21%) and Wockhardt (up 0.54%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.07% to 6.695 compared with the previous session close of 6.690. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9525 compared with its close of 90.9150 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement gained 0.40% to Rs 160,354. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.11% to 97.63. The United States 10-year bond yield slipped 0.52% to 3.996. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 56 cents or 0.79% to $71.40 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Mamata Machinery rose 0.44%. The company announced that it has secured its first Rest of the World (ROW) order for its Packaging Machinery Segment from a customer in South Africa. Lupin shed 0.30%. The company said that it has received the establishment inspection report (EIR) from the US Food and Drug Administration for its Goa facility, with a satisfactory voluntary action indicated (VAI) classification.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mastek’s UK arm bags 5-year $67 mln deal with UK Home office]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/masteks-uk-arm-bags-5-year-67-mln-deal-with-uk-home-office/1679861</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679861</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the agreement, the company will deliver managed specialist engineering and cloud platform services across policing, forensics, justice, migration, and borders policy.

Under the agreement, the company will deliver managed specialist engineering and cloud platform services across policing, forensics, justice, migration, and borders policy. Mastek will help Home Office in supporting, maintaining, and enhancing their flagship Biometrics Services Gateway (BSG) and National DNA Database (NDNAD) systems. These systems and services will enable passports, visa, study and asylum routes, DNA search and match caseworking, and its enforcement operations to name a few. The service aims to enable the Home Office Biometrics Programme in delivering its responsibility to provide biometrics-related services to users in the Home Office and Policing, as well as more widely in the UK Government and with international partners. Mastek expects significant growth in this contract, as the department plans to deliver various vital and complex upgrades to the BSG and NDNAD systems over the coming few years. Abhishek Singhh, president UKI & Europe, Mastek, said, "This milestone deepens our partnership with the Home Office and reflects sustained confidence in Mastek’s deep domain knowledge in biometrics integration systems, DNA search and match technologies and advanced engineering capabilities. We look forward to operating secure, compliant, and resilient services for the Home Office 24x7 at a national scale, enabling collaboration across departments, with Europe and internationally. We thank the Home Office for creating an excellent environment for supplier collaboration and delivery with our teams, who anchor Mastek’s role as a trusted partner to the UK Public Sector.” Mastek is an IT company providing enterprise digital and cloud transformation services to the Government/public sector, healthcare, life science, retail, and financial services sectors. The company’s service offerings include application development, Oracle suite and cloud migration, digital commerce, application support & maintenance, BI & analytics, assurance & testing and agile consulting. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 11.19% to Rs 108.35 crore despite 3.69% decline in net sales to Rs 905.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. The counter advanced 0.28% to Rs 1,593 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Mastek_31982240985_2732.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Vishal Mega Mart Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-vishal-mega-mart-ltd-counter/1679859</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679859</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Redington Ltd, Sarda Energy & Minerals Ltd, Finolex Cables Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 27 February 2026.

Redington Ltd, Sarda Energy & Minerals Ltd, Finolex Cables Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 27 February 2026. Vishal Mega Mart Ltd clocked volume of 7625.18 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 73.17 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 104.22 lakh shares. The stock lost 6.81% to Rs.118.85. Volumes stood at 402.26 lakh shares in the last session. Redington Ltd witnessed volume of 677.1 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 68.71 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9.86 lakh shares. The stock increased 16.13% to Rs.284.00. Volumes stood at 13.46 lakh shares in the last session. Sarda Energy & Minerals Ltd clocked volume of 53.11 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 17.28 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3.07 lakh shares. The stock gained 5.90% to Rs.549.50. Volumes stood at 3.11 lakh shares in the last session. Finolex Cables Ltd saw volume of 39.95 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.65 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.43 lakh shares. The stock increased 5.59% to Rs.922.15. Volumes stood at 12.53 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd recorded volume of 973.96 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.89 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 89.45 lakh shares. The stock gained 14.69% to Rs.425.55. Volumes stood at 738.93 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VishalMegaMartLtd_95033477_86391.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Huhtamaki India appoints Anil Kaul as CFO]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/huhtamaki-india-appoints-anil-kaul-as-cfo/1679856</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679856</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Anil Kaul, Finance Controller at Huhtamaki India since June 2022, holds an MBA in Finance and brings 25 years of experience across finance functions.

Anil Kaul, Finance Controller at Huhtamaki India since June 2022, holds an MBA in Finance and brings 25 years of experience across finance functions. Previously, he spent 15 years at Owens Corning India, serving as plant controller, tax leader, and accounting leader, with expertise in financial management, strategic leadership, and risk & compliance oversight. Huhtamaki India is India's leading manufacturer and supplier of sustainable, flexible, and innovative solutions in packaging and labeling products. The company’s net profit jumped 159.2% to Rs 30.30 crore in Q4 CY26 from Rs 11.69 crore in Q4 CY25, while net sales slightly fell 0.3% to Rs 599.13 crore. Shares of Huhtamaki India fell 1.14% to Rs 177 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HuhtamakiPPL_85875272626_1106.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mamata Machinery rises after securing First ROW order from South Africa]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mamata-machinery-rises-after-securing-first-row-order-from-south-africa/1679852</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679852</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the order marks a significant milestone as it expands its global footprint for its established markets of the United States and India.

The company said the order marks a significant milestone as it expands its global footprint for its established markets of the United States and India. The delivery of the order is scheduled for the second quarter of FY27. Mamata Machinery stated that as part of its long-term growth strategy, it has been actively pursuing opportunities in emerging international markets for its packaging machinery segment, which remains its key growth driver. The South African order validates these efforts and reflects the company’s growing recognition as a trusted partner in advanced packaging technologies globally. The company continues to engage with customers across Europe, Africa, the Middle East, Asia, and South-Central America through sustained marketing initiatives, including participation in leading trade shows and exhibitions, to further strengthen its global presence. Mamata Machinery is engaged in the manufacture and export of machinery that makes plastic bags and pouches, packaging machines, and extrusion equipment. The company's consolidated net profit fell 10.3% to Rs 7.87 crore on an 8.5% decline in revenue to Rs 67.22 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MamataMachineryLtd_74071189_18506.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market under pressure; Nifty slips below 25,300 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-under-pressure-nifty-slips-below-25300-level/1679850</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679850</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade as investors remained cautious amid FII selling and weak global cues.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major losses in the afternoon trade as investors remained cautious amid FII selling and weak global cues. The Nifty dropped below the 25,300 level. Realty, FMCG and private bank shares declined while IT and media shares advanced. At 13:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 592.64 points or 0.72% to 81,655.60. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 198.10 points or 0.78% to 25,295.20. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index shed 0.73% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.73%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,543 shares rose and 2,489 shares fell. A total of 189 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 4.05% to 13.59. Gainers & Losers: Trent (up 1.57%), HCL Technologies (up 1.30%), Infosys (up 1.23%), Apollo Hospital Enterprises (up 0.95%) and Eternal (up 0.65%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Bharti Airtel (down 2.99%), HDFC Life Insurance (down 2.62%), Dr Reddy’s Laboratories (down 2.43%), Shriram Finance (down 2.23%) and Indigo (down 2.23%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Netweb Technologies India gained 4.10% after announcing a strategic partnership with Vertiv to jointly develop and validate GPU-based AI infrastructure solutions. The leading Indian high-end computing solutions provider will collaborate with Vertiv to engineer and validate its in-house GPU compute platforms alongside Vertiv’s integrated, end-to-end AI data center solutions. Gem Aromatics advanced 1.01% after the company’s subsidiary, Krystal Ingredients has commenced the production of additional products, including Gem Cool 5 (Cooling Agents) and Safranal (Citral Derivatives) at its Dahej facility, Gujarat. Kirloskar Brothers (KBL) declined 1.41%. The company said that it has secured orders worth Rs 214 crore from Adani Power and its subsidiaries for supply and installation of pump systems for thermal power projects. The scope of work includes supply and erection, testing and commissioning of circulating water pumps (concrete volute pump technology) and auxiliary cooling water pumps, along with associated electrical and control systems. The projects are located in Madhya Pradesh, Assam, Chhattisgarh and Bihar. Steel Exchange India advanced 3.72% after the company announced that its board will meet on Wednesday (04 March 2026) to consider a proposal to raise funds amounting to Rs 350 crore. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services shed 0.41%. The company has entered into multiple agreements to provide its corporate expense management solutions to leading domestic entities. The company will offer Zaggle Corporate Expense Cards to employees and associates of Chennai Super Kings and Superking Ventures. Each contract is valid for a period of one year. Separately, Zaggle has signed a five-year agreement with Saurashtra Cement to deploy its Zaggle Save platform for employee expense management and benefits administration. Global Markets: European markets traded mixed on Tuesday as investors awaited key economic data releases across the region. Inflation figures from Germany, France, and Spain are set to be published, alongside unemployment data from Germany and France. Investors are also watching for the latest U.K. housing price data, which could provide further insight into the strength of the property market and broader economic conditions. Asian market traded mixed on Friday, after U.S. stocks declined overnight as Nvidia shares tumbled despite a quarterly earnings beat. In Asian tech stocks, SK Hynix, which is a key supplier of high-bandwidth memory to Nvidia, dipped over 2%. Samsung Electronics, which has been a decades-old partner of Nvidia, was down 0.69%. Gold prices held broadly steady on Friday, with investors digesting the previous day's U.S.-Iran nuclear talks, while the dollar, hovering near three-week highs, pressured the yellow metal. An Omani mediator of U.S. and Iran nuclear talks has reportedly given an optimistic readout over the latest round of negotiations, but uncertainty still hung over energy markets with no sign of a breakthrough that would avert potential U.S. strikes. Following these developments, Brent crude futures settled down 10 cents, or 0.14%, to $70.75 a barrel. Overnight on Wall Street, the S&P 500 pulled back after the latest results from tech titan Nvidia and software giant Salesforce failed to boost the broader market. The broad market index fell 0.54% to end at 6,908.86, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.18% and closed at 22,878.38. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 17.05 points, or 0.03%, to settle at 49,499.20. Nvidia shares fell more than 5%, even after the chip giant posted fourth-quarter earnings and revenue that were higher than widely reported forescasts. On the other end, Salesforce, which has been one of the biggest victims of recent artificial intelligence disruption fears, rose 4% after the software company’s latest quarterly results were higher than widely reported forecasts on the top and bottom lines. However, the company issued a disappointing fiscal 2027 revenue forecast. Sentiment has been fragile in software and cybersecurity stocks this year as worries remain about the rapidly developing capabilities of AI products that could interfere with incumbent software vendors’ businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEBI introduces structured Life Cycle Funds with glide path, exit load norms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sebi-introduces-structured-life-cycle-funds-with-glide-path-exit-load-norms/1679849</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679849</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Board of India has introduced a detailed regulatory framework for Life Cycle Funds as part of its revised categorisation and rationalisation norms for mutual fund schemes.

The Securities and Exchange Board of India has introduced a detailed regulatory framework for Life Cycle Funds as part of its revised categorisation and rationalisation norms for mutual fund schemes. Definition and structure Life Cycle Funds are defined as open-ended funds with a target date maturity following a glide path strategy and investing across various asset classes, including equity, debt, InvITs, ETCDs, Gold ETFs and Silver ETFs. These schemes must follow the asset allocation structure. The framework specifies relatively higher permissible equity exposure in the earlier years to maturity. As the scheme approaches maturity, the permissible equity exposure reduces, with corresponding allocation ranges for debt and other permitted asset classes. Tenure and launch conditions Mutual funds may launch Life Cycle Funds with a minimum tenure of 5 years and a maximum tenure of 30 years. Such funds may be launched only in tenures that are multiples of five years. A mutual fund can have a maximum of six Life Cycle Funds open for subscription at any given point in time. Additionally, when a Life Cycle Fund has less than one year remaining to maturity, it may be merged with the nearest maturity Life Cycle Fund, subject to obtaining positive consent from unitholders. Asset allocation glide path Sebi prescribed detailed allocation ranges for different maturity buckets. For instance, in a 30-year Life Cycle Fund, equity allocation may range between 65% and 95% when the fund has 15 to 30 years remaining to maturity. As the fund approaches maturity, the permissible equity allocation reduces in stages, and allocation to debt correspondingly increases. For years to maturity below five years, Life Cycle Funds may take equity arbitrage exposure of up to 50% in addition to the specified equity range, provided that total investment in equity and equity-related instruments remains within the prescribed limits for such schemes. Where years to maturity are between one and three years, exposure in debt instruments is restricted to AA and above rated instruments with residual maturity less than the target maturity of the scheme. ETCD exposure is permitted only in Gold and Silver. Exit load structure To promote financial discipline, Life Cycle Funds shall levy an exit load of 3% on exits within one year of investment, 2% on exits within two years of investment and 1% on exits within three years of investment. Naming and benchmark requirements Life Cycle Funds are required to include the maturity year in the scheme nomenclature, for example "Life Cycle Fund 2055." Such schemes shall follow the benchmark framework prescribed for Multi Asset Allocation Funds. Regulatory intent By codifying tenure, glide path allocation bands, exit load structure and naming conventions, SEBI has established a standardised framework for target date, goal-based investing products within the mutual fund ecosystem.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/notebook-with-mutual-funds-sign-on-a-table-business-concept_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITC Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itc-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1679847</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679847</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITC Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

ITC Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 315.4, down 0.91% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.83% on the day, quoting at 25284.25. The Sensex is at 81620.9, down 0.76%.ITC Ltd has lost around 1.79% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which ITC Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 52023, down 1.17% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 56.93 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 231.46 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 316.7, down 1.11% on the day. ITC Ltd tumbled 20.15% in last one year as compared to a 14.28% rally in NIFTY and a 1.43% spurt in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 19.74 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITC_29088800077_301.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/patanjali-foods-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1679848</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679848</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Patanjali Foods Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Patanjali Foods Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 509.8, down 1.38% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.83% on the day, quoting at 25284.25. The Sensex is at 81620.9, down 0.76%.Patanjali Foods Ltd has added around 0.8% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Patanjali Foods Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 52023, down 1.17% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 7.31 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 29.95 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 511.95, down 0.84% on the day. Patanjali Foods Ltd tumbled 13.13% in last one year as compared to a 14.28% rally in NIFTY and a 1.43% spurt in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 33.46 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RuchiSoyaInds_47333195530_704.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lupin gets satisfactory USFDA inspection report for Goa facility]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lupin-gets-satisfactory-usfda-inspection-report-for-goa-facility/1679846</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679846</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The EIR follows an inspection conducted at the site from 10 November to 21 November, 2025, confirming compliance with regulatory standards.

The EIR follows an inspection conducted at the site from 10 November to 21 November, 2025, confirming compliance with regulatory standards. Nilesh Gupta, managing director (MD), Lupin, stated, “We are pleased to have received the EIR with a VAI classification from the US FDA for our Goa facility. This outcome reflects our continued focus on quality excellence and regulatory compliance, reinforcing our commitment to delivering safe and effective medicines to patients worldwide.” Lupin is a global pharmaceutical leader headquartered in Mumbai, India, with products distributed in over 100 markets. It specializes in pharmaceutical products, including branded and generic formulations, complex generics, biotechnology products, and active pharmaceutical ingredients. The pharmaceutical company reported a 37.46% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,175.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 855.16 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of Lupin shed 0.03% to currently trade at Rs 2,322.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Lupin_22827798980_3026.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEBI resets mutual fund rulebook, caps thematic overlap at 50% and discontinues solution-oriented category]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sebi-resets-mutual-fund-rulebook-caps-thematic-overlap-at-50-and-discontinues-solution-oriented-category/1679844</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679844</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Board of India has overhauled the framework governing categorisation and rationalisation of mutual fund schemes, tightening portfolio overlap norms, standardising nomenclature and discontinuing the solution-oriented schemes category with effect from 26 February 2026.

The Securities and Exchange Board of India has overhauled the framework governing categorisation and rationalisation of mutual fund schemes, tightening portfolio overlap norms, standardising nomenclature and discontinuing the solution-oriented schemes category with effect from 26 February 2026. In a circular issued on 26 February 2026, SEBI superseded Clause 2.6 of Chapter 2 of the Master Circular for Mutual Funds dated 27 June 2024 and introduced revised categories, scheme characteristics and uniform descriptions across equity, debt, hybrid, life cycle and fund of fund segments. 50% overlap ceiling for sectoral and thematic equity schemes SEBI has mandated that sectoral and thematic equity schemes shall ensure that portfolio overlap does not exceed 50% with other equity schemes in the sectoral/thematic category and other equity scheme categories, except large cap schemes. Portfolio overlap is to be computed on a quarterly basis using the average of daily overlap values at the individual ISIN level, in accordance with the methodology prescribed in Annexure A of the circular. Existing sectoral and thematic schemes have been given three years from the date of the circular to comply. Mutual funds must reduce 35% of the excess overlap in the first year, an additional 35% in the second year and the remaining 30% in the third year. Schemes unable to meet the criteria after three years shall be mandatorily merged in accordance with applicable provisions. Further, mutual funds offering both value and contra funds must ensure that portfolio overlap between the two schemes does not exceed 50%. Sectoral and thematic funds may be launched only as per the list of sectors and themes published and updated half yearly by the Association of Mutual Funds in India in consultation with SEBI. Solution-oriented schemes discontinued The solution-oriented schemes category stands discontinued with effect from 26 February 2026. Existing schemes under this category are required to stop accepting subscriptions with immediate effect and shall be merged with another scheme having similar asset allocation and risk profile, subject to prior approval from SEBI. Uniform naming and true-to-label requirement SEBI has directed that, for ease of identification and to ensure schemes remain true to label, the scheme name shall be the same as the scheme category. Words or phrases that highlight or emphasise only the return aspect of the scheme shall not be used in the name. The “type of scheme” description appearing in offer documents and marketing material must strictly adhere to the uniform description prescribed in the circular. Consequent changes to nomenclature, investment objective, investment strategy, benchmark or other parameters to align with the revised categories shall not be treated as fundamental attribute changes. Existing schemes must comply within six months from 26 February 2026. Life Cycle Funds framework introduced The circular provides a detailed framework for Life Cycle Funds, defined as open-ended funds with a target date maturity following a glide path strategy across equity, debt, InvITs, ETCDs, Gold and Silver ETFs. Life Cycle Funds may be launched with a minimum tenure of 5 years and a maximum of 30 years, in multiples of five years. A mutual fund may have a maximum of six such funds open for subscription at any given time. Funds with less than one year to maturity may be merged with the nearest maturity Life Cycle Fund, subject to positive consent from unitholders. These schemes will follow prescribed asset allocation bands based on years to maturity and will carry graded exit loads of 3% within one year of investment, 2% within two years and 1% within three years. Debt and hybrid categories retained with safeguards Duration-based classifications for debt schemes, from overnight to long term funds, have been retained. SEBI clarified that Macaulay duration must be disclosed at the portfolio level. In respect of medium term and medium to long term funds, fund managers may reduce portfolio duration in anticipated adverse situations in the interest of investors. Such decisions must be recorded with written justification, placed before trustees and reported in the half yearly trustee report to SEBI. Hybrid schemes continue under conservative, balanced, aggressive, dynamic asset allocation, multi asset, arbitrage and equity savings categories with defined asset allocation ranges. Foreign securities will not be treated as a separate asset class. Standardised framework for Fund of Funds Sebi lays down a standardised framework for domestic, overseas and domestic and overseas fund of fund schemes with multiple underlying funds. The framework prescribes categorisation, benchmark construction principles, nomenclature requirements and limits on the number of FoFs that may be launched by an AMC under each category. Existing FoFs exceeding the permitted number under any category may be grandfathered, but fresh launches beyond the prescribed limits will not be permitted. AMCs are required to align or re-categorise existing FoFs in accordance with the framework. Monthly disclosure of portfolio overlap Mutual funds are required to disclose category-wise portfolio overlap levels on their websites on a monthly basis, covering equity schemes versus other equity schemes, debt schemes versus other debt schemes and hybrid schemes versus other hybrid schemes. What this means for investors The regulator’s message is clear. Schemes must be true to label, product clutter must reduce, and thematic crowding cannot masquerade as differentiation. For investors, it promises clearer categories, cleaner comparisons and fewer look-alike schemes hiding behind creative names. If the 2017 categorisation exercise was about decluttering the shelf, the 2026 reset is about ensuring every product on that shelf actually does what it says on the label.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/yellow-warning-mutual-funds-highway-road-sign-picture-id512_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mphasis Ltd spurts 1.45%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mphasis-ltd-spurts-145-gains-for-third-straight-session/1679840</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679840</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mphasis Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Mphasis Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 2294.2, up 1.45% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.84% on the day, quoting at 25282.25. The Sensex is at 81656.68, down 0.72%. Mphasis Ltd has dropped around 19.04% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Mphasis Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 20.72% in last one month and is currently quoting at 30554.2, up 0.49% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.89 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 6.53 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2295, up 0.85% on the day. Mphasis Ltd is up 2.09% in last one year as compared to a 14.27% spurt in NIFTY and a 17.73% spurt in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 30.27 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Mphasis_88855176_3361.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd up for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oracle-financial-services-software-ltd-up-for-third-consecutive-session/1679841</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679841</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 6947.5, up 1.33% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.84% on the day, quoting at 25282.25. The Sensex is at 81656.68, down 0.72%. Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd has slipped around 13.29% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty IT index of which Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 20.72% in last one month and is currently quoting at 30554.2, up 0.49% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.13 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.61 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 6926, up 0.58% on the day. Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd is down 10.52% in last one year as compared to a 14.27% jump in NIFTY and a 17.73% jump in the Nifty IT index. The PE of the stock is 17.06 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OracleFinServ_27814195267_13105.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Oil Corporation Ltd spurts 0.64%, gains for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-oil-corporation-ltd-spurts-064-gains-for-fifth-straight-session/1679837</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679837</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today.

Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is up for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 187.67, up 0.64% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25277.2. The Sensex is at 81638.36, down 0.74%. Indian Oil Corporation Ltd has gained around 15.24% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 6.96% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37181.8, down 0.22% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 102.34 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 168.87 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 187.64, up 0.06% on the day. Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is up 65.36% in last one year as compared to a 14.25% jump in NIFTY and a 23.59% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 8.06 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IOCL_64283819279_12002.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd soars 0.21%, up for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-petroleum-corporation-ltd-soars-021-up-for-fifth-straight-session/1679838</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679838</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 386.8, up 0.21% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25277.2. The Sensex is at 81638.36, down 0.74%. Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd has risen around 6.75% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 6.96% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37181.8, down 0.22% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 35.5 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 71.57 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 388.4, up 0.15% on the day. Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd is up 63% in last one year as compared to a 14.25% spurt in NIFTY and a 23.59% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 6.81 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BPCL_78782939994_2290.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEBI shifts gold, silver ETF valuation to domestic spot prices from April 1]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sebi-shifts-gold-silver-etf-valuation-to-domestic-spot-prices-from-april-1/1679839</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679839</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Board of India has revised the way mutual funds will value physical gold and silver held in their schemes, moving away from international benchmarks to domestic spot prices published by recognized stock exchanges.

The Securities and Exchange Board of India has revised the way mutual funds will value physical gold and silver held in their schemes, moving away from international benchmarks to domestic spot prices published by recognized stock exchanges. In a circular issued on 26 February 2026, the regulator said that with effect from 1 April 2026, mutual funds will be required to use polled spot prices published by recognized stock exchanges for valuing physical gold and silver. These are the same prices used for settlement of physically delivered gold and silver derivative contracts. Currently, gold and silver held by Exchange Traded Funds are valued using the AM fixing prices of the London Bullion Market Association, with adjustments for currency conversion, transportation costs, customs duty, taxes and notional premiums or discounts to arrive at domestic valuations. The shift follows discussions in the Mutual Fund Advisory Committee, public consultation and stakeholder feedback. SEBI said using exchange-published spot prices, which are subject to regulatory oversight and transparency norms, would ensure valuations that better reflect domestic market conditions and bring uniformity across fund houses. The change comes under the newly notified SEBI Mutual Funds Regulations, 2026, which will take effect from 1 April 2026. The valuation will be subject to the investment valuation norms specified in the Seventh Schedule of the regulations. The Association of Mutual Funds in India will, in consultation with SEBI, prescribe a uniform policy for implementation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bullions-154931__340_gold.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vishal Mega Mart tumbles as equity changes hands in mega block deal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vishal-mega-mart-tumbles-as-equity-changes-hands-in-mega-block-deal/1679836</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679836</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to media reports, the floor price for the transaction was set at Rs 115 per share, implying a discount of nearly 10% to the previous closing price of Rs 127.60.

According to media reports, the floor price for the transaction was set at Rs 115 per share, implying a discount of nearly 10% to the previous closing price of Rs 127.60. The total size of the block deal is estimated at around Rs 3,508 crore, with a 150-day lock-in applicable on the remaining stake. Samayat Services LLP, which held a 54.09% stake in Vishal Mega Mart as of 31 December 2025, planned to offload up to 30.5 crore shares at Rs 115 each. At the indicated price, the transaction would fetch approximately Rs 3,508 crore for the promoter entity. Kotak Securities and Morgan Stanley India Company acted as key advisors to the deal. Samayat Services LLP has been gradually trimming its holding in the company since Vishal Mega Mart’s listing in December 2024. In June 2025, it had sold around 90 crore shares, representing a 19.6% stake, for about Rs 10,220 crore. Several large institutional investors, including SBI Mutual Fund and HDFC Mutual Fund, had participated in that earlier transaction. Vishal Mega Mart is a leading retail player. It offers products across three major product categories, i.e., apparel, general merchandise and FMCG, through a pan-India network of 771 Vishal Mega Mart stores as of 31 December 2025 and Vishal Mega Mart mobile application and website. It reported a 19.10% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 312.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 262.72 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 17.04% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 3,670.41 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VishalMegaMartLtd_95033477_86391.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Netweb Tech rises on strategic AI infra Tie-up with Vertiv]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/netweb-tech-rises-on-strategic-ai-infra-tie-up-with-vertiv/1679833</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679833</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The leading Indian high-end computing solutions provider will collaborate with Vertiv to engineer and validate its in-house GPU compute platforms alongside Vertiv’s integrated, end-to-end AI data center solutions.

The leading Indian high-end computing solutions provider will collaborate with Vertiv to engineer and validate its in-house GPU compute platforms alongside Vertiv’s integrated, end-to-end AI data center solutions. Under the tie-up, Netweb’s rack-scale solutions will leverage Vertiv’s liquid cooling systems, including coolant distribution units and free cooling chillers, along with advanced power infrastructure such as busways and uninterruptible power supply (UPS) units with dynamic load management. Hirdey Vikram, Senior vice president at Netweb, said, “This initiative allows us to design complex cooling technologies, including Direct-to-Chip cooling for GPU-accelerated AI and HPC systems, right from the product conceptualization stage. The collaboration will deliver fully validated, rack-scale AI systems where compute, cooling, and power work in seamless integration.” The partnership is aimed at addressing rising power demands of AI workloads and managing extreme thermal densities from high-performance accelerators. The validated rack-scale solutions are expected to enable higher rack densities, faster deployment, and reliable performance for demanding AI training and inference applications. Netweb Technologies is India’s leading high-end computing solutions (HCS) provider, with fully integrated design and manufacturing capabilities. The company’s HCS offering comprises HPC, private cloud, HCI, AI systems and enterprise workstations, high-performance storage (HPS), and data center servers. The company’s standalone net profit soared 146.7% to Rs 73.31 crore on a 141% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 804.92 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NetwebTechnologiesIndiaLtd_73333970_78854.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>