<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Captain Polyplast jumps after securing Rs 28-cr PM KUSUM B solar pump order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/captain-polyplast-jumps-after-securing-rs-28-cr-pm-kusum-b-solar-pump-order/1661828</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661828</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[This empanelment, added to the earlier order for 500 solar pumps from MSEDCL, strengthens the company’s order book in the renewable energy and agri-infrastructure segment.

This empanelment, added to the earlier order for 500 solar pumps from MSEDCL, strengthens the company’s order book in the renewable energy and agri-infrastructure segment. The move underscores Captain Polyplast’s growing presence in government-backed solar irrigation programs and reflects sustained demand for solar pumping solutions amid policy support for clean energy adoption in agriculture. Ritesh Khichadia, whole time director of Captain Polyplast, said, “This additional empanelment under the PM KUSUM B scheme further strengthens our order book and improves revenue visibility for the coming periods. Along with the earlier orders for 500 solar pumps, it supports steady growth in our solar pump business and adds to a more balanced revenue mix. Continued demand under government-supported solar irrigation programs reflects our execution capabilities, manufacturing strength, and experience across regions. Looking ahead, we see sustained opportunities from expanding solar irrigation initiatives and expect this segment to contribute meaningfully to our growth while supporting long-term value creation.” Captain Polyplast is engaged in manufacturing and selling quality micro irrigation systems and allied products having its manufacturing facilities at Shapar (Veraval), Rajkot. Further, the company also undertakes installation of micro irrigation systems, providing of agronomical services to farmers and carrying out business activities. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 73.9% to Rs 4.24 crore, even as net sales jumped 49.7% to Rs 79.73 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CaptainPolyp_16291275550_34354.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD stable around three-month high as break above 1.1800 extends]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-stable-around-three-month-high-as-break-above-11800-extends/1661827</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661827</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro is holding its recent gains against the US dollar as a break above 1.1800 mark extends.

Euro is holding its recent gains against the US dollar as a break above 1.1800 mark extends. Economic calendar is thin while US economic data showed a mixed outing yesterday. European equities ended modestly higher on Tuesday with some indices hitting fresh highs. Meanwhile, the US dollar index is witnessing continued stress amid optimism the Federal Reserve will consider more rate cuts next year. EUR/USD pair is currently trading at 1.1847, up 0.10% on the day – holding near three-month top. On NSE, EUR/INR futures are quoting flat at 105.90 after witnessing good improvement from lows under 105.70 mark in the early moves.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/golden-coins-1426194_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Monarch Surveyors rises after securing Rs 8-cr Nashik Municipal Corporation contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/monarch-surveyors-rises-after-securing-rs-8-cr-nashik-municipal-corporation-contract/1661825</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661825</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves carrying out survey and allied works for lands requisitioned for the Sinhastha Kumbh Mela 2027-28 in Nashik and Trimbak.

The contract involves carrying out survey and allied works for lands requisitioned for the Sinhastha Kumbh Mela 2027-28 in Nashik and Trimbak. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, does not fall under related party transactions, and neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the work, the company said. The project will commence immediately as per the letter of acceptance, with completion timelines defined under the contract terms. The work will be executed in cash consideration and is subject to necessary approvals from governmental authorities. The contract marks a key assignment for Monarch in preparation for one of India’s largest religious gatherings, reinforcing the company’s expertise in survey and engineering consultancy services. Monarch Surveyors and Engineering Consultants are engaged in the business to provide comprehensive consultancy services under Concept to Commissioning of infrastructure projects which includes Survey, design and technical supervision for roads, railways, metros, town planning, geospatial, mapping, land acquisition, water, transmission Line, pipelines and other civil engineering sectors. Our objective is to create consistent value for our clients by delivering uncompromising quality of services at optimum cost through continuous improvement in elemental technologies of this field, maintaining integrity and design processes which fosters excellence in all the aspects of our operations. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 16.1% to Rs 34.83 crore on a 10.5% rise in revenue to Rs 154.14 crore in FY25 compared with FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MonarchSurveyorsandEngineeringConsultantsLimited_26476128_94045.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex , Nifty trade with small gains; broader mrkt outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-small-gains-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1661822</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661822</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key benchmarks indices continued to trade with minor gains in mid-morning trade.

The key benchmarks indices continued to trade with minor gains in mid-morning trade. The market showed resilience despite FII outflows and the Sensex's weekly derivatives expiry today. Market participants will closely monitoring rupee movement, FII activity, IPO-related developments, and global cues. The Nifty hovered above the 26,200 level. Metal shares surged for the six consecutive trading sessions. At 11:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 85.95 points or 0.10% to 85,608.72. The Nifty 50 index advanced 36.90 points or 0.14% to 26,214.05. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.24% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.22%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,101 shares rose and 1,730 shares fell. A total of 205 shares were unchanged. The stock market will be closed tomorrow, 25 December 2025, on account of Christmas. IPO Update: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 4,56,54,272 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:21 IST on Wednesday (24 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 3.45 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it will close on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index jumped 0.45% to 10,775.10 extending its gains for a six straight session, up 2.97% over the period. Hindustan Copper (up 4.95%), Hindustan Zinc (up 2.87%), National Aluminium Company (up 2.12%), Vedanta (up 1.74%) and Hindalco Industries (up 1.3%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals dropped 0.77% after the company announced that it has received an order worth Rs 46.20 crore from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company (MSEDCL). ArisInfra Solutions rose 0.04%. The company announced that it has secured an asphalt supply order valued at approximately Rs 35 crore through its subsidiary, Buildmex-Infra. JD Cables advanced 0.78% after the company has secured a significant EPC infrastructure contract worth about Rs 244 crore from Kaushal Engineering for a key national highway development project (NHDP) in Jharkhand. Global Market: Asian market traded mixed on Wednesday, with several indexes set to close early in lieu of the Christmas Eve holiday. Media reports from Japan said that the country was set to issue about 29.6 trillion yen (about $190 billion) in new government bonds to fund its fiscal 2026 budget. The South Korean won strengthened against the greenback after media reports stated that South Korea’s national pension fund was carrying out strategic foreign exchange hedging activities. Spot gold prices hit another record Wednesday, crossing $4,500 per ounce for the first time, driven by a weaker dollar, geopolitical tensions and U.S. Federal Reserve rate-cut expectations. Gold has notched a series of all-time highs this year, soaring over 70% year to date. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose for a fourth straight session as artificial intelligence names continued to outperform during a holiday-shortened week. US GDP grew 4.3% in third quarter compared with 3.8% growth recorded in Second quarter. This is also the highest quarterly GDP growth in the US economy in the past 2 years. The S&P 500 added 0.46%, closing at a record level of 6,909.79. The broad market index is now just below its intraday all-time high of 6,920.34. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.57% to end at 23,561.84. Gains in tech giants such as Nvidia and Broadcom lifted the index. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 79.73 points, or 0.16%, and settled at 48,442.41.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Helios Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/helios-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1661823</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661823</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Helios Mutual Fund has announced the Mr.

Helios Mutual Fund has announced the Mr. Abhinav Khemani, Vice President & Head - Compliance, a key personnel of the AMC has been designated as Chief Compliance Officer of the AMC with effect from December 22, 2025 (“Effective Date”) under the SEBI (Mutual Funds) Regulations, 1996, and shall continue to be a Key Personnel of the AMC.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T Transportation Infrastructure secures Mumbai Metro Line 4 order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-transportation-infrastructure-secures-mumbai-metro-line-4-order/1661818</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661818</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore.

As per L&T’s internal classification, the contract falls under the ‘significant’ category, with an estimated value in the range of Rs 1,000 crore to Rs 2,500 crore. The contract, Package CA-298, awarded by the Mumbai Metropolitan Region Development Authority (MMRDA), covers the electrification of the 24.72 km-long Line 4, running from Bhakti Park (Wadala) to Cadbury Junction, which includes 22 elevated stations. The scope of work includes design, manufacture, supply, installation, integration, testing, and commissioning of power supply and traction systems along the route. L&T will also provide a SCADA system for Metro Lines 4 and 4A, covering 32 stations, depots, and receiving substations. Additional works include electrical and mechanical installations, lifts and escalators for 22 elevated stations and 2 depots, along with five years of comprehensive maintenance. All work will be executed by L&T’s in-house design and execution team. This marks L&T’s third consecutive order in the Line 4 & 4A corridor. The company had earlier won package CA-234, covering rolling stock, CBTC signalling, telecommunications, platform screen doors, and depot machinery, and package CA-168, involving 19.5 km of ballast-less track works across 15 stations. Larsen & Toubro is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services. The company reported a 15.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Larsen & Toubro rose 0.07% to currently trade at Rs 4,062.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crompton Greaves gains after bagging Rs 46-cr solar pumping systems order from MSEDCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crompton-greaves-gains-after-bagging-rs-46-cr-solar-pumping-systems-order-from-msedcl/1661817</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661817</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said it has secured EPC contracts for the design, manufacture, supply, installation, testing, and commissioning of Solar Photovoltaic Water Pumping Systems (SPWPS) with PV modules under the MTSKPY/PM-KUSUM scheme at various locations across Maharashtra.

In an exchange filing, the company said it has secured EPC contracts for the design, manufacture, supply, installation, testing, and commissioning of Solar Photovoltaic Water Pumping Systems (SPWPS) with PV modules under the MTSKPY/PM-KUSUM scheme at various locations across Maharashtra. The order covers 2,000 solar water pumping systems, with a total work order value of Rs 46,20,48,229. The company said the order is scheduled to be executed within 60 days from the date of issuance of the Notice to Proceed (NTP) or work order. Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals also clarified that neither its promoters nor members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding authority, and the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals manufactures and markets a wide spectrum of consumer products, ranging from fans, lamps and luminaries to pumps and household appliances such as water heaters, coolers, mixer grinders and irons. The company’s standalone net profit fell 43.13% to Rs 70.10 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 123.28 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations declined marginally to Rs 1,631.73 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 1,645.33 crore in Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CromptonGreavesConsumerElectricalLtd_65592784027_65733.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund announces add in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-mutual-fund-announces-add-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1661819</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661819</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Mutual Fund has announced Mr.

Axis Mutual Fund has announced Mr. Nandik has been designated as Head – Equity & Hybrid SIF and Equity – Passives and key personnel of Axis Asset Management Company Limited (‘Axis AMC’) from December 09, 2025. He shall be additionally responsible for oversight of Axis Quant Fund & Axis Momentum Fund. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Scheme Name Fund Manager Axis Quant Fund & Axis Momentum Fund Mr. Nandik Mallik

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at JBM Auto Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-jbm-auto-ltd-counter/1661814</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661814</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HEG Ltd, Ajanta Pharma Ltd, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd, Olectra Greentech Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 24 December 2025.

HEG Ltd, Ajanta Pharma Ltd, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd, Olectra Greentech Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 24 December 2025. JBM Auto Ltd saw volume of 6.66 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 19.02 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 35021 shares. The stock increased 10.69% to Rs.639.70. Volumes stood at 34655 shares in the last session. HEG Ltd recorded volume of 1.65 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.83 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 34048 shares. The stock gained 3.42% to Rs.557.85. Volumes stood at 94543 shares in the last session. Ajanta Pharma Ltd saw volume of 27903 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 4.45 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6277 shares. The stock increased 5.01% to Rs.2,800.00. Volumes stood at 38552 shares in the last session. Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd witnessed volume of 10806 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 2.18 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4957 shares. The stock increased 2.93% to Rs.7,495.85. Volumes stood at 7207 shares in the last session. Olectra Greentech Ltd recorded volume of 38358 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 2.18 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 17619 shares. The stock gained 5.56% to Rs.1,263.05. Volumes stood at 20448 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JBMAuto_44376176143_23341.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee: INR softens after recent rebound ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-inr-softens-after-recent-rebound/1661815</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661815</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee slipped in early moves today, giving up after recent rebound took it near three week high against the US dollar.

Indian rupee slipped in early moves today, giving up after recent rebound took it near three week high against the US dollar. Quarter and year end trades saw steady demand for the dollar and INR eased 14 paise to 89.77 per US dollar. The INR has been under stress recently but sustained uptick in equities and comfortable forex cover could cap losses now.India's forex reserves jumped by $1.689 billion to $688.949 billion during the week ended December 12, the Reserve Bank of India said last week. In the previous reporting week as well, the overall reserves has increased by $1.033 billion to $687.26 billion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growing-from-coin-jar-picture-id622446130_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LIC Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lic-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1661816</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661816</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[LIC Mutual Fund has announced 26 December 2025 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme.

LIC Mutual Fund has announced 26 December 2025 as the record date for the declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) will be: LIC MF Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan - IDCW Option: 0.12

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ArisInfra Solutions bags Rs 35-cr Asphalt supply order via subsidiary]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/arisinfra-solutions-bags-rs-35-cr-asphalt-supply-order-via-subsidiary/1661807</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661807</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order has been awarded by Goswami Infra Projects.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order has been awarded by Goswami Infra Projects. The contract involves the supply of asphalt along with execution-linked works. The total project value is around Rs 35 crore and is scheduled to be executed over a period of 12 months. Ronak Morbia, chairman & managing director of Arisinfra Solutions, said, “This order validates our execution-led, network-driven approach in an infrastructure segment where reliability and delivery precision are critical. Our ability to scale quickly without owning heavy assets allows us to partner effectively, control execution outcomes, and consistently meet demanding project timelines.” ArisInfra Solutions is a B2B tech company that simplifies the procurement process for construction materials throughout India. It serves real estate and infrastructure developers. It provides a complete digital platform for sourcing materials such as cement, steel, aggregates, RMC, and more. The company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 15.26 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 1.98 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 38.4% year-on-year to Rs 241.19 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. The scrip shed 0.43% to currently trade at Rs 137.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArisinfraSolutionsLtd_84388621_93589.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1661808</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661808</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 27 December 2025.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 27 December 2025. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager(s) New Fund Manager(s) Mirae Asset Liquid Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Money Market Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Dynamic Bond Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Aggressive Hybrid Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo (debt portion), Mr. Harshad Borawake and Mr. Vrijesh Kasera Mr. Basant Bafna (debt portion), Mr. Harshad Borawake and Mr. Vrijesh Kasera Mirae Asset Balanced Advantage Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo (debt portion) and Mr. Harshad Borawake Mr. Basant Bafna (debt portion) and Mr. Harshad Borawake Mirae Asset Equity Savings Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset CRISIL IBX Gilt Index - April 2033 Index Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Nifty AAA PSU Bond Plus SDL Apr 2026 50:50 Index Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Nifty SDL Jun 2027 Index Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Nifty SDL June 2028 Index Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Nifty 8-13 yr G-Sec ETF Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Multi Asset Allocation Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo (debt portion), Mr. Harshad Borawake, Mr. Siddharth Srivastava and Mr. Ritesh Patel Mr. Basant Bafna (debt portion), Mr. Harshad Borawake, Mr. Siddharth Srivastava and Mr. Ritesh Patel Mirae Asset CRISIL-IBX Financial Services 9-12 Months Debt Index Fund Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna Mirae Asset Income plus Arbitrage Active FOF Mr. Mahendra Jajoo Mr. Basant Bafna

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JD Cables jumps after bagging Rs 244-cr NHDP project in Jharkhand]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jd-cables-jumps-after-bagging-rs-244-cr-nhdp-project-in-jharkhand/1661790</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661790</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves execution of balance civil and electrical works, including construction of the Chauparan Flyover, Barkatha Flyover, a Road Over Bridge (ROB), and associated electrical works for the six-laning of the Bihar–Jharkhand border (Chordaha to Gorhar section) of NH-2.

The order involves execution of balance civil and electrical works, including construction of the Chauparan Flyover, Barkatha Flyover, a Road Over Bridge (ROB), and associated electrical works for the six-laning of the Bihar–Jharkhand border (Chordaha to Gorhar section) of NH-2. The stretch covers Km 249.525 to Km 320.810 and is being implemented under NHDP Phase V on an EPC basis. The total contract value stands at Rs 243.99 crore, approved change of scope, price escalation, and other applicable taxes, duties, labour cess and material royalty, the company said. Any change in law by the central or Jharkhand government will be dealt with as per the provisions of the main contract. The project is scheduled to be completed within one year from the date of execution of the agreement. JD Cables said the order will significantly strengthen its order book, improve revenue visibility and reinforce its execution capabilities in large and complex EPC infrastructure projects, particularly in the highways and transportation segment. Piyush Garodia, MD, JD Cables, said, “The award of this prestigious EPC contract reflects the strong confidence placed in our execution capabilities, technical expertise, and proven delivery track record. The NH-2 six-laning project is strategically important and aligns well with our strengths in executing complex infrastructure works within defined timelines.” He added, “This order significantly strengthens our order book and deepens our presence in national highway projects. We remain focused on disciplined execution, quality excellence, and sustainable value creation for our shareholders and other stakeholders.” JD Cables are engaged in manufacturing of Cables and Conductors which widely include manufacturing of Power Cables, Control Cables, Aerial Bunched Cables, Single-core service wire and All Aluminium Conductor (A.A.C.), All Aluminium Alloy Conductor (A.A.A.C.), Aluminium conductor steel reinforced (A.C.S.R.) Conductors used for transmission and distribution of electricity. Rajesh Jhunjhunwala, Whole-Time Director & Head – EPC, JD Cables, said: “This landmark order is a strong validation of our EPC execution strength and on ground delivery capabilities. We have initiated detailed mobilisation and resource planning, including procurement scheduling, deployment of experienced project teams, and robust quality and safety systems to ensure timely completion within the stipulated one-year timeline. Our focus will remain on disciplined execution, seamless coordination with all stakeholders, and stringent adherence to technical specifications to deliver this project efficiently and reliably.” The company’s standalone net profit surged 384.1% to Rs 22.17 crore in FY25, driven by a 148.5% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 250.33 crore, compared with FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JDCablesLtd_48912059_95607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,200 level; media shares climb]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25200-level-media-shares-climb/1661789</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661789</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with decent gains in morning trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with decent gains in morning trade. The market showed resilience despite FII outflows and the Sensex's weekly derivatives expiry today. Market participants will closely monitoring rupee movement, FII activity, IPO-related developments, and global cues. The Nifty traded above the 26,200 level. Media shares extended their rally for a fourth consecutive session. At 10:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 133.24 points or 0.16% to 85,658.08. The Nifty 50 index advanced 46.55 points or 0.19% to 26,225.35. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index climbed 0.33% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.23%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,095 shares rose and 1,524 shares fell. A total of 206 shares were unchanged. The stock market will be closed tomorrow, 25 December 2025, on account of Christmas. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index jumped 0.65% to 1,422.75. The index rallied 2.12% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Nazara Technologies (up 3.15%), Prime Focus (up 2.23%), D B Corp (up 0.9%), Saregama India (up 0.78%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (up 0.47%), PVR Inox (up 0.44%) and Tips Music (up 0.07%) advanced. Stocks in Spotlight: ACME Solar Holdings gained 1.10% after the company said it has received a Letter of Award from REMC to set up a 130 MW renewable energy Round-the-Clock (RTC) power project. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers & Chemicals (GNFC) rose 0.52%. The company said that it has awarded a contract worth Rs 0360 crore to Toyo Engineering India for the supply of an Ammonium Nitrate-II plant on a LEPC (lump-sum engineering, procurement & construction) basis. RPP Infra Projects declined 2.15%. The company announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 66.25 crore from Indian Port Rail & Ropeway Corporation (IPRCL), a Government of India enterprise under the Ministry of Ports, Shipping & Waterways.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikran Engineering jumps on Rs 2,035 crore solar EPC order win]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikran-engineering-jumps-on-rs-2035-crore-solar-epc-order-win/1661788</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661788</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has secured a work order worth Rs 2,035.26 crore from Onix Renewables to set up 600 MW AC solar power projects across multiple locations in Maharashtra.

The company has secured a work order worth Rs 2,035.26 crore from Onix Renewables to set up 600 MW AC solar power projects across multiple locations in Maharashtra. The order will be executed on a turnkey EPC basis. The scope of work includes design, engineering, procurement, supply, erection, testing and commissioning, along with the supply of solar PV modules and inverters. The project is expected to be completed within a 12-month timeline. Chairman and managing director Rakesh Markhedkar said the order strengthens the company's renewable energy order book and reflects confidence in its execution capabilities. He added that the win positions Vikran Engineering for sustained growth while supporting India’s clean energy ambitions. Vikran Engineering is a diversified EPC player. The company provides end-to-end turnkey solutions spanning conceptualization, design, supply, installation, testing, and commissioning, enabling it to capture the full value chain of project execution. On a standalone basis, net profit of Vikran Engineering rose 339.42% to Rs 9.14 crore while net sales rose 10.71% to Rs 176.29 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VikranEngineeringLtd_15725401_76742.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Legally binding commitments under FTAs to unlock global markets for Indian professional services]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/legally-binding-commitments-under-ftas-to-unlock-global-markets-for-indian-professional-services/1661786</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661786</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Commerce Secretary, Rajesh Agrawal, has emphasised the importance of enhanced stakeholder coordination, reforms in the domestic ecosystem, and legally binding commitments on professional services under various FTAs to unlock global markets for Indian professional services, while inaugurating a Chintan Shivir on Professional Services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-167741__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oswal Pumps rises after bagging Rs 180 crore contract from MSEDCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oswal-pumps-rises-after-bagging-rs-180-crore-contract-from-msedcl/1661787</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661787</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract covers the design, manufacture, and installation of off-grid DC solar water pumping systems for farmers in Maharashtra.

The contract covers the design, manufacture, and installation of off-grid DC solar water pumping systems for farmers in Maharashtra. These systems will have capacities of 3HP, 5HP, and 7.5HP. The scope includes full transportation, testing, and commissioning at each site. Additionally, the project provides a five-year warranty, ongoing maintenance, and a Remote Monitoring System (RMS) under the PM Kusum B "Magel Tyala Saur Krushi Pump" Yojana. The letter of empanelment is valid up to one year. The installation is be completed within 60 days from the date of issuance of work order. Oswal Pumps manufactures solar-powered and grid-connected submersible and monoblock pumps, electric motors comprising induction and submersible motors, and solar modules, which it sells under the 'Oswal‘ brand. The company's consolidated net profit jumped 48.24% to Rs 97.50 crore on a 73.90% increase in revenue to Rs 539.64 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OswalPumpsLtd_50250161_39908.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ACME Solar rises on bagging renewable energy project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/acme-solar-rises-on-bagging-renewable-energy-project/1661770</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661770</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company disclosed that the project has been awarded at a tariff of Rs 4.35 per unit for a period of 25 years.

The company disclosed that the project has been awarded at a tariff of Rs 4.35 per unit for a period of 25 years. ACME Solar Holdings is a fully integrated renewable energy company in India with a diversified portfolio across solar, wind, storage, hybrid and Firm and Dispatchable Renewable Energy (FDRE) projects. The company’s consolidated net profit stood at Rs 115.06 crore in Q2 FY26, up 652.51% as against Rs 15.29 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 80.18% YoY to Rs 467.74 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ACMESolarHoldingsLtd_41904745_71636.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GNFC awards Rs 360-cr Ammonium Nitrate-II plant contract to Toyo Engineering India]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gnfc-awards-rs-360-cr-ammonium-nitrate-ii-plant-contract-to-toyo-engineering-india/1661767</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661767</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract has been awarded to a domestic entity and is scheduled to be executed over a period of 20 months.

The contract has been awarded to a domestic entity and is scheduled to be executed over a period of 20 months. GNFC clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in Toyo Engineering India, and the transaction does not fall under related party transactions. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fert. & Chem is leading entities engaged in the manufacturing and selling of fertilizers, industrial chemical products and providing IT services. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 70.5% to Rs 179 crore on 2.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,968 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers & Chemicals rose 0.10% to Rs 490.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GNFC_11816154185_213.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>