<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 01:24:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Weighted average lending rate on fresh rupee loans rises on monthly basis to 8.67% in Jan-26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/weighted-average-lending-rate-on-fresh-rupee-loans-rises-on-monthly-basis-to-867-in-jan-26/1679924</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679924</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated today that the weighted average lending rate (WALR) on fresh rupee loans of SCBs stood at 8.67 per cent in January 2026 (8.28 per cent in December 2025).

Reserve Bank of India (RBI) stated today that the weighted average lending rate (WALR) on fresh rupee loans of SCBs stood at 8.67 per cent in January 2026 (8.28 per cent in December 2025). The WALR on outstanding rupee loans of SCBs declined to 9.04 per cent in January 2026 from 9.06 per cent in December 2025. RBI noted that 1-Year median Marginal Cost of Funds based Lending Rate (MCLR) of SCBs increased to 8.45 per cent in February 2026 from 8.40 per cent in January 2026. The weighted average domestic term deposit rate (WADTDR) on fresh rupee term deposits of SCBs stood at 5.66 per cent in January 2026 (5.67 per cent in December 2025). The WADTDR on outstanding rupee term deposits of SCBs declined to 6.64 per cent in January 2026 from 6.68 per cent in December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-3321166__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper soars more than 2% as break above $6 per pound extends]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-soars-more-than-2-as-break-above-6-per-pound-extends/1679923</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679923</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures are edging higher today after the break above $6 per pound stayed in place.

COMEX Copper futures are edging higher today after the break above $6 per pound stayed in place. The metal is up 2.10% at $6.13 per pound and has soared around 3.50% this month. The current levels are highest in last four-weeks. Meanwhile, in Asia today, China's Shanghai Composite index added 0.39%. Hong Kong’s Hang Seng index surged 0.95% while Japan’s Nikkei average edged up 0.16% to hit another record high. European stocks moved up modestly. The US stocks ended mixed yesterday as tech-heavy Nasdaq fell 1.20% although the Dow managed to end the day slightly higher.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee settles down]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-settles-down/1679921</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679921</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 91.1700 per Dollar on Friday (27 February 2026), versus its previous close of 91.0550 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Omnitech Engineering IPO subscribed 1.14 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/omnitech-engineering-ipo-subscribed-114-times/1679920</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679920</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Omnitech Engineering received bids for 2,16,31,632 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Friday (27 February 2026).

Omnitech Engineering received bids for 2,16,31,632 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Friday (27 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.14 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026, and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 66 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue comprises both an offer for sale and a fresh issue of equity shares (of Rs 5 face value) worth aggregating to Rs 165 crore and Rs 418 crore, respectively. The entire portion of the offer for sale is by Udaykumar Arunkumar Parekh. Of the net proceeds, the company proposed to utilize Rs 50 crore towards repayment and/or prepayment, in full or in part, of certain outstanding borrowings availed by the company; Rs 233.558 crore towards setting up of two new manufacturing facilities at Village Chhapara (in Rajkot District) [with Rs 132.844 crore for facility 1 and Rs 100.714 crore for facility 2]; Rs 18.698 crore for funding towards capital expenditure requirements for purchase and installation of solar panels on the rooftop at, and purchase of new equipment/machinery for, the existing manufacturing facility at Village Chhapara; and the balance towards general corporate purposes. Outstanding borrowings at the end of Sep 2025 stood at Rs 382.913 crore. Omnitech Engineering (OEL), promoted by Udaykumar Arunkumar Parekh, is a key player in high-precision components and assemblies, serving global clients across energy, automation, and industrial equipment sectors. The company operates 3 strategically located facilities near Mundra Port, with exports contributing approximately 79% of revenue. As of September 2025, OEL’s order book stood at Rs 1,765 crore, representing 5x FY25 sales, highlighting robust demand and strong business momentum. Ahead of the IPO of Omnitech Engineering on 24 February 2026, the company raised Rs 174.59 crore from anchor investors by allotting 76.91 lakh shares at Rs 227 each to 17 anchor investors. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 27.79 crore and sales of Rs 228.17 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Factory data, services activity & industrial production numbers to remain in focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/factory-data-services-activity-industrial-production-numbers-to-remain-in-focus/1679919</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679919</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equity markets enter the next week with a significant boost from domestic macro data, despite persistent global trade anxieties.

Indian equity markets enter the next week with a significant boost from domestic macro data, despite persistent global trade anxieties. The headline event was India’s Q3 FY26 GDP growth, which came in at a robust 7.8% under the newly revised 2022-23 base series, comfortably beating the widely reported estimate of 7.4%. This resilience is further supported by a cooling inflation trajectory, with January CPI settling at a multi-month low of 2.75%. While domestic fundamentals appear rock-solid, global cues remain a mixed bag. Latest data showed that the U.S. core PCE remained sticky at 3.0%, while China’s factory activity slipped into contraction with a January PMI of 49.3, signaling fragile global demand. Going ahead, themes like banking and auto could witnessed renewed interest from investors in the wake of strong credit growth and rural recovery. Caution would prevail with respect to export-oriented IT stocks as new chapters from the “Claude Code” get published. In India, the final reading for the HSBC Manufacturing PMI for the month of February would be unveiled on Monday (02 March 2026). The HSBC India Manufacturing PMI rose to 57.5 in February 2026 from 55.4 in January, preliminary estimates showed. This signals robust expansion in factory activity and marks a four-month high, as output growth accelerated, supported by stronger domestic demand, while new orders increased at the fastest pace since last November. Monday would also see the release of Industrial Production data for January 2026. The industrial production in India rose by 7.9% from the previous year in December of 2025, picking up from the upwardly revised 7.2% advance in the earlier month, marking the sharpest pace of growth since October of 2023. On Wednesday (04 March 2026), the final reading for the HSBC Services PMI and the HSBC Composite PMI for the month of February would be made public. The HSBC India Services PMI edged down to 58.4 in February 2026 from 58.5 in January, pointing to a slightly slower but still strong expansion in services activity, preliminary estimates showed. While overall business activity softened marginally, services firms recorded a notable acceleration in new export orders, with international sales rising at the fastest pace since August 2025. The HSBC India Composite PMI increased to 59.3 in February 2026 from a final 58.4 in the previous month, flash data showed. It was the highest reading since last November, amid a quicker upturn in factory production, as growth of services activity was broadly similar to that in January. On Friday (06 March 2026), the Foreign Exchange Reserves position for the period ended on February 27 would be released. Foreign Exchange Reserves in India decreased to $723,610 million in the week eneded on February 20 from $725,730 million in the previous week. In China, the RatingDog Manufacturing PMI for February 2026 would be released on Monday (02 March 2026). The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI increased to 50.3 in January 2026 from December’s reading of 50.1. The year-to-date (YTD) Foreign Direct Investment for January 2026 would be announced on the same day. Foreign direct investment (FDI) into China fell 9.5% to CNY 747.77 billion in 2025, following a sharp 24.7% decline in 2024 and marking the third consecutive year of contraction. On Wednesday (04 March 2026), the NBS Manufacturing PMI and the NBS Non-Manufacturing PMI for the month of February would be unveiled. China’s official NBS Manufacturing PMI fell to 49.3 in January 2026 from 50.1 in the previous month. The latest reading signaled a loss of momentum in factory activity at the start of the year. China’s official NBS Non-Manufacturing PMI fell to 49.4 in January 2024 from 50.2 in the previous month, missing market expectations of 50.3. The deterioration reflected weak post-holiday demand, cautious consumer spending, and persistent stress in the property sector. Wednesday would also see the publication of the RatingDog Services PMI for February 2026. The RatingDog China General Services PMI edged up to 52.3 in January 2026 from December’s six-month low of 52.0. The reading signaled the strongest services-sector expansion since October. In the United States, the ISM Manufacturing PMI for the month of February would be made public on Monday (02 March 2026). The ISM Manufacturing PMI for the US unexpectedly rose to 52.6 in January 2026 from 47.9 in December. On Wednesday (04 March 2026), the ISM Services PMI for February 2026 would be released. The ISM Services PMI for the US steadied at 53.8 in January 2026, the same as a downwardly revised 53.8 in December. On Friday (06 March 2026), the Non Farm Payrolls data for the month of February would be announced. The US economy added 130K payrolls in January 2026, much higher than a downwardly revised 48K rise in December. The Retail Sales data for January 2026 would also be made public on the same day. US retail sales unexpectedly stalled in December 2025, following a 0.6% increase in November. Friday would also see the unveiling of the Unemployment Rate for February 2026. The US unemployment rate ticked down to 4.3% in January 2026 from 4.4% in December. The number of unemployed declined by 141,000 to 7.36 million, while total employment rose by 528,000 to 164.52 million.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Deposits with Scheduled commercial banks grew by 10.5% as at end Dec-25]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/deposits-with-scheduled-commercial-banks-grew-by-105-as-at-end-dec-25/1679918</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679918</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to latest Reserve Bank of India (RBI) data, deposits with Scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) grew (y-o-y) by 10.5 per cent as at end-December 2025 as compared to 11.0 per cent a year ago and 9.9 per cent a quarter ago.

According to latest Reserve Bank of India (RBI) data, deposits with Scheduled commercial banks (SCBs) grew (y-o-y) by 10.5 per cent as at end-December 2025 as compared to 11.0 per cent a year ago and 9.9 per cent a quarter ago. Branches across all population groups, except metropolitan, recorded improvement in deposit growth in December 2025 from a year ago. Deposit growth (y-o-y) pertaining to public sector banks improved to 9.9 per cent in December 2025 as compared to 9.1 per cent last year, whereas the same for private sector banks decelerated by 2.1 percentage points during the said period and stood at 11.3 per cent in December 2025. Term deposits, the prime driver of deposit accumulation, recorded 11.5 per cent growth (y-o-y) in December 2025 and outpaced the growth of current deposits (11.1 per cent) and savings deposits (8.3 per cent). The household sector remained the largest contributor with 60.1 per cent of deposits as at end-December 2025. During first three quarters of FY:2025-26 i.e., April-December 2025, the household sector drove more than three-fourths of total change in SCBs’ deposits. The contribution of female depositors in total SCB’s deposits inched up to 20.8 per cent in December 2025 as compared to 20.6 per cent a year ago. The share of Deposits held by senior citizens increased to 20.7 per cent in December 2025 from 20.2 per cent a year ago. Nearly 70.5 per cent of term deposits were having the original maturity of one to three years as of December 2025, whereas 19.5 per cent of the term deposits were short-term deposits with original maturity period up to one year. The transmission effects of monetary easing phase were evident, as the share of term deposits offering interest rate of ‘less than 7 per cent’ rose to 56.3 per cent in December 2025 from 29.2 per cent a year ago.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end with major losses; Nifty ends below 25,200 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-with-major-losses-nifty-ends-below-25200-level/1679903</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679903</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equity benchmarks ended the week lower, due to sustained foreign institutional investor (FII) outflows and a sharp correction in information technology stocks.

Indian equity benchmarks ended the week lower, due to sustained foreign institutional investor (FII) outflows and a sharp correction in information technology stocks. Volatility linked to the monthly F&O expiry further amplified market swings. Additionally, weak global cues and heightened geopolitical tensions kept investor sentiment cautious. Despite brief mid-week recoveries, persistent selling in index heavyweights led to a negative weekly close. In the week ended on Friday, 27 February 2026, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 1,527.52 points or 1.84% to settle at 81,287.19. The Nifty 50 index fell 392.6 points or 1.53% to settle at 25,178.65. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index fell 1.09% to close at 16,007.94. The BSE 250 Small-Cap index declined 0.86% to close at 6,290.95. Weekly Index Movement: The key equity indices ended with moderate gains on Monday, extending a two-day rally after the US Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs. Investors will monitor crude oil prices and movements in gold prices. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 479.95 points or 0.58% to 83,294.66. The Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. The key equity benchmarks suffered a major setback on Tuesday, as a brutal sell-off in the information technology sector dragged the market into the deep red. The expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE intensified volatility. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,068.74 points or 1.28% to 82,225.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 288.35 points or 1.12% to 25,424.65. The key domestic indices equity benchmarks managed to claw back some ground on Wednesday, ending marginally in the green after a highly volatile session. The Sensex finished with a slight gain of 50.15 points or 0.06% to settle at 82,276.07, while the Nifty 50 advanced 57.70 points or (0.23%) to close at 25,482.35. The key equity Benchmark benchmarks ended in sideways trend on Thursday, as market participants monitored Prime Minster Narendra Modi’s visit to Israel. The visit comes amid heightened geopolitical tensions in the region, U.S. warnings, and evolving global diplomatic dynamics, adding a layer of caution to market sentiment. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 558.72 points or 0.66% to 83,674.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 146.65 points or 0.57% to 25,807.20. Domestic equity indices ended sharply lower on Friday, as investors turned cautious amid sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) and weak global cues. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 961.42 points or 1.17% to 81,287.19. The Nifty 50 index dropped 317.90 points or 1.25% to 25,178.65. Two Banks Flag Fraud Cases IDFC First Bank slumped 12.06%. The bank said that it has uncovered fraudulent transactions worth around Rs 590 crore at one of its branches in Chandigarh, allegedly involving a few employees. In a regulatory filing made on Sunday, the private sector bank said that based on a preliminary internal assessment (upon receipt of communication from a particular Department of Government of Haryana), the bank has identified an incident involving unauthorized and fraudulent activities by certain employees at a particular branch in Chandigarh and potentially involving other counterparties. Detailing the events that led to the aforementioned discover, the bank stated that it had received a request from a particular Department of Haryana Government for closure of its account and transfer of funds to another bank. In the process, certain discrepancies were observed in the amount mentioned vis-à-vis the balance in the account. Meanwhile, AU Small Finance Bank slumped 6.83%. The Haryana government decisively removed the bank from its list of empanelled lenders due to serious allegations of fraudulent activities. In a statement, the bank said that on 18 February 2026, it received a separate communication from the department seeking information regarding suspected unauthorised transactions between a government account and another customer account. As of 21 February 2026, deposits from the Government of Haryana with AU Small Finance Bank stood at Rs 538 crore across nearly 200 accounts, accounting for about 0.4% of the bank's overall deposits as of 31 December 2026. Economy: India’s economy expanded 7.8% in the December quarter, beating expectations and reflecting the impact of a revamped GDP calculation framework aimed at improving accuracy. Growth for the previous quarter has been revised up to 8.4% from 8.2% under the new series, while the full-year FY26 estimate has been raised to 7.6% from 7.4%. In January, the Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation introduced changes to the GDP, inflation and industrial production series, including shifting the GDP base year to FY23 from 2012, to enhance data quality and policy relevance. Pakistan and Afghanistan conflict: Pakistan has launched Operation Ghazab lil-Haq against the Afghan Taliban, citing what it described as “unprovoked aggression” along the border, as clashes between the two neighbours intensified. In a declared “open war,” Pakistan launched overnight airstrikes in Afghanistan, heavily bombing multiple key cities, including Kabul and Kandahar, and claiming that 133 people were killed in what Islamabad called a “strong and effective” retaliation for “unprovoked firing” from across the border. PM Modi Visit to Israel: Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s visit to Israel comes against the backdrop of ongoing India–Israel free trade agreement talks aimed at enhancing trade and investment between the two countries Israeli President Isaac Herzog described India as “an essential part of a great future for the Middle East”, while emphasising the growing importance of India-Israel cooperation during his bilateral meeting with Prime Minister Narendra Modi as part of the latter’s two-day state visit to the country. Stocks in Spotlight: JSW Infrastructure rose 0.74%. The company’s board approved the issuance of 25 crore equity shares with face value of Rs 2 each, to fund its multi-year expansion program. The fundraising may be undertaken through one or more of following modes such as qualified institutional placement (QIP), further public offer (FPO), rights issue or through any other permissible mode. The issuance of shares will also enable compliance with SEBI’s Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) requirement. As previously guided, the company remains on a strong growth trajectory, with operating EBITDA expected to double by FY28 from FY26 levels to reach around Rs 5,000 crore. This outlook is underpinned by clear execution visibility across the under-construction Projects in the Ports segment and the transition of rolling assets from capex to EBITDA contribution within the Logistics segment. R&B Denims slumped 11.46%. The company secured sales orders aggregating to around Rs 215.88 crore for the supply of around 12,000,000 meters of denim fabric products from established merchant exporters. Shilpa Medicare added 3.19%. The company said that its subsidiary Shilpa Biologicals and SteinCares have entered into a strategic licensing agreement to commercialize a biosimilar across Latin America. Under the agreement, SteinCares will hold exclusive rights to register, commercialize, and distribute the biosimilar across the region while Shilpa Biologicals will complete product development and provide long-term commercial manufacturing from its facility in Dharwad, India. Schaeffler India rallied 12.10%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 31.5% to Rs 327.96 crore on 26.9% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,643.06 crore in Q4 CY2025 over Q4 CY2024. Dynacons Systems & Solutions fell 1.78%. The company has secured a contract worth Rs 108.88 crore from Punjab & Sind Bank for the supply, implementation and management of on-premises private cloud infrastructure. Sundaram Clayton surged 4.99%. The company’s board approved the appointment of R Venkatesh as chief executive officer (CEO) with effect from 1 April 2026. b The development comes after board approved the resignation of Vivek S Joshi as CEO with effect from 31st march 2026, due to personal reasons. Aurobindo Pharma added 5.25%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Eugia Pharma Specialities, has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) to manufacture and market Everolimus tablets. Kirloskar Brothers (KBL) declined 0.77%. The company said that it has secured orders worth Rs 214 crore from Adani Power and its subsidiaries for supply and installation of pump systems for thermal power projects. The scope of work includes supply and erection, testing and commissioning of circulating water pumps (concrete volute pump technology) and auxiliary cooling water pumps, along with associated electrical and control systems. The projects are located in Madhya Pradesh, Assam, Chhattisgarh and Bihar. Samhi Hotels declined 1.60%. The company through its wholly-owned subsidiary, Duet India Hotels (Navi Mumbai), has signed operating agreements with Marriott Hotels India for two upcoming hotel projects in Navi Mumbai and Thane. Global Markets: China’s central bank kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged, maintaining the one-year Loan Prime Rate (LPR) at 3% and the five-year LPR at 3.5%. In the U.S., the economy expanded at an annualized rate of 1.4% in Q4 2025, the slowest pace since Q1 2025. This follows a 4.4% growth recorded in Q3 and came in well below market forecasts of 3%, according to the advance estimate.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's GDP growth softens to 7.8% in Q3FY26 compared to 8.4% in Q2, fiscal year GDP estimated to expand 7.6%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-gdp-growth-softens-to-78-in-q3fy26-compared-to-84-in-q2-fiscal-year-gdp-estimated-to-expand-76/1679901</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679901</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ministry of Statistics stated today that India’s gross domestic product (GDP) growth slowed to 7.8% in the third quarter of fiscal year 2026, easing compared to previous quarter's 8.4% rise.

Ministry of Statistics stated today that India’s gross domestic product (GDP) growth slowed to 7.8% in the third quarter of fiscal year 2026, easing compared to previous quarter's 8.4% rise. Real GDP or GDP at Constant Prices in Q3 of FY 2025-26 is estimated at Rs 84.54 lakh crore, against Rs 78.41 lakh crore in Q3 of FY 2024-25. Nominal GDP or GDP at Current Prices in Q3 of FY 2025-26 is estimated at Rs 90.91 lakh crore, against Rs 83.46 lakh crore in Q3 of FY 2024-25, showing a growth rate of 8.9%. Real GDP or GDP at Constant Prices is estimated to attain a level of Rs 322.58 lakh crore in the FY 2025-26, against the First Revised Estimate (FRE) of GDP for the year 2024-25 of Rs 299.89 lakh crore. The growth rate in Real GDP during 2025-26 is estimated at 7.6% as compared to 7.1 % in 2024-25. Nominal GDP or GDP at Current Prices is estimated to attain a level of Rs 345.47 lakh crore in the year 2025-26, against Rs 318.07 lakh crore in 2024-25, showing a growth rate of 8.6%. Ministry of Statistics and Programme Implementation (MoSPI) released a New Series of Annual and Quarterly National Accounts Estimates with base year 2022–23, which replaces the previous series with base year of 2011–12. Detailed data showed that agriculture sector growth eased to 1.7% in Q3FY26 compared to 2.8% in previous quarter. Manufacturing growth edged up marginally from 13.2% to 13.3%. In services, Financial, Real Estate, Ownership of dwelling, IT and Professional services growth raced higher to 11% in Q3FY26 compared to 9.9% in previous quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices tumble as FII selling, geopolitical tensions drag Nifty below 25,200]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-tumble-as-fii-selling-geopolitical-tensions-drag-nifty-below-25200/1679902</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679902</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, pressured by continued foreign institutional investor outflows and escalating geopolitical tensions.

Domestic equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, pressured by continued foreign institutional investor outflows and escalating geopolitical tensions. Investor sentiment remained fragile amid rising hostilities between Pakistan and Afghanistan and lingering uncertainty over US-Iran talks. The Nifty slipped below the 25,200 mark, weighed down by losses in auto and FMCG stocks. The index opened on a weak note and stayed under sustained selling pressure through most of the session. A fresh wave of selling in the final hours intensified the decline, pulling the benchmark closer to the day’s low by the closing bell. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 961.42 points or 1.17% to 81,287.19. The Nifty 50 index dropped 317.90 points or 1.25% to 25,178.65. Bharti Airtel (down 2.47%), ICICI Bank (down 1.82%) and HDFC Bank (down 1.24%) were major Nifty drags today. The broader market outperformed the key equity indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tumbled 1.09% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index slumped 0.86%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 1,660 shares rose and 2,528 shares fell. A total of 196 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 4.89% to 13.70. Economy: India’s economy expanded 7.8% in the December quarter, beating expectations and reflecting the impact of a revamped GDP calculation framework aimed at improving accuracy. Growth for the previous quarter has been revised up to 8.4% from 8.2% under the new series, while the full-year FY26 estimate has been raised to 7.6% from 7.4%. In January, the Ministry of Statistics & Programme Implementation introduced changes to the GDP, inflation and industrial production series, including shifting the GDP base year to FY23 from 2012, to enhance data quality and policy relevance. Pakistan and Afghanistan conflict: Pakistan has launched "Operation Ghazab lil-Haq" against the Afghan Taliban, accusing it of unprovoked aggression along the border as tensions sharply escalated between the two sides. Declaring what it described as an open war, Pakistan carried out overnight airstrikes across Afghanistan, targeting major cities including Kabul and Kandahar. Islamabad said the strikes were a strong and effective response to cross-border firing and claimed that 133 people were killed in the operation. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.15% to 6.680 compared with the previous session close of 6.690. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.0600 compared with its close of 90.9150 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.34% to Rs 160,254. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.04% to 97.76. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.65% to 3.991. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 66 cents or 0.93% to $71.41 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 280 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. Most European shares advanced on Friday as traders parsed through several earnings reports and economic data at the end of the week. Inflation figures from Germany, France, and Spain are set to be published, alongside unemployment data from Germany and France. Investors are also watching for the latest U.K. housing price data, which could provide further insight into the strength of the property market and broader economic conditions. Most Asian markets ended higher, supported by regional buying interest. This came despite a weak overnight session on Wall Street, where U.S. indices closed lower after Nvidia shares tumbled, even though the company reported quarterly earnings beat. Overnight on Wall Street, the S&P 500 pulled back after the latest results from tech titan Nvidia and software giant Salesforce failed to boost the broader market. The broad market index fell 0.54%, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.18%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.03%. Nvidia shares fell more than 5%, even after the chip giant posted fourth-quarter earnings and revenue that were higher than widely reported forecasts. On the other end, Salesforce, which has been one of the biggest victims of recent artificial intelligence disruption fears, rose 4% after the software company’s latest quarterly results were higher than widely reported forecasts on the top and bottom lines. However, the company issued a disappointing fiscal 2027 revenue forecast. Sentiment has been fragile in software and cybersecurity stocks this year as worries remain about the rapidly developing capabilities of AI products that could interfere with incumbent software vendors’ businesses. New Listing: Shares of Gaudium IVF and Women Health settled at Rs 80.48 on the BSE, representing a premium of 1.87% compared with the issue price of Rs 79. The stock was listed at Rs 83, reflecting a premium of 5.06% to the issue price. The stock has hit a high of Rs 87.15 and a low of Rs 79.05. On the BSE, 5.96 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Stocks in Spotlight: Vishal Mega Mart declined 7.68% to Rs 117.80 after multiple block deals resulted in nearly 14% of the company’s equity changing hands on the exchanges. Samayat Services LLP, which held a 54.09% stake in Vishal Mega Mart as of 31 December 2025, planned to offload up to 30.5 crore shares at Rs 115 each. Netweb Technologies India gained 4.36% after announcing a strategic partnership with Vertiv to jointly develop and validate GPU-based AI infrastructure solutions. The leading Indian high-end computing solutions provider will collaborate with Vertiv to engineer and validate its in-house GPU compute platforms alongside Vertiv’s integrated, end-to-end AI data center solutions. MSTC rose 1.95% after it secured a contract from Coal India to provide end-to-end services for Non-Regulated Sector (NRS) linkage auctions. The mandate is valid for a period of three years. Kirloskar Brothers (KBL) shed 0.55%. The company said that it has secured orders worth Rs 214 crore from Adani Power and its subsidiaries for supply and installation of pump systems for thermal power projects. The scope of work includes supply and erection, testing and commissioning of circulating water pumps (concrete volute pump technology) and auxiliary cooling water pumps, along with associated electrical and control systems. The projects are located in Madhya Pradesh, Assam, Chhattisgarh and Bihar. Steel Exchange India slipped 1.08%. The company announced that its board will meet on Wednesday (04 March 2026) to consider a proposal to raise funds amounting to Rs 350 crore. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services slipped 1.33%. The company has entered into multiple agreements to provide its corporate expense management solutions to leading domestic entities. The company will offer Zaggle Corporate Expense Cards to employees and associates of Chennai Super Kings and Superking Ventures. Each contract is valid for a period of one year. Separately, Zaggle has signed a five-year agreement with Saurashtra Cement to deploy its Zaggle Save platform for employee expense management and benefits administration. Mamata Machinery rose 0.43%. The company announced that it has secured its first Rest of the World (ROW) order for its Packaging Machinery Segment from a customer in South Africa. Indian Oil Corporation rose 0.56%. The company has announced that a meeting of its board of directors is scheduled for Friday, 6 March 2026, to consider the declaration of a second interim dividend for the financial year 2025–26. Mastek shed 0.35%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Mastek (UK) has secured a five-year engineering, integration, and product development contract from the UK’s Home Office, with an overall budget of approximately euro 49 million ($67 million). Huhtamaki India declined 1.68%. The company said that its board has approved the appointment of Anil Kaul as chief financial officer (CFO) of the company with effect from 27 February 2026. Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (GMDC) fell 1.17%. The company said that it has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with NTPC to jointly explore opportunities in coal and lignite gasification and downstream utilisation. Jio Financial Services shed 0.31%. The company said that it has subscribed to 3,35,71,923 equity shares of Rs 10 each of Jio Credit (JCL), a wholly owned subsidiary, for cash at a premium of Rs 585.70 per equity share, aggregating to Rs 1,999.88 crore. NBCC (India) lost 1.39%. The company has received work orders worth approximately Rs 775.27 crore from the Delhi Development Authority (DDA) for the comprehensive redevelopment of staff quarters in New Delhi. Dee Development Engineers dropped 2.57%. The company has secured a letter of intent (LoI) for manufacturing alloy steel seamless pipes at its new forged seamless pipe plant in Anjar, Gujarat. IPO Update: Omnitech Engineering received bids for 2,16,02,526 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:57 IST on Friday (27 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.14 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026 and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's April-January fiscal deficit at 63% of FY26 target]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-april-january-fiscal-deficit-at-63-of-fy26-target/1679896</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679896</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s fiscal deficit for the first ten months of the current financial year reached ₹9.81 lakh crore, accounting for 63% of the full-year budget estimate, according to government data released on Friday.

India’s fiscal deficit for the first ten months of the current financial year reached ₹9.81 lakh crore, accounting for 63% of the full-year budget estimate, according to government data released on Friday. This marks an improvement compared with the same period last year, when the deficit had touched 74.5% of the annual target. Between April and January, the Centre’s total receipts stood at ₹27.09 lakh crore, representing 79.5% of the budgeted goal. Overall expenditure during the period was ₹36.90 lakh crore, or 74.3% of the full-year target. Revenue collections showed steady progress. Revenue receipts amounted to ₹26.52 lakh crore, including ₹20.94 lakh crore in tax revenue and ₹5.57 lakh crore from non-tax sources. Tax collections reached 78.3% of the annual estimate, higher than the 74.4% recorded in the corresponding period last year. Non-tax revenue achieved 83.5% of the target, though this was lower than the 88.1% level seen a year earlier. A significant boost to non-tax revenue came from the Reserve Bank of India’s dividend transfer of ₹2.69 lakh crore to the central government, up from ₹2.11 lakh crore in the previous fiscal. Meanwhile, the revenue deficit for the April–January period stood at ₹1.96 lakh crore, equivalent to 37.3% of the budgeted estimate for the full financial year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's share in global trade poised for a major leap]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-share-in-global-trade-poised-for-a-major-leap/1679895</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679895</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s role and share in global trade are poised for a major leap in line with the country’s ambition and journey towards Viksit Bharat, government noted in a latest update.

India’s role and share in global trade are poised for a major leap in line with the country’s ambition and journey towards Viksit Bharat, government noted in a latest update. Over the past decades, India has significantly deepened its integration with global markets, supported by strong export performance, resilient services trade, and an expanding network of trade partnerships, reflecting growing competitiveness and adaptability to changing global demand dynamics. The country has not only increased its share in global trade but has also diversified its trading partnerships. According to UNCTAD’s Trade and Development Report 2025, India ranks third among Global South economies in terms of the diversity index of trade partnerships. With an index score higher than that of all countries in the Global North, India’s trade ecosystem underscores resilience in the face of tariff uncertainties and emerging global challenges. An expanding network of FTAs strengthens India’s trade strategy by ensuring reliable market access. These agreements help reinforce the country’s trajectory towards a stronger global trade presence by supporting export-oriented firms expand production and integrate more deeply into global value chains.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty March futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-march-futures-trade-at-premium/1679893</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679893</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 30 March 2026 futures closed at 25,341, a premium of 162.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,178.65 in the cash market.

The Nifty 30 March 2026 futures closed at 25,341, a premium of 162.35 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,178.65 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index tumbled 317.90 points or 1.25% to 25,178.65. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 4.89% to 13.70. Infosys, HDFC Bank and L&T Finance were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The March 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 30 March 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 961 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,200 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-961-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25200-level/1679892</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679892</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended sharply lower today, weighed down by sustained FII selling and soft global cues.

The key equity indices ended sharply lower today, weighed down by sustained FII selling and soft global cues. Investor sentiment was further hit by rising tensions between Pakistan and Afghanistan, alongside unresolved US-Iran talks. Nifty closed below the 25,200 level, reflecting a cautious mood across the board. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 961.42 points or 1.17% to 81,287.19. The Nifty 50 index dropped 317.90 points or 1.25% to 25,178.65. The broader market outperformed the key equity indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tumbled 1.09% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index slumped 0.86%. The market breadth was strong. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 4.89% to 13.70. Among the sectoral indices, the Media index (up 0.60%), the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 0.17%) and the Nifty IT index (up 0.16%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Realty index (down 2.26%), the Nifty Auto index (down 1.86%) and the Nifty FMCG index (down 1.69%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy India’s gross domestic product (GDP) grew 7.8% in the third quarter of FY26, surpassing market estimates of 7.4%, supported by robust festive demand and revisions to the country’s economic data series. Economic activity received a boost during the quarter as higher consumer spending in the festive season lifted overall output. Additionally, GST rate cuts across select sectors provided further momentum, contributing to stronger-than-expected growth. Pakistan and Afghanistan conflict Pakistan has launched Operation Ghazab lil-Haq against the Afghan Taliban, citing what it described as “unprovoked aggression” along the border, as clashes between the two neighbors intensified. In a declared “open war,” Pakistan launched overnight airstrikes in Afghanistan, heavily bombing multiple key cities, including Kabul and Kandahar, and claiming that 133 people were killed in what Islamabad called a “strong and effective” retaliation for “unprovoked firing” from across the border. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.15% to 6.680 compared with the previous session close of 6.690. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.0600 compared with its close of 90.9150 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.34% to Rs 160,254. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.04% to 97.76. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.65% to 3.991. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 66 cents or 0.93% to $71.41 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares traded mixed on Friday as traders parsed through several earnings reports and economic data at the end of the week. Inflation figures from Germany, France, and Spain are set to be published, alongside unemployment data from Germany and France. Investors are also watching for the latest U.K. housing price data, which could provide further insight into the strength of the property market and broader economic conditions. Most Asian markets ended higher, supported by regional buying interest. This came despite a weak overnight session on Wall Street, where U.S. indices closed lower after Nvidia shares tumbled, even though the company reported quarterly earnings beat. In Asian tech stocks, SK Hynix, which is a key supplier of high-bandwidth memory to Nvidia, dipped over 2%. Samsung Electronics, which has been a decades-old partner of Nvidia, was down 0.69%. Gold prices held broadly steady on Friday, with investors digesting the previous day's U.S.-Iran nuclear talks, while the dollar, hovering near three-week highs, pressured the yellow metal. An Omani mediator of U.S. and Iran nuclear talks has reportedly given an optimistic readout over the latest round of negotiations, but uncertainty still hung over energy markets with no sign of a breakthrough that would avert potential U.S. strikes. Following these developments, Brent crude futures settled down 10 cents, or 0.14%, to $70.75 a barrel. Overnight on Wall Street, the S&P 500 pulled back after the latest results from tech titan Nvidia and software giant Salesforce failed to boost the broader market. The broad market index fell 0.54% to end at 6,908.86, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.18% and closed at 22,878.38. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 17.05 points, or 0.03%, to settle at 49,499.20. Nvidia shares fell more than 5%, even after the chip giant posted fourth-quarter earnings and revenue that were higher than widely reported forecasts. On the other end, Salesforce, which has been one of the biggest victims of recent artificial intelligence disruption fears, rose 4% after the software company’s latest quarterly results were higher than widely reported forecasts on the top and bottom lines. However, the company issued a disappointing fiscal 2027 revenue forecast. Sentiment has been fragile in software and cybersecurity stocks this year as worries remain about the rapidly developing capabilities of AI products that could interfere with incumbent software vendors’ businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index falls 2.26%, NIFTY Tumbles 1.25% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-falls-226-nifty-tumbles-125/1679891</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679891</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index ended down 2.26% at 780.6 today.

Nifty Realty index ended down 2.26% at 780.6 today. The index has gained 1.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, SignatureGlobal India Ltd added 4.17%, Godrej Properties Ltd dropped 3.72% and Phoenix Mills Ltd slipped 3.34%. The Nifty Realty index has fallen 4.00% over last one year compared to the 11.68% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Auto index has dropped 1.86% and Nifty FMCG index has dropped 1.69% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has slid 1.25% to close at 25178.65 while the SENSEX has dropped 1.17% to close at 81287.19 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends with major losses; Nifty settles below 25,200 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-with-major-losses-nifty-settles-below-25200-level/1679879</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679879</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity indices ended sharply lower on Friday, as investors turned cautious amid sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) and weak global cues.

Domestic equity indices ended sharply lower on Friday, as investors turned cautious amid sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) and weak global cues. Market sentiment was further weighed down by escalating geopolitical tensions following the declaration of open conflict between Pakistan and Afghanistan. In addition, US-Iran talks ended without a resolution, adding to overall uncertainty and keeping risk appetite subdued. Nifty ended below the 25,200 level. Realty, metal and FMCG shares declined, while media, consumer durables and IT stocks advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 961.42 points or 1.17% to 81,287.19. The Nifty 50 index dropped 317.90 points or 1.25% to 25,178.65. The broader market outperformed the key equity indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tumbled 1.09% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index slumped 0.86%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 1,668 shares rose and 2,518 shares fell. A total of 198 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 4.89% to 13.70. Pakistan and Afghanistan conflict Pakistan has launched Operation Ghazab lil-Haq against the Afghan Taliban, citing what it described as “unprovoked aggression” along the border, as clashes between the two neighbours intensified. In a declared “open war,” Pakistan launched overnight airstrikes in Afghanistan, heavily bombing multiple key cities, including Kabul and Kandahar, and claiming that 133 people were killed in what Islamabad called a “strong and effective” retaliation for “unprovoked firing” from across the border. Economy India’s gross domestic product (GDP) grew 7.8% in the third quarter of FY26, surpassing market estimates of 7.4%, supported by robust festive demand and revisions to the country’s economic data series. Economic activity received a boost during the quarter as higher consumer spending in the festive season lifted overall output. Additionally, GST rate cuts across select sectors provided further momentum, contributing to stronger-than-expected growth. New Listing: Shares of Gaudium IVF and Women Health were at Rs 80 on the BSE, representing a premium of 1.27% as compared with the issue price of Rs 79. The stock was listed at Rs 83, reflecting a premium of 5.06% to the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 87.15 and a low of 79.05. On the BSE, over 5.96 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. IPO Update: Omnitech Engineering received bids for 1,83,50,310 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Friday (27 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.97 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026 and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index slumped 2.27% to 780.50. The index rose 0.23% in the past trading session. Godrej Properties (down 3.97%), Sobha (down 3.56%), Phoenix Mills (down 3.48%), Brigade Enterprises (down 3.18%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 2.93%), Lodha Developers (down 2.4%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.52%), DLF (down 1.21%) and Anant Raj (down 1.19%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Netweb Technologies India gained 4.17% after announcing a strategic partnership with Vertiv to jointly develop and validate GPU-based AI infrastructure solutions. The leading Indian high-end computing solutions provider will collaborate with Vertiv to engineer and validate its in-house GPU compute platforms alongside Vertiv’s integrated, end-to-end AI data center solutions. Gem Aromatics shed 0.28%. The company’s subsidiary, Krystal Ingredients has commenced the production of additional products, including Gem Cool 5 (Cooling Agents) and Safranal (Citral Derivatives) at its Dahej facility, Gujarat. Kirloskar Brothers (KBL) shed 0.78%. The company said that it has secured orders worth Rs 214 crore from Adani Power and its subsidiaries for supply and installation of pump systems for thermal power projects. The scope of work includes supply and erection, testing and commissioning of circulating water pumps (concrete volute pump technology) and auxiliary cooling water pumps, along with associated electrical and control systems. The projects are located in Madhya Pradesh, Assam, Chhattisgarh and Bihar. Steel Exchange India slipped 0.84%. The company announced that its board will meet on Wednesday (04 March 2026) to consider a proposal to raise funds amounting to Rs 350 crore. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services slipped 2.45%. The company has entered into multiple agreements to provide its corporate expense management solutions to leading domestic entities. The company will offer Zaggle Corporate Expense Cards to employees and associates of Chennai Super Kings and Superking Ventures. Each contract is valid for a period of one year. Separately, Zaggle has signed a five-year agreement with Saurashtra Cement to deploy its Zaggle Save platform for employee expense management and benefits administration. Mamata Machinery rose 0.68%. The company announced that it has secured its first Rest of the World (ROW) order for its Packaging Machinery Segment from a customer in South Africa. Indian Oil Corporation rose 0.46%. The company has announced that a meeting of its board of directors is scheduled for Friday, 6 March 2026, to consider the declaration of a second interim dividend for the financial year 2025–26. Mastek shed 0.45%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Mastek (UK) has secured a five-year engineering, integration, and product development contract from the UK’s Home Office, with an overall budget of approximately euro 49 million ($67 million). Huhtamaki India declined 1.37%. The company said that its board has approved the appointment of Anil Kaul as chief financial officer (CFO) of the company with effect from 27 February 2026. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) shed 0.31%. The company said that it has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, Bharat Petroleum Global Energy Services (Singapore) Pte to setting up trading desk in Singapore. Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (GMDC) fell 1.34%. The company said that it has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with NTPC to jointly explore opportunities in coal and lignite gasification and downstream utilisation. Jio Financial Services shed 0.43%. The company said that it has subscribed to 3,35,71,923 equity shares of Rs 10 each of Jio Credit (JCL), a wholly owned subsidiary, for cash at a premium of Rs 585.70 per equity share, aggregating to Rs 1,999.88 crore. Glenmark Pharmaceuticals rose 0.49%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Glenmark USA, will launch Sodium Phosphates InjectionUSP, 15 mM P/5 mL, 45 mM P/15 mL and 150 mM P/50 mL (3 mM P/mL) Single-Dose Vials. NBCC (India) lost 1.74%. The company has received work orders worth approximately Rs 775.27 crore from the Delhi Development Authority (DDA) for the comprehensive redevelopment of staff quarters in New Delhi. Dee Development Engineers dropped 4.01%. The company has secured a letter of intent (LoI) for manufacturing alloy steel seamless pipes at its new forged seamless pipe plant in Anjar, Gujarat. Global Markets: European markets traded mixed on Friday as investors awaited key economic data releases across the region. Inflation figures from Germany, France, and Spain are set to be published, alongside unemployment data from Germany and France. Investors are also watching for the latest U.K. housing price data, which could provide further insight into the strength of the property market and broader economic conditions. Most Asian markets ended in higher, supported by regional buying interest. This came despite a weak overnight session on Wall Street, where U.S. indices closed lower after Nvidia shares tumbled, even though the company reported a quarterly earnings beat. In Asian tech stocks, SK Hynix, which is a key supplier of high-bandwidth memory to Nvidia, dipped over 2%. Samsung Electronics, which has been a decades-old partner of Nvidia, was down 0.69%. Gold prices held broadly steady on Friday, with investors digesting the previous day's U.S.-Iran nuclear talks, while the dollar, hovering near three-week highs, pressured the yellow metal. An Omani mediator of U.S. and Iran nuclear talks has reportedly given an optimistic readout over the latest round of negotiations, but uncertainty still hung over energy markets with no sign of a breakthrough that would avert potential U.S. strikes. Following these developments, Brent crude futures settled down 10 cents, or 0.14%, to $70.75 a barrel. Overnight on Wall Street, the S&P 500 pulled back after the latest results from tech titan Nvidia and software giant Salesforce failed to boost the broader market. The broad market index fell 0.54% to end at 6,908.86, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.18% and closed at 22,878.38. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 17.05 points, or 0.03%, to settle at 49,499.20. Nvidia shares fell more than 5%, even after the chip giant posted fourth-quarter earnings and revenue that were higher than widely reported forescasts. On the other end, Salesforce, which has been one of the biggest victims of recent artificial intelligence disruption fears, rose 4% after the software company’s latest quarterly results were higher than widely reported forecasts on the top and bottom lines. However, the company issued a disappointing fiscal 2027 revenue forecast. Sentiment has been fragile in software and cybersecurity stocks this year as worries remain about the rapidly developing capabilities of AI products that could interfere with incumbent software vendors’ businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GPT Infra acquires 100% stake in Alcon, enters Signalling EPC segment  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gpt-infra-acquires-100-stake-in-alcon-enters-signalling-epc-segment/1679877</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679877</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Alcon is engaged in the business of signalling, telecommunication and allied works for Indian Railways.

Alcon is engaged in the business of signalling, telecommunication and allied works for Indian Railways. Its turnover was Rs 100.20 crore in FY25. The said acquisition will enable the company to augment its product offerings, strengthen its market presence, and accelerate its expansion into the Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) space. Through this transaction, GPT Infraprojects will obtain full management and operational control of Alcon Builders & Engineers. The move aligns with the company’s strategic plan to integrate Alcon’s operations with its own, enabling operational and commercial synergies while creating long-term value for stakeholders. The company acquired a stake for total consideration of Rs 151.83 crore. GPT Infraprojects is the flagship company of GPT Group and is a premier infrastructure company based out of Kolkata. The company operates through two business divisions—infrastructure and sleepers. The company is engaged in the execution of civil and infrastructure projects, especially large bridges and ROBs for railways. In sleepers, the company manufactures and supplies concrete sleepers for railways in India and Africa. The company reported a 5.9% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 20.15 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 21.42 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 2.1% year-on-year to Rs 283.93 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025, from Rs 278.08 crore a year ago. The scrip shed 0.32% to Rs 123.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GPTInfraproject_86027425388_26416.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold holds firm after 10% February surge]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-holds-firm-after-10-february-surge/1679867</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679867</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold traded with marginal gains near $5195 per ounce during Asian trade on Friday and was on track to end February with gains of around 10%, supported by strong safe-haven demand amid geopolitical tensions and economic uncertainty.

Gold traded with marginal gains near $5195 per ounce during Asian trade on Friday and was on track to end February with gains of around 10%, supported by strong safe-haven demand amid geopolitical tensions and economic uncertainty. Renewed tensions in the Middle East kept bullion supported after US military deployments near Iran and the lack of progress in nuclear talks this week, although both sides agreed to continue discussions. These factors helped gold recover most of its late-January losses. Additional support came from fresh geopolitical risks in South Asia following reports of conflict between Pakistan and Afghanistan, though the impact remained limited. Ongoing concerns over US trade disruptions and slowing growth in major economies also sustained demand for defensive assets. In domestic markets, MCX gold futures for April delivery traded 0.4% higher at Rs 160288 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Microfinance stocks slide after Bihar clears MFI regulation Bill]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/microfinance-stocks-slide-after-bihar-clears-mfi-regulation-bill/1679865</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679865</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The legislation introduces tighter oversight and compliance requirements for lenders operating in the state.

The legislation introduces tighter oversight and compliance requirements for lenders operating in the state. Fusion Finance fell 5.65%, while Utkarsh Small Finance Bank dropped 5.47%. Spandana Sphoorty Financial declined 1.28%, AU Small Finance Bank slipped 1.27%, Equitas Small Finance Bank fell 1.12% and Jana Small Finance Bank was down 0.4% in trade. The Bill seeks to regulate microfinance institutions and small loan providers, prohibit coercive recovery practices and ensure transparency in lending operations, including fair and clearly disclosed interest rates. Under the new framework, microfinance companies will be required to obtain prior permission from the state finance department before commencing loan disbursement operations in Bihar. Even entities that already hold a licence from the Reserve Bank of India must register with the state’s Director of Institutional Finance before starting business in the state. Registration will be mandatory within 90 days of the commencement of the Act. Without a valid certificate of registration, valid for three years, no entity will be permitted to grant or recover loans in Bihar. Commencing operations without registration will be treated as a criminal offence. The legislation also provides for the establishment of special courts in every district, presided over by a first-class judicial magistrate, to hear disputes relating to interest rates and cases where borrowers are alleged to have been driven to suicide due to usurious or coercive lending practices. Lenders will be required to prominently display the effective rate of interest at their offices, on their websites and in advertisements or brochures. They must also maintain an office in Bihar and execute written loan agreements in Hindi.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Home First Finance Company India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679864</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679864</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Vesuvius India Ltd, CreditAccess Grameen Ltd and JK Tyre & Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 February 2026.

Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Vesuvius India Ltd, CreditAccess Grameen Ltd and JK Tyre & Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 February 2026. Home First Finance Company India Ltd tumbled 7.54% to Rs 1087.55 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.12 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17941 shares in the past one month. Vishal Mega Mart Ltd crashed 7.52% to Rs 118. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 128.18 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.33 lakh shares in the past one month. Vesuvius India Ltd lost 5.87% to Rs 503.55. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 32575 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 90454 shares in the past one month. CreditAccess Grameen Ltd shed 5.56% to Rs 1264.55. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.52 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 29300 shares in the past one month. JK Tyre & Industries Ltd plummeted 5.37% to Rs 502.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 89265 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.29 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HomeFirstFinanceCompanyIndiaLtd_56604898_71865.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Renaissance Global Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/renaissance-global-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679863</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679863</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Flexituff Ventures International Ltd, R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd, Shankar Lal Rampal Dye-Chem Ltd and Fino Payments Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 February 2026.

Flexituff Ventures International Ltd, R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd, Shankar Lal Rampal Dye-Chem Ltd and Fino Payments Bank Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 February 2026. Renaissance Global Ltd crashed 17.70% to Rs 119.75 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 27.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.27 lakh shares in the past one month. Flexituff Ventures International Ltd lost 9.97% to Rs 8.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 7460 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2692 shares in the past one month. R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd tumbled 9.95% to Rs 70.6. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 32150 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5.55 lakh shares in the past one month. Shankar Lal Rampal Dye-Chem Ltd fell 9.62% to Rs 46.7. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4590 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3503 shares in the past one month. Fino Payments Bank Ltd corrected 9.49% to Rs 188.3. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 87017 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6901 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RenaissanceJew_35784122165_27346.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>