<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:26:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-closed-lower/1664666</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664666</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower 90.2550 per Dollar on Tuesday (13 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.2400 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Q3 PAT climbs 20% YoY to Rs 390 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-life-insurance-q3-pat-climbs-20-yoy-to-rs-390-cr/1664653</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664653</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income witnessed a sharp surge of 397.63% YoY, reaching Rs 22,891 crore for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.

Total income witnessed a sharp surge of 397.63% YoY, reaching Rs 22,891 crore for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 447.19 crore, up by 18.99% from Rs 375.82 crore in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, net premium income fell 3.69% YoY to Rs 11,809.26 crore. The first-year gross premium rose 8.86% to Rs 2,081.13 crore, while the renewal premium jumped 5.99% to Rs 6,593.89 crore. However, the single premium declined 21.56% to Rs 3,551 crore. Net commission grew 15.23% YoY to Rs 1,237.51 crore. The company’s value of new business (VNB) stood at Rs 615 crore in Q3 FY26. The company’s retail annualised premium equivalent (APE) grew by 9.9% year-on-year from Rs 1,926 crore in Q3-FY2025 to Rs 2,116 crore in Q3-FY2026. The number of retail policies sold increased 11.7% YoY during the same period. Meanwhile, total APE rose 3.6% YoY to Rs 2,525 crore in Q3 FY26. The assets under management of the company grew by 6.5% year-on-year to Rs 3,30,729 crore at December 31, 2025 from Rs 3,10,414 crore at December 31, 2024. On the nine month basis, the company’s profit jumped 23.5% YoY to Rs 992 crore in 9M FY26, primarily driven by higher investment income from Shareholders funds. Total income increased 8.47% YoY to Rs 59,637.83 crore in 9M FY26. Anup Bagchi, MD & CEO, ICICI Prudential Life Insurance said, “Our 9M-FY2026 performance reflects our ongoing commitment to increasing profitability through balanced business growth. Profit after Tax registered a strong growth of 23.5% year-on-year to ₹ 992 crore in 9M-FY2026. Value of New Business (VNB), which is the measure of profitability for a life insurance company, stood at ₹ 1,664 crore with a margin of 24.4% in 9M-FY2026. In Q3-FY2026, our VNB stood at ₹ 615 crore, on the back of 9.9% year-on-year growth in retail APE. Notably, the number of policies sold increased by 11.7% year-on-year in the same period. Our industry-leading claim settlement ratio of 99.3% in 9M-FY2026, achieved with an average turnaround time of 1.1 days (non-investigative), underscores our commitment to honouring the promises made to our customers and their families.” ICICI Prudential Life is promoted by ICICI Bank and Prudential Corporation Holdings, headquartered in the United Kingdom. The company offers an array of products in the protection and savings category that match the different life stage requirements of customers, enabling them to provide a financial safety net to their families as well as achieve their long-term financial goals. The counter rose 0.62% to end at Rs 684.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIPrudentialLifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_18603840404_22005.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper stays supported after 2% gain in last session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-stays-supported-after-2-gain-in-last-session/1664650</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664650</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures stayed supported amid largely steady equities.

COMEX Copper futures stayed supported amid largely steady equities. The metal is consolidating above $6 per pound, rising for third session and holding onto the momentum after a more than 2% gain yesterday. COMEX Copper futures are currently trading at $6.06 per pound, up 0.44% on the day. MCX Copper futures are quoting at Rs 1312.35 per kg, down marginally on the day. Meanwhile, Asian markets were mixed as Hong Kong stocks hit 2-month high while China market eased. European markets drifted lower marginally. The US stocks recovered in last session. The major averages climbed well off their lows of the session and into positive territory, with the Dow and the S&P 500 reaching new record closing highs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/closeup-of-blue-chart-growth-progress-picture-id177428264_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Coking Coal subscribed 146.80 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-coking-coal-subscribed-14680-times/1664648</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664648</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 50,93,16,75,600 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 50,93,16,75,600 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 146.80 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The offer is a pure offer-for-sale (OFS) of up to 46.57 crore equity shares of face value Rs 10 each by Coal India. At the upper price band of Rs 23 per equity share, Coal India will raise Rs 1,071 crore. The IPO includes a reservation of up to 2.32 crore equity shares for eligible employees and up to 4.66 crore shares for eligible shareholders of Coal India under the shareholder reservation portion. Ahead of the IPO of Bharat Coking Coal on 8 January 2026, the company raised Rs 273.13 crore from anchor investors by allotting 11.87 crore shares at Rs 23 each to 15 anchor investors. Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) produces coking coal, non-coking coal, and washed coal. BCCL is India's largest producer of coking coal and operates primarily in the Jharia coalfields of Jharkhand and the Raniganj coalfields of West Bengal. It is the wholly owned subsidiary of Coal India and was conferred with Mini Ratna status in 2014. The primary product is coking coal, catering to the steel and power industries. BCCL had an estimated coking coal reserve of approximately 7,910 million tonnes (mt) as of 01 April 2024. It accounted for 58.50% of the total domestic coking coal production in India in FY 2025. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 123.88 crore and sales of Rs 5,659 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR ends flat, local stocks soften]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-ends-flat-local-stocks-soften/1664647</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664647</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee saw muted trades as local stocks stayed slippery.

Indian Rupee saw muted trades as local stocks stayed slippery. INR currently quotes at 90.20 per US dollar, almost unchanged on the day. US dollar index dipped under 99 mark yesterday and currently quotes at 98.70. The local stock markets eased today. The NIFTY and Sensex fell after rising in early moves amid profit selling pressure. The Sensex settled 250.48 points or 0.3 percent lower at 83,627.69, while the broader Nifty declined to 25,732.30, down 57.95 points or 0.22 percent. The earlier recovery was triggered by renewed momentum in India-US trade talks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Amagi Media Labs subscribed 6%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/amagi-media-labs-subscribed-6/1664645</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664645</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 17,46,600 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 17,46,600 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.06 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 41 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The IPO consists of a fresh issue of Rs 816.0 crore and offer for sale of 2,69,42,343 equity shares. At the upper end price, the issue size stands at Rs 1788.62 crore. The offer for sale (OFS) by PI Opportunities Fund-I includes up to 98,89,646 shares at the upper price band of Rs 361 per share, aggregating Rs 357.02 crore. Accel India VI (Mauritius) and Trudy Holdings are each offering up to 50,72,582 shares at the same price, amounting to Rs 183.12 crore apiece. In addition, PI Opportunities Fund-II is proposing to sell up to 3,411,792 shares at Rs 361 per share, valued at Rs 123.17 crore. Norwest Venture Partners plans to offload up to 3,381,721 shares worth Rs 122.08 crore, while multiple individual investors will collectively offer up to 228,024 shares, aggregating Rs 8.03 crore. Amagi Media Labs proposes to utilise Rs 550.06 crore from the net fresh issue proceeds towards technology and cloud infrastructure and the balance will be utilised towards funding inorganic growth through unidentified acquisitions and for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Amagi Media Labs on 12 January 2026, the company raised Rs 804.87 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 2.22 crore shares at Rs 361 each to 42 anchor investors. Amagi Media Labs (Amagi) is a software-as-a-service (SaaS) company that connects media companies to their audiences through cloud-native technology. Its platform helps content providers and distributors upload and deliver video over the internet (commonly known as streaming) through smart televisions, smartphones and applications, instead of traditional cable or set-top box services. It also helps monetize such content through targeted advertising services for advertisers. s The company enables broadcasters, content owners, and streaming platforms to launch, manage, and monetise live linear channels on Free Ad-supported Streaming TV (FAST) platforms such as Pluto TV, Samsung TV Plus, Roku Channel, and others. The company’s customers include global media companies such as Vevo, Lionsgate Studios, DAZN, E.W. Scripps, Sinclair, Inc., VIZIO, Roku, The Trade Desk, JioAds and the Tennis Channel. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 6.47 crore and income from operations of Rs 704.82 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end lower as early rally fizzles; profit-taking bites]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-lower-as-early-rally-fizzles-profit-taking-bites/1664644</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664644</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks closed lower on Tuesday after an early rebound fizzled out, leaving markets bruised by heavy intraday selling and fragile sentiment.

Domestic equity benchmarks closed lower on Tuesday after an early rebound fizzled out, leaving markets bruised by heavy intraday selling and fragile sentiment. The BSE Sensex slid as much as 995 points from the day’s high, while the Nifty 50 dropped 296 points as selling pressure intensified through the session. The Nifty, which touched an intraday high of 25,899.80 in early trade, slipped below the 25,750 mark by the close. Consumer durables and pharmaceutical stocks were among the worst hit. The decline was driven largely by profit-taking in heavyweight stocks after the recent rally, with investors choosing to lock in gains amid uncertain global cues. Rising crude oil prices added to the pressure, stoking concerns over inflation and the current account outlook. Persistent foreign institutional selling weighed on sentiment, even as domestic participation remained robust. The rupee’s weakness against the dollar further dampened risk appetite, especially for import-sensitive sectors. From a technical perspective, market indicators continued to flag fragile momentum, suggesting limited near-term upside and keeping traders cautious amid elevated volatility. The S&P BSE Sensex slipped 250.48 points or 0.30% to 83,627.69. The Nifty 50 index lost 57.95 points or 0.22% to 25,732.30. Trent (down 3.39%), Larsen & Tourbo (down 3.25%) and Reliance Industries (down 2.14%) were major drags today. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.46%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 2,038 shares rose and 2,099 shares fell. A total of 201 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, slipped 1.49% to 11.20. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.36% to 6.629 compared with previous session close of 6.605. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2175 compared with its close of 90.1750 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement shed 0.32% to Rs 141,580. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.06% to 98.96. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.195. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement gained $1.05 or 1.64% to $64.92 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European indices traded lower on Tuesday as investors kept a wary eye on geopolitical developments, key inflation data, and the new quarterly earnings season. Most Asian markets ended higher as traders shrugged off geopolitical flashpoints in Iran and Venezuela, as well as a criminal investigation into U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Japan’s benchmark Nikkei 225 jumped 3.13% to lead gains in the region. Japan’s ruling Liberal Democratic Party is expected to dissolve the country’s Lower House later this month and opt for a snap election likely in February, according to media reports. Traders also kept a close eye on oil prices amid ongoing protests in Iran. President Donald Trump is reportedly weighing options for intervention in Iran, according to multiple media reports. Trump in a social media post on Monday stateside reportedly said any country doing business with Iran will face a 25% tariff “on any and all business being done with the United States of America.” That new tariff on imports from Iran’s trading partners is “effective immediately.” Overnight in the U.S., stocks rallied off their session lows, with the S&P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average hitting new all-time highs. The S&P 500 rose 0.16% to end at 6,977.27, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average ticked up 86.13 points, or 0.17%, and settled at 49,590.20. Both indexes touched fresh all-time intraday highs and closed at records. The Nasdaq Composite was up 0.26% and closed at 23,733.90. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) rose 0.99%. The company reported an 11.74% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 10,657 crore, despite 1.96% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,087 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 13.92%, while revenue from operations increased 4.87% in Q3 FY26. The decline in profitability was impacted due to one-time exceptional charges including Rs 2,120 crore related to the statutory impact of new labour codes and it also made a provision towards a legal claim of of Rs 1,010 crore during the December quarter. HCL Technologies shed 0.19%. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 3.75% to Rs 4,076 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,235 crore in Q2 FY26. However, revenue from operations increased 6.04% to Rs 33,872 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 31,942 crore posted in Q2 FY26. For FY26, HCL Tech expects revenue growth of 4-4.5% YoY in constant currency, services revenue growth of 4.75-5.25% YoY, and an EBIT margin of 17-18%. Larsen & Toubro slipped 3.25% after media reports said Kuwait is considering cancelling and rebidding oil project tenders worth $8.7 billion, stoking concerns over potential order inflows. According to a Middle East-focused business news platform, Kuwait is reviewing five major upstream oil and gas contracts after bids reportedly came in above budget. The report said L&T was the lowest bidder in tenders valued at more than $4.5 billion, making the stock sensitive to any adverse developments. Responding to a BSE query, L&T clarified that the projects referred to in the media report are not part of its order book. The company added that it does not comment on the status of tenders or the commercial decisions of its clients, easing concerns about any impact on confirmed orders. Kalpataru rose 0.33% after the company’s collections jumped 17% to Rs 1,101 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 943 crore in Q3 FY25. Maharashtra Scooters surged 6.73% after the company reported a 24.84% surge in standalone net profit to Rs 4.12 crore on a 11.22% rise in total income to Rs 6.44 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Omaxe soared 12.63% after the company unveiled plans to invest Rs 500 crore in a new mixed-use development project, Omaxe Chowk, in Ludhiana. Lotus Chocolate Company slumped 9.71% after the company’s standalone net profit tumbled 96.22% to Rs 0.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3.71 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 18.90% to Rs 133.63 crore in the third quarter of FY26 from Rs 146.69 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. GTPL Hathway fell 7.93%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 8.3% to Rs 11.01 crore on 5.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 932.62 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Anand Rathi Wealth added 0.51%. The company reported 29.6% rise in net profit to Rs 100.1 crore on a 22.2% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 289.6 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Indo Thai Securities rose 2.11% after the company reported a 1,629.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.12 crore on a 400.18% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 27.71 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Puravankara shed 0.22%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary Starworth Infrastructure & Construction (SICL) has received a letter of intent (LoI) for the construction of an East Bangalore-based proposed residential project "Sattva AANGANE". A B Infrabuild advanced 3.50% after the company announced that it has received a letter of acceptance worth Rs 55.26 crore for a new infrastructure project from East Coast Railways, Indian Railways. B.R. Goyal Infrastructure rose 1.72% after the company received a work order worth Rs 86.70 crore from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for user fee collection at Simliya and Fatehpur fee plazas on NH-76 in Rajasthan. Oriental Hotels gained 2.84% after its consolidated net profit jumped 44.08% to Rs 20.69 crore on a 14.23% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 139.25 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. IPO Update: Bharat Coking Coal's IPO received bids for 50,91,41,64,600 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:54 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 146.75 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. Amagi Media Labs' IPO received bids for 17,05,518 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:54 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.06 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1664641</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664641</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2025 futures closed at 25,780.40, a premium of 48.10 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,732.30 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2025 futures closed at 25,780.40, a premium of 48.10 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,732.30 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index lost 57.95 points or 0.22% to 25,732.30. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, slipped 1.49% to 11.20. HDFC Bank, Reliance Industries and Tata Consultancy Services were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/investor-watching-the-change-of-stock-market-on-laptop-pict_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 250 pts lower; PSU bank index outperforms; VIX slides 1.49% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-250-pts-lower-psu-bank-index-outperforms-vix-slides-149/1664632</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664632</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with minor losses today, weighed down by profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

The key equity barometers ended with minor losses today, weighed down by profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. Investor sentiment remained cautious amid developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical concerns. The Nifty slipped below the 25,750 mark, after touching an intraday high of 25,899.80 in early trade. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex slipped 250.48 points or 0.30% to 83,627.69. The Nifty 50 index lost 57.95 points or 0.22% to 25,732.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.46%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, slipped 1.49% to 11.20. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 0.78%), the Nifty Media index (up 0.76%) and the Nifty IT index (up 0.65%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Consumer Durables index (down 0.89%), the Nifty Realty index (down 0.62%) and the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.47%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.36% to 6.629 compared with previous session close of 6.605. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2175 compared with its close of 90.1750 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement shed 0.32% to Rs 141,580. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.06% to 98.96. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.195. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement gained $1.05 or 1.64% to $64.92 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets traded lower on Tuesday as investors kept a wary eye on geopolitical developments, key inflation data, and the new quarterly earnings season. Most Asian markets ended higher as traders shrugged off geopolitical flashpoints in Iran and Venezuela, as well as a criminal investigation into U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Japan’s benchmark Nikkei 225 jumped 3.13% to lead gains in the region. Japan’s ruling Liberal Democratic Party is expected to dissolve the country’s Lower House later this month and opt for a snap election likely in February, according to media reports. Traders will also be keeping a close eye on oil prices amid ongoing protests in Iran. President Donald Trump is reportedly weighing options for intervention in Iran, according to multiple media reports. Trump in a social media post on Monday stateside reportedly said any country doing business with Iran will face a 25% tariff “on any and all business being done with the United States of America.” That new tariff on imports from Iran’s trading partners is “effective immediately.” Overnight in the U.S., stocks rallied off their session lows, with the S&P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average hitting new all-time highs. The S&P 500 rose 0.16% to end at 6,977.27, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average ticked up 86.13 points, or 0.17%, and settled at 49,590.20. Both indexes touched fresh all-time intraday highs and closed at records. The Nasdaq Composite was up 0.26% and closed at 23,733.90.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers ends with modest cuts; Nifty settles below 25,750 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-ends-with-modest-cuts-nifty-settles-below-25750-mark/1664631</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664631</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity indices ended marginally lower on Tuesday, weighed down by profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

Domestic equity indices ended marginally lower on Tuesday, weighed down by profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. Investor sentiment remained cautious amid developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical concerns. The Nifty slipped below the 25,750 mark, after touching an intraday high of 25,899.80 in early trade. Consumer durabels, realty and pharma shares declined, while PSU bank, media and IT shares advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex slipped 250.48 points or 0.30% to 83,627.69. The Nifty 50 index lost 57.95 points or 0.22% to 25,732.30. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.16% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.46%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 2,041 shares rose and 2,097 shares fell. A total of 200 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, slipped 1.49% to 11.20. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Amagi Media Labs received bids for 15,49,923 shares as against 2,72,66,589 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:45 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.06 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (13 January 2026) and it will close on Friday (16 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 343 and 361 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 41 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 50,28,19,84,800 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:45 IST on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 144.93 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index slipped 0.89% to 37,173.55. The index tumbled 3.03% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Dixon Technologies (India) (down 5.02%), Whirlpool of India (down 2.19%), Kalyan Jewellers India (down 1.62%), Havells India (down 1.29%), PG Electroplast (down 0.65%), Voltas (down 0.51%), V-Guard Industries (down 0.41%), Bata India (down 0.2%), Kajaria Ceramics (down 0.11%) and Blue Star (down 0.01%) declined. On the other hand, Century Plyboards (India) (up 2.1%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (up 0.52%) and Amber Enterprises India (up 0.44%) edged higher. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) rose 0.83%. The company reported an 11.74% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 10,657 crore, despite 1.96% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,087 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 13.92%, while revenue from operations increased 4.87% in Q3 FY26. The decline in profitability was impacted due to one-time exceptional charges including Rs 2,120 crore related to the statutory impact of new labour codes and it also made a provision towards a legal claim of of Rs 1,010 crore during the December quarter. HCL Technologies shed 0.25%. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 3.75% to Rs 4,076 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,235 crore in Q2 FY26. However, revenue from operations increased 6.04% to Rs 33,872 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 31,942 crore posted in Q2 FY26. For FY26, HCLTech expects revenue growth of 4–4.5% YoY in constant currency, services revenue growth of 4.75–5.25% YoY, and an EBIT margin of 17–18%. Larsen & Toubro slipped 3.23% after media reports said Kuwait is considering cancelling and rebidding oil project tenders worth $8.7 billion, stoking concerns over potential order inflows. According to a Middle East-focused business news platform, Kuwait is reviewing five major upstream oil and gas contracts after bids reportedly came in above budget. The report said L&T was the lowest bidder in tenders valued at more than $4.5 billion, making the stock sensitive to any adverse developments. Meanwhile, Larsen & Toubro said its transportation infrastructure business vertical has secured a significant order for an arterial cable-stayed bridge over the Muri Ganga river in the South 24 Parganas district of West Bengal. Kalpataru jumped 5.45% after the company’s collections jumped 17% to Rs 1,101 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 943 crore in Q3 FY25. Maharashtra Scooters surged 6.73% after the company reported a 24.84% surge in standalone net profit to Rs 4.12 crore on a 11.22% rise in total income to Rs 6.44 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Omaxe soared 7.26% after the company unveiled plans to invest Rs 500 crore in a new mixed-use development project, Omaxe Chowk, in Ludhiana. Lotus Chocolate Company slumped 9.86% after the company’s standalone net profit tumbled 96.22% to Rs 0.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 3.71 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 18.90% to Rs 133.63 crore in the third quarter of FY26 from Rs 146.69 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. GTPL Hathway fell 8.24%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 8.3% to Rs 11.01 crore on 5.1% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 932.62 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Indo Thai Securities rose 1.82% after the company reported a 1,629.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.12 crore on a 400.18% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 27.71 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Puravankara shed 0.22%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary Starworth Infrastructure & Construction (SICL) has received a letter of intent (LoI) for the construction of an East Bangalore-based proposed residential project "Sattva AANGANE". Anand Rathi Wealth added 0.51%. The company reported 29.6% rise in net profit to Rs 100.1 crore on a 22.2% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 289.6 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. A B Infrabuild advanced 3.50% after the company announced that it has received a letter of acceptance worth Rs 55.26 crore for a new infrastructure project from East Coast Railways, Indian Railways. B.R. Goyal Infrastructure rose 1.72% after the company received a work order worth Rs 86.70 crore from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for user fee collection at Simliya and Fatehpur fee plazas on NH-76 in Rajasthan. Oriental Hotels gained 2.84% after its consolidated net profit jumped 44.08% to Rs 20.69 crore on a 14.23% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 139.25 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets declined on Tuesday as investors kept a wary eye on geopolitical developments, key inflation data, and the new quarterly earnings season. Most Asian markets advanced as traders shrugged off geopolitical flashpoints in Iran and Venezuela, as well as a criminal investigation into U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. Japan’s benchmark Nikkei 225 jumped 3.13% to lead gains in the region. Japan’s ruling Liberal Democratic Party is expected to dissolve the country’s Lower House later this month and opt for a snap election likely in February, according to media reports. Traders will also be keeping a close eye on oil prices amid ongoing protests in Iran. President Donald Trump is reportedly weighing options for intervention in Iran, according to multiple media reports. Trump in a social media post on Monday stateside reportedly said any country doing business with Iran will face a 25% tariff “on any and all business being done with the United States of America.” That new tariff on imports from Iran’s trading partners is “effective immediately.” Overnight in the U.S., stocks rallied off their session lows, with the S&P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average hitting new all-time highs. The S&P 500 rose 0.16% to end at 6,977.27, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average ticked up 86.13 points, or 0.17%, and settled at 49,590.20. Both indexes touched fresh all-time intraday highs and closed at records. The Nasdaq Composite was up 0.26% and closed at 23,733.90.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Infrastructure Index falls 1.14%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-infrastructure-index-falls-114/1664630</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664630</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Infrastructure index closed down 1.14% at 9226.55 today.

Nifty Infrastructure index closed down 1.14% at 9226.55 today. The index has slipped 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Oil & Natural Gas Corpn Ltd rose 3.42%, Larsen & Toubro Ltd fell 3.27% and Godrej Properties Ltd dropped 2.69%. The Nifty Infrastructure index has soared 15.00% over last one year compared to the 11.46% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index gained 0.78% and Nifty Media index increased 0.76% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has declined 0.22% to close at 25732.3 while the SENSEX has slid 0.30% to close at 83627.69 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s logistics costs have reduced to 7.97% of GDP]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-logistics-costs-have-reduced-to-797-of-gdp/1664628</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664628</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s logistics sector has made remarkable progress in recent years, achieving a significant milestone with logistics costs now reduced to 7.97% of GDP, government noted in a latest update.

India’s logistics sector has made remarkable progress in recent years, achieving a significant milestone with logistics costs now reduced to 7.97% of GDP, government noted in a latest update. This reflects the success of sustained reforms and integrated planning, positioning the nation closer to global benchmarks. It also demonstrates how coordinated infrastructure development and digital integration are reshaping the logistics landscape, making it more efficient, competitive, and future-ready. At the heart of this transformation is the PM Gati Shakti National Master Plan, which has brought together railways, highways, ports, and airports into a unified framework. By enabling seamless multimodal connectivity, the plan aims to strengthen industry competitiveness, support initiatives such as Ease of Doing Business and Make in India, and ensure balanced regional growth. The Gati Shakti Cargo Terminals (GCTs) are a key pillar of this vision, driving modern logistics solutions that will continue to enhance India’s role as a global trade hub.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/logistics-advertisement-1316717_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank of Maharashtra gains as Q3 PAT climbs 27% YoY to Rs 1,779 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-of-maharashtra-gains-as-q3-pat-climbs-27-yoy-to-rs-1779-cr/1664622</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664622</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 37.27% to Rs 2,007.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,462.31 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax (PBT) climbed 37.27% to Rs 2,007.38 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,462.31 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net interest income (NII) grew 16.27% to Rs 3,422 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 2,943 crore recorded in corresponding quarter last year. Net interest margin stood at 3.87% as on 31 December 2025 Operating profit rose 18.78% year-on-year to Rs 2,736 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,303 crore in Q3 FY25. Provision & contingencies other than taxes declined by 13.38% to Rs 728.19 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 840.7 crore in Q3 FY25. On a year-on-year basis, gross NPAs declined to 1.60% as of 31 December 2025, from 1.80% as of 31 December 2024, while net NPAs fell to 0.15% in Q3 FY26 from 0.20% a year ago. The provision coverage ratio improved to 98.41% in Q3 FY26, compared with 98.28% in the year-ago period. The bank said it held cumulative Covid-19 provisions of Rs 1,200 crore as of 31 December 2025. On a year-on-year basis, total business grew 17.24% to Rs 5,95,163 crore, driven by a 15.29% rise in total deposits to Rs 3,21,661 crore and a 19.62% increase in global advances to Rs 2,73,502 crore. The bank’s RAM (retail, agriculture and MSME) business expanded 20.26%, while retail advances surged 36.40% compared with the year-ago period. As of 31 December 2025, the total Basel III capital adequacy ratio stood at 17.06%, with the Common Equity Tier 1 (CET1) ratio at 13.10%. On a year-on-year basis, the cost-to-income ratio improved to 37.19% in Q3 FY26 from 38.27% in Q3 FY25. Return on assets (ROA) rose to 1.86% in Q3 FY26 from 1.78% in Q3 FY25, while return on equity (ROE) improved to 23.79% in Q3 FY26 from 22.36% in the year-ago quarter. The board of directors has approved an interim dividend of 10%, amounting to Rs 1 per equity share of face value Rs 10, for FY 2025–26 (nine months), within the limits prescribed by the RBI. Bank of Maharashtra is engaged in providing banking services. The Bank's segments include Treasury, Corporate/Wholesale Banking, Retail Banking and Other banking operations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BankofMaha_49685557243_5607.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Supply Chain Solutions jumps after bagging 3-year contract from Daimler India]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-jumps-after-bagging-3-year-contract-from-daimler-india/1664621</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664621</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the agreement, TVS SCS will manage end-to-end warehouse operations within DICV’s manufacturing facility, ensuring seamless material flow, optimised inventory, and enhanced operational efficiency.

Under the agreement, TVS SCS will manage end-to-end warehouse operations within DICV’s manufacturing facility, ensuring seamless material flow, optimised inventory, and enhanced operational efficiency. By leveraging advanced technologies including IoT-based tracking for real-time visibility, automation-led systems to reduce manual handling, predictive analytics for smarter planning, and digital dashboards for centralized performance monitoring. These capabilities will help strengthen DICV’s production ecosystem and support its focus on efficiency and quality. Sukumar K, CEO – India & MEA, TVS Supply Chain Solutions, said "We are pleased to extend our long-standing partnership with Daimler through this significant engagement. Our global experience with Daimler, combined with our expertise in in-plant logistics, automation-led operations, and real-time visibility solutions, positions us well to drive measurable efficiencies. We look forward to further strengthening their production ecosystem and supporting their commitment to world-class manufacturing." C. Muthu Maruthachalam, President & Chief Operating Officer, Daimler India Commercial Vehicles, said, "Efficient in-plant logistics is vital to our production success. Partnering with TVS Supply Chain Solutions allows us to leverage their proven expertise and technology-driven approach to enhance our operational performance.” TVS Supply Chain Solutions (TVS SCS) is an India-based multinational company, who pioneered the development of the supply chain solutions market in India. The company's customers span across numerous industries such as automotive, industrial, consumer, tech and tech infra, rail and utilities, and healthcare. On consolidated basis, the company’s net profit jumped 67.6% to Rs 15.64 crore on 6% increase in net sales to Rs 2662.63 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSSupplyChainSolutionsLtd_13681781_28638.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold pauses after $100 surge, Fed and tariff risks persist]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-pauses-after-100-surge-fed-and-tariff-risks-persist/1664620</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664620</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices slipped below $4,600 per ounce in early Asian trade on Tuesday, easing after a sharp rally of more than $100 following renewed concerns over the US Federal Reserve’s independence, escalating geopolitical risks, and fresh tariff threats from President Donald Trump.

Gold prices slipped below $4,600 per ounce in early Asian trade on Tuesday, easing after a sharp rally of more than $100 following renewed concerns over the US Federal Reserve’s independence, escalating geopolitical risks, and fresh tariff threats from President Donald Trump. The sharp surge in gold—and a parallel rally in silver—was directly driven by safe-haven demand sparked by President Donald Trump’s tariff actions and escalating geopolitical uncertainty. Trump’s announcement of a 25% tariff on countries trading with Iran, coupled with repeated warnings of possible military action, triggered a broad flight to safety across financial markets. This tariff turmoil has significantly lifted demand for precious metals, with investors turning to gold and silver for protection against policy risk, trade disruption, and geopolitical instability. In the domestic market, MCX February gold futures edged lower by 0.23% to ₹1,41,700 per 10 grams, tracking the global pullback amid profit-taking. Investor focus has now shifted to US inflation data due later today, which could provide clearer signals on the Fed’s policy outlook following signs of cooling in the labor market. While the Federal Reserve is widely expected to keep rates unchanged this month, markets continue to price in potential rate cuts later in the year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dixon-technologies-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1664618</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664618</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HEG Ltd, AU Small Finance Bank Ltd, Vodafone Idea Ltd and Graphite India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 January 2026.

HEG Ltd, AU Small Finance Bank Ltd, Vodafone Idea Ltd and Graphite India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 January 2026. Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd lost 5.01% to Rs 11249.9 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 65491 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 42438 shares in the past one month. HEG Ltd tumbled 4.93% to Rs 541.9. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.45 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.26 lakh shares in the past one month. AU Small Finance Bank Ltd crashed 3.75% to Rs 969.05. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 5.66 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 34210 shares in the past one month. Vodafone Idea Ltd pared 3.73% to Rs 10.84. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 634.76 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 956.37 lakh shares in the past one month. Graphite India Ltd shed 3.66% to Rs 597.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.12 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.37 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DixonTechnologiesIndiaLtd_22760470989_35727.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T slips on Kuwait tender rebid reports; company says projects not in order book]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-slips-on-kuwait-tender-rebid-reports-company-says-projects-not-in-order-book/1664617</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664617</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to a Middle East-focused business news platform, Kuwait is reviewing five major upstream oil and gas contracts after bids reportedly came in above budget.

According to a Middle East-focused business news platform, Kuwait is reviewing five major upstream oil and gas contracts after bids reportedly came in above budget. The report said L&T was the lowest bidder in tenders valued at more than $4.5 billion, making the stock sensitive to any adverse developments. Responding to a BSE query, L&T clarified that the projects referred to in the media report are not part of its order book. The company added that it does not comment on the status of tenders or the commercial decisions of its clients. Separately, L&T has secured a significant order in its transportation infrastructure business to construct an arterial extradosed cable-stayed bridge over the Muri Ganga River in South 24 Parganas, West Bengal. The project includes a 3.2 km, 2+2 lane bridge with a maximum span of 177 metres, approach roads on the Kakdwip and Sagar Island sides, and advanced traffic management, bridge health monitoring, and architectural and hybrid street lighting. For L&T, a “significant” order is defined as a contract valued between Rs 1,000 crore and Rs 2,500 crore. L&T is a diversified EPC major operating across infrastructure, energy, hydrocarbons, defence, manufacturing and services in India and overseas. The company reported a 15.6% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SIP AuM rises to Rs 16.63 lakh crore in December with 9.79 crore SIP accounts: AMFI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sip-aum-rises-to-rs-1663-lakh-crore-in-december-with-979-crore-sip-accounts-amfi/1664616</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664616</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The net assets under the management (AUM) of the Indian mutual fund industry at the end of December 2025 stood at Rs 80.23 lakh crore, according to data from the Association of Mutual Funds of India (AMFI).

The net assets under the management (AUM) of the Indian mutual fund industry at the end of December 2025 stood at Rs 80.23 lakh crore, according to data from the Association of Mutual Funds of India (AMFI). This is slightly lower as compared with the figure of Rs 80.80 lakh crore recorded in November 2025. The AUM of open-ended plans fell to Rs 79.98 lakh crore in December 2025 from Rs 80.55 lakh crore in November 2025. Investors continued to be drawn to equity plans in this category, with net inflows of Rs 28,054.06 crore. Within equity, Flexi Cap Fund drew the most significant inflows in December, attracting Rs 10,019.27 crore. Mid Cap Funds followed suit with inflows of Rs 4,175.81 crore, while ELSS saw net outflows of Rs 717.73 crore. Debt funds witnessed net outflows in December, totaling Rs 1,32,410.37 crore. This category had recorded net outflows of Rs 25,692.63 crore in November. Liquid Funds recorded maximum outflows of Rs 47,307.95 crore. Other debt segments like Money Market Funds, Overnight Funds and Ultra Short Duration Funds also saw significant inflows. Hybrid schemes, offering a mix of equity and debt exposure, recorded net inflows of Rs 10,755.57 crore in December 2025. This was largely driven by Arbitrage Funds, which attracted Rs 26,411.54 crore. The systematic investment plan (SIP) contributions rose to Rs 31,002 crore in December 2025, up by 0.53% from Rs Rs 29,445 crore in November 2025. The number of contributing SIP accounts also rose from 9.42 crore in November to 9.79 crore in December, while SIP assets under management (AUM) climbed to Rs 16.63 lakh crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Karma Energy Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/karma-energy-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1664609</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664609</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd, Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd, Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 January 2026.

Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd, Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd, Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd and Shyam Telecom Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 January 2026. Karma Energy Ltd crashed 10.00% to Rs 47.25 at 14:20 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1113 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1744 shares in the past one month. Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd lost 8.87% to Rs 685. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 25750 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4498 shares in the past one month. Jubilant Agri & Consumer Products Ltd tumbled 8.48% to Rs 2200. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1307 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 154 shares in the past one month. Eldeco Housing & Industries Ltd slipped 7.04% to Rs 865.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 343 shares in the past one month. Shyam Telecom Ltd corrected 6.83% to Rs 12. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9064 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7014 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KarmaEner_72744909020_39082.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops 505 pts; consumer durables shares tumble]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-505-pts-consumer-durables-shares-tumble/1664604</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664604</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with substantial losses in the mid-afternoon trade, amid profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

The key equity indices traded with substantial losses in the mid-afternoon trade, amid profit booking, foreign fund outflows and the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. Investors remained cautious as they tracked developments related to the India–US trade deal, ongoing Q3 earnings announcements and geopolitical developments. The Nifty slipped below the 25,650 mark. Consumer durables share extended losses for the fourth consecutive trading session. At 14:32 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex fell 505.31 points or 0.60% to 83,333.17. The Nifty 50 index dropped 148.50 points or 0.58% to 25,646.60. In the broader market. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.45% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.21%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,866 shares rose and 2,110 shares fell. A total of 220 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index dropped 1.46% to 36,958.45. The index fell 3.59% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Dixon Technologies (India) (down 5.17%), PG Electroplast (down 2.07%), Kalyan Jewellers India (down 1.87%), Whirlpool of India (down 1.87%), Havells India (down 1.75%), Voltas (down 1.34%), Amber Enterprises India (down 0.88%), Blue Star (down 0.76%), V-Guard Industries (down 0.65%) and Kajaria Ceramics (down 0.56%) declined. On the other hand, Century Plyboards (India) (up 0.41%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (up 0.24%) and Cera Sanitaryware (up 0.24%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.35% to 6.628 compared with previous session close of 6.605. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2875 compared with its close of 90.1750 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement shed 0.18% to Rs 141,769. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.11% to 98.73. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.195. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement gained 56 cents or 0.88% to $64.43 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Indo Thai Securities rose 1.95% after the company reported a 1,629.29% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.12 crore on a 400.18% jump in total revenue from operations to Rs 27.71 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Puravankara shed 0.26%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary Starworth Infrastructure & Construction (SICL) has received a letter of intent (LoI) for the construction of an East Bangalore-based proposed residential project "Sattva AANGANE". Anand Rathi Wealth shed 0.03%. The company reported 29.6% rise in net profit to Rs 100.1 crore on a 22.2% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 289.6 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>