<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:55:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's forex reserves soar by $8.66 billion to hit an all-time high of $725.7 billion]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-forex-reserves-soar-by-866-billion-to-hit-an-all-time-high-of-7257-billion/1679078</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679078</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's foreign exchange reserves rose by $8.66 billion from a week earlier to hit an all-time high of $725.727 billion in the week ending February 13, latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) showed on Friday.

India's foreign exchange reserves rose by $8.66 billion from a week earlier to hit an all-time high of $725.727 billion in the week ending February 13, latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) showed on Friday. For the week ending February 13, foreign currency assets rose by $3.55 billion, gold by $4.99 billion and Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) by $103 million, the official data showed. India's reserve position with the IMF was also up by $19 million to $4.734 billion in the reporting week, RBI data showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-2891849__340_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India and Brazil aim for $30 billion trade partnership by 2030]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-and-brazil-aim-for-30-billion-trade-partnership-by-2030/1679076</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679076</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Brazilian President Mr Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva said that bilateral trade between India and Brazil could reach $30 billion by 2030 — doubling current volumes — as he addressed the India-Brazil Business Forum.

Brazilian President Mr Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva said that bilateral trade between India and Brazil could reach $30 billion by 2030 — doubling current volumes — as he addressed the India-Brazil Business Forum. The declaration came against a backdrop of rapidly deepening ties. Bilateral trade stood at a mere $2.4 billion in 2006 when both nations formalised their strategic partnership. It has since risen to $15 billion — a 25 per cent increase last year alone — yet both leaders described the figure as falling well short of potential. "The distance between Brazil and India is merely a detail in the face of the potential of friendship between our two nations," said Lula, adding that both countries had for too long directed their commercial attention towards other countries at the expense of each other. "We have now resolved to change that behaviour." Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal echoed the ambition but was equally candid about the gap. "Our bilateral trade, even though it grew by 25 per cent to $15 billion, is truly suboptimal," he said. "We have to be significantly more ambitious today." Minister Goyal pointed to the structural complementarities underpinning the relationship — Brazil's reserves of niobium, lithium and iron ore alongside its agricultural dominance, and India's technological depth and manufacturing capacity. "Together we have the potential to reshape global value chains, with resources, innovation and a forward-looking vision," he said, inviting Brazilian companies to co-invest and co-create in India. "Brazil is a global agriculture powerhouse producing several products that help feed billions. Its aerospace, automotive and digital technology industries are rapidly evolving, offering abundant opportunities for collaboration. All of this comes together to make Brazil our strategic partner in global supply chains," Goyal added.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/handshake-3378255__340_personal_finance.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hsbc-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1679077</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679077</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HSBC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

HSBC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The quantum of dividend (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.190 HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.215 HSBC Balanced Advantage Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.122 HSBC Balanced Advantage Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.143 HSBC Multi Asset Allocation Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 1.200 HSBC Multi Asset Allocation Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.440 HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Regular Plan – Annual IDCW Option: 1.500 HSBC Aggressive Hybrid Fund – Direct Plan – Annual IDCW Option: 1.700 HSBC Flexi Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 4.000 HSBC Flexi Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 4.150 HSBC Asia Pacific (Ex Japan) DYF – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 2.150 HSBC Asia Pacific (Ex Japan) DYF – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 2.150

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC MF announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1679073</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679073</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW in the following schemes.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced 25 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW in the following schemes. The proposed IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: HDFC Balanced Advantage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.250 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.250

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Morepen Labs surges after bagging Rs 825 crore CDMO contract from global pharma firm]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/morepen-labs-surges-after-bagging-rs-825-crore-cdmo-contract-from-global-pharma-firm/1679075</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679075</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company stated that the supplies under the said mandate are expected to commence within the next 4–5 months, with execution scheduled through Q1 of the following financial year, subject to customary operational and regulatory processes.

The company stated that the supplies under the said mandate are expected to commence within the next 4–5 months, with execution scheduled through Q1 of the following financial year, subject to customary operational and regulatory processes. Morepen Labs further said that this engagement marks one of the most significant single CDMO mandates in the Company’s history, as it scales its global manufacturing footprint. Sushil Suri, chairman & managing director, said: "This mandate represents an important milestone in the evolution of Morepen’s manufacturing platform. We view CDMO as a natural extension of our established API strengths, creating additional avenues of scale, stability, and long-term value creation while continuing to reinforce our core businesses." Morepen Laboratories is a vertically integrated pharmaceutical and healthcare company delivering APIs, branded generics, medical devices, and consumer wellness products worldwide. The company's consolidated net profit rose 3.07% to Rs 27.51 crore on a 6.93% increase in revenue to Rs 484.16 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. On the BSE, over 20.92 lakh shares of the company had changed hands at the counter as compared with the average trading volume of 1.56 lakh shares. In the last one year, the scrip has lost 12.08% while the benchmark S&P BSE Sesnex and the S&P BSE Healthcare index have gained 11.90% and 9.85%, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MorepenLabs_34238238875_2685.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RailTel Corp gains after bagging Rs 1,136-cr Maharashtra contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railtel-corp-gains-after-bagging-rs-1136-cr-maharashtra-contract/1679065</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679065</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[RailTel, in consortium with Ashoka Buildcon, has been selected as the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for the modernization of offices of the Inspector General of Registration (IGR) and Controller of Stamps under the Government of Maharashtra.

RailTel, in consortium with Ashoka Buildcon, has been selected as the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for the modernization of offices of the Inspector General of Registration (IGR) and Controller of Stamps under the Government of Maharashtra. As per the letter of intent (LoI), the accepted rate is Rs 24.75 per page. The average number of pages scanned annually over the past five years, as per the Request for Proposal (RFP), stood at 9.18 crore pages. Based on this volume, the estimated financial impact over the five-year contract period is approximately Rs 1,136.18 crore. RailTel was incorporated in 2000, with the objective of creating nationwide broadband and VPN services, telecom, and multimedia networks to modernize the train control operation and safety system of Indian Railways. The company’s standalone net profit declined 4.07% to Rs 62.40 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.05 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 18.99% YoY to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RailtelCorporationofIndia_16552082.1677406_22070.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Bank gains after clarifying stake bid in CreditAccess Grameen]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-bank-gains-after-clarifying-stake-bid-in-creditaccess-grameen/1679064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679064</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a stock exchange filling dated 22 February 2026, the bank said it had received queries regarding bidding for a stake in CreditAccess Grameen.

In a stock exchange filling dated 22 February 2026, the bank said it had received queries regarding bidding for a stake in CreditAccess Grameen. “The bank has neither submitted nor is planning to submit any bid for a stake in CreditAccess Grameen”, it said. The bank added that there was no material event requiring disclosure under Regulations 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and disclosure requirements) Regulations, 2015, and that it would continue to comply with disclosre norms. The clarification was submitted to the National Stock Exchange of India and BSE, where the bank is listed under NSE symbol AXISBANK and BSE scrip code 532215. Axis Bank is a private sector bank. It has the third-largest network of branches among private sector banks and an international presence through branches in DIFC (Dubai) and Singapore along with representative offices in Abu Dhabi, Sharjah, Dhaka and Dubai and an offshore banking unit in GIFT City. The bank reported a 2.94% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 6,489.57 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 6,303.77 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AxisBank_99376846491_5554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Ports rises after signing major MoU with NMDC, Brazil-based Vale]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-ports-rises-after-signing-major-mou-with-nmdc-brazil-based-vale/1679067</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679067</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The aforementioned MoU was signed at the recent India–Brazil Business Forum Summit that was held in New Delhi.

The aforementioned MoU was signed at the recent India–Brazil Business Forum Summit that was held in New Delhi. Vale is a Brazilian multinational corporation engaged in metals and mining and one of the largest logistics operators in Brazil. Vale is the largest producer of iron ore and nickel in the world. It also produces manganese, ferroalloys, copper, bauxite, potash, kaolin, and cobalt. The company also operates numerous hydroelectricity plants, and a large network of railroads, ships, and ports used to transport its products. The tripartite agreement establishes a strategic framework for the development of an iron ore blending facility and a dedicated Special Economic Zone (SEZ) at Gangavaram Port. Under this collaboration, the parties will jointly develop, operationalize, and manage an integrated SEZ-based ecosystem for the blending, value addition, and commercialisation of iron ore. This initiative is designed to strengthen the iron ore export value chain on India’s East Coast while enhancing efficiency, scale, and global competitiveness in mineral processing and trade. With this development, the capacity of Gangavaram Port will increase up to 75 MMT, and it will become a hub for iron ore exports for India and the region. Ashwani Gupta, whole-time director & CEO, APSEZ, said: "This collaboration reflects a shared commitment to building resilient, future-ready infrastructure that strengthens India’s position in global supply chains. By integrating high-quality mineral logistics with advanced port capabilities, we are supporting industry requirements while contributing to the country’s broader economic growth. Our partnership with NMDC and Vale will help establish a modern, efficient, and sustainable ecosystem for the iron ore sector on the East Coast. Gangavaram Port is poised to become the first port in India capable of handling Valemax vessels — the world’s largest very large ore carriers (VLOCs)." Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) is the largest private port operator in India. APSEZ operates a portfolio of 15 domestic ports/terminals with an international presence at 4 global ports/terminals. Along with its port operations, it has its wide logistics network and offers various port-based marine services to its owned ports/terminals as well as other ports. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 24.9% to Rs 3,176.72 crore on 21.9% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 9,704.59 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniPorts_15044199473_21281.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market opens on firm note; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-opens-on-firm-note-breadth-strong/1679058</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679058</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with substantial gains in early trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with substantial gains in early trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark. Barring the Nifty IT index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the green, with the PSU Bank, Financial Services and Auto indices gaining the most. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 611.33 points or 0.74% to 83,426.04. The Nifty 50 index surged 182.40 points or 0.71% to 25,754.05. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.39% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index gained 0.98%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,038 shares rose and 977 shares fell. A total of 253 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 934.61 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,637.15 crore in the Indian equity market on 20 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Sathlokhar Synergys E&C Global rose 0.89%. The company has secured new orders aggregating to Rs 37.57 crore for the execution of civil and pre-engineered building (PEB) works. Suraj Estate Developers added 0.96%. The company announced that it has entered into an agreement to acquire a 100% stake in Hally Pacific to undertake the development of a plot situated in Prabhadevi, Mumbai. Quality Power Electrical Equipments gained 1.49% after the company announced that its material subsidiary, Mehru Electrical and Mechanical Engineers, has received a letter of award (LoA) worth Rs 18 crore for the supply of instrument transformers from a domestic entity. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.07% to 6.730 compared with previous session close of 6.674. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7300 compared with its close of 90.9450 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 1.91% to Rs 159,855. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.34% to 97.39. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.51% to 4.068. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement lost 71 cents or 0.71% to $71.05 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian stock markets traded mostly with gains on Monday as investors monitored developments related to the United States tariffs. While the Supreme Court ruled on Friday that the Trump administration unlawfully imposed the measures last year, US President Donald Trump used different legal means to raise global levies to 15% from 10% over the weekend. Markets in China and Japan were closed for a holiday. On Friday, U.S. stocks rose after the Supreme Court ruling, potentially providing relief for companies burdened by higher costs from the duties and easing concern about sticky inflation still plaguing the U.S. economy. The S&P 500 advanced 0.69% and closed at 6,909.51, while the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9% and settled at 22,886.07. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 230.81 points, or 0.47%, and ended at 49,625.97. The 30-stock index recovered from a 200-point loss earlier in the session on disappointing economic data. Data released on Friday showed that the US economy expanded an annualized 1.4% in Q4 2025, the least since Q1 2025, following a 4.4% growth in Q3 and well below widely reported forecasts of 3%, the advance estimate showed.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd Spikes 2.06%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-ltd-spikes-206/1679053</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679053</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd rose 2.06% today to trade at Rs 601.75.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd rose 2.06% today to trade at Rs 601.75. The BSE Metal index is up 0.8% to quote at 39868.69. The index is up 5.26 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Vedanta Ltd increased 1.16% and APL Apollo Tubes Ltd added 0.71% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 36.55 % over last one year compared to the 10.09% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Zinc Ltd has lost 13.89% over last one month compared to 5.26% gain in BSE Metal index and 1.68% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 65037 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 12.8 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 732.6 on 28 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 378.65 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dee Development Engineers jumps after bagging Rs 173 crore orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dee-development-engineers-jumps-after-bagging-rs-173-crore-orders/1679054</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679054</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has received domestic contracts worth around Rs 88 crore on a job work basis, including a letter of intent (LoI) from Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) for the manufacturing and supply of critical piping solutions, including headers and vessels.

The company has received domestic contracts worth around Rs 88 crore on a job work basis, including a letter of intent (LoI) from Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) for the manufacturing and supply of critical piping solutions, including headers and vessels. The orders are to be executed within one year. Further, the company secured additional domestic contracts aggregating over Rs 42 crore from a joint venture between an Indian and a foreign power sector conglomerate (name undisclosed due to commercial reasons) for the manufacturing and supply of critical piping solutions on a job work basis, to be delivered within one year. Its material subsidiary, DEE Piping Systems (Thailand) Co., has bagged international orders worth approximately US$ 9.5 million from a US-based OEM in the power sector. The contract includes manufacturing of HRSG piping for 11 units on a job work basis (US$ 8 million), to be delivered by December 2028, and pipe fittings and flanges for seven units on a material basis (US$ 1.5 million), to be delivered by December 2027. The promoter group has no interest in the awarding entity, and the transactions are not related party transactions. DEE Development Engineers (DDEL) is an engineering company providing specialized process piping solutions for industries such as oil and gas, power (including nuclear), process industries, and chemicals through engineering, procurement, and manufacturing services. The company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 18.28 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with a net loss of Rs 13.33 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales increased 77% YoY to Rs 298.67 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DeeDevelopmentEngineersLtd_25916295_34369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at deep red opening for equities; Trump raises global average tariff to 15% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-deep-red-opening-for-equities-trump-raises-global-average-tariff-to-15/1679038</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679038</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 133.50 points, suggesting a deep red start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 133.50 points, suggesting a deep red start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 934.61 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,637.15 crore in the Indian equity market on 20 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 2,011.24 crore in the cash market so far in February (till 20 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian stock markets traded mostly with gains on Monday as investors monitored developments related to the United States tariffs. While the Supreme Court ruled on Friday that the Trump administration unlawfully imposed the measures last year, US President Donald Trump used different legal means to raise global levies to 15% from 10% over the weekend. Markets in China and Japan were closed for a holiday. On Friday, U.S. stocks rose after the Supreme Court ruling, potentially providing relief for companies burdened by higher costs from the duties and easing concern about sticky inflation still plaguing the U.S. economy. The S&P 500 advanced 0.69% and closed at 6,909.51, while the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9% and settled at 22,886.07. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 230.81 points, or 0.47%, and ended at 49,625.97. The 30-stock index recovered from a 200-point loss earlier in the session on disappointing economic data. Data released on Friday showed that the US economy expanded an annualized 1.4% in Q4 2025, the least since Q1 2025, following a 4.4% growth in Q3 and well below widely reported forecasts of 3%, the advance estimate showed. Domestic Market: The Indian equity markets staged a resilient recovery on Friday, February 20, 2026, recouping a portion of the previous session's steep losses. The Sensex climbed 316.57 points while the Nifty 50 managed to close above the crucial 25,550 mark. Despite a cautious start triggered by escalating U.S.-Iran tensions and high crude oil prices, broad-based buying in heavyweights like Hindalco, NTPC and L&T, supported by positive news from the India AI Impact Summit, offset continued weakness in the IT sector, allowing both benchmark indices to end the week with marginal gains. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex rose 0.38% to settle at 82,814.71. The Nifty 50 index rose 116.90 points or 0.46% to close at 25,571.25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Bharti Airtel, RailTel Corp, Cipla, Highway Infrastructure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-railtel-corp-cipla-highway-infrastructure/1679037</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679037</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 23 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 23 February 2026. Initial Public Offer (IPO): Shree Ram Twistex IPO opens for subscription today. The issue size is Rs 110.24 crore, comprising entirely a fresh issue. The price band has been fixed at Rs 95 to Rs 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions IPO opens for subscription today. The total issue size aggregates up to Rs 3,100 crore, comprising a fresh issue of Rs 1,200 crore and an offer for sale of up to Rs 1,900 crore. The price band has been set at Rs 1,000 to Rs 1,053 per share. Stocks to Watch: Bharti Airtel, in partnership with Zscaler Inc. (a leader in cloud security), announced the launch of the AI & Cyber Threat Research Center—India, advancing national cyber resilience, protecting sectors, industries, and assets, and accelerating trusted AI adoption. Suraj Estate Developers announced that it has entered into an agreement to acquire a 100% stake in Hally Pacific to undertake the development of a plot situated in Prabhadevi, Mumbai. Quality Power Electrical Equipments announced that its material subsidiary, Mehru Electrical and Mechanical Engineers, has received a letter of award (LoA) worth Rs 18 crore for the supply of instrument transformers from a domestic entity. Sathlokhar Synergys E&C Global has secured new orders aggregating to Rs 37.57 crore for the execution of civil and pre-engineered building (PEB) works. WeWork India Management said that it has entered into a lease deed for capacity addition in Bengaluru, admeasuring 169,485 square feet, which will result in an increase in its operational capacity. Cipla announced that the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) has classified the cGMP inspection at the Rodopi, Greece, facility of Pharmathen International S.A., which supplies lanreotide injection to Cipla USA Inc. (a wholly owned arm of Cipla), as Official Action Indicated (OAI). Meanwhile, Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) raised its stake in Cipla to 9.091% from 7.055% between 27 November 2025 and 2 February 2026. RailTel Corporation of India, in consortium with Ashoka Buildcon, has received the Letter of Intent (LoI) from the Inspector General of Registration (IGR). The contract, worth Rs 1,136.18 crore, involves the selection of an MSP for the modernization of offices of the IGR and the Controller of Stamps under the Maharashtra Government. As per the letter of intent (LoI), the accepted rate is Rs 24.75 per page. The average number of pages scanned annually over the past five years, as per the Request for Proposal (RFP), stood at 9.18 crore pages. Based on this volume, the estimated financial impact over the five-year contract period is approximately Rs 1,136.18 crore. Highway Infrastructure has entered into a contract agreement for the operation and collection of user fees at Moti Naroli Fee Plaza in Gujarat, amounting to Rs 154.59 crore. Additionally, the company has entered into a contract agreement for the development of a road under Town Planning Scheme-08 from Kumedi to Lasudiya Mori (up to AB Road), Indore. The contract is worth Rs 69.68 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axiscades Technologies arm bags contracts from Hindustan Aeronautics]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axiscades-technologies-arm-bags-contracts-from-hindustan-aeronautics/1679036</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679036</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has secured a domestic supply order, to be executed over multiple years, with a total consideration of approximately Rs 25 crore.

The company has secured a domestic supply order, to be executed over multiple years, with a total consideration of approximately Rs 25 crore. Under this order, Mistral Solutions will supply Single Board Computer, further contributing to the LCA Mk1A program for HAL. All systems will be manufactured and delivered from AXISCADES’ newly commissioned DAL (Devanahalli Atmanirbhar Complex) facility located at the Bangalore Aerospace Park, near Kempegowda International Airport. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity. The promoter, promoter group and group companies do not have any interest in the awarding entity. The contract does not fall within the ambit of related party transactions. Commenting on the development,C. Manikandan, CEO, Mistral Solutions, said: “This order win reflects the AXISCADES Group’s increasing value addition to ‘Make in India’ initiative.” Bengaluru-based Axiscades Technologies is an end-to-end technology and product engineering company operating across aerospace, defence and ESAI domains, with capabilities spanning the full product development lifecycle. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 87.39% year-on-year to Rs 27.66 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 14.76 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 25% YoY to Rs 343.17 crore in Q3 FY26. Shares of Axiscades Technologies fell 2.71% to end at Rs 1,415.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AXISCADESEngg_38496178544_21304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>