<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DoT releases National Frequency Allocation Plan 2025 (NFAP-2025)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dot-releases-national-frequency-allocation-plan-2025-nfap-2025/1662487</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662487</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Department of Telecommunications (DoT), Ministry of Communications, released the National Frequency Allocation Plan 2025 (NFAP-2025) — a key policy document that governs the management and allocation of radio-frequency spectrum in India.

The Department of Telecommunications (DoT), Ministry of Communications, released the National Frequency Allocation Plan 2025 (NFAP-2025) — a key policy document that governs the management and allocation of radio-frequency spectrum in India. NFAP-2025 will come into effect from 30 December 2025. The NFAP-2025 will provide the allocation of radio-frequency spectrum to various radio-communication services in the frequency range 8.3 kHz to 3000 GHz. It serves as an essential reference for spectrum managers, wireless operators, and telecom equipment manufacturers. NFAP-2025 introduces several strategic and future-ready revisions to meet the growing spectrum demand for next-generation technologies. Identification of the 6425–7125 MHz band for International Mobile Telecommunications (IMT), significantly enhancing mid-band spectrum availability for 5G, 5G Advanced, and future 6G networks. Allocation of Ka, Q, and V bands for satellite-based services, crucial for high-throughput Geo-Stationary Orbit (GSO) satellites and large non-GSO satellite constellations. Additional spectrum for In-Flight and Maritime Connectivity (IFMC) to ensure seamless broadband access in the air and at sea. Support for emerging technologies such as Vehicle-to-Everything (V2X) communication, LEO/MEO satellite services, and expanded broadband connectivity solutions. These enhancements will ensure that India’s spectrum management remains responsive, high-capacity, and harmonised with global standards, supporting both current and future digital innovations, which will help in enhancing development of eco-system in India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/world-1195593__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at muted start for equities on final day of the year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-muted-start-for-equities-on-final-day-of-the-year/1662482</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662482</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 5.00 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 5.00 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,844.02 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 6,159.81 crore in the Indian equity market on 30 December 2025, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 30,752.24 crore so far in December. This follows their cash sales of Rs 17,500.31 crore in November and Rs 2,346.89 crore in October. Global Markets: Asia market fell on the holiday-shortened and final trading day of the year. Markets in Hong Kong and Australia will close early for the holidays, while Japan and South Korea are shut for the day. China’s economy ended the year on a slightly less gloomy note, as factory activity expanded in December for the first time since March, beating expectations, according to official data released Wednesday. The official manufacturing purchasing managers index rose to 50.1 in December, higher than 49.2 reading that was recorded in November. A reading above 50 indicates expansion. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 fell modestly, notching a third consecutive losing session. The broad market index lost 0.14% and closed at 6,896.24, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.24% and settled at 23,419.08. The Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 0.20% and ended at 48,367.06. The three major averages have slumped to start the week, dragged down by losses in tech. Nvidia posted back-to-back losing sessions, as did another AI stock Palantir Technologies. Domestic Market: The benchmark equity indices closed marginally lower on Tuesday as persistent foreign institutional selling and thin year-end trading kept sentiment subdued. The absence of fresh domestic cues and caution ahead of the Q3 earnings season also weighed on the indices. The Nifty slipped below the 25,950 level after hitting an intraday high of 26,976.75 in early trade. Volatility remained elevated due to the monthly derivatives expiry. Consumer durables and IT stocks declined, while metal, PSU bank and auto shares ended higher. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 20.46 points or 0.02% to 84,675.08. The Nifty 50 index lost 3.25 points or 0.01% to 25,938.85. The 50 unit index is down 0.91% in four consecutive sessions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RITES wins $3.6 million locomotive supply order from Zimbabwe-based entity]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rites-wins-36-million-locomotive-supply-order-from-zimbabwe-based-entity/1662480</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662480</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the supply of operational Cape Gauge diesel electric locomotives and is scheduled to be executed within a period of three months, RITES said in a regulatory filing.

The order involves the supply of operational Cape Gauge diesel electric locomotives and is scheduled to be executed within a period of three months, RITES said in a regulatory filing. The contract has been awarded by an international entity and does not fall under related party transactions. The company further clarified that the promoter or promoter group has no interest in the entity awarding the contract. The total consideration for the order stands at $3.6 million (USD Three Million Six Hundred Thousand only). RITES is a Navratna Public Sector Enterprise and a leading player in the transport consultancy and engineering sector in India, having diversified services and geographical reach. The company has an experience spanning 50 years and undertaken projects in over 55 countries in Asia, Africa, Latin America, South America, and Middle East region. As on September, the Government of India held 72.20% in the company. The company reported a 32.24% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 109.10 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 82.50 crore a year earlier. Revenue from operations grew 1.45% YoY to Rs 548.74 crore for the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of Rites fell 3.08% to end at Rs 237.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RitesLtd_46602882106_24268.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Bharat Forge, Power Grid, Titan Company, RITES]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-bharat-forge-power-grid-titan-company-rites/1662479</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662479</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Stocks to Watch: Bharat Forge has received a contract worth Rs 1,661.9 crore from the Ministry of Defence for the supply of 255,128 CQB carbines (5.56 x 45 mm) to the Indian Army.

Stocks to Watch: Bharat Forge has received a contract worth Rs 1,661.9 crore from the Ministry of Defence for the supply of 255,128 CQB carbines (5.56 x 45 mm) to the Indian Army. The contract stipulates order execution within five years. Power Grid Corporation of India has been declared the successful bidder for the selection of battery energy storage developers for setting up a cumulative capacity of 2,000 MWh (1,000 MW x 2 hours) of standalone battery energy storage systems in Andhra Pradesh. The project comprises a 150 MW/300 MWh battery energy storage system at the 400/220 kV substation at Kalikiri in Chittoor district, Andhra Pradesh. RITES has received a Letter of Award for the supply of in-service Cape gauge diesel-electric locomotives from Berhard Development Corporation, Zimbabwe. The order is valued at $3.6 million. Dynacons Systems & Solutions said that it has received orders worth Rs 249 crore from RBI for the implementation & maintenance of enterprise applications platform software. Titan Company said that its board has approved the appointment of Sandhya Venugopal Sharma, IAS, as chairperson and additional director of the company, effective January 4, 2026. Arfin India announced that it has received an order worth Rs 321 crore from Diamond Power Infra for the supply of Aluminium sector conductors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>