<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:50:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee sees tight moves against US dollar]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-sees-tight-moves-against-us-dollar/1679732</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679732</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee saw a narrow movement today, mimicking action in last session.

Indian Rupee saw a narrow movement today, mimicking action in last session. INR closed flat at 90.92 per US dollar. The US dollar index is consolidating near four-week high and currently trades up marginally at 97.70. Domestic equity indices ended sideways on Thursday after a volatile trading session. The benchmarks opened with strong gains in early morning trade, supported by buying interest in IT and pharma stocks. However, as the day progressed, momentum weakened and profit-booking emerged. In the mid-afternoon session, the Nifty slipped into negative territory amid heightened volatility triggered by the monthly Sensex F&O expiry. Although the index staged a mild recovery in the final hour of trade, it ultimately settled on a flat note, keeping INR in a tight range just like the previous session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-accountant-financial-papers-analysis-charts-pict_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery subscribed 1.23 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pngs-reva-diamond-jewellery-subscribed-123-times/1679730</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679730</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 70,31,776 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Thursday (26 February 2026).

PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 70,31,776 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Thursday (26 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.23 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. The IPO comprises a fresh issue of equity shares worth up to Rs 380 crore. The objectives for the fresh issue include Rs 286.56 for funding expenditure towards setting up 15 new stores, Rs 35.4 crore for marketing and promotional expenses, and the remaining amount for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery on 23 February 2026, raised Rs 170.58 crore from anchor investors by allotting 44.19 lakh shares at Rs 386 each to 16 anchor investors. P.N. Gadgil & Sons, its corporate promoter, divested its diamond business through a slump sale to PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery under a business transfer agreement (BTA). Following this transaction, PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery operates as a separate entity in the diamond jewelry segment. PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery offers different types of jewellery using diamonds and precious and semi-precious stones, which are studded into precious metals such as gold and platinum. The product offerings include rings, earrings, necklaces, pendants, solitaires, bangles, bracelets, mangalsutra, nose rings, and chains to cater to diverse customer segments and occasions. Prices start at around Rs 20,000 and go up to high-value jewelry pieces. As of September 30, 2025, the company had 13 distinct jewelry collections, including in-house design team and curated selections from third-party manufacturers and Karigars. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 20.13 crore and income from operations of Rs 156.72 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee sustains momentum]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-sustains-momentum/1679729</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679729</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 91.0550 per Dollar on Thursday (26 February 2026), versus its previous close of 91.0825 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper sees marginal loss]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-sees-marginal-loss/1679728</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679728</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures consolidated around two-week high with modest profit selling pulling the counter down.

COMEX Copper futures consolidated around two-week high with modest profit selling pulling the counter down. The counter currently trades at $6.03 per pound, down 0.23% on the day. In Asia, China's Shanghai Composite index closed flat after latest gains. Hong Kong’s Hang Seng index slipped 1.40% while Japan’s Nikkei average added 0.29% after hitting fresh record high. European stocks saw mixed moves. The US stocks edged up in last session. The Dow added 0.60% while Nasdaq jumped 1.3% and the S&P 500 rose 0.80%. MCX Copper futures are currently quoting at Rs 1206 per kg, down 0.44% on the day with lows around Rs 1200 per kg mark providing some downside support to the counter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/closeup-of-blue-chart-growth-progress-picture-id177428264_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Omnitech Engineering IPO subscribed 13%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/omnitech-engineering-ipo-subscribed-13/1679725</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679725</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Omnitech Engineering received bids for 25,03,314 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Thursday (26 February 2026).

Omnitech Engineering received bids for 25,03,314 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Thursday (26 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.13 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026, and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 66 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue comprises both an offer for sale and a fresh issue of equity shares (of Rs 5 face value) worth aggregating to Rs 165 crore and Rs 418 crore, respectively. The entire portion of the offer for sale is by Udaykumar Arunkumar Parekh. Of the net proceeds, the company proposed to utilize Rs 50 crore towards repayment and/or prepayment, in full or in part, of certain outstanding borrowings availed by the company; Rs 233.558 crore towards setting up of two new manufacturing facilities at Village Chhapara (in Rajkot District) [with Rs 132.844 crore for facility 1 and Rs 100.714 crore for facility 2]; Rs 18.698 crore for funding towards capital expenditure requirements for purchase and installation of solar panels on the rooftop at, and purchase of new equipment/machinery for, the existing manufacturing facility at Village Chhapara; and the balance towards general corporate purposes. Outstanding borrowings at the end of Sep 2025 stood at Rs 382.913 crore. Omnitech Engineering (OEL), promoted by Udaykumar Arunkumar Parekh, is a key player in high-precision components and assemblies, serving global clients across energy, automation, and industrial equipment sectors. The company operates 3 strategically located facilities near Mundra Port, with exports contributing approximately 79% of revenue. As of September 2025, OEL’s order book stood at Rs 1,765 crore, representing 5x FY25 sales, highlighting robust demand and strong business momentum. Ahead of the IPO of Omnitech Engineering on 24 February 2026, the company raised Rs 174.59 crore from anchor investors by allotting 76.91 lakh shares at Rs 227 each to 17 anchor investors. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 27.79 crore and sales of Rs 228.17 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yes Bank flags unauthorized forex transactions from Latin American Country]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yes-bank-flags-unauthorized-forex-transactions-from-latin-american-country/1679724</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679724</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[These unauthorised transactions were attempted on specific BIN numbers only, the bank added.

These unauthorised transactions were attempted on specific BIN numbers only, the bank added. The private sector lender further informed that the aforementioned transactions were carried out on 15 merchants that are based out of Latin American Country, in the early hours on 24 February 2026, between 3:30 AM and 8:30 AM (IST). The specific country does not mandate two factor authentication for e-commerce transactions. As a security measure, the bank has subsequently restricted e-commerce transactions from the specific Latin American Country. The internal investigation by the Bank has revealed that during the incident period transactions approximately equivalent of $0.28 million have been approved on behalf of 5000 customers. Due to the Bank’s monitoring and control mechanisms, 688 unauthorised transaction attempts were declined, which led to safeguarding of approximately equivalent to $0.1 million. “The bank is working with Card Network to raise chargeback to ensure that the impacted customers do not face any financial loss,” Yes Bank said in a statement. As per media reports, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has summoned senior officials of Yes Bank after the recent data breach involving the bank's co-branded multi-currency forex card. The RBI has sought a detailed explanation from Yes Bank on how sensitive card data was stored and protected, whether encryption and mandated cybersecurity protocols were followed, and why existing safeguards failed to prevent the breach, media report said. The central bank is reportedly also examining the timeline of detection and reporting, the extent of customer impact, the steps taken to block compromised cards and limit losses, as well as the bank's oversight of third-party service providers. According to media reports, the regulator has additionally asked for clarity on internal accountability and the corrective measures being implemented to prevent a recurrence. Yes Bank, a full-service commercial bank headquartered in Mumbai, offers a wide array of products, services, and digital solutions, catering to Retail, MSME, and Corporate clients. The bank operates its brokerage business through Yes Securities, a subsidiary of the bank. The bank has a pan-India presence including an International Banking Unit (IBU) at GIFT City, and a representative office in Abu Dhabi. The bank had reported 55.4% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 952 crore on a 9.7% increase in total income to Rs 4,098 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip advanced 1.40% to end at Rs 21.03 on the BSE today. On the BSE, 89.07 lakh shares of the bank had changed hands at the counter as compared with the average trading volume of 18.70 lakh shares recorded in the past two weeks. In December 2025, NSE Indices had announced a rebalancing of the Nifty Bank index. The the Index Maintenance Sub-Committee (Equity) had decided to include Yes Bank into the Nifty Bank index. The Committee had stated that this rebalancing would take place in four monthly tranches, with the execution happening on the last trading of December 2025, January 2026, February 2026 and March 2026. Following this rebalancing, the stock of Yes Bank has reportedly recorded significant index-related inflows. According to media reports, Yes Bank is set to receive about $140 million in cumulative inflows, spread across the four tranches. Of this, around $26 million is estimated to flow in during today’s February tranche, following inflows of $91 million in December and $13 million in January. The balance inflows would occur at the end of March.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/YesBank_75840425465_25267.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBL Bank receives RBI nod for SBI Mutual Fund to acquire up to 10% stake]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbl-bank-receives-rbi-nod-for-sbi-mutual-fund-to-acquire-up-to-10-stake/1679723</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679723</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approval has been granted pursuant to an application made by SBI Mutual Fund to the RBI.

The approval has been granted pursuant to an application made by SBI Mutual Fund to the RBI. It is subject to various conditions, including compliance with the Banking Regulation Act, 1949; the Reserve Bank of India (Commercial Banks – Acquisition and Holding of Shares or Voting Rights) Directions, 2025; the Foreign Exchange Management Act, 1999; and regulations issued by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI), along with other applicable statutes and guidelines. As per the RBI letter, SBI Mutual Fund has been granted one year from the date of approval to acquire the proposed shareholding. The fund must ensure that its aggregate holding does not exceed 9.99% of the bank’s paid-up share capital or voting rights at any time. Further, if the aggregate holding of SBI Mutual Fund falls below 5% at any point, prior RBI approval will be required to increase it to 5% or more of the paid-up share capital or voting rights of the bank. As of 20 February 2026, SBI Mutual Fund held 1.88% of RBL Bank’s equity share capital. RBL Bank provides a wide range of banking and financial services, including wholesale banking, retail banking, treasury operations, and other banking-related activities. As of 31st December 2025, the bank has 1,921 total touch points of which 580 are bank branches and 1,341 business correspondent branches. Of 1,341 BC branches, 291 are banking outlets. RBL Finserve, a 100% subsidiary of the Bank, accounts for 1,084 business correspondent branches. RBL Bank reported a massive 555.47% surge in standalone net profit to Rs 213.88 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 32.63 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 2.33% YoY to Rs 4,71,700 crore as on 31st December 2025. The counter shed 0.85% to settle at Rs 327 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RBLBankLtd_63443224104_5982.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers end sideways; Nifty closes near 25,500 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-end-sideways-nifty-closes-near-25500-level/1679722</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679722</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended in sideways trend, as market participants monitored Prime Minster Narendra Modi’s visit to Israel.

The key equity benchmarks ended in sideways trend, as market participants monitored Prime Minster Narendra Modi’s visit to Israel. The visit comes amid heightened geopolitical tensions in the region, U.S. warnings, and evolving global diplomatic dynamics, adding a layer of caution to market sentiment. The Nifty briefly slipped into negative territory amid volatility surrounding the monthly F&O expiry before recovering marginally in the final hour to close little changed. Nifty ended near the 25,500 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex shed 27.46 points or 0.03% to 82,248.61. The Nifty 50 index rose 14.05 points or 0.06% to 25,496.55. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rallied 0.55% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.07%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 3.15% to 13.06. PM Modi Visit to Israel: Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s visit to Israel comes against the backdrop of ongoing India–Israel free trade agreement talks aimed at enhancing trade and investment between the two countries Israeli President Isaac Herzog described India as “an essential part of a great future for the Middle East”, while emphasising the growing importance of India-Israel cooperation during his bilateral meeting with Prime Minister Narendra Modi as part of the latter’s two-day state visit to the country. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.07% to 6.687 compared with the previous session close of 6.682. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9400 compared with its close of 90.9100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 1.16% to Rs 159,273. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.10% to 97.76. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.05% to 4.047. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement declined $1.09 or 1.54% to $70.85 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 65 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European stocks traded mixed on Thursday as investors digested a deluge of regional corporate earnings as well as numbers from chip giant Nvidia on Wall Street. Asian markets ended mixed, with South Korean and Japanese stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker. Stocks in Spotlight: Sundaram Clayton surged 8.51% after the company’s board approved the appointment of R Venkatesh as chief executive officer (CEO) with effect from 1 April 2026. b The development comes after board approved the resignation of Vivek S Joshi as CEO with effect from 31st march 2026, due to personal reasons. Aurobindo Pharma added 0.62%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Eugia Pharma Specialities, has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) to manufacture and market Everolimus tablets. Capillary Technologies India declined 1.19%. The company has announced the acquisition of Session M Inc., a U.S.-based loyalty and customer engagement platform, from payments giant Mastercard Inc. in an all-cash deal valued at approximately $20 million. Alembic Pharmaceuticals shed 0.79%. The company announced that it has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA), Lamotrigine Orally Disintegrating Tablets USP, 25 mg, 50 mg, 100 mg, and 200 mg. Balu Forge Industries hit an upper circuit of 10% after it has entered into a legally binding memorandum of understanding (MoU) for the supply of empty artillery shells from its greenfield manufacturing facility in Belgaum, Karnataka. Tejas Networks soared 16.07% after the company announced that it has signed an agreement with NEC Corporation to manufacture and supply 5G massive MIMO radios. E2E Networks added 1.66% after the company announced that its board has approved the opening of the issue of qualified institutional placement (QIP) of equity shares. Praveg slipped 0.82%. The company has received a letter of award (LoA) from the Directorate of Tourism, Government of Meghalaya, for the development, operation and maintenance of luxury cottages at Umiam in Meghalaya. Diamond Power Infrastructure advanced 2.89% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 93.08 crore from KPI Green Energy for the supply of power cables. Dynacons Systems & Solutions rallied 3.68% after it has secured a contract worth Rs 108.88 crore from Punjab & Sind Bank for the supply, implementation and management of on-premises private cloud infrastructure. IPO Update: Omnitech Engineering received bids for24,51,900 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer , according to stock exchange data at 16:27 IST on Thursday (26 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.13 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026 and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 69,64,352 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:27 IST on Thursday (26 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.17 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Currency in circulation gains 8.6% this fiscal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/currency-in-circulation-gains-86-this-fiscal/1679720</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679720</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation edged up 1.1% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 40.44 lakh crore as on February 15, 2026.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation edged up 1.1% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 40.44 lakh crore as on February 15, 2026. The central bank stated further that the overall reserve money edged up 0.3% in the same period to Rs 49.65 lakh crore. Currency in circulation gained 10.8% on a year ago basis compared to 5.6% rise at the same time last year. In the current fiscal year, the currency in circulation moved up 8.6% so far while the reserve money has added 2.2%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/balance-between-time-and-money-picture-id497638624_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty March futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-march-futures-trade-at-premium/1679718</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679718</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 30 March 2026 futures closed at 25,637, a premium of 140.45 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,496.55 in the cash market.

The Nifty 30 March 2026 futures closed at 25,637, a premium of 140.45 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,496.55 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index rose 14.05 points or 0.06% to 25,496.55. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 3.15% to 13.06. HDFC Bank, Eternal and Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The March 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 30 March 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty end flat after choppy session; broader market outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-end-flat-after-choppy-session-broader-market-outperforms/1679716</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679716</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended flat on Thursday after a choppy session.

The key equity indices ended flat on Thursday after a choppy session. The benchmarks opened strong on buying in IT and pharma shares but lost steam as profit-booking emerged. The Nifty briefly slipped into negative territory amid volatility surrounding the monthly F&O expiry before recovering marginally in the final hour to close little changed. Nifty ended near the 25,500 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex shed 27.46 points or 0.03% to 82,248.61. The Nifty 50 index rose 14.05 points or 0.06% to 25,496.55. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rallied 0.55% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.07%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 3.15% to 13.06. Among the sectoral indices, the Healthcare index (up 1.24%), the Nifty Pharma index (up 1.08%) and the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 0.95%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Media index (down 0.68%), the Nifty FMCG index (down 0.16%) and the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 0.01%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.07% to 6.687 compared with the previous session close of 6.682. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9225 compared with its close of 90.9100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 0.83% to Rs 159,801. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.08% to 97.74. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.12% to 4.054. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement shed 39 cents or 0.55% to $70.46 a barrel. Global Markets: European stocks traded mixed on Thursday, as investors digested a deluge of regional corporate earnings as well as numbers from chip giant Nvidia on Wall Street. Asian markets ended mixed, with South Korean and Japanese stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Pharma Index rises 1.08%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-pharma-index-rises-108/1679713</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679713</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Pharma index closed up 1.08% at 23301.65 today.

Nifty Pharma index closed up 1.08% at 23301.65 today. The index is up 7.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Mankind Pharma Ltd gained 5.75%, Alkem Laboratories Ltd rose 2.26% and Zydus Lifesciences Ltd added 2.05%. The Nifty Pharma index is up 15.00% over last one year compared to the 13.08% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index added 0.95% and Nifty Auto index added 0.80% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 added 0.06% to close at 25496.55 while the SENSEX is down 0.03% to close at 82248.61 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finance-108655__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends sideways; Nifty settles near 25,500 level; VIX drops 3.15%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-sideways-nifty-settles-near-25500-level-vix-drops-315/1679712</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679712</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity indices ended sideways on Thursday after a volatile trading session.

Domestic equity indices ended sideways on Thursday after a volatile trading session. The benchmarks opened with strong gains in early morning trade, supported by buying interest in IT and pharma stocks. However, as the day progressed, momentum weakened and profit-booking emerged. In the mid-afternoon session, the Nifty slipped into negative territory amid heightened volatility triggered by the monthly Sensex F&O expiry. Although the index staged a mild recovery in the final hour of trade, it ultimately settled on a flat note, reflecting cautious investor sentiment. Nifty ended near the 25,500 level. Pharma, PSU bank and oil & gas shares advanced, while media, FMCG and financial services stocks declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex shed 27.46 points or 0.03% to 82,248.61. The Nifty 50 index rose 14.05 points or 0.06% to 25,496.55. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rallied 0.55% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.07%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,170 shares rose and 2,034 shares fell. A total of 163 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 3.15% to 13.06. PM Modi Visit to Israel: Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s visit to Israel comes against the backdrop of ongoing India–Israel free trade agreement talks aimed at enhancing trade and investment between the two countries Israeli President Isaac Herzog described India as “an essential part of a great future for the Middle East”, while emphasising the growing importance of India-Israel cooperation during his bilateral meeting with Prime Minister Narendra Modi as part of the latter’s two-day state visit to the country. IPO Update: Omnitech Engineering received bids for 22,60,104 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.12 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026 and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 66,78,816 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 1.17 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Pharma index surged 1.08% to 23,301.65. The index rallied 3.89% in the five consecutive trading sessions. Mankind Pharma (up 5.81%), Alkem Laboratories (up 2.27%), Glenmark Pharmaceuticals (up 2.02%), Zydus Lifesciences (up 1.98%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 1.50%), Laurus Labs (up 1.48%), Lupin (up 1.37%), Divis Laboratories (up 1.10%), Dr Reddys Laboratories (up 1.03%) and Aurobindo Pharma (up 0.87%) advanced. On the other hand, Ajanta Pharma (down 1.23%), Wockhardt (down 1.10%) and Biocon (down 0.49%) edged lower. Stocks in Spotlight: Sundaram Clayton surged 8.51% after the company’s board approved the appointment of R Venkatesh as chief executive officer (CEO) with effect from 1 April 2026. b The development comes after board approved the resignation of Vivek S Joshi as CEO with effect from 31st march 2026, due to personal reasons. Aurobindo Pharma added 0.62%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Eugia Pharma Specialities, has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) to manufacture and market Everolimus tablets. Capillary Technologies India declined 1.19%. The company has announced the acquisition of Session M Inc., a U.S.-based loyalty and customer engagement platform, from payments giant Mastercard Inc. in an all-cash deal valued at approximately $20 million. Alembic Pharmaceuticals shed 0.79%. The company announced that it has received final approval from the US Food & Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA), Lamotrigine Orally Disintegrating Tablets USP, 25 mg, 50 mg, 100 mg, and 200 mg. Balu Forge Industries hit an upper circuit of 10% after it has entered into a legally binding memorandum of understanding (MoU) for the supply of empty artillery shells from its greenfield manufacturing facility in Belgaum, Karnataka. Tejas Networks soared 16.07% after the company announced that it has signed an agreement with NEC Corporation to manufacture and supply 5G massive MIMO radios. E2E Networks added 1.66% after the company announced that its board has approved the opening of the issue of qualified institutional placement (QIP) of equity shares. Praveg slipped 0.82%. The company has received a letter of award (LoA) from the Directorate of Tourism, Government of Meghalaya, for the development, operation and maintenance of luxury cottages at Umiam in Meghalaya. Diamond Power Infrastructure advanced 2.89% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 93.08 crore from KPI Green Energy for the supply of power cables. Dynacons Systems & Solutions rallied 3.68% after it has secured a contract worth Rs 108.88 crore from Punjab & Sind Bank for the supply, implementation and management of on-premises private cloud infrastructure. Global Markets: European stocks traded in a mixed on Thursday, as investors digested a deluge of regional corporate earnings as well as numbers from chip giant Nvidia on Wall Street. Asian markets ended mixed with South Korea and Japan stocks hitting record highs Wednesday, after a tech-driven rally on Wall Street that was fueled by easing concerns around artificial intelligence-led disruption to select industries. U.S. equities rose on Tuesday, led by gains in Advanced Micro Devices and software stocks, as investors’ fears around artificial intelligence disruption to certain industries eased. The S&P 500 advanced 0.77% to close at 6,890.07, while the Nasdaq Composite rose 1.04% and settled at 22,863.68. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 370.44 points, or 0.76%, and ended at 49,174.50. Shares of AMD jumped 8.8% after Meta Platforms announced a multiyear deal with the semiconductor company. The new partnership entails deploying up to 6 gigawatts of AMD’s graphics processing units for AI data centers. Meta will also invest in AMD through a performance-based warrant for up to 160 million shares of the chipmaker.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background-picture-i_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Home First Finance Company India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679700</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679700</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sagility Ltd, Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd and Tips Music Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 February 2026.

Sagility Ltd, Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd, Aegis Logistics Ltd and Tips Music Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 February 2026. Home First Finance Company India Ltd tumbled 5.08% to Rs 1182.75 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.33 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18293 shares in the past one month. Sagility Ltd crashed 4.21% to Rs 40.98. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 17.51 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19.18 lakh shares in the past one month. Nippon Life India Asset Management Ltd lost 3.92% to Rs 937.2. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 27279 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 55073 shares in the past one month. Aegis Logistics Ltd slipped 3.79% to Rs 699.7. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.37 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.05 lakh shares in the past one month. Tips Music Ltd corrected 3.36% to Rs 538.45. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3661 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6016 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HomeFirstFinanceCompanyIndiaLtd_56604898_71865.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[US dollar continues to dominate global foreign exchange transactions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/us-dollar-continues-to-dominate-global-foreign-exchange-transactions/1679701</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679701</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The US dollar is crucial for Americans and global markets alike, and its international standing affects investments, borrowing costs and everyday prices, noted a latest blog post from the St.

The US dollar is crucial for Americans and global markets alike, and its international standing affects investments, borrowing costs and everyday prices, noted a latest blog post from the St. Louis Federal Reserve. The US dollar (USD) is the most widely used, employed in 89% of foreign exchange transactions in 2025, according to data in the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) Triennial Central Bank Survey. The USD has been the dominant reserve currency since 1945, with dollar-denominated securities, mostly US Treasuries and investment-grade corporate bonds, making up approximately 57% of global foreign exchange reserves, for a value of $7.4 trillion, according to another IMF dataset, Currency Composition of Official Foreign Exchange Reserves (COFER), as of the third quarter of 2025. Euro-denominated securities are in second place, making up approximately 20% of global foreign exchange reserves. Governments and central banks hold large quantities of US dollar assets because the US government and corporations issue a large amount of dollar-denominated, liquid assets that are seen as safe. To earn such a reputation for its assets, the US has had solid legal and economic institutions and an open and generally well-regulated financial system. All these factors reduce the perceived risk of investing in such assets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/foreign-currency-exchange-rate-on-digital-led-display-scree_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dynacons Systems gains on bagging Rs 109-cr order from Punjab & Sind Bank]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dynacons-systems-gains-on-bagging-rs-109-cr-order-from-punjab-sind-bank/1679697</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679697</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The five-year domestic contract involves the design and implementation of IT infrastructure, underlying system software and cloud services to support the deployment and hosting of the bank’s applications, including its Data Center and Disaster Recovery (DC–DR) environment.

The five-year domestic contract involves the design and implementation of IT infrastructure, underlying system software and cloud services to support the deployment and hosting of the bank’s applications, including its Data Center and Disaster Recovery (DC–DR) environment. Dynacons will oversee the end-to-end execution of the project, ensuring infrastructure readiness and operational management over the contract tenure. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in Punjab & Sind Bank. It also stated that the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Dynacons Systems & Solutions provides IT infrastructure solutions. The company provides services nation wide. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 28% to Rs 23.48 crore on 9.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 340.59 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Punjab and Sind Bank is a leading public sector bank and a major bank in northern India. The bank provides customer service through innovative products and services for different customer segments. The bank’s standalone net profit jumped 19.3% to Rs 336.42 crore on 8.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3549.27 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip rose 0.62% to Rs 25.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DynaconsSys_66434123216_20947.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679695</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679695</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Usha Martin Education & Solutions Ltd, UR Sugar Industries Ltd, Flexituff Ventures International Ltd and Filatex Fashions Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 February 2026.

Usha Martin Education & Solutions Ltd, UR Sugar Industries Ltd, Flexituff Ventures International Ltd and Filatex Fashions Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 February 2026. R M Drip & Sprinklers Systems Ltd crashed 19.96% to Rs 78.4 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 19893 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.12 lakh shares in the past one month. Usha Martin Education & Solutions Ltd lost 12.90% to Rs 4.12. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 58560 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2247 shares in the past one month. UR Sugar Industries Ltd tumbled 10.58% to Rs 2.45. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.08 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.17 lakh shares in the past one month. Flexituff Ventures International Ltd fell 8.82% to Rs 9.82. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 153 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2677 shares in the past one month. Filatex Fashions Ltd pared 8.70% to Rs 0.21. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 170 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 149.74 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RMDripSprinklersSystemsLtd_34584827303_71578.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold trades soft as investors await US jobs and inflation numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-trades-soft-as-investors-await-us-jobs-and-inflation-numbers/1679689</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679689</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures slipped below $5200 per ounce in Asia on Thursday as investors remained cautious ahead of US unemployment data due today and key growth and inflation figures due on Friday.

Gold futures slipped below $5200 per ounce in Asia on Thursday as investors remained cautious ahead of US unemployment data due today and key growth and inflation figures due on Friday. Mild selling pressure was seen at higher levels, though losses were capped as geopolitical tensions in the Middle East, ongoing uncertainty over US trade policies, and a softer dollar index near 97.5 continued to support the metal close to four-week highs. The buildup of US troops ahead of nuclear talks in Geneva and fresh sanctions on Iran kept safe-haven demand intact, while expectations that the Federal Reserve will keep interest rates unchanged helped limit downside. In the domestic market, MCX April gold futures declined over 1% to Rs 159,384 per 10 grams, with immediate support seen around Rs 159,100 and Rs 158,850.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with moderate losses; realty shares extent losses for 4th day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-moderate-losses-realty-shares-extent-losses-for-4th-day/1679683</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679683</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The frontline equity benchmarks trade with limited losses in the mid-afternoon trade amid a shift toward a risk-off sentiment.

The frontline equity benchmarks trade with limited losses in the mid-afternoon trade amid a shift toward a risk-off sentiment. The Nifty traded below the 25,450 mark after hitting a day's high of 25,572.95 in early afternoon trade. Realty shares extended losses for the fourth consecutive trading session. At 14:27 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 155.38 points or 0.19% to 82,120.69. The Nifty 50 index fell 47.10 points or 0.18% to 25,435.90. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rose 0.17% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.14%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,921 shares rose and 2,136 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 0.42% to 793.50. The index fell 3.31% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Lodha Developers (down 2.15%), Godrej Properties (down 1.2%), SignatureGlobal India (down 1.1%), Sobha (down 1%), DLF (down 0.44%), Anant Raj (down 0.27%), Phoenix Mills (up 0.54%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 0.51%) and Brigade Enterprises (up 0.41%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.16% to 6.693 compared with the previous session close of 6.682. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.8800 compared with its close of 90.9100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 1.12% to Rs 159,333. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.02% to 97.64. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.02% to 4.050. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 16 cents or 0.23% to $70.85 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Praveg added 0.72%. The company has received a letter of award (LoA) from the Directorate of Tourism, Government of Meghalaya, for the development, operation and maintenance of luxury cottages at Umiam in Meghalaya. Diamond Power Infrastructure advanced 2.89% after the company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 93.08 crore from KPI Green Energy for the supply of power cables.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at KSB Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-ksb-ltd-counter/1679682</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679682</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, Maharashtra Seamless Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 February 2026.

Tejas Networks Ltd, Home First Finance Company India Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, Maharashtra Seamless Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 February 2026. KSB Ltd clocked volume of 132.59 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 179.08 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 74039 shares. The stock gained 8.56% to Rs.778.50. Volumes stood at 2.29 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd registered volume of 493.21 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 59.93 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 8.23 lakh shares. The stock rose 13.44% to Rs.360.50. Volumes stood at 6.05 lakh shares in the last session. Home First Finance Company India Ltd witnessed volume of 67.92 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 46.22 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.47 lakh shares. The stock dropped 5.25% to Rs.1,182.30. Volumes stood at 3.89 lakh shares in the last session. Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd registered volume of 85.7 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.42 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 10.18 lakh shares. The stock slipped 1.13% to Rs.1,734.60. Volumes stood at 7.79 lakh shares in the last session. Maharashtra Seamless Ltd witnessed volume of 6.72 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.74 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 86793 shares. The stock increased 4.75% to Rs.570.55. Volumes stood at 1.2 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KSB_11705810441_342.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>