<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at possible red opening for equities; Asian markets mostly decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-possible-red-opening-for-equities-asian-markets-mostly-decline/1662316</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662316</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 22.50 points, indicating a negative 2opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were down 22.50 points, indicating a negative 2opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 2,759.89 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 2,643.85 crore in the Indian equity market on 29 December 2025, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 26,908.22 crore so far in December. This follows their cash sales of Rs 17,500.31 crore in November and Rs 2,346.89 crore in October. Global Markets: Asia markets mostly fell on Tuesday, after the tech sell-down on Wall Street continued on AI bubble fears. Investors will be focused on China’s military exercises around Taiwan, after the world’s second-largest economy announced new drills surrounding the island Monday. Overnight in the U.S., stocks fell on Monday, spurred by losses in technology, after the S&P 500 scaled to record levels last week. The S&P 500 dropped 0.35% and closed at 6,905.74, while the Nasdaq Composite shed 0.50% and settled at 23,474.35. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back by 249.04 points, or 0.51%, and ended at 48,461.93. Meanwhile, silver pulled back more than 6% after reaching $80 per ounce for the first time ever overnight. This comes as the precious metal has had a massive run-up in 2025, surging almost 150% to become one of the year’s hottest trades. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks closed lower on Monday, with the Sensex and Nifty giving up early gains as muted year-end trading volumes and sustained foreign fund outflows curbed risk appetite. Investors stayed cautious ahead of the upcoming Q3 corporate earnings season. The Nifty settled below the 25,950 mark after touching an intraday high of 26,106.80, weighed down by weakness in consumer durables and IT stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 345.91 points or 0.41% to 84,695.54. The Nifty 50 index lost 100.20 points or 0.38% to 25,942.10.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Lupin, RVNL, BEL, Waaree Energies, GNFC, NTPC Green Energy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-lupin-rvnl-bel-waaree-energies-gnfc-ntpc-green-energy/1662314</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662314</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025. New Listing Gujarat Kidney & Super Speciality is slated to make its market debut on the mainboard today. The IPO was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. Stocks to Watch: Lupin said that it has entered into an exclusive License, Supply, and Distribution Agreement with China-based Gan & Lee Pharmaceuticals for a novel fortnightly GLP-1 receptor agonist, Bofanglutide. Bofanglutide injection is indicated for the treatment of type 2 diabetes and for weight management in overweight or obese individuals. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) said that it has emerged as the lowest bidder for an order worth Rs 201.23 crore from East Coast Railway. The project involves setting up a wagon Periodic Overhaul (POH) workshop with a capacity of 200 wagons at Kantabanji. Bharat Electronics (BEL) said that it has received additional orders worth Rs 569 crore since December 12. These orders include radars, tank overhauls, communication equipment, fire control systems, simulators, antenna stabilisation systems, security software, components, upgrades, and spares. Waaree Energies said that Amit Paithankar has resigned as whole-time director and chief executive officer of the company to pursue opportunities outside the organisation, effective May 15, 2026. The company further said that the Board has approved the appointment of Jignesh Rathod, currently Director–Operations, as chief executive officer-designate with immediate effect. The Board has also appointed Jignesh Rathod as chief executive officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective May 16, 2026. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers & Chemicals (GNFC) said that T Natarajan has resigned as managing director with effect from December 29 following an order from the Government of Gujarat. The Government of Gujarat has nominated Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS, as managing director with effect from December 29. NTPC Green Energy announced the commencement of commercial operations of the ninth part capacity of 13.98 MW of the 1,255 MW Khavda-I Solar PV project of NTPC Renewable Energy. With this addition, the current commercial capacity of NTPC Green Energy stands at 7,996.30 MW, while the total installed capacity of the NGEL Group has increased to 8,010.28 MW.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITCONS E-Solutions bags Rs 4.15-cr manpower outsourcing contract from HAL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itcons-e-solutions-bags-rs-415-cr-manpower-outsourcing-contract-from-hal/1662311</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662311</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[As part of the agreement, the company will deploy 75 personnel to provide manpower outsourcing services.

As part of the agreement, the company will deploy 75 personnel to provide manpower outsourcing services. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity. The contract will be executed over a two-year period, beginning 1 January 2026, and ending 31 December 2027, with a provision for extension by mutual consent. The total consideration for the contract is Rs 41.53 million (Rs 4.15 crore), inclusive of all applicable duties and taxes. The company stated that the transaction does not fall under related party transactions, and that neither the promoter nor the promoter group entities have any interest in Hindustan Aeronautics. ITCONS E-Solutions is engaged in the business of recruitment and staffing services. Hindustan Aeronautics is engaged in the business of Manufacture of Aircraft and Helicopters and Repair, Maintenance of Aircraft and Helicopters. Shares of ITCONS E-Solutions slipped 1.46% to end at Rs 437.60 while shares of Hindustan Aeronautics shed 0.80% to Rs 4,374 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>