<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:25:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/manaksia-aluminium-company-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663826</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663826</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd, Yasho Industries Ltd, N K Industries Ltd and Goyal Aluminiums Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 08 January 2026.

NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd, Yasho Industries Ltd, N K Industries Ltd and Goyal Aluminiums Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 08 January 2026. Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd tumbled 11.13% to Rs 32.67 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 84546 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53611 shares in the past one month. NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd crashed 11.12% to Rs 33.88. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 23035 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19934 shares in the past one month. Yasho Industries Ltd lost 11.01% to Rs 1175.9. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3531 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 718 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd slipped 9.94% to Rs 61.9. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62 shares in the past one month. Goyal Aluminiums Ltd pared 9.82% to Rs 8.82. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.8 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManaksiaAlumi_41111727342_64845.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Univastu India signs MoU with URBS Systems for data centre projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/univastu-india-signs-mou-with-urbs-systems-for-data-centre-projects/1663825</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663825</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The MoU covers the development of hyperscale, edge, colocation, and AI/HPC data centers in line with the Maharashtra Data Center Policy, with a focus on energy-efficient and ESG-aligned infrastructure.

The MoU covers the development of hyperscale, edge, colocation, and AI/HPC data centers in line with the Maharashtra Data Center Policy, with a focus on energy-efficient and ESG-aligned infrastructure. Under the arrangement, Univastu India will act as the local project developer and EPC partner and will coordinate with government authorities for project execution. Univastu India is in the construction business. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 50.6% to Rs 4.64 crore on a 14% rise in revenue to Rs 48.34 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Univastu India shed 0.75% to Rs 66.75 on the NSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnivastuIndiaLtd_62157064244_70992.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold retreats despite elevated geopolitical tensions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-retreats-despite-elevated-geopolitical-tensions/1663824</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663824</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures slipped nearly 1% to around 4423 per ounce on Thursday, extending losses from the previous session as investors digested mixed US economic data.

Gold futures slipped nearly 1% to around 4423 per ounce on Thursday, extending losses from the previous session as investors digested mixed US economic data. The decline was driven largely by a stronger dollar, with the dollar index hovering near 98.6 and marking a third straight session of gains. Geopolitical developments remained in focus, with Washington outlining plans to take long-term control over Venezuelan crude sales and seizing additional Venezuelan-linked oil tankers. The White House also confirmed discussions on acquiring Greenland, including the possibility of military involvement, keeping global uncertainty elevated. In the domestic market, MCX February gold futures traded lower by 0.7% at ₹137095. Market attention now shifts to US weekly jobless claims and the December employment report for further direction.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-alkyl-amines-chemicals-ltd-counter/1663820</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663820</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Trident Ltd, Niva Bupa Health Insurance Company Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Alok Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 08 January 2026.

Trident Ltd, Niva Bupa Health Insurance Company Ltd, SignatureGlobal India Ltd, Alok Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 08 January 2026. Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd witnessed volume of 20.59 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 54.75 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 37607 shares. The stock increased 6.10% to Rs.1,632.10. Volumes stood at 39252 shares in the last session. Trident Ltd clocked volume of 831.81 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 33.21 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 25.05 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.69% to Rs.27.47. Volumes stood at 41.08 lakh shares in the last session. Niva Bupa Health Insurance Company Ltd witnessed volume of 103.28 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.68 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.59 lakh shares. The stock increased 4.32% to Rs.79.64. Volumes stood at 24 lakh shares in the last session. SignatureGlobal India Ltd registered volume of 34.47 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 14.4 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.39 lakh shares. The stock slipped 9.84% to Rs.996.60. Volumes stood at 2.54 lakh shares in the last session. Alok Industries Ltd clocked volume of 278.4 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.45 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 26.65 lakh shares. The stock gained 2.84% to Rs.16.32. Volumes stood at 27.17 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlkylAmines_27532524959_633.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 649 pts; media shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-649-pts-media-shares-decline/1663821</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663821</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in the mid- afternoon trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in the mid- afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,950 mark. media shares extended losses for second consecutive trading session. At 14:27 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 649.21 points or 0.76% to 84,311.93. The Nifty 50 index dropped 217.40 points or 0.83% to 25,923.35. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 1.76% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.73%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,062 shares rose and 3,058 shares fell. A total of 185 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index declined 1.08% to 11,159.80. The index fell 3.16% in for the two consecutive trading session. Hindustan Zinc (down 6.16%), Jindal Steel (down 5.5%), Jindal Stainless (down 5.43%), National Aluminium Company (down 5.13%) and Hindustan Copper (down 5.02%), NMDC (down 4.64%), Hindalco Industries (down 3.74%), Vedanta (down 3.25%), Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 3.17%) and Welspun Corp (down 3.12%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.26% to 6.628 compared with previous session close of 6.611. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.0250 compared with its close of 89.8700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.81% to Rs 136,909. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.07% to 98.82. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.39% to 4.155. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement rose 7 cents or 0.12% to $60.03 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Precision Electronics tanked 5.38%. The company said that it has secured a domestic order worth Rs 49 lakh from a private entity in the Aerospace & Defense segment. DEE Development Engineers surged 10.07% after the company reported an update on its order book for December 2025, showing steady inflows and execution across its core businesses. Gujarat Pipavav Port declined 1.03% after the company reported a 1.69% drop in container volumes to 174,000 twenty-foot equivalent units (TEU) in Q3 FY26, compared with 177 TEUs recorded in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LG Electronics India slips after three-month lock-in expiry]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lg-electronics-india-slips-after-three-month-lock-in-expiry/1663822</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663822</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Around 1.52 crore shares, or nearly 2% of the company’s outstanding equity, have reportedly become eligible for trading following the end of the lock-in.

Around 1.52 crore shares, or nearly 2% of the company’s outstanding equity, have reportedly become eligible for trading following the end of the lock-in. Market participants noted that the expiry does not necessarily signal immediate selling, as it merely permits these shares to be traded. The stock’s decline comes amid heightened investor caution typically seen around lock-in expiries, as additional free float can weigh on sentiment in the near term. Meanwhile, LG Electronics India concluded an Advance Pricing Agreement (APA) with the Central Board of Direct Taxes on 5 January 2026, resolving transfer pricing matters for a nine-year period from 1 April 2014 to 31 March 2023. Following the APA, contingent liabilities of Rs 172.44 crore related to direct taxes and Rs 315.30 crore linked to royalty payments to LG Electronics Inc. will become nil. The settlement will result in a net tax expense of Rs 17.71 crore, excluding applicable interest. In addition, the company will pay Rs 3.86 crore to LG Electronics Inc. under secondary adjustment provisions in line with India’s transfer pricing regulations. LG Electronics India, a subsidiary of South Korea-based LG Electronics, is one of India's leading consumer durables companies. It manufactures and sells a wide range of products, including TVs, refrigerators, washing machines, and air conditioners, serving both retail and institutional customers. The company’s standalone net profit declined 27.3% to Rs 389.43 crore despite 1% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,174.03 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The stock was listed on the exchanges on 14 October 2025 at Rs 1,715, marking a premium of 50.44% over the issue price of Rs 1,140. The initial public offering of LG Electronics India was subscribed 54.02 times. The issue opened for subscription on 7 October 2025 and closed on 9 October 2025, with a price band of Rs 1,080 to Rs 1,140 per share. At the current price, the stock is up 25.46% over its IPO price of Rs 1,140, but down 16.61% from its listing price of Rs 1,715.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LGElectronicsIndiaLtd_35129397_18787.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Pipavav Port drops after container volumes slip 2% YoY in Q3 FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-pipavav-port-drops-after-container-volumes-slip-2-yoy-in-q3-fy26/1663819</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663819</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Dry Bulk volumes jumped 20.83% to 0.87 metric tons (MT) in Q3 FY26 from 0.72 MT in Q3 FY25.

Dry Bulk volumes jumped 20.83% to 0.87 metric tons (MT) in Q3 FY26 from 0.72 MT in Q3 FY25. Liquid volumes rose 2.56% to 0.40 MT in Q3 FY26 compared with 0.39 MT in Q3 FY25. Ro-Ro volumes surged 40.91% to 62,000 units in Q3 FY26 from 44,000 units in Q3 FY25.Meanwhile the numbers of container trains handled declined to 438 in Q3 FY26 from Rs 496 in Q3 FY25. Containers handled on trains dropped 4.46% to 107,000 TEUs in Q3 FY26, compared with 112,000 TEUs in Q3 FY25. Gujarat Pipavav Port is engaged in operating and maintaining an all-weather Port at Pipavav, District Amreli, in Gujarat, having multi-cargo and multi-user operations. The company’s Port is one of the principal gateways on the West Coast of India and provides access to shipping lines through international routes as well as for the cargo belt in North and North-West Region of India. Revenue from operations rose 31.9% year-on-year to Rs 299.35 crore, compared with Rs 227.04 crore in Q2 FY25. Sequentially, revenue was up 19.5% from Rs 250.45 crore in Q1 FY26. Adjusted net profit (PAT) jumped 70.1% YoY to Rs 128.44 crore, compared with Rs 75.49 crore in the year-ago quarter, and 23.1% higher sequentially from Rs 104.33 crore in Q1 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujPipavavPort_89824764870_12232.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude edges up after recent losses]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-edges-up-after-recent-losses/1663818</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663818</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures traded above $56 per barrel on Thursday, recovering from a two-day decline as falling US inventories and geopolitical developments lent support.

WTI crude oil futures traded above $56 per barrel on Thursday, recovering from a two-day decline as falling US inventories and geopolitical developments lent support. EIA data showed US crude stockpiles dropped by 3.8 million barrels last week, highlighting tighter near-term supply. Market focus also remained on US actions targeting Venezuelan crude, with Washington outlining plans to oversee long-term oil sales and stepping up sanctions enforcement through additional tanker seizures. These moves kept supply risks in focus. However, gains were limited by a steady US dollar, with the dollar index hovering near 98.5 after two consecutive sessions of gains amid mixed US economic data.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FRAI Urges Govt to Reconsider Sharp Tax Hike on Legal Tobacco, Cites Threat to Small Retailers’ Livelihoods]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/frai-urges-govt-to-reconsider-sharp-tax-hike-on-legal-tobacco-cites-threat-to-small-retailers-livelihoods/1663817</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663817</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Federation of Retailer Association of India (FRAI) expressed serious concerns over a steep increase in taxes of legal tobacco products, requesting a consideration to lower the taxes to ensure interest of small retailers is looked into while also preventing illegal operators from taking over the market.

Federation of Retailer Association of India (FRAI) expressed serious concerns over a steep increase in taxes of legal tobacco products, requesting a consideration to lower the taxes to ensure interest of small retailers is looked into while also preventing illegal operators from taking over the market. The demand from the association comes after the Finance Ministry notification of the Chewing Tobacco, Jarda Scented Tobacco and Gutkha Packing Machines (Capacity Determination and Collection of Duty) Rules, 2026 that have imposed an excise duty of Rs 2,050-8,500 per 1,000 sticks, depending on cigarette length, effective February 1. This action caused caused widespread anxiety among small retailers, hawkers and pavement sellers who depend on daily consumption goods, particularly tobacco products, for their livelihoods.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/currency-3088153__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Precision Electronics bags Rs 49-lakh domestic order in Aerospace & Defense segment]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/precision-electronics-bags-rs-49-lakh-domestic-order-in-aerospace-defense-segment/1663815</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663815</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company will supply masts with accessories, with delivery scheduled within the current financial year.

The company will supply masts with accessories, with delivery scheduled within the current financial year. The transaction is not a related-party deal, and neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the customer entity. Precision Electronics is a diverse telecom infrastructure enabler with active interest spanning telecom infrastructure development, system integration, and manufacture and supply of high-end telecom equipment. The company reported a standalone net loss of Rs 1.40 crore in Q2 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 1.17 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales surged 48.4% year-on-year to Rs 15.15 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Precision Electronics tanked 4.91% to currently trade at Rs 192.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PrecElectronic_6758329937_2063.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 25,900 level; European mrkt decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-25900-level-european-mrkt-decline/1663813</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663813</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade as concerns over U.S.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade as concerns over U.S. tariffs and continued foreign fund outflows overshadowed pockets of optimism around earnings growth. The Nifty traded below the 25,900 level. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 726.85 points or 0.86% to 84,234.29. The Nifty 50 index dropped 246.40 points or 0.94% to 25,888.10. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 1.69% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 1.77%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,016 shares rose and 3,031 shares fell. A total of 199 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: SBI Life Insurance Company (up 0.50%), ICICI Bank (up 0.41%), HCL Technologies (up 0.39%), Bharat Electronics (up 0.26%) and Eternal (up 0.41%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Hindalco Industries (down 3.79%), Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (down 3.22%), Jio Financial Services (down 3.08%), Wipro (down 2.79%) and JSW Steel (down 2.71%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Madhya Bharat Agro Products (MBAPL) fell 4.07%. The company reported a sharp 77.47% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 31.75 crore on a robust 115.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 612.38 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Gland Pharma jumped 0.01%. The company received an approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) filed for Olopatadine Hydrochloride Ophthalmic Solution USP, 0.7%. P N Gadgil Jewellers fell 1.65%. The company reported a 35.60% year-on-year (YoY) increase in total revenue to Rs 3,302 crore for the third quarter of FY26, up from Rs 2,435 crore in the same period last year. Granules India shed 0.74%. The company said that its arm Granules Pharmaceuticals, Inc has received tentative approval from the USFDA for its Abbreviated New Drug Application for generic Amphetamine Extended-Release Tablets, equivalent to DYANAVEL XR. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) declined 1.49%. The company said it has received a supply order from the Corps of Electronics and Mechanical Engineers (EME) of the Indian Army for overhaul, upgrade, and obsolescence management of the indigenous Pinaka Multi-Rocket Launcher Systems. Global Markets: European shares opened lower on Thursday as regional market jitters grow over U.S. President Donald Trump’s threat to annex Greenland. Asia-Pacific markets traded mixed after Wall Street closed lower amid rising geopolitical tensions and comments from U.S. President Donald Trump. U.S. defense stocks fell after Trump said he “will not permit” defense companies to issue dividends or stock buybacks until they address his complaints about the industry, including executive pay packages and production issues. In U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average snapped a three-day winning streak, falling 466 points, or 0.94%, to close at 48,996.08. The S&P 500 declined 23.89 points or 0.34% to end at 6,920.93, while the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite edged up 37.10 points or 0.16% to close at 23,584.28.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-bank-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1663810</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663810</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2128.9, down 0.7% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25915.25. The Sensex is at 84313.4, down 0.76%.Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd has gained around 0.06% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.8% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59990.85, down 0.49% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 12.14 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 24.47 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2135.9, down 0.65% on the day. Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd jumped 18.92% in last one year as compared to a 10.15% rally in NIFTY and a 20.59% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 31.84 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KotakMahBank_47062626511_2330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/samvardhana-motherson-international-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1663811</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663811</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 118.37, down 0.82% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25915.25. The Sensex is at 84313.4, down 0.76%.Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd has gained around 1.39% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 3.97% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28692.4, down 0.72% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 111.46 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 130.11 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 118.24, down 1.32% on the day. Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd jumped 19.38% in last one year as compared to a 10.15% rally in NIFTY and a 22.23% spurt in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 67.78 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MothersonSumi_60777480057_2966.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shriram Finance Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shriram-finance-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1663812</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663812</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shriram Finance Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Shriram Finance Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 994.05, down 0.18% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.86% on the day, quoting at 25915.25. The Sensex is at 84313.4, down 0.76%.Shriram Finance Ltd has gained around 17.4% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Shriram Finance Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 0.48% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27853.35, down 0.62% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 24.09 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 99.26 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 997.3, down 0.35% on the day. Shriram Finance Ltd jumped 76.89% in last one year as compared to a 10.15% rally in NIFTY and a 20.22% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 20.83 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShriramFinanceLtd_71599469_1745.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Meesho slips on senior management changes, lock-in expiry overhang]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/meesho-slips-on-senior-management-changes-lock-in-expiry-overhang/1663808</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663808</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, Meesho said Megha Agarwal, General Manager – Business and a senior management personnel, tendered her resignation on 7 January 2026.

In an exchange filing, Meesho said Megha Agarwal, General Manager – Business and a senior management personnel, tendered her resignation on 7 January 2026. The company added that detailed disclosures will be made at the prescribed time. Separately, the company announced an internal role change. Milan Partani, currently General Manager – User Growth and Content Commerce, will assume the role of General Manager – Commerce Platform and will continue to be classified as a senior management personnel. The stock had already come under pressure in the previous session, slipping about 5% after the expiry of a one-month shareholder lock-in period. Around 10.99 crore shares, or nearly 2% of the company’s outstanding equity, reportedly became eligible for trading following the lock-in expiry. Market participants noted that eligibility does not necessarily translate into immediate selling. Meesho made its stock market debut on 10 December 2025. The stock is up 49.23% over its IPO price of Rs 111 and has gained 2.76% from its listing price of Rs 161.20. Post listing, the stock surged 57.97% from its listing price to hit a record high of Rs 254.65 on 18 December 2025, before witnessing profit-taking. The stock is currently down about 35% from its peak levels. The company’s initial public offering had seen strong investor demand, with the issue subscribed 79.03 times. The IPO was open for subscription between December 3 and December 5 at a price band of Rs 105 to Rs 111 per share. Meesho has said it plans to use the IPO proceeds to strengthen its cloud infrastructure, invest in technology and AI talent, scale up marketing and brand-building initiatives, pursue inorganic growth opportunities and meet general corporate requirements. Meesho operates a multi-sided e-commerce platform connecting consumers, sellers, logistics partners and content creators. Order fulfilment is handled through its in-house logistics arm, Valmo, along with third-party logistics partners. For the quarter ended September 2025, the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 700.72 crore, while revenue stood at Rs 5,577.54 crore. Net merchandise value per annual transacting seller grew at a CAGR of 16.86% between FY23 and FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MeeshoLtd_15936426_77963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd spurts 0.51%, up for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-bank-ltd-spurts-051-up-for-five-straight-sessions/1663804</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663804</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today.

ICICI Bank Ltd rose for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1435, up 0.51% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.83% on the day, quoting at 25924.45. The Sensex is at 84326.41, down 0.75%. ICICI Bank Ltd has added around 4.35% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which ICICI Bank Ltd is a constituent, has added around 0.77% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59990.85, down 0.52% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 96.09 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 91.47 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1435.8, up 0.36% on the day. ICICI Bank Ltd is up 13.67% in last one year as compared to a 10.19% gain in NIFTY and a 20.56% gain in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 20.62 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIBank_93786457618_5418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd up for fifth session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aegis-logistics-ltd-up-for-fifth-session/1663805</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663805</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

Aegis Logistics Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 750.6, up 0.21% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.83% on the day, quoting at 25924.45. The Sensex is at 84326.41, down 0.75%. Aegis Logistics Ltd has dropped around 0.27% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Aegis Logistics Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 1.37% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35763.5, down 1.74% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.69 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.54 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 49.86 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisLogistics_61348536029_9.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ipca Laboratories Ltd spurts 2.08%, rises for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ipca-laboratories-ltd-spurts-208-rises-for-fifth-straight-session/1663806</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663806</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ipca Laboratories Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today.

Ipca Laboratories Ltd gained for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1545.7, up 2.08% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.83% on the day, quoting at 25924.45. The Sensex is at 84326.41, down 0.75%. Ipca Laboratories Ltd has gained around 6.53% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Ipca Laboratories Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.57% in last one month and is currently quoting at 23286.25, down 0.8% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.8 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 1.95 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 39.65 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IpcaLabs_21705510910_3617.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IDFC First Bank gains after cutting savings account interest rates]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/idfc-first-bank-gains-after-cutting-savings-account-interest-rates/1663803</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663803</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the revised structure, balances of up to Rs 1 lakh continue to earn 3%, while deposits above Rs 1 lakh and up to Rs 10 lakh will now earn 5%.

Under the revised structure, balances of up to Rs 1 lakh continue to earn 3%, while deposits above Rs 1 lakh and up to Rs 10 lakh will now earn 5%. Balances above Rs 10 lakh and up to Rs 10 crore will earn 6.5%. This marks a sharp cut from the earlier regime, under which balances above Rs 5 lakh and up to Rs 5 crore earned 7% interest, while deposits above Rs 5 crore and up to Rs 10 crore earned 6.75%. Market participants viewed the move as margin-accretive, as it lowers the bank’s cost of funds. Deposit slabs above Rs 10 crore remain unchanged, with rates of 6% for balances up to Rs 25 crore, 5% up to Rs 100 crore and 4% beyond Rs 100 crore. IDFC First Bank is a new-age private sector bank. The bank's board will consider Q3 results on 31 January 2026. Its net profit surged 75.55% to Rs 352.31 crore on a 10.71% increase in total income to Rs 11,828.34 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IDFCBank_27126132357_54759.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Niyogin Fintech posts 91% jump revenue; ;loan AUM rises to Rs 321 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/niyogin-fintech-posts-91-jump-revenue-loan-aum-rises-to-rs-321-crore/1663807</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663807</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The gross loan AUM as on 31 December 2025 was Rs 321.1 crore, up 33% YoY.

The gross loan AUM as on 31 December 2025 was Rs 321.1 crore, up 33% YoY. The IserveU Tech order book at the end of December 2025 period stood at Rs 620 crore. Tashwinder Singh, CEO and managing director, Niyogin Fintech, said: “During the quarter, we delivered resilient performance across our core businesses, supported by strong execution and traction in our platform-led offerings. In light of evolving conditions in select unsecured lending segments, we adopted a more cautious approach to loan disbursements while inking new partnerships to scale in the coming quarters. iServeU continued its strong momentum with robust revenue growth and an expanding order book.” Niyogin Fintech caters to India’s underserved MSMEs and is a B2B company that operates on a tech centric platform-based model, wherein it delivers ‘banking as a service’ or BaaS platforms and credit in both rural and urban India through a partnership-led strategy. Niyogin ties up with business correspondents, banks and neobanks/fintechs to offer BaaS platforms, while it provides credit and other financial services through its financial professional network (or chartered accountants). The company had reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 0.28 crore in the quarter ended September 2025 as against net loss of Rs 4.19 crore during the previous quarter ended September 2024. Sales declined 3.34% to Rs 70.10 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip shed 0.94% to currently trade at Rs 50.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NiyoginFintechLtd_57567287046_64793.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>