<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Protean eGov Technologies bags Rs 25-cr order for Ethiopia Agriculture DPI Project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/protean-egov-technologies-bags-rs-25-cr-order-for-ethiopia-agriculture-dpi-project/1664215</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664215</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the contract, Protean eGov Technologies will act as the system integrator and provide end-to-end technology, programme management and engineering services.

Under the contract, Protean eGov Technologies will act as the system integrator and provide end-to-end technology, programme management and engineering services. This includes the design, development, deployment and ongoing support of an AI-powered digital platform aimed at building Global Digital Public Goods (DPGs) for a unified agricultural ecosystem in Ethiopia. The project will focus on creating unique farmer and farm IDs, integrating data related to crops, soil and livestock, and offering AI-driven advisory services to support the agricultural sector. The scope of work covers the complete lifecycle of the platform, from development to deployment and maintenance. The company said the order aligns with its strategy to expand its DPI capabilities in international markets and marks a key milestone in its efforts to develop and implement digital public goods for the agriculture sector. The contract, valued at Rs 25 crore, is scheduled to be executed within 17 calendar months from the date of execution. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It added that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. Protean eGov Technologies is engaged in developing digital public infrastructure and citizen-centric e-governance solutions. In Q2 FY26, the company reported a 14.9% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 23.86 crore, while net sales increased 14% to Rs 250.50 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ProteaneGovTechnologiesLtd_21133431_14537.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PTC Industries’ arm secures major order from Blue Origin for BE-4 Engines]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ptc-industries-arm-secures-major-order-from-blue-origin-for-be-4-engines/1664193</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664193</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the manufacture and supply of high-integrity superalloy investment castings for Blue Origin’s heavy-lift orbital launch vehicle.

The order involves the manufacture and supply of high-integrity superalloy investment castings for Blue Origin’s heavy-lift orbital launch vehicle. The contract was awarded following the successful completion of extensive qualification processes and applicable international regulatory and compliance requirements. The value of the purchase order is significant and is expected to have a positive impact on the Company’s revenue. However, in view of confidentiality applicable under the terms of the order placed by Blue Origin, the value of the order is not being disclosed. The order is scheduled to be executed over a period of two years from the commencement of supply. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding entity. It added that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. PTC Industries is a leading Indian manufacturer of precision metal components for critical applications. Through its wholly owned subsidiary Aerolloy Technologies, the company is manufacturing and supplying titanium and superalloy castings for aerospace and defence applications within India as well as for exports. The company reported 4.79% growth in consolidated net profit to Rs 18.14 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 17.31 crore posted in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations surged 72.21% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 124.63 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of PTC Industries rose 0.40% to close at Rs 17,591.80 on the BSE on 9 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PTCInds_85881590_5380.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Globus Spirits reports multi-fold jump in Q3 PAT to Rs 31 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/globus-spirits-reports-multi-fold-jump-in-q3-pat-to-rs-31-crore/1664192</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664192</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax surged 2,779% year-on-year to Rs 42.32 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1.47 crore in the year-ago quarter, aided by lower costs and improved operating performance.

Profit before tax surged 2,779% year-on-year to Rs 42.32 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1.47 crore in the year-ago quarter, aided by lower costs and improved operating performance. EBITDA jumped 112% to Rs 78.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 36.8 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 11% in Q3 FY26 as against 6% in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, revenue from the Prestige & Above segment surged 4% year-on-year to Rs 44.9 crore, while sales volume grew 9% to 0.32 million cases in Q3 FY26. Globus Spirits is primarily engaged in the business of manufacturing and selling Indian Made Indian Liquor (IMIL), Indian Made Foreign Liquor (IMFL), bulk alcohol, hand sanitizer, and franchise bottling. Shares of Globus Spirits fell 2.57% to close at Rs 1,058.25 on the BSE on 9 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlobusSpirits_86341491738_25785.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IREDA Q3 PAT jumps 15% YoY to Rs 1,381 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ireda-q3-pat-jumps-15-yoy-to-rs-1381-cr/1664186</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664186</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) surged 16.59% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,718.43 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) surged 16.59% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,718.43 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a standalone basis, the company’s standalone net profit jumped 37.64% to Rs 585 crore on 25.44% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 2,130 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) rallied 33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 717 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Operating profit stood at Rs 857 crore in Q3 FY26, up 31% as compared with Rs 652 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of borrowing declined to 7.07% in Q3 FY26, compared to 7.68% in the corresponding quarter of the previous fiscal. Net interest margin increased 3.74% in Q3 FY26, compared with 3.33% recorded in corresponding quarter last year. Yield on loan assets (Gross) stood at 9.70% as on 31 December 2025, compared with 9.96% as on 31 December 2024. Provision coverage ratio (Stage III) stood at 56.08% as on 31 December 2025, compared with 44.52% as on 30 December 2024. The company’s outstanding loan book stood at Rs 87,975 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 68,960 crore as of 31 December 2024. Gross non-performing assets (GNPA) rose to Rs 3,297 crore in the December quarter of FY26, from Rs 1,845 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. The gross NPA ratio increased to 3.75% in the December quarter of FY26, compared with 2.68% in the year-ago period. Net non-performing assets (NNPA) rose to Rs 1,448 crore in the December quarter of FY26, from Rs 1,024 crore in the corresponding quarter last year, while the net NPA ratio increased to 1.68% from 1.50% over the same period. IREDA is a 'Navratna' Government of India Enterprise under the administrative control of Ministry of New and Renewable Energy (MNRE). IREDA is a Public Limited Government Company established as a Non-Banking Financial Institution in 1987 engaged in promoting, developing and extending financial assistance for setting up projects relating to new and renewable sources of energy and energy efficiency/conservation. Shares of Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency fell 3.19% to end at Rs 136.65 on the BSE on 9 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks reports dismal Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-reports-dismal-q3-performance/1664175</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664175</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year.

The company’s total revenue from operations plunged 88.38% to Rs 306.79 crore in Q3 FY26, down from Rs 2,642.24 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Pre-tax loss for the quarter stood at Rs 302.87 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to a profit before tax of Rs 211.27 crore in Q3 FY25. The company’s inventory stood at Rs 2,363 crore in Q3 FY26, largely unchanged from Rs 2,383 crore in the previous quarter. Management said the inventory will be converted into finished goods and shipped over the coming months. Trade receivables declined to Rs 3,284 crore at the end of Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,026 crore in Q2, reflecting improved collections. The company reported a cash balance of Rs 537 crore at the end of the quarter. Net debt reduced to Rs 3,349 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 3,738 crore in the preceding quarter, primarily due to lower working capital requirements, partially offset by capital expenditure. Gross debt stood at Rs 885 crore, with cash and cash equivalents of Rs 537 crore. During the quarter, the company strengthened its order wins by securing additional packages under Bharatnet Phase-III, where it remains a key supplier of IP/MPLS routers, having won 7 of the 12 packages announced so far. It was also selected as the 5G RAN supplier for a section of the Delhi–Mumbai railway corridor under a Kavach pilot project. Further, the company received expansion orders for DWDM and GPON OLT equipment from leading private telecom operators in India, and won a DWDM backbone buildout order from a broadband ISP in Africa, along with a network transformation deal for its MPLS-TP products for a power sector customer in Southeast Asia. The company said its long-term outlook remains positive, supported by strong structural drivers and rapid technology transitions across the telecom and networking landscape. Growing adoption of AI applications is driving a sharp increase in data traffic, while continued expansion of 4G networks and fresh 5G deployments in emerging markets are creating sustained demand. Investments in AI data centres are also translating into significant connectivity requirements. The company is seeing increasing traction for its new products across India and international markets, with wireless solutions beginning to lead international engagements in regions such as Europe, Latin America and Africa. At the same time, adoption of its wireline products is rising among private telecom operators in India. The company is also scaling up its international wireless engagements through strategic partnerships with NEC and Rakuten, while recent strategic wins for its optical products in Europe, Africa and Asia are providing momentum for further international expansion. Arnob Roy, COO of Tejas Networks said, “In Q3 FY26, our revenue was driven largely by sale of Wireline products to India Pvt and International customers. During the quarter we engaged in multiple field trials for our Wireless products in India and International markets; commercial negotiations are expected to close in the coming months.” Sumit Dhingra, CFO said, “In Q3 FY26 we had a revenue of Rs 307 crore, a QoQ growth of 17%. We ended the quarter with an order book of Rs 1,329 crore. Our net debt was 3,349 crore compared to 3,738 crore in Q2 FY26 mainly due to lower working capital, partly offset by capex; gross debt of 3,885 crore and cash of 537 crore.” Tejas Networks designs and manufactures wireline and wireless networking products, with a focus on technology, innovation, and R&D. TNL carrier-class products are used by telecom service providers, utilities, governments, and defense networks in 75+ countries. Tejas Networks is a part of the Tata Group, with Panatone Finvest (a subsidiary of Tata Sons) being the majority shareholder. Shares of Tejas Networks tanked 5.68% to close at Rs 416.70 on the BSE on 9 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Meta Infotech receives purchase orders worth Rs 3 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/meta-infotech-receives-purchase-orders-worth-rs-3-crore/1664174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664174</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order mix comprises annual subscriptions and implementation services for cloud-based security and support solutions under the product and services category.

The order mix comprises annual subscriptions and implementation services for cloud-based security and support solutions under the product and services category. The total order value stands at Rs 260.98 lakh, which includes fresh orders of Rs 113.19 lakh and renewal orders amounting to Rs 147.79 lakh, with contract periods extending up to February 2030. Meta Infotech is engaged in trading and providing services related to cybersecurity software products. The company reported a 60.7% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 10.51 crore, while revenue from operations rose 40.3% to Rs 152.13 crore in FY25 over FY24. Shares of Meta Infotech fell 3.74% to close at Rs 109.40 on the BSE on 9 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MetaInfotechLtd_21921703_94283.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Saatvik Green Energy bags Rs 14-cr solar module order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/saatvik-green-energy-bags-rs-14-cr-solar-module-order/1664135</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664135</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order is scheduled to be executed by February 2026.

The order is scheduled to be executed by February 2026. Saatvik Green Energy is an integrated solar energy solutions provider engaged in manufacturing high-efficiency photovoltaic (PV) modules and offering EPC services for utility-scale, commercial, and industrial projects. The company’s net profit rose 36% year-on-year to Rs 83.24 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 61.20 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 61.6% YoY to Rs 768.03 crore from Rs 475.30 crore in Q2 FY25. Shares of Saatvik Green Energy declined 2.99% to close at Rs 405.15 on the BSE on 9 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SAATVIKGREENENERGYLIMITED_74895602_94178.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Niraj Cement Structurals bags Rs 47-cr railway infra contract from Western Railways]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/niraj-cement-structurals-bags-rs-47-cr-railway-infra-contract-from-western-railways/1664116</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664116</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project includes a Y-connection at Adipur to enable direct rail access to Mundra Port and Bhuj.

The project includes a Y-connection at Adipur to enable direct rail access to Mundra Port and Bhuj. The scope of work covers earthworks for formation, construction of major and minor bridges, PSC slab bridges, RCC box bridges, RUB/LHS in lieu of level crossings, station buildings and platforms, protection works such as stone pitching, toe walls, retaining walls and side drains, as well as track laying and linking, supply of ballast and other associated permanent way works. The contract also involves the construction of a high-level passenger platform at Gopalpur across a stretch of around 10 km and is to be completed within 18 months. The company said the order does not involve any promoter or related-party interest. As of 10 January 2025, the company’s market capitalization stood at Rs 215.56 crore on the BSE. Niraj Cement Structurals is engaged in infrastructural services. The company’s consolidated net profit soared 124.7% to Rs 8.81 crore, supported by a 24.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 171.74 crore in Q2 FY26 compared to Q2 FY25. Shares of Niraj Cement Structurals tanked 4.60% to close at Rs 36.11 on the BSE on 9 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NirajCement_49785710_28015.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>