<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:48:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Loyal Textile Mills Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/loyal-textile-mills-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1672686</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672686</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[IZMO Ltd, GNG Electronics Ltd, Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd and DJ Mediaprint & Logistics Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 February 2026.

IZMO Ltd, GNG Electronics Ltd, Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd and DJ Mediaprint & Logistics Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 February 2026. Loyal Textile Mills Ltd spiked 18.56% to Rs 301.15 at 12:01 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 3732 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1196 shares in the past one month. IZMO Ltd soared 11.41% to Rs 787.75. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 7833 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9013 shares in the past one month. GNG Electronics Ltd surged 9.99% to Rs 322.1. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 82683 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5202 shares in the past one month. Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd rose 9.98% to Rs 39.13. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 3096 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2885 shares in the past one month. DJ Mediaprint & Logistics Ltd spurt 9.78% to Rs 97.64. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 34927 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 47131 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LoyalTextile_78454566449_997.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sai Life Sciences jumps on strong Q3 show]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sai-life-sciences-jumps-on-strong-q3-show/1672684</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672684</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sai Life Sciences rose 5.29% to Rs 854.10 after the company reported a strong operational and financial performance for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SaiLifeSciencesLtd_92232367_68121.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Piramal Pharma's subsidiary inks pact with Blue-Zone to recycle waste anaesthesia gas  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/piramal-pharmas-subsidiary-inks-pact-with-blue-zone-to-recycle-waste-anaesthesia-gas/1672683</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672683</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[By combining the innovative waste anaesthesia gas capture, collection, and processing technology developed by Blue-Zone, with the global manufacturing and marketing capabilities of Piramal, this collaboration will support customers’ efforts to minimize the environmental impact of volatile anaesthetics.

By combining the innovative waste anaesthesia gas capture, collection, and processing technology developed by Blue-Zone, with the global manufacturing and marketing capabilities of Piramal, this collaboration will support customers’ efforts to minimize the environmental impact of volatile anaesthetics. This collaboration will also help ensure that these essential products remain the primary method of providing general anaesthesia for patients around the world. Pending regulatory approval in Europe of Blue-Zone’s Phoenix Deltasorb waste anaesthetic gas capture system, Blue-Zone will offer these systems to PCC’s customers in Europe, initially in France and Germany. Blue-Zone will be responsible for all activities involving the supply and use of its systems in healthcare facilities. PCC will process captured waste anaesthetic gas using Blue Zone’s technology to produce Sevoflurane USP for human use in Canada. The parties anticipate that the scope of the waste anaesthetic gas capture, collection and recycling, and the marketing of Sevoflurane USP using waste anaesthetic gas, will expand into additional geographies. PCC is a global leader in anaesthesia, pain management and intrathecal therapy. PCC maintains a wide global footprint, delivering continuous supply to hospitals in more than 100 countries around the world. Piramal Pharma offers a portfolio of differentiated products and services through its 17 global development and manufacturing facilities and a global distribution network in over 100 countries. The company a consolidated net loss of Rs 136.19 crore in the quarter ended December 2025 as against net profit of Rs 3.68 crore during the previous quarter ended December 2024. Sales declined 2.92% to Rs 2139.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.79% to currently trade at Rs 157.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PiramalPharmaLtd_79555676_76066.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1672680</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672680</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Concord Biotech Ltd, Data Patterns (India) Ltd and Kirloskar Brothers Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 February 2026.

Godfrey Phillips India Ltd, Concord Biotech Ltd, Data Patterns (India) Ltd and Kirloskar Brothers Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 06 February 2026. Hitachi Energy India Ltd surged 12.56% to Rs 21605 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 20689 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8407 shares in the past one month. Godfrey Phillips India Ltd spiked 11.59% to Rs 2211.85. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 2.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 35838 shares in the past one month. Concord Biotech Ltd soared 8.36% to Rs 1265.25. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 34348 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4849 shares in the past one month. Data Patterns (India) Ltd advanced 7.30% to Rs 2711. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.67 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 55123 shares in the past one month. Kirloskar Brothers Ltd exploded 7.22% to Rs 1655.25. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 67553 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4074 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HitachiEnergyIndiaLimited_51485438_74646.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kriti Industries gains as Q3 net loss narrows sharply]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kriti-industries-gains-as-q3-net-loss-narrows-sharply/1672678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672678</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales declined 35.3% YoY to Rs 135.79 crore during the quarter.

Net sales declined 35.3% YoY to Rs 135.79 crore during the quarter. Total expenditure tumbled 37.64% YoY to Rs 137.77 crore in Q3 FY26, aided by a 34.22% drop in raw material costs and a 46.88% fall in other expenses. The company’s loss before tax narrowed to Rs 2.51 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 10.38 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Kriti Industries (India) is engaged in the manufacture of piping products and solutions, including accessories, gas pipes, telecom ducts, submersible pipes, and casing pipes.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KritiInds_33190066192_3606.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LIC jumps on strong Q3 show; nine-month metrics steady]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lic-jumps-on-strong-q3-show-nine-month-metrics-steady/1672677</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672677</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 17.46% YoY to Rs 12,930.44 crore in Q3 FY26, while total income increased 15.74% YoY to Rs 2,36,776.30 crore compared with Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 17.46% YoY to Rs 12,930.44 crore in Q3 FY26, while total income increased 15.74% YoY to Rs 2,36,776.30 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Consolidated profit before tax rose 3.42% YoY to Rs 13,188.05 crore during the quarter. On a standalone basis, LIC reported a steady performance for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. Profit after tax increased 16.68% YoY to Rs 33,998 crore, compared with Rs 29,138 crore in the corresponding period last year. The insurer retained its leadership position in the Indian life insurance market, with an overall market share of 57.07% for the nine-month period, marginally lower than 57.42% a year ago. During the period, LIC held a 35.84% market share in the individual segment and a dominant 71.36% share in the group business. Product mix continued to improve, with individual business non-participating annualised premium equivalent surging 47.44% YoY to Rs 10,045 crore. As a result, the share of non-par APE within the individual business rose to 36.46% in 9M FY26 from 27.68% in the year-ago period. Individual business APE grew 11.95% YoY to Rs 27,552 crore, while group business APE rose 23.14% YoY to Rs 16,455 crore. Overall APE increased 15.88% YoY to Rs 44,007 crore during the period. Value of new business climbed 27.96% YoY to Rs 8,288 crore, supported by an expansion in net VNB margin by 170 bps to 18.8%, reflecting improved profitability of fresh business. On the premium front, individual new business premium income increased 5.89% YoY to Rs 44,941 crore. Group business premium income rose 13.56% YoY to Rs 1,35,302 crore, taking total premium income up 9.02% YoY to Rs 3,71,293 crore for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The contribution of bancassurance and alternate channels to individual new business premium improved to 7.45% in 9M FY26 from 4.73% in 9M FY25, indicating gradual diversification of distribution channels. Assets under management grew 8.01% YoY to Rs 59,16,680 crore as of December 31, 2025. The solvency ratio strengthened to 2.19 from 2.02 a year ago, while operating efficiency improved, with the expense ratio declining by 132 bps to 11.65% from 12.97% in the corresponding period last year. Yield on investments on policyholders’ funds, excluding unrealised gains, stood at 8.77%, slightly lower than 8.82% recorded a year earlier. R Doraiswamy, CEO & MD, LIC said the consumers and the companies in the life insurance industry have responded positively to the various initiatives of the government, especially to GST 2.0. At LIC, we have further increased our performance by achieving higher and better parameters on volume growth as well as product and channel diversification. LIC is engaged in the business of Life Insurance in and outside India. It offers a range of individual and group insurance solutions including participating, non-participating and unit linked business. The portfolio comprises of various insurance and investment products such as protection, pension, savings, investment, annuity, health, variable and CRAC.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Life-Insurance-Corporation-of-India_13079731_12024.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gland Pharma receives USFDA nod for Zoledronic Acid Injection]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gland-pharma-receives-usfda-nod-for-zoledronic-acid-injection/1672679</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672679</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approved product is bioequivalent and therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Zoledronic Acid Injection, 4 mg/100 mL (0.04 mg/mL), manufactured by InfoRLife.

The approved product is bioequivalent and therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug (RLD), Zoledronic Acid Injection, 4 mg/100 mL (0.04 mg/mL), manufactured by InfoRLife. Zoledronic Acid Injection is indicated for the treatment of hypercalcemia of malignancy, multiple myeloma, and bone metastases of solid tumors. According to IQVIA data, the product recorded US sales of approximately $6.7 million during the twelve months ended November 2025. Gland Pharma was established in 1978 in Hyderabad and has grown over the years from a contract manufacturer of small-volume liquid parenteral products to become one of the largest and fastest growing injectable-focused companies, with a global footprint across 60 countries, including the United States, Europe, Canada, Australia, India, and other markets. The counter shed 0.48% to Rs 1,840.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlandPharmaLtd._31222392_14546.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of India releases discussion paper on Exploring Safeguards In Digital Payments To Curb Frauds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/reserve-bank-of-india-releases-discussion-paper-on-exploring-safeguards-in-digital-payments-to-curb-frauds/1672676</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672676</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a discussion paper on “Exploring safeguards in digital payments to curb frauds”.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a discussion paper on “Exploring safeguards in digital payments to curb frauds”. It noted that over the past decade, digital payments in India have expanded at an unprecedented pace, reflecting a structural shift in the way individuals and businesses conduct financial transactions. However, it has been accompanied with growing sophistication of fraudulent activities targeting innocent customers. In alignment with the objective of promoting digital payments in a safe and secure manner, it is proposed to issue a Discussion Paper exploring the introduction of calibrated safeguards in digital payments such as introduction of lagged credits, additional authentication for specific class of users like senior citizens, etc. The proposed measures are intended to mitigate frauds and strengthen customer protection.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper posts nearly 149% YoY rise in Q3 PAT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-copper-posts-nearly-149-yoy-rise-in-q3-pat/1672673</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672673</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 442.82 crore, up 101.1% YoY.

Total operating expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 442.82 crore, up 101.1% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 212.52 crore, up by 151.7% from Rs 84.43 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company’s board has approved an interim dividend of Re 1 per share for the financial year 2025-26. The company has fixed Friday, 13 February 2026 as the ‘record date’ to determine the eligibility of the shareholders to receive the interim dividend. The dividend would be paid on or before Friday, 06 March 2026. Hindustan Copper is a central public sector undertaking under the administrative control of Ministry of Mines, Government of India. The principal activities of the company are exploration, exploitation, mining of copper and copper ore including beneficiation of minerals, smelting and refining. As on 31 December 2025, the Government of India held 66.14% in the company. The scrip declined 3.52% to currently trade at Rs 585.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindCopper_52829551966_3898.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with minor losses; PSU bank share decline ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-minor-losses-psu-bank-share-decline/1672671</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672671</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with small losses in the early afternoon after the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) maintained a status quo in its latest policy announcement.

The key equity benchmarks traded with small losses in the early afternoon after the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) maintained a status quo in its latest policy announcement. As widely expected by the Street, the Monetary Policy Committee (MPC), chaired by Governor Sanjay Malhotra, retained a neutral stance and left all key interest rates unchanged, keeping the benchmark repo rate steady at 5.25%. The Nifty traded below the 25,650 mark. PSU Bank shares declined after advancing for previous four consecutive trading sessions. At 11:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, fell 92.37 points or 0.11% to 83,217.16. The Nifty 50 index fell 46.85 points or 0.18% to 25,595.95. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.82% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.82%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,422 shares rose and 2,388 shares fell. A total of 202 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India (RBI’s) Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held its first monetary policy review of the calendar year 2026. RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra kept the key policy rate - repo rate unchanged at 5.25%. Headline inflation during November and December remained below the tolerance band of the inflation target. The revised outlook for CPI inflation in Q1 and Q2 of next year, at 4% and 4.2% respectively, revise slightly upwards, said RBI governor Sanjay Malhotra. The Indian economy continues on a steady, improving trajectory, with real GDP poised to register significant higher growth of 7.4% this year, as compared to the previous year, amidst global headwinds, the governor noted. Going forward, economic activity is expected to hold up well in the next year, he added. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index fell 1.40% to 8,797.20. The index added 3.28% in the previous four consecutive trading session. Canara Bank (down 1.49%), Punjab National Bank (down 1.47%), State Bank of India (down 1.43%), Bank of Baroda (down 1.34%), Union Bank of India (down 1.32%), Indian Bank (down 1.1%), UCO Bank (down 0.7%), Bank of India (down 0.68%), Indian Overseas Bank (down 0.66%) and Central Bank of India (down 0.49%) declined. Most bank stocks declined on Friday after the Reserve Bank of India’s Monetary Policy Committee kept the policy repo rate unchanged at 5.25% at the end of its meeting on February 6, 2026. The MPC voted unanimously to retain the repo rate under the liquidity adjustment facility at 5.25%. As a result, the standing deposit facility rate remains at 5.00%, while the marginal standing facility rate and the Bank Rate continue at 5.50%. The committee also decided to maintain its neutral policy stance. In its statement, the RBI said the global economy showed notable resilience in 2025, supported by trade front-loading, a milder-than-expected impact of tariffs, broad fiscal stimulus, and accommodative monetary policy. Inflation is easing gradually, although it remains above target in several advanced economies. US bond yields continue to trade with an upward bias as expectations of near-term rate cuts recede amid firm economic data. Global equities have advanced, led by sustained investments in technology stocks, even as fiscal pressures, geopolitical uncertainty, and monetary policy divergence keep financial markets volatile. On the domestic front, the RBI raised its real GDP growth forecast for FY26 to 7.4% from 7.3% earlier. Growth projections for Q1 FY27 and Q2 FY27 were revised upwards to 6.9% and 7.0%, respectively. The central bank raised its CPI inflation forecast for FY26 to 2.1% from 2%. Inflation for Q4 FY26 is projected at 3.2%, while CPI inflation for Q1 FY27 and Q2 FY27 is expected at 4.0% and 4.2%, respectively. The MPC noted that external headwinds have intensified since the previous policy meeting, although the successful completion of recent trade deals bodes well for the overall economic outlook. It added that the near-term domestic growth and inflation outlook remains positive. Looking ahead, the committee said it will continue to be guided by evolving macroeconomic conditions and incoming data from the new statistical series while charting the future course of monetary policy. The minutes of the MPC meeting will be released on 20 February 2026. The next policy meeting is scheduled for April 6-8, 2026. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharti Airtel added 1.61%. The company reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Data Patterns (India) rallied 8.70% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 30.54% to Rs 58.30 crore on a 47.92% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 173.13 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) rallied 6.88% after its consolidated net profit climbed 17.5% YoY to Rs 12,930.44 crore in Q3 FY26. Total income jumped 15.7% YoY to Rs 236,776.30 crore during the quarter. Bharti Hexacom added 6.08% after it has recorded a 48.7% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 481.29 crore on 4.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,359.90 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asian market edged lower as South Korea led the losses on Friday, following the tech-driven sell off on Wall Street. South Korea’s market, which is heavily weighted in favor of companies in the chip and automotive industries, have seen sharp swings in the past week as sentiment over tech stocks sours. Pharmaceutical stocks in Japan also slumped on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled his website offering discounted prescription medicines. On the commodities front, spot silver prices continued their decline, falling 1.63% after crashing about 13% on Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 1.20%, while the S&P 500 lost 1.23%, pushing it into negative territory for the year. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite posted the biggest decline, dropping 1.59%. Tech giant Alphabet came under pressure after reporting fourth-quarter results and flagging a sharp rise in artificial intelligence spending, with capital expenditure totaling $185 billion for 2026. Qualcomm slid more than 8% after posting a weaker forecast because of a global memory shortage.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nykaa rallies after Q3 PAT jumps over two-fold to Rs 63 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nykaa-rallies-after-q3-pat-jumps-over-two-fold-to-rs-63-cr/1672672</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672672</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax surged sharply 182.72% YoY to Rs 125.98 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional items and tax surged sharply 182.72% YoY to Rs 125.98 crore during the quarter. Exceptional items stood at Rs 16.36 crore which is related to labour code compliance. EBITDA grew 63% YoY to Rs 230 crore in Q3 FY 2026. EBITDA margins expanded to 8.0% in Q3 FY2026 as against 6.2% in Q3 FY2025. Consolidated GMV grew 28% to Rs 5,795 Cr in Q3 FY2026. Beauty business’ gross merchandise value (GMV) jumped 27% YoY to Rs 4,302 core during the quarter, supported by sustained momentum across e-commerce, physical retail, and owned brands under the House of Nykaa House of Nykaa – Beauty and Fashion GMV for the quarter stood at Rs 872 crore, registering a robust 48% YoY growth. Falguni Nayar, executive chairperson, founder and CEO Nykaa said, “Q3 FY2026 marked a record quarter for Nykaa, with our highest-ever GMV and EBITDA margin, while sustaining our long-term growth trajectory. Over a 13-year journey, Nykaa has evolved into a multi- platform lifestyle business addressing more than $100 billion beauty and fashion opportunity and serving over 52 million customers across One Nykaa. This performance reflects steady execution against our strategic priorities, as we continue to invest in assortment expansion, offline growth, and technology-led discovery, alongside a disciplined focus on efficiency. These foundations position us well for sustained, long-term growth.” FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) journey began in 2012 as a digital-first, consumer tech beauty company. It has expanded its offerings to include fashion and B2B, launching platforms such as Nykaa Fashion, Nykaa Man, and Nykaa Superstore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/FSNE-CommerceVenturesLtd_51987676_75803.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SKF India Q3 PAT drops 43% YoY to Rs 62 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/skf-india-q3-pat-drops-43-yoy-to-rs-62-crore/1672649</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672649</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 54.09% year-on-year to Rs 576.64 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations fell 54.09% year-on-year to Rs 576.64 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax for the third quarter of FY26 stood at Rs 96.44 crore, registering a 34.48% decline from Rs 147.21 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 55.84% year-on-year to Rs 510.63 crore in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, the cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 208.42 crore (down 32.89% YoY), while employee benefit expenses declined 60.25% year-on-year to Rs 34.87 crore. On a nine-month basis, the company’s net profit declined 21.21% year-on-year to Rs 285.70 crore, while revenue from operations fell 14.50% to Rs 3,168.85 crore in 9M FY26, compared with 9M FY25. SKF India, a subsidiary of the global SKF Group, manufactures bearings and related components at its facility in Pune, Maharashtra. The counter shed 0.12% to Rs 1,762.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SKFIndia_44720588884_37.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI announces various policy measures relating to regulations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-announces-various-policy-measures-relating-to-regulations/1672648</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672648</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a statement on Developmental and Regulatory Policies.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has come up with a statement on Developmental and Regulatory Policies. Here are various developmental and regulatory policy measures relating to Regulations. 1. Advertising, Marketing and Sales of Financial Products and Services by Regulated Entities (REs): RBI has decided to issue comprehensive instructions to REs on advertising, marketing and sales of financial products and services. 2. Conduct of Regulated Entities in Recovery of Loans and Engagement of Recovery Agents: Currently, different sets of instructions are applicable to different categories of Regulated Entities (REs) with respect to the engagement of recovery agents and conduct related aspects of loan recovery. It has now been decided to review and harmonise all the extant conduct related instructions on engagement of recovery agents and other aspects related to recovery of loans. 3. Review of framework of Limiting Customer Liability in digital transactions: The extant instructions on limiting the liability of customers in unauthorised electronic banking transactions were issued in 2017, which deal with scenarios and timelines for zero / limited liability of a customer. In view of the rapid adoption of technology in the banking sector and payments systems, since issuance of these instructions, the existing instructions have been reviewed. 4. Bank Lending to Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs): While bank lending to InvITs was allowed subsequently, lending to REITs was not permitted hitherto. Upon review and considering the presence of strong regulatory and governance framework for listed REITs, it is proposed to permit commercial banks to extend finance to REITs, subject to appropriate prudential safeguards. The existing guidelines in respect of lending to InvITs are also being harmonised for parity with prudential safeguards proposed for lending to REITs. 5. Review of Lending norms for UCBs: It is now proposed to rationalise the extant regulatory norms applicable for unsecured loans by UCBs; limits for lending to nominal members; and the tenor and moratorium requirements for housing loans. The proposed review shall adopt inter alia, a tiered and simplified approach while maintaining prudential discipline, taking into consideration the growth in total loans and advances of the UCBs over the past few years. Draft directions in this regard will be issued shortly for public consultation. 6. Exemption from registration to eligible NBFCs not availing public funds and not having customer interface (including ‘Type I NBFCs’):. Considering their significantly lower systemic-risk profile, it is proposed that such Type-I NBFCs with asset size not exceeding Rs 1,000 crore, may be exempted from registration requirement with the Reserve Bank subject to certain specified conditions. The proposed exemption will reduce compliance requirements for these NBFCs. Accordingly, draft Amendment Directions will be issued shortly for feedback from stakeholders. 7. Amendment of NBFC Branch Authorisation Directions-2025: At per extant regulatory requirement, NBFC - Investment and Credit Companies (ICCs) engaged in the business of lending against gold collateral with over 1,000 branches are required to obtain prior RBI approval for opening new branches. In view of the comprehensive prudential and governance framework applicable to NBFC-ICCs, it is proposed to dispense with the requirement of prior approval for opening branches by such NBFCs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/debt-loan-credit-money-financial-problem-concept-picture-id_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra Manulife MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-manulife-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1672620</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672620</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra Manulife Mutual Fund has announced 09 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

Mahindra Manulife Mutual Fund has announced 09 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Mahindra Manulife Aggressive Hybrid Fund: Regular Plan Monthly – IDCW: 0.18 Direct Plan Monthly – IDCW: 0.18

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI revises FY26 GDP growth forecast to 7.4% from 7.3% earlier]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-revises-fy26-gdp-growth-forecast-to-74-from-73-earlier/1672619</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672619</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has revised GDP growth forecast for the ongoing financial year to 7.4% from 7.3% today.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has revised GDP growth forecast for the ongoing financial year to 7.4% from 7.3% today. Real GDP growth for Q1 FY27 has also been revised to 6.9% from 6.7% and Q2 to 7% from 6.8%, with risks evenly balanced. The central bank noted that sustained buoyancy in services sector, GST rationalisation, healthy rabi prospects, monetary easing and benign inflation environment should support private consumption. Investment activity, supported by high-capacity utilisation, conducive financial conditions, healthy balance sheets of financial institutions and corporates, robust credit growth and Government’s continued thrust on capital expenditure, is expected to maintain its momentum. Moreover, robust domestic demand is likely to attract fresh investments by the private sector.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-growth-1-1057028_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Life Insurance Corporation of India counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-life-insurance-corporation-of-india-counter/1672616</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672616</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Bajaj Holdings & Investment Ltd, Medplus Health Services Ltd, Kirloskar Brothers Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 06 February 2026.

Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Bajaj Holdings & Investment Ltd, Medplus Health Services Ltd, Kirloskar Brothers Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 06 February 2026. Life Insurance Corporation of India witnessed volume of 11.24 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 15.64 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 71889 shares. The stock increased 7.37% to Rs.902.35. Volumes stood at 41256 shares in the last session. Go Digit General Insurance Ltd registered volume of 1.28 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 15.16 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 8459 shares. The stock slipped 0.80% to Rs.310.10. Volumes stood at 12564 shares in the last session. Bajaj Holdings & Investment Ltd recorded volume of 45253 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 12.41 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 3647 shares. The stock lost 2.05% to Rs.10,681.00. Volumes stood at 7789 shares in the last session. Medplus Health Services Ltd recorded volume of 52599 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 11.8 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4457 shares. The stock gained 0.50% to Rs.866.70. Volumes stood at 3468 shares in the last session. Kirloskar Brothers Ltd witnessed volume of 43652 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 9.14 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4775 shares. The stock increased 7.72% to Rs.1,663.00. Volumes stood at 2576 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Life-Insurance-Corporation-of-India_13079731_12024.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank stocks slide as RBI holds repo rate at 5.25%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-stocks-slide-as-rbi-holds-repo-rate-at-525/1672617</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672617</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The MPC voted unanimously to retain the repo rate under the liquidity adjustment facility at 5.25%.

The MPC voted unanimously to retain the repo rate under the liquidity adjustment facility at 5.25%. As a result, the standing deposit facility rate remains at 5.00%, while the marginal standing facility rate and the Bank Rate continue at 5.50%. The committee also decided to maintain its neutral policy stance. In its statement, the RBI said the global economy showed notable resilience in 2025, supported by trade front-loading, a milder-than-expected impact of tariffs, broad fiscal stimulus, and accommodative monetary policy. Inflation is easing gradually, although it remains above target in several advanced economies. US bond yields continue to trade with an upward bias as expectations of near-term rate cuts recede amid firm economic data. Global equities have advanced, led by sustained investments in technology stocks, even as fiscal pressures, geopolitical uncertainty, and monetary policy divergence keep financial markets volatile. On the domestic front, the RBI raised its real GDP growth forecast for FY26 to 7.4% from 7.3% earlier. Growth projections for Q1 FY27 and Q2 FY27 were revised upwards to 6.9% and 7.0%, respectively. The central bank raised its CPI inflation forecast for FY26 to 2.1% from 2%. Inflation for Q4 FY26 is projected at 3.2%, while CPI inflation for Q1 FY27 and Q2 FY27 is expected at 4.0% and 4.2%, respectively. The MPC noted that external headwinds have intensified since the previous policy meeting, although the successful completion of recent trade deals bodes well for the overall economic outlook. It added that the near-term domestic growth and inflation outlook remains positive. Looking ahead, the committee said it will continue to be guided by evolving macroeconomic conditions and incoming data from the new statistical series while charting the future course of monetary policy. The minutes of the MPC meeting will be released on 20 February 2026. The next policy meeting is scheduled for April 6-8, 2026. Following the announcement, the Nifty Bank index fell 0.64% to 59,681.20, while the Nifty 50 rose 0.55% to 25,501.35. Among bank stocks, IndusInd Bank fell 1.85%, while Punjab National Bank declined 1.84% and Bank of Baroda slid 1.81%. Union Bank of India shed 1.73%, Canara Bank dropped 1.62% and State Bank of India slipped 1.61%. Losses were relatively modest in Yes Bank, which declined 1.17%, IDFC First Bank, down 1.15%, Federal Bank, lower by 0.97%, HDFC Bank, which eased 0.85%, and AU Small Finance Bank, down 0.56%. In contrast, ICICI Bank gained 0.24%, Axis Bank rose 0.35%, and Kotak Mahindra Bank outperformed with a 1.03% jump, bucking the broader weakness in banking stocks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas MF announces IDCW & Monthly Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/baroda-bnp-paribas-mf-announces-idcw-monthly-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1672615</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672615</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 09 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme.

Baroda BNP Paribas Mutual Fund has announced 09 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following scheme. The amount IDCW (Rs. per unit) will be: Baroda BNP Paribas Arbitrage Fund – Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option & Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs. 0.06 each

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sayaji Hotels (Indore) rises after Q3 PAT jumps 29% YoY to Rs 6 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sayaji-hotels-indore-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-29-yoy-to-rs-6-cr/1672614</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672614</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations increased 6.5% year on year (YoY) to Rs 32.13 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations increased 6.5% year on year (YoY) to Rs 32.13 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 7.77 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025, up 47.4% as against Rs 5.27 crore recorded in the corresponding quarter the previous year. Total expenses rose 2.2% to Rs 24.43 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 24.98 crore in Q3 FY25. Food & beverages consumed stood at Rs 5 crore (down 9.09% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 6.89 crore (up 8.16% YoY) during the period under review. Sayaji Hotels (Pune) is primarily engaged in the business of owning, operating & managing hotels.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SayajiHotelsIndoreLtd_39546350_76340.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty slides below 25,550 mark; IT shares decline for 3rd day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-slides-below-25550-mark-it-shares-decline-for-3rd-day/1672606</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672606</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the morning trade, dragged down by IT heavyweights amid a weak trend in US equities.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with moderate losses in the morning trade, dragged down by IT heavyweights amid a weak trend in US equities. The Nifty traded below the 25,550 mark, while IT shares extended losses for the three consecutive trading session. At 10:28 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 321.50 points or 0.39% to 82,973.01. The Nifty 50 index fell 108.75 points or 0.42% to 25,534.05. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.97% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 1.09%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,261 shares rose and 2,333 shares fell. A total of 206 shares were unchanged. Earnings to Watch: Tata Steel, Baazar Style Retail, Shipping Corporation of India, Lemon Tree Hotels, Whirlpool of India, Sun TV Network, Shree Cement, Sonata Software, BEML, BLS International Services, Bosch, Centum Electronics, CESC, Crompton Greaves, JK Tyre & Industries, Jana Small Finance Bank, Jubilant Pharmova, Kalpataru, Kalyan Jewellers India will declare their result later today. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) announced its monetary policy decision on Friday, 6 February 2026. The Sanjay Malhotra-led Monetary Policy Committee (MPC), which met from 4 to 6 February for its sixth and final bi-monthly policy review of FY26, unanimously voted to keep the key repo rate unchanged at 5.25%, continuing its pause on interest rates amid an improving growth outlook. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index fell 1.44% to 35,621.25. The index tanked 7.74% in three consecutive trading session. Oracle Financial Services Software (down 3.76%), Coforge (down 3.49%), Persistent Systems (down 2.6%), LTIMindtree (down 2.38%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 2.02%), Mphasis (down 1.81%), Infosys (down 1.36%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.35%), Wipro (down 1.09%) and HCL Technologies (down 0.87%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Pitti Engineering declined 2.14% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 29.61% QoQ to Rs 28.22 crore despite a flat 0.06% decline in net sales to Rs 477.42 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit fell by 1.9%, despite a 15% increase in net sales in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hitachi Energy India surged 11.88% after the company’s standalone net profit soared 90.29% to Rs 261.42 crore on 27.71% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2021.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. NCC slipped 2.89% after the company reported 36.60% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 122.46 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 193.18 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 8.91% YoY to Rs 4,868.29 crore during the third quarter of FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>