<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:49:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cochin Shipyard jumps on Rs 5,000 crore Navy vessel bid win]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cochin-shipyard-jumps-on-rs-5000-crore-navy-vessel-bid-win/1678181</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678181</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has emerged as the L1 bidder in a key defence tender floated for the construction of five Next Generation Survey Vessels for the Indian Navy.

The company has emerged as the L1 bidder in a key defence tender floated for the construction of five Next Generation Survey Vessels for the Indian Navy. The shipbuilder stated that the estimated total order value is around Rs 5,000 crore. It added that the final award of the contract is subject to completion of necessary formalities, and further updates will be shared in due course. Cochin Shipyard is a leading player in the construction of all kinds of vessels and the repair and refit of all types of vessels, including periodic upgrades and life extensions of ships. The company reported an 18.3% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.67 crore on a 17.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,350.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CochinShipyardLtd_99942576320_5762.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Supply Chains gains after inking MoU with Italy’s ALA Group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-supply-chains-gains-after-inking-mou-with-italys-ala-group/1678182</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678182</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ALA Group brings more than 35 years of experience as a specialised aerospace and defence supply-chain integrator, supporting leading OEMs, MROs, and defence programmes across Europe, North America, and selected international markets.

ALA Group brings more than 35 years of experience as a specialised aerospace and defence supply-chain integrator, supporting leading OEMs, MROs, and defence programmes across Europe, North America, and selected international markets. For the year 2024, it reported revenue of $345 million. As part of the proposed collaboration, TVS SCS and ALA Group will jointly provide integrated supply chain services across both production and aftermarket lifecycles for aerospace and defence programmes. The collaboration will initially focus on India, with potential to evaluate opportunities in other geographies over time. The company said that Aerospace and Defence market in India, estimated at approximately $28 billion, are among the most dynamic and profitable segments within industrial supply chains, driven by sustained demand for complex, regulated, and mission-critical logistics and procurement services. TVS SCS will leverage its long-standing defence and utilities supply chain experience gained through its UK operations, together with its strong domestic presence in India. This includes procurement, market access, government and stakeholder engagement, regulatory and licensing expertise, warehousing and logistics infrastructure, digital platforms, and robust local execution capabilities. ALA Group on the other hand, will contribute its global aerospace and defence domain expertise, technology platforms, and long-standing relationships, especially in the production supply chain with international OEMs and operators across Europe, the US, and the UK, enabling a differentiated, compliant, and scalable value proposition for aerospace and defence stakeholders in India. Currently, TVS SCS’ aerospace, defence and utilities operations generate approximately $140 million in annual revenues, largely anchored in defence and utility programmes in the United Kingdom. R. Dinesh, Executive Chairman, TVS Supply Chain Solutions, said, “This collaboration with ALA Group reflects our long-term strategy of building globally relevant capabilities in complex and regulated sectors. By combining TVS Supply Chain Solutions’ scale, digital platforms, and strong presence in India with ALA’s aerospace and defence domain expertise, we are positioning the company to participate meaningfully in the evolving global aerospace and defence supply chain ecosystem.” He further added, “Importantly, this partnership enables us to build on our established aftermarket and in-service supply chain strengths and extend our support to production programmes, particularly in aerospace where these capabilities are increasingly relevant.” Vittorio Genna, CEO and Co-Founder, ALA Group, added, “From the beginning, ALA has focused on combining technical depth, operational excellence, and long-term partnerships. The collaboration with TVS Supply Chain Solutions reflects this vision and creates a solid platform for sustainable growth across multiple regions, supporting both civil and defence aerospace programs.” TVS Supply Chain Solutions (TVS SCS) is an India-based multinational company, who pioneered the development of the supply chain solutions market in India. The company's customers span across numerous industries such as automotive, industrial, consumer, tech and tech infra, rail and utilities, and healthcare. TVS Supply Chain Solutions reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 10.72 crore in Q3 December 2025 compared with a net loss of Rs 24.65 crore posted in Q3 December 2024. Revenue from operations jumped 11.09% YoY to Rs 2,715.81 crore during the quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSSupplyChainSolutionsLtd_13681781_28638.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HFCL gains on bagging Rs 61-cr optical fiber cable order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hfcl-gains-on-bagging-rs-61-cr-optical-fiber-cable-order/1678178</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678178</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the supply of optical fiber cables as per customer specifications.

According to an exchange filing, the order pertains to the supply of optical fiber cables as per customer specifications. The contract is scheduled to be executed by May 2026. HFCL clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. The company further stated that the transaction does not qualify as a related-party contract under applicable regulatory norms. HFCL is a diversified telecom infrastructure enabler with businesses spanning telecom infrastructure development, system integration, and the manufacture and supply of high-end telecom equipment, optical fiber, and optical fiber cables (OFC). The company reported a 41.04% jump in consolidated profit to Rs 102.37 crore on a 19.65% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,210.79 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HFCL_23392864533_1189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DSP MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dsp-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1678179</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678179</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[DSP Mutual Fund has announced 19 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

DSP Mutual Fund has announced 19 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs. per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: DSP Mid Cap Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 2.500 DSP Mid Cap Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 5.800 DSP Equity Savings Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 0.8000 DSP Equity Savings Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 0.8000

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Highway Infra zooms on bagging Rs 155-cr order from NHAI]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/highway-infra-zooms-on-bagging-rs-155-cr-order-from-nhai/1678176</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678176</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order entails engagement of a user fee agency for collection of toll at Moti Narol Fee Plaza (Km 969.096), Ena Fee Plaza (Km 1005.426) and Gandevi Fee Plaza (Km 1032.991).

The order entails engagement of a user fee agency for collection of toll at Moti Narol Fee Plaza (Km 969.096), Ena Fee Plaza (Km 1005.426) and Gandevi Fee Plaza (Km 1032.991). The project covers multiple packages of the eight-lane Vadodara–Mumbai Expressway, including the Ankleshwar–Manubar (Pkg-4), Kim–Ankleshwar (Pkg-5), Ena–Kim (Pkg-6) and Gandevi–Ena (Pkg-7) sections in Gujarat. The scope of work includes operation and collection of user fee at the Moti Narol Fee Plaza, along with upkeep and maintenance of adjacent toilet blocks and replenishment of consumables. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is valued at Rs 154.59 crore and is to be executed within 90 days. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It also confirmed that the contract does not fall under related-party transactions. Highway Infrastructure are an infrastructure development and management company. The company is engaged in the business of tollway collection, EPC Infra and real estate businesses. The company reported a 96% year-on-year surge in net profit to Rs 6.41 crore for Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations declined 9.2% to Rs 126.86 crore compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HighwayInfrastructureLtd_53703943_66257.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Texmaco Rail & Engineering spurts after bagging Rs 219-cr order from MRVC]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/texmaco-rail-engineering-spurts-after-bagging-rs-219-cr-order-from-mrvc/1678175</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678175</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the contract involves the design, supply, installation, testing and commissioning of signalling equipment in connection with the construction of a proposed line under the Mumbai Suburban Railway Project (MUTP-IIIA).

According to an exchange filing, the contract involves the design, supply, installation, testing and commissioning of signalling equipment in connection with the construction of a proposed line under the Mumbai Suburban Railway Project (MUTP-IIIA). The work is to be completed within 36 months from issuance of Notice to Proceed. The company also clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group members have any interest in the awarding entity. The company also confirmed that the contract does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. The company said the project is scheduled to be completed within 36 months from the date of issuance of the Notice to Proceed. Texmaco Rail clarified that none of its promoters or promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding authority. It also confirmed that the contract does not fall under the ambit of related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. Texmaco Rail & Engineering (TEXMACO) is a listed company and part of the Adventz Group. Texmaco is a key player in the railway and infrastructure sector. It operates across three business segments: Freight Cars, Rail Infrastructure & Green Energy, and Infrastructure – Electrical. The company reported a 44.65% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 42.27 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 76.38 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 21.45% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,041.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TexmacoRail_96355740994_27419.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Infosys edges higher after forming collaboration pact with Anthropic]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/infosys-edges-higher-after-forming-collaboration-pact-with-anthropic/1678174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678174</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The collaboration will begin in telecommunications with a dedicated Anthropic Center of Excellence to build and deploy AI agents tailored to industry-specific operations.

The collaboration will begin in telecommunications with a dedicated Anthropic Center of Excellence to build and deploy AI agents tailored to industry-specific operations. The collaboration will further expand across industries, including financial services, manufacturing, and software development. At its core, the collaboration integrates Anthropic's Claude models, including Claude Code, with Infosys Topaz AI offerings to help enterprises automate complex workflows, accelerate software delivery, and adopt AI with the governance and transparency that regulated industries require. A core focus will be agentic AI – systems that go beyond answering questions to independently handling multi-step tasks like processing claims, generating and testing code, or managing compliance reviews. Using tools like the Claude Agent SDK, Infosys and Anthropic will help clients build AI agents that can work persistently across long, complex processes rather than one-off interactions. The collaboration will also help organizations modernize legacy systems, combining Infosys Topaz and Claude to accelerate migration and reduce the cost of updating aging infrastructure. Salil Parekh, chief executive officer, Infosys, said: “AI is not just transforming business – it is redefining the way industries operate and innovate. Our collaboration with Anthropic marks a strategic leap toward advancing enterprise AI, enabling organizations to unlock value and become more intelligent, resilient, and responsible. From modernizing financial services with intelligent risk management and compliance, to enabling engineering businesses to lead with AI-driven design and manufacturing, the goal is to leverage the joint expertise of Infosys and Anthropic to accelerate AI value realization for global enterprises." Infosys is a global leader in next-generation digital services and consulting. The company reported a 9.6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,654 crore on a 2.22% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 45,479 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Infosys_56909713360_2806.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge lower in early trade; breadth positive]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-lower-in-early-trade-breadth-positive/1678164</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678164</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in early trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in early trade. The Nifty traded tad below the 25,600 level. Metal, realty, and private bank shares declined, while IT and PSU bank stocks advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 220.42 points or 0.26% to 83,056.73. The Nifty 50 index fell 91.80 points or 0.36% to 25,591.50. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.21% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.18%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,690 shares rose and 1,242 shares fell. A total of 161 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 972.13 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,666.98 crore in the Indian equity market on 16 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Texmaco Rail & Engineering rose 3.87% after the company announced that it has secured a Rs 219 crore contract from Mumbai Railway Vikas Corporation for construction work in the Mumbai suburban railway network. NTPC rose 0.12%. The company announced that its joint venture NTPC-SAIL Power Company has commenced operations of an additional 5 MW at its Bhilai Solar Project, taking the group’s total commercial capacity to 86,729 MW. Cochin Shipyard jumped 6.63% after the company said that it has emerged as the L1 (lowest) bidder for a Rs 5,000 crore order from the Ministry of Defence to manufacture five survey vessels for the Indian Navy. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.07% to 6.673 compared with the previous session close of 6.668. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7450 compared with its close of 90.7400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.54% to Rs 153,920. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 97.13. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.59% to 4.028. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 59 cents or 0.87% to $68.34 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian markets treaded carefully on Tuesday. The Mainland Chinese, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan, and South Korean markets were closed on Tuesday for Lunar New Year holidays. U.S. markets were shut on Monday for Presidents’ Day. Japan’s weakening economy remained in focus on Tuesday, one day after much softer than expected GDP numbers. The country on Monday reported its economy grew an annualized 0.2% in the fourth quarter, far below the widely reported gain forecast of 1.6% as government spending dragged on activity. In today's session, the Japanese yen strengthened 0.15% against the greenback to 153.28 per dollar. The weak figures highlight the challenges ahead for Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and should support her push for more aggressive fiscal stimulus, media reports said. The Bank of Japan next meets on rates in March, with traders forecasting only a slim chance for a hike. Widely reported polls in the media suggest that investors expect the central bank to wait until July before tightening policy again. Meanwhile, oil saw some price gains as investors looked ahead to the U.S. and Iran nuclear negotiations that are scheduled to begin in Geneva later in the day. The higher volatility in crude was triggered by the latest drill that was reportedly held by Iran’s Revolutionary Guards in the Hormuz Strait on Monday. The passage accounts for about 20% of global oil shipments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cochin Shipyard Ltd Spikes 5.82%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cochin-shipyard-ltd-spikes-582/1678155</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678155</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cochin Shipyard Ltd rose 5.82% today to trade at Rs 1553.6.

Cochin Shipyard Ltd rose 5.82% today to trade at Rs 1553.6. The BSE Capital Goods index is up 0.31% to quote at 69168.33. The index is up 8.16 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd increased 2.17% and Elgi Equipments Ltd added 1.29% on the day. The BSE Capital Goods index went up 21.21 % over last one year compared to the 9.48% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Cochin Shipyard Ltd has added 1.77% over last one month compared to 8.16% gain in BSE Capital Goods index and 0.45% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 36530 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 1.02 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2547.25 on 06 Jun 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 1180.45 on 18 Feb 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CochinShipyardLtd_99942576320_5762.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Lupin, NTPC, Cochin Shipyard, Texmaco Rail & Engineering, BLS E-Services]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-lupin-ntpc-cochin-shipyard-texmaco-rail-engineering-bls-e-services/1678146</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678146</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&O trading on 17 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&O trading on 17 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Lupin announced that it has entered into a licensing and supply agreement with Spektus to commercialize its antidepressant formulation DeslaFlex in Canada. NTPC announced that its joint venture NTPC-SAIL Power Company has commenced operations of an additional 5 MW at its Bhilai Solar Project, taking the group’s total commercial capacity to 86,729 MW. Cochin Shipyard has emerged as the L1 (lowest) bidder for a Rs 5,000 crore order from the Ministry of Defence to manufacture five survey vessels for the Indian Navy. Texmaco Rail & Engineering has secured a Rs 219 crore contract from Mumbai Railway Vikas Corporation for construction work in the Mumbai suburban railway network. BLS E-Services announced that it has signed binding term sheet, to acquire a 100% stake in Atyati Technologies for Rs 154 crore. TVS Supply Chain Solutions has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Italy-based ALA Group to provide services to the Indian aerospace and defence market.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KFin Tech appoints Nazish Hussain Mir as CTO]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kfin-tech-appoints-nazish-hussain-mir-as-cto/1678144</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678144</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[He is currently directing the adoption of applied artificial intelligence (AI) across the software development lifecycle, including the implementation of agentic coding frameworks and AI-assisted engineering workflows to improve productivity, reliability, and delivery precision.

He is currently directing the adoption of applied artificial intelligence (AI) across the software development lifecycle, including the implementation of agentic coding frameworks and AI-assisted engineering workflows to improve productivity, reliability, and delivery precision. Nazish pursued BTech from KL University, serves as the head of WebileApps (India), a wholly owned subsidiary and the core digital transformation arm of KFin Technologies. Since co-founding WebileApps in 2009, he has led its evolution from a specialized startup into a 400-person engineering organization supporting fintech, capital markets, and healthcare platforms across Indian and international markets. Nazish worked with Wipro before founding Webileapps. Under his leadership, WebileApps transitioned from a services-led organization into a strategic engineering partner for financial institutions, specializing in managed services and large-scale platform modernization. Meanwhile, the company reported a 2.02% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 91.99 crore on 27.88% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 370.87 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. KFin Technologies (KFintech) is a leading technology-driven financial services platform. The company provides services and solutions to asset managers and corporate issuers across asset classes in India and provides several investor solutions, including transaction origination and processing for mutual funds and private retirement schemes to global asset managers across 18 jurisdictions. The counter rallied 3.40% to settle at Rs 1,001 on Monday, 16 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KFinTechnologiesLtd_30241335_73556.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty hints at negative opening for equities; all eyes on US-Iran nuclear negotiations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-hints-at-negative-opening-for-equities-all-eyes-on-us-iran-nuclear-negotiations/1678145</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678145</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 43 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 43 points, suggesting a negative start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 972.13 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,666.98 crore in the Indian equity market on 16 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 2,345.69 crore in the cash market so far in February (till 13 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian markets treaded carefully on Tuesday. Mainland Chinese, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan and South Korea markets were closed on Tuesday for Lunar New Year holidays. U.S markets were shut on Monday for Presidents’ Day. Japan’s weakening economy remained in focus on Tuesday, one day after much softer than expected GDP numbers. The country on Monday reported its economy grew an annualised 0.2% in the fourth quarter, far below the widely reported gain forecast of 1.6% as government spending dragged on activity. In today's session, the Japanese yen strengthened 0.15% against the greenback to 153.28 per dollar. The weak figures highlight the challenges ahead for Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and should support her push for more aggressive fiscal stimulus, media reports said. The Bank of Japan next meets on rates in March, with traders forecasting only a slim chance for a hike. Widely reported polls in the media suggest that investors expect the central bank to wait until July before tightening policy again. Meanwhile, oil saw some price gains as investors looked ahead to the U.S and Iran nuclear negotiations that are scheduled to being in Geneva later in the day. The higher volatility in crude was triggered by the latest drill that was reportedly held by Iran’s Revolutionary Guards in the Hormuz Strait on Monday. The passage accounts for about 20% of global oil shipments. Domestic Market: Benchmark equity indices finished firmly higher on Monday, buoyed by robust buying in banks and financial counters. The Nifty reversed its two-day slide and settled above the 25,650 mark after a sharp intraday recovery. The session began on a cautious note amid mixed global signals, with the Nifty slipping to 25,372.70 in early trade. However, strong domestic buying quickly reversed the trend, triggering a steady upmove through the day. Gains gathered momentum in the latter half of the session, lifting the index to an intraday high of 25,697 before it closed near the day’s peak. The S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 650.39 points or 0.79% to 83,277.15. The Nifty 50 index rallied 211.65 points or 0.83% to 25,682.75. The 50-unit index fell 1.86% in the past two sessions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>