<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:03:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Apollo Tyres Ltd Slides 1.65%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apollo-tyres-ltd-slides-165/1666111</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666111</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Apollo Tyres Ltd fell 1.65% today to trade at Rs 498.55.

Apollo Tyres Ltd fell 1.65% today to trade at Rs 498.55. The BSE Auto index is down 0.88% to quote at 59404.39. The index is down 4.13 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Hyundai Motor India Ltd decreased 0.8% and Ashok Leyland Ltd lost 0.77% on the day. The BSE Auto index went up 17.92 % over last one year compared to the 7.85% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Apollo Tyres Ltd has lost 2.17% over last one month compared to 4.13% fall in BSE Auto index and 4.41% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 1276 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 61193 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 540.3 on 14 Nov 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 368 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ApolloTyres_97944783969_23.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge lower in early trade; breadth negative]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-lower-in-early-trade-breadth-negative/1666113</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666113</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded with minor cuts in early trade.

The key equity barometers traded with minor cuts in early trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,250 mark. Pharma, metal, and auto shares advanced, while consumer durables and realty stocks declined. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 173.03 points or 0.21% to 82,007.44. The Nifty 50 index lost 6.85 points or 0.04% to 25,222.65. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.23% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.33%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,371 shares rose and 1,720 shares fell. A total of 159 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 2,938.33 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,665.69 crore in the Indian equity market on 20 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: AU Small Finance Bank (SFB) rose 1.52% after the company reported a 26.34% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 667.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 528.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Persistent Systems shed 0.12%. The company reported a 6.79% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 439.4 crore despite a 5.52% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3778.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 17.82% and 23.38%, respectively, in Q3 FY26. Vikram Solar declined 2.05%. The company reported a sharp 405.47% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 96.14 crore on 7.79% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,105.95 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.04% to 6.676 compared with the previous session close of 6.673. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.1975 compared with its close of 90.9700 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 2.54% to Rs 154,358. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 98.60. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.28% to 4.283. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement shed 74 cents or 1.14% to $64.18 a barrel. Global Markets: The Asian market edged lower on Wednesday, while gold jumped to a record high level after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on countries resisting the transfer of Greenland to the United States. Spot gold prices rose over 1% to an all-time high of $4,813 per ounce as investors rushed into safe haven assets. On Saturday, Trump said that exports from eight European countries would face tariffs of 10% from Feb. 1, rising to 25% by June 1 if talks fail to deliver U.S. control of mineral-rich Greenland. He also threatened to slap 200% tariffs on French wine and champagne, following reports that President Emmanuel Macron was unwilling to join his proposed “Board of Peace.” Trump further criticized the U.K., calling its plan to transfer sovereignty of the Chagos Islands, which is home to a joint U.K.-U.S. military base, to Mauritius an “act of great stupidity,” citing the move as further justification for acquiring Greenland on national security grounds. European leaders have labeled President Donald Trump’s latest tariff threats “unacceptable” and are reportedly weighing retaliatory measures. France is said to be urging the European Union to deploy its strongest economic response tool, the so-called Anti-Coercion Instrument. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 870.74 points, or 1.76%, to end the session at 48,488.59. The S&P 500 dipped 2.06% to settle at 6,796.86. The Nasdaq Composite slid 2.39%, closing at 22,954.32. It was the worst session since October for all three major averages. U.S. Treasury yields spiked and the U.S. dollar declined as Trump’s threat caused a flight from U.S. assets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR plunges to fresh record low beyond Rs 91/$mark; Firm dollar demand from importers weigh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-plunges-to-fresh-record-low-beyond-rs-91mark-firm-dollar-demand-from-importers-weigh/1666109</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666109</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee is plunging to fresh lifetime low levels in opening trades on Wednesday amid persistent global trade tensions between USD-EU and sustained foreign fund outflows.

The Indian rupee is plunging to fresh lifetime low levels in opening trades on Wednesday amid persistent global trade tensions between USD-EU and sustained foreign fund outflows. Weakness in greenback overseas also failed to support the counter. Meanwhile, firm dollar demand from importers due to the absence of a trade deal announcement between the US and India is also weighing on the local unit. INR opened at Rs 91.05 per dollar and hit a record low of 91.22 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee depreciated 7 paise to close at a record low of 90.97 against the US dollar Moreover, a sluggish domestic stock market triggered by sustained foreign capital outflow further weighed on the local unit. Local shares tumbled on Tuesday, with benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty falling for a second straight session amid rising geopolitical and tariff tensions. The BSE Sensex slumped 1,065.71 points, or 1.28 percent, to 82,180.47 while the broader NSE Nifty index ended down 353 points, or 1.38 percent, at 25,232.50.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: AU SFB, Persistent Systems, Vikram Solar, IndiaMART, Cyient DLM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-au-sfb-persistent-systems-vikram-solar-indiamart-cyient-dlm/1666099</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666099</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 21 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 21 January 2026. Result Today: Anant Raj, Bajaj Consumer Care, Bank of India, Dalmia Bharat, Dr Reddys Laboratories, Gallantt Ispat, Gravita India, Hindustan Petroleum Corporation, Jindal Stainless, KEI Industries, Oracle Financial Services Software, PNB Housing Finance, Rajratan Global Wire, Sagar Cements, Supreme Industries, Tata Communications, Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem, Thangamayil Jewellery, UTI Asset Management Company, Eternal will announce their quarterly earnings today. Listing In the Mainboard segment, the Amagi Media Labs IPO will debut today. Meanwhile, in the SME segment, INDO SMC, GRE Renew Enertech, and Narmadesh Brass Industries are set to list today. Stocks to Watch: AU Small Finance Bank (SFB) reported a 26.34% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 667.66 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 528.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Persistent Systems reported a 6.79% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 439.4 crore despite of 5.52% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3778.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year on year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 17.82% and 23.38% respectively in Q3 FY26. Vikram Solar reported a sharp 405.47% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 96.14 crore on 7.79% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,105.95 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. IndiaMART reported a 55.6% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 188 crore on 13.4% jump in revenue to Rs 402 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY26. Cyient DLM reported 2.2% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 11.2 crore on 31.8% decrease in revenue to Rs 303 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Supreme Petrochem has reported 36.7% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 30.6 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 48.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased by 14.6% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,281 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/invest-investment-investor-finance-financial-finances-money_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty indicates green opening for key indices; gold hits fresh record high of $4,813/ounce ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-indicates-green-opening-for-key-indices-gold-hits-fresh-record-high-of-4813ounce/1666100</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666100</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 37.00 points, suggesting a green opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 37.00 points, suggesting a green opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 2,938.33 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 3,665.69 crore in the Indian equity market on 20 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 32,253.55 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market edged lower on Wednesday while gold jumped to a record high level after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened fresh tariffs on countries resisting the transfer of Greenland to the United States. Spot gold prices rose over 1% to an all-time high of $4,813 per ounce as investors rushed into safe haven assets. On Saturday, Trump said that exports from eight European countries would face tariffs of 10% from Feb. 1, rising to 25% by June 1 if talks fail to deliver U.S. control of mineral-rich Greenland. He also threatened to slap 200% tariffs on French wine and champagne, following reports that President Emmanuel Macron was unwilling to join his proposed “Board of Peace.” Trump further criticized the U.K., calling its plan to transfer sovereignty of the Chagos Islands, which is home to a joint U.K.-U.S. military base, to Mauritius an “act of great stupidity,” citing the move as further justification for acquiring Greenland on national security grounds. European leaders have labeled President Donald Trump’s latest tariff threats “unacceptable” and are reportedly weighing retaliatory measures. France is said to be urging the European Union to deploy its strongest economic response tool, the so-called Anti-Coercion Instrument. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 870.74 points, or 1.76%, to end the session at 48,488.59. The S&P 500 dipped 2.06% to settle at 6,796.86. The Nasdaq Composite slid 2.39%, closing at 22,954.32. It was the worst session since October for all three major averages. U.S. Treasury yields spiked and the U.S. dollar declined as Trump’s threat caused a flight from U.S. assets. Domestic Market: Benchmark equity indices closed sharply lower on Tuesday, with the Nifty slipping below the 25,250 level as selling pressure intensified across the board. All NSE sectoral indices ended in the red, with realty stocks leading the declines. Shares came under pressure amid renewed trade tensions between the US and Europe, rising geopolitical risks, and weaker-than-expected Q3 earnings from a few heavyweight companies. Persistent foreign institutional selling, a sharp sell-off in the broader market, and the weekly expiry of Nifty derivatives added to volatility. Investors also remained cautious ahead of a potential US Supreme Court ruling on Trump-era tariffs, as an adverse outcome could materially shift global trade dynamics, even though the timing and verdict remain uncertain. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,065.71 points or 1.28% to 82,180.47. The Nifty 50 index dropped 353 points or 1.38% to 25,232.50.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lemon Tree Hotels expands footprint in UP with Keys Select Chitrakoot]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lemon-tree-hotels-expands-footprint-in-up-with-keys-select-chitrakoot/1666098</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666098</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The property shall be managed by Carnation Hotels, a wholly owned subsidiary of Lemon Tree Hotels.

The property shall be managed by Carnation Hotels, a wholly owned subsidiary of Lemon Tree Hotels. This hotel will feature 48 well-appointed rooms, a restaurant, a banquet hall, a meeting room, recreational facilities including a fitness centre and a swimming pool. The Chitrakoot Airport is at a distance of 10 kms from the property while the Prayagraj Airport, is approximately 105 kms away. The Chitrakutdham Karwi Railway Station is just 5kms from the property. The hotel is well connected by both public and private transport. Vilas Pawar, CEO - Managed & Franchise Business, Lemon Tree Hotels, commented, “With this signing, we are pleased to extend our religious and leisure portfolio at a place ideal for pilgrims and travellers seeking spiritual reflection, quiet contemplation, and a meaningful connection with India’s timeless heritage. The state has eight operational and fourteen upcoming hotels." Lemon Tree Hotels (LTHL) is one of the largest hotel chains in India and owns/leases/operates/franchises hotels across the upscale, upper-midscale, midscale, and economy segments. The group offers seven brands to meet guests’ needs across all levels, viz., Aurika Hotels & Resorts, Lemon Tree Premier, Lemon Tree Hotels, Red Fox Hotels by Lemon Tree Hotels, Keys Prima by Lemon Tree Hotels, Keys Select by Lemon Tree Hotels, and Keys Lite by Lemon Tree Hotels. The company reported a 16.73% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 34.60 crore, while revenue from operations rose 7.7% to Rs 306.28 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip declined 0.96% to Rs 134.30 on Tuesday, 20 January 2025..

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LemonTreeHotelsLtd_62193476144_40619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>