<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:43:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aviation stocks slump as Middle East crisis disrupts global flight operations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aviation-stocks-slump-as-middle-east-crisis-disrupts-global-flight-operations/1680137</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680137</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[InterGlobe Aviation, the parent of IndiGo, dropped 6.30%, while SpiceJet declined 5.35% amid concerns over rising operational challenges.

InterGlobe Aviation, the parent of IndiGo, dropped 6.30%, while SpiceJet declined 5.35% amid concerns over rising operational challenges. The conflict involving Israel, the United States and Iran has led to multiple airspace shutdowns across the Middle East, significantly affecting international flight routes, particularly those connecting India to Europe via major Gulf hubs. At the same time, a spike in global crude oil prices has added to investor worries, as higher fuel costs directly impact airline profitability. The Indian Association of Tour Operators reported a noticeable increase in booking cancellations and rescheduling requests on Sunday, citing disruptions caused by airspace restrictions. The ongoing crisis has heightened uncertainty for the aviation sector, with investors factoring in the dual impact of disrupted routes and elevated fuel expenses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InterglobeAviat_28069694232_33159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Apollo Micro Systems Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apollo-micro-systems-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1680136</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680136</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Safari Industries (India) Ltd, Easy Trip Planners Ltd, Birla Corporation Ltd and KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 March 2026.

Safari Industries (India) Ltd, Easy Trip Planners Ltd, Birla Corporation Ltd and KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 02 March 2026. Apollo Micro Systems Ltd lost 9.84% to Rs 214.5 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 7.43 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.51 lakh shares in the past one month. Safari Industries (India) Ltd tumbled 7.51% to Rs 1716. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6198 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4322 shares in the past one month. Easy Trip Planners Ltd crashed 7.19% to Rs 8. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 24.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 60.88 lakh shares in the past one month. Birla Corporation Ltd corrected 6.81% to Rs 933. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 12093 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5170 shares in the past one month. KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd dropped 6.78% to Rs 930.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.4 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.73 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ApolloMicroSystemsLtd_44894477773_71623.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oil hits eight month highs on supply worries]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oil-hits-eight-month-highs-on-supply-worries/1680135</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680135</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Oil prices surged sharply on Monday, with WTI crude oil futures climbing more than 8% to trade above $72 per barrel, the highest level in over eight months, after earlier gains of nearly 10%.

Oil prices surged sharply on Monday, with WTI crude oil futures climbing more than 8% to trade above $72 per barrel, the highest level in over eight months, after earlier gains of nearly 10%. The rally followed unprecedented joint US and Israeli strikes on Iran, sharply escalating geopolitical tensions in the Middle East. Markets are closely watching the risk of supply disruptions through the Strait of Hormuz, which carries around one-fifth of global oil flows. While Iran said the strait remains open, several shipping firms began rerouting vessels. Tehran also launched retaliatory missile strikes on US bases across the region. The rally came despite OPEC+ agreeing to raise output by 206,000 barrels per day in April, ending a three-month pause.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kridhan Infra Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kridhan-infra-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1680134</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680134</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finkurve Financial Services Ltd, Race Eco Chain Ltd, Vaswani Industries Ltd and InfoBeans Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 March 2026.

Finkurve Financial Services Ltd, Race Eco Chain Ltd, Vaswani Industries Ltd and InfoBeans Technologies Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 02 March 2026. Kridhan Infra Ltd crashed 20.00% to Rs 2.76 at 14:04 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.97 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5139 shares in the past one month. Finkurve Financial Services Ltd tumbled 16.92% to Rs 65.22. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.1 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8001 shares in the past one month. Race Eco Chain Ltd lost 15.99% to Rs 97.45. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 19 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 575 shares in the past one month. Vaswani Industries Ltd slipped 14.09% to Rs 52.91. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 28290 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 23934 shares in the past one month. InfoBeans Technologies Ltd shed 13.37% to Rs 179.2. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 44345 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 30804 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KridhanInfra_47544164337_40506.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks trade in negative terrain; media shares drop]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-trade-in-negative-terrain-media-shares-drop/1680131</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680131</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with substantial losses in the mid-afternoon trade adopted a risk-off approach amid escalating geopolitical tensions following the US-Israel attacks on Iran.

The key equity benchmarks traded with substantial losses in the mid-afternoon trade adopted a risk-off approach amid escalating geopolitical tensions following the US-Israel attacks on Iran. Traders are closely monitoring crude oil and metal prices. The Nifty slipped below the 24,800 level, reflecting weak market sentiment. Media shares declined after advancing in the past trading session. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 1,351.91 points or 1.66% to 79,911.22. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 420.15 points or 1.67% to 24,762.05. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index declined 1.79% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 2.32%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 612 shares rose and 3,688 shares fell. A total of 167 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 27.23% to 17.44. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 2.22% to 1,386.25. The index advanced 0.60% in the past trading session. Hathway Cable & Datacom (down 5.13%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 4.38%), D B Corp (down 3.89%), Nazara Technologies (down 3.53%), Sun TV Network (down 3.4%), Network 18 Media & Investments (down 2.55%), Saregama India (down 2.39%), Tips Music (down 2.27%), PVR Inox (down 1.79%) declined. US-Iran Conflict: The United States and Israel have launched major coordinated military strikes on Iran, marking a significant escalation in long-running Middle East tensions. On 1 March 2026, Iran launches missile and drone strikes on U.S. bases across six Middle Eastern countries amid escalating military tensions. Iran’s Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei was reportedly killed in the attacks, escalating tensions further. Following his death, Iran appointed Ayatollah Alireza Arafi to its interim leadership council, which will assume charge of the country’s affairs. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.54% to 6.697 compared with the previous session close of 6.661. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.4700 compared with its close of 91.0800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement gained 4.23% to Rs 168,950. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.83% to 98.42. The United States 10-year bond yield jumped 0.18% to 3.965. In the commodities market, Brent crude for May 2026 settlement surged $6.21 or 8.52% to $79.08 a barrel. amid heightened geopolitical tensions. According to media reports, Saudi Arabia’s state-owned oil major Aramco temporarily shut down its Ras Tanura refinery on Monday as a precautionary measure after an Iranian drone strike reportedly sparked a fire at the facility. Stocks in Spotlight: Suraksha Diagnostic fell 2.06% after its group chief financial officer (CFO) and key managerial personnel (KMP), K S Ravindra, has tendered his resignation due to personal reasons. The company said Ravindra will step down from his role on or before 31 May, 2026, close of business hours.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Ventive Hospitality Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-ventive-hospitality-ltd-counter/1680130</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680130</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Chalet Hotels Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, Interglobe Aviation Ltd, KEI Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 02 March 2026.

Chalet Hotels Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, Interglobe Aviation Ltd, KEI Industries Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 02 March 2026. Ventive Hospitality Ltd saw volume of 3.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.79 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 61205 shares. The stock increased 1.49% to Rs.705.05. Volumes stood at 39349 shares in the last session. Chalet Hotels Ltd notched up volume of 5.36 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.51 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 97235 shares. The stock slipped 3.29% to Rs.781.55. Volumes stood at 1.05 lakh shares in the last session. Tejas Networks Ltd clocked volume of 1121.29 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.89 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 229.32 lakh shares. The stock gained 10.49% to Rs.481.55. Volumes stood at 1265.13 lakh shares in the last session. Interglobe Aviation Ltd registered volume of 27.13 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.03 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.73 lakh shares. The stock slipped 5.52% to Rs.4,560.90. Volumes stood at 11.99 lakh shares in the last session. KEI Industries Ltd registered volume of 12.57 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 3.96 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.17 lakh shares. The stock rose 1.39% to Rs.5,151.00. Volumes stood at 3.94 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VentiveHospitalityLtd_19888170_40188.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold soars above $5400 as war fears grip markets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-soars-above-5400-as-war-fears-grip-markets/1680129</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680129</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures surged nearly $200 to an intraday high of $5,434 per ounce on Monday, moving closer to record levels set in late January, as safe-haven demand spiked after joint strikes by the United States and Israel on Iran over the weekend.

Gold futures surged nearly $200 to an intraday high of $5,434 per ounce on Monday, moving closer to record levels set in late January, as safe-haven demand spiked after joint strikes by the United States and Israel on Iran over the weekend. The escalation intensified regional risks and disrupted shipping across the Gulf. Bullion rose more than 11% in February, marking its eight consecutive monthly gain—the longest streak since 1973—driven by heightened geopolitical uncertainty and shifting global alliances. In India, MCX gold futures climbed nearly 5% to Rs 169,294 per 10 grams. Silver futures also surged by more than 5% in the local market whereas internationally it rose by nearly 3% at $96 levels. Gains were partially capped by a firmer US dollar, with the dollar index rising above 98 to a five-week high as investors also sought refuge in the greenback amid the escalating conflict.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Mobilise App Lab logs in with a glitchy start]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-mobilise-app-lab-logs-in-with-a-glitchy-start/1680126</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680126</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 64.10, a discount of 19.88% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 64.10, a discount of 19.88% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 67.30 and a low of Rs 61.25. About 5.33 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Mobilise App Lab's IPO was subscribed 20.06 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it closed on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 75 to Rs 80 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 25,12,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for funding requirement in product development through talent hiring for the company, funding requirement toward business development and marketing activities aimed at driving the organization’s expansion across domestic markets, funding towards the infrastructure of the company and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Mobilise App Lab on 20 February 2026, raised Rs 5.70 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 7.13 lakh shares at Rs 80 per share to 3 anchor investors. Mobilise App Lab is an Indian SaaS-based IT solutions company founded in 2013 that provides digital platforms to streamline enterprise operations. It initially launched EDUPro ERP to help educational institutions manage admissions, attendance, fees, exams and academics. Later, it developed OpsSuite ERP, a computerized maintenance management system that enables businesses to manage assets, work orders, inventory, preventive maintenance and supplier operations. The platform is deployed across multiple Indian states and serves industries such as healthcare, food and beverages and facility management. The company had a total of 95 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 13.24 crore and net profit of Rs 4.01 crore for the period ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MobiliseAppLabLtd_95364701_95811.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Kiaasa Retail opens on a loose hem]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-kiaasa-retail-opens-on-a-loose-hem/1680124</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680124</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 123, a 3.15% discount to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 123, a 3.15% discount to the issue price. The stock was currently frozen at its lower limit of 5% to the listing price. The stock touched a high of Rs 123 and a low of Rs 116.85, with around 5.57 lakh shares changing hands on the counter. Kiaasa Retail's IPO was subscribed 1.99 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it closed on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 121 to Rs 127 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 54,90,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 50.22% from 71.84% pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for expenditure for opening new stores and for general corporate purpose. Ghaziabad-based Kiaasa Retail is an Indian women's fashion brand founded in 2018. It specializes in ethnic and fusion wear. The company operates over 100 stores across more than 80 cities in India, alongside a strong online presence. It offers a wide product range including kurtas, suit sets, lehengas, bottoms, dupattas and fashion accessories. Kiaasa runs its retail network through FOFO (Franchise Owned, Franchise Operated), COCO (Company Owned, Company Operated), and FICO (Franchise Invested, Company Operated) models to ensure operational efficiency and broader market reach. As of 28 February 2025, Kiaasa operated 113 brand outlets across 70 cities and employed 340 full-time staff. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 57.91 crore and net profit of Rs 6.63 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KiaasaRetailLtd_81195752_95381.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India AI Impact Summit 2026 Spurs $200B+ Investments]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-ai-impact-summit-2026-spurs-200b-investments/1680122</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680122</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The India AI Impact Summit 2026, held from 16–21 February 2026, marked a significant milestone in the global artificial intelligence landscape.

The India AI Impact Summit 2026, held from 16–21 February 2026, marked a significant milestone in the global artificial intelligence landscape. During the Summit, India achieved a Guinness World Record for the “Most pledges received for an AI responsibility campAIgn in 24 hours,” with over 2.5 lakh validated pledges reaffirming public commitment towards responsible AI adoption. A key announcement at the Summit was the expansion of India’s sovereign compute capacity. In addition to the 38,000+ GPUs already provisioned under the IndiaAI Mission, an additional 20,000 GPUs will be added in the coming weeks, further strengthening national AI infrastructure. The Summit catalysed significant investment commitments across the AI value chain - over USD 200 billion in AI-related investments are expected across infrastructure, foundation models, hardware and applications.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-3033203__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty tumble nearly 2%; European mrkt decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-tumble-nearly-2-european-mrkt-decline/1680120</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680120</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with sharp losses in the afternoon trade as investors turned risk-averse amid escalating geopolitical tensions following the US-Israel attacks on Iran.

The key equity benchmarks traded with sharp losses in the afternoon trade as investors turned risk-averse amid escalating geopolitical tensions following the US-Israel attacks on Iran. The Nifty slipped below the 24,700 mark, reflecting weak market sentiment. All the sectoral indices on the NSE were traded in red while auto, realty and oil & gas stocks emerging top laggards. At 13:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 1595.65 points or 1.97% to 79,690.25. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 497.10 points or 1.97% to 24,680.20. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index slumped 2.24% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tumbled 2.70%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 579 shares rose and 3,651 shares fell. A total of 183 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, sizzled 24.11% to 17.01. Gainers & Losers: Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL) (up 1.01%), Oil and Natural Gas Corporation of India (ONGC) (up 0.80%), Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 0.63%), Bharti Airtel (up 0.16%) and Hindalco Industries (up 0.10%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Larsen & Toubro (down 6.67%), Indigo Paints (down 5.90%), Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) (down 5.52%), Jio Financial Services (down 4.13%) and Asian Paints (down 3.71%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: KVS Castings rallied 6.43% after the company announced the commencement of commercial operations at its new manufacturing facility, Unit-2, from 2 March 2026. Zydus Lifesciences fell 2.46%. The company has received final approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg, and Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg. Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) dropped 3.36% after the company’s coking coal production fell 1.6% to 3.26 million tonnes in February 2026 compared with 3.31 million tonnes in February 2025. Paras Defence and Space Technologies rallied 8.65% after the company announced the incorporation of a new subsidiary, Paras Semiconductors. Monthly Auto Sales: Hyundai Motor India fell 1.44%. The company has recorded total sales of 66,134 units in February 2026, thereby registering a year-on-year growth of 12.6%. While domestic sales rose by 9.8% YoY to 52,407 units, exports increased by 24.8% to 13,727 units in February 2026. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles slipped 3.55%. The company has recorded total sales of 63,331 units in February 2026, registering a robust 35% YoY growth over 46,811 units in sold February 2025. Total electric vehicle (EV) sales rose 57% to 8,385 units in February 2026 from 5,343 units in the corresponding month last year, significantly outpacing the 35% growth recorded in overall passenger vehicle (PV) volumes. Eicher Motors dropped 2.92%. The company’s unlisted subsidiary, VE Commercial Vehicles (VECV), reported a 23.4% year-on-year jump in commercial vehicle (CV) sales to 9,986 units in February 2026. Ashok Leyland slumped 1.61%. The company reported a 24% jump in total sales (domestic & exports) to 22,157 units in February 2026, compared with 17,903 units sold in February 2025. Bajaj Auto fell 2.96%. The company reported 27% increase in total auto sales for February 2026, selling 4.48 lakh units as against 3.52 lakh units sold in February 2025. Escorts Kubota tumbled 4.04%. The company’s agri-machinery business division sales grew by 20.4% to 10,339 units in February 2026 as against 8,590 units sold in February 2025. TVS Motor Company shed 2.24%. The company registered sales of 529,308 units in February 2026, which is 31% higher as compared with the 403,976 units sold in February 2025. Hero MotoCorp declined 3.14%. The company has recorded a 44% year-on-year (YoY) rise in total two-wheeler dispatches in February 2026, selling 558,216 units during the month as compared with 388,068 units in February 2025. US-IRAN Conflict: The United States and Israel have launched major coordinated military strikes on Iran, marking a significant escalation in long-running Middle East tensions. On 1 March 2026, Iran launches missile and drone strikes on U.S. bases across six Middle Eastern countries amid escalating military tensions. Iran’s Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei was reportedly killed in the attacks, escalating tensions further. Iran named Ayatollah Alireza Arafi to its interim leadership council, which will be at the helm of the country following the killing of supreme leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, on Sunday. Global Markets: European and Asian markets traded lower on Monday after the United States and Israel launch their most ambitious attacks on Iran in decades, killing Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei. U.S. and Israeli strikes, and the Iranian retaliation, have sent shockwaves across the Middle East and through sectors from shipping to air travel to oil on warnings of rising energy costs and disruption to business in the Gulf, a strategic waterway and global trade hub. Most Gulf equities fell on Sunday, though Boursa Kuwait suspended trading and the UAE ordered its stock markets closed on Monday, a sign of the growing economic disruption sweeping the Gulf. Oil futures initially jumped 8% before trimming gains to about 4%. West Texas Intermediate futures last traded at $69.68, while Brent crude was at $76.13 per barrel. Gold futures jumped 2.3% as investors piled into the global safe haven. Stock futures tumbled in overnight trading after the weekend strikes in Iran. Futures on the Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 517 points, or 1%. S&P 500 futures lost 1%, and Nasdaq 100 futures declined a little more than 1%. On Friday, stocks saw a sharp sell-off after the latest producer price index data came in much hotter than expected, adding sticky inflation to a list of concerns that has caused market turbulence this month. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 521.28 points, or 1.05%, to close at 48,977.92. The S&P 500 closed down 0.43% at 6,878.88, while the Nasdaq Composite lost 0.92% to settle at 22,668.21. The S&P 500 and Nasdaq finished in the red for February amid growing fears about the impact of artificial intelligence on specific industries and the overall economy. Fueling the downbeat sentiment, January’s producer price index, a measure of wholesale inflation, showed a 0.5% increase for the month. Media reports had suggested that the headline reading could come in at 0.3%. The core PPI reading, which excludes food and energy prices, recorded a 0.8% gain, much more than the 0.3% rise that was widely reported in the media.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Escalating Middle East tensions lift safe-haven DXY to 5-week high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/escalating-middle-east-tensions-lift-safe-haven-dxy-to-5-week-high/1680119</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680119</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Dollar index hovers around 5-week high, lifted by safe haven demand amid escalating tensions in the Middle East.

Dollar index hovers around 5-week high, lifted by safe haven demand amid escalating tensions in the Middle East. The United States (US) and Israel launched coordinated strikes on Iran over the weekend, reportedly killing Iran’s Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei. Tehran responded with attacks on US assets in neighboring countries, including the United Arab Emirates (UAE), Bahrain, Kuwait, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Jordan, Iraq, and Syria. Meanwhile, in the US, Federal Reserve (Fed) Governor Mi Lan called for significant interest rate cuts as soon as possible, arguing that underlying price pressures remain subdued and that persistently high rates reflect distortions in inflation measurement. The dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 98.37, up close to 1% and at its highest levels since January 23. Among basket currencies, EUR/USD and GBP/USD are both plunging by near 1%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-exchange-rate-544949__340_commodities.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BSE SME Accord Transformer & Switchgear switches on with a premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bse-sme-accord-transformer-switchgear-switches-on-with-a-premium/1680121</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680121</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip listed at Rs 50, a 8.70% premium to the issue price.

The scrip listed at Rs 50, a 8.70% premium to the issue price. The stock was currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% to the listing price. The stock touched a high of Rs 52.50 and a low of Rs 47.50, with around 29.07 shares changing hands on the counter. Accord Transformer & Switchgear's IPO was subscribed 332.11 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it closed on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 43 to Rs 46 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 55,62,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilise the net proceeds for capital expenditure towards purchase of machinery and equipment, funding of the working capital requirement of the company and general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Accord Transformer & Switchgear on 20 February 2026, raised Rs 7.29 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 15.84 lakh shares at Rs 46 each to 6 anchor investors. Accord Transformer & Switchgear is engaged in the design, engineering, manufacturing, and supply of a wide range of transformers, control panels and distribution equipment, catering to both standard and customised requirements across power transmission and distribution, renewable energy, industrial applications, infrastructure, and EV charging networks. With two manufacturing facilities in Rajasthan, supported by an office in Gurugram, the company operates with advanced machinery, in-house testing laboratories, and an integrated management system. As of 31st December 2025, the company had 114 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 45.21 crore and net profit of Rs 2.91 crore for the period ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ACCORDTRANSFORMERSWITCHGEARLIMITED_32333832_95953.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-bank-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1680114</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680114</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

HDFC Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 877.3, down 1.18% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.9% on the day, quoting at 24699.2. The Sensex is at 79712.32, down 1.94%.HDFC Bank Ltd has lost around 7.53% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which HDFC Bank Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.7% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60529, down 1.5% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 167.4 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 285.05 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 883.5, down 1.17% on the day. HDFC Bank Ltd jumped 3.12% in last one year as compared to a 11.66% rally in NIFTY and a 23.91% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 18.69 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HDFCBank_24534281400_4987.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-bank-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1680115</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680115</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 409.7, down 1.32% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.9% on the day, quoting at 24699.2. The Sensex is at 79712.32, down 1.94%.Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd has eased around 1.47% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.7% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60529, down 1.5% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 83.59 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 154.19 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 411.9, down 1.36% on the day. Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd jumped 6.99% in last one year as compared to a 11.66% rally in NIFTY and a 23.91% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 30.51 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KotakMahBank_47062626511_2330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NLC India Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nlc-india-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1680116</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680116</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NLC India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

NLC India Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 250.65, down 3.61% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.9% on the day, quoting at 24699.2. The Sensex is at 79712.32, down 1.94%.NLC India Ltd has lost around 0.34% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which NLC India Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 1.4% in last one month and is currently quoting at 37045.2, down 2.4% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 7.21 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 15.5 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 18.61 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NLCIndia_49674266520_2303.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Finance Ltd down for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-finance-ltd-down-for-fifth-straight-session/1680117</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680117</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bajaj Finance Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Bajaj Finance Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 973.7, down 2.23% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.9% on the day, quoting at 24699.2. The Sensex is at 79712.32, down 1.94%.Bajaj Finance Ltd has added around 0.96% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which Bajaj Finance Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.97% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27869.75, down 1.66% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 54.07 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 84.16 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 976.2, down 2.5% on the day. Bajaj Finance Ltd jumped 12.85% in last one year as compared to a 11.66% rally in NIFTY and a 19.4% spurt in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 38.58 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajFin_55786316_3722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd eases for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nazara-technologies-ltd-eases-for-fifth-straight-session/1680118</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680118</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nazara Technologies Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Nazara Technologies Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 255.55, down 3.49% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.9% on the day, quoting at 24699.2. The Sensex is at 79711.9, down 1.94%.Nazara Technologies Ltd has eased around 10.21% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Nazara Technologies Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 0.01% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1416.15, down 2.45% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.8 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 21.32 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 401.59 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NazaraTechnologies_39505358.8300902_33311.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd spurts 0.61%, gains for five straight sessions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tube-investments-of-india-ltd-spurts-061-gains-for-five-straight-sessions/1680110</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680110</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tube Investments of India Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row.

Tube Investments of India Ltd is up for a fifth straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 2770.1, up 0.61% on the day as on 12:44 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 1.95% on the day, quoting at 24687.9. The Sensex is at 79659.36, down 2%. Tube Investments of India Ltd has risen around 10.66% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Tube Investments of India Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 0.86% in last one month and is currently quoting at 28158.85, down 3.17% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 10.33 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 7.88 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark March futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2772.5, up 0.52% on the day. Tube Investments of India Ltd is up 4.92% in last one year as compared to a 11.61% gain in NIFTY and a 32.75% gain in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 38.53 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TubeInvestmentsofIndiaLtd_81529932771_40963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Atul Auto reports 18% YoY increase in February’26 sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/atul-auto-reports-18-yoy-increase-in-february26-sales/1680111</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680111</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s domestic sales increased 24.58% to 2,940 units in February 2026, compared to 2,360 units posted in February 2025.

The company’s domestic sales increased 24.58% to 2,940 units in February 2026, compared to 2,360 units posted in February 2025. Atul Auto is a leading three-wheeler manufacturing company in Rajkot, Gujarat, India. It has a complete range of 3-wheeler products across the fuel range: diesel, petrol, CNG, LPG, and electric. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 98.06% to Rs 15.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7.75 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations grew by 18.39% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 230.86 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter slipped 3.93% to Rs 476 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AtulAuto_3226523977_14817.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>