<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sky Gold and Diamonds rallies after Q3 PAT soars 120% YoY]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sky-gold-and-diamonds-rallies-after-q3-pat-soars-120-yoy/1674028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674028</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 80.54 crore in Q3 FY26, up 120.42% YoY from Rs 36.54 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 80.54 crore in Q3 FY26, up 120.42% YoY from Rs 36.54 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, PAT rose 20.23% from Rs 66.99 crore in Q2 FY26. Net sales jumped 77.13% YoY to Rs 1,767.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 997.97 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue increased 19.08% from Rs 1,484.46 crore. Profit before tax more than doubled to Rs 106.13 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 115.01% YoY increase over Rs 49.36 crore in Q3 FY25. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PBT rose 20.74% from Rs 87.90 crore. Total expenditure rose 74.9% YoY to Rs 1,645.29 crore. Raw material consumption increased 56.17% YoY to Rs 1,624.94 crore, while employee expenses rose 88.93% YoY to Rs 15.19 crore. Interest cost climbed 73.75% YoY to Rs 21.18 crore, while depreciation declined 12.24% YoY to Rs 2.51 crore. Sky Gold and Diamonds is one of India's fastest-growing B2B jewellery manufacturers, specialising in lightweight, design-led and studded jewellery.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SkyGold_39345065_73265.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude oil stays slippery, WTI futures linger around $63 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-oil-stays-slippery-wti-futures-linger-around-63-per-barrel/1674027</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674027</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Crude oil futures eased on Monday as diplomatic talks between the US and Iran alleviated near-term supply concerns.

Crude oil futures eased on Monday as diplomatic talks between the US and Iran alleviated near-term supply concerns. The discussions, held in Oman on Friday, were described by Tehran as “a step forward,” signaling potential de-escalation in tensions over Iran’s nuclear program. Despite gains earlier in 2026 driven by geopolitical risks and supply disruptions, prices pulled back last week amid progress in negotiations. Investors are now awaiting this week’s OPEC+ and IEA reports for further guidance on global oil supply and market direction, while keeping an eye on upcoming US-Iran and US-Israel meetings. The WTI Crude oil futures are currently trading at $63.06 per barrel, down 0.72% on the day. Oil lost around 2.50% in last week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/oil-refinery-chemical-petrochemical-plant-picture-id5822566_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Suprajit Engg slides after Q3 PAT drop 63% YoY to Rs 13 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/suprajit-engg-slides-after-q3-pat-drop-63-yoy-to-rs-13-cr/1674026</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674026</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax tanked 32.31% year on year to Rs 40.80 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax tanked 32.31% year on year to Rs 40.80 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) edged up 0.04% year-on-year to Rs 111.9 crore in Q3 FY26, while the EBITDA margin slipped to 13% from 14.3% in the same quarter last year. Total expenses jumped 19.94% to Rs 9,41.15 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 784.62 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses were at Rs 224.68 crore (up 22.78% YoY), while the cost of material consumed stood at Rs 452.84 crore (up 4.25% YoY) during the period under review. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs 1.50 (150%) per equity share of face value Re. 1 each for FY26 and fixed Friday, February 13, 2026, as the record date for the payment of the interim dividend. Suprajit Engineering is engaged in the business of manufacturing auto components consisting mainly of control cables, speedo cables, auto lamps, and other components for automobiles and caters to both domestic and international markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SuprajitEngg_27714167571_6045.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold gains steam as investors brace for jobs and CPI reports]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-gains-steam-as-investors-brace-for-jobs-and-cpi-reports/1674024</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674024</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold surged more than 1% in the electronic trades on Monday, rising above $5,050 per ounce in electronic trading as investors positioned for key US economic data later this week.

Gold surged more than 1% in the electronic trades on Monday, rising above $5,050 per ounce in electronic trading as investors positioned for key US economic data later this week. A softer US dollar, which fell 0.3% to 97.22, added support to the yellow metal ahead of the January jobs report, December retail sales, and the delayed CPI release. Markets currently anticipate the Federal Reserve will keep interest rates steady in March, with potential cuts later in the year. On the MCX, April gold futures rose 1.3% to Rs 157,450 per 10 grams, while March silver futures jumped nearly 5% to Rs 260,750 per kg. Traders are closely monitoring these data points for clues on inflation and the labor market, which could shape the Fed’s policy decisions. Safe-haven demand remains a key driver, as geopolitical and economic uncertainties continue to influence investor sentiment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-shelter-finance-corporation-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1674022</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674022</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Concord Biotech Ltd, REC Ltd, Westlife Foodworld Ltd and Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 February 2026.

Concord Biotech Ltd, REC Ltd, Westlife Foodworld Ltd and Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 February 2026. India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd lost 5.41% to Rs 746.85 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 80363 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 39433 shares in the past one month. Concord Biotech Ltd crashed 4.54% to Rs 1278.5. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 97986 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13484 shares in the past one month. REC Ltd tumbled 3.42% to Rs 359.75. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 14.12 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.92 lakh shares in the past one month. Westlife Foodworld Ltd corrected 3.37% to Rs 524. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 26416 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.44 lakh shares in the past one month. Caplin Point Laboratories Ltd plummeted 3.33% to Rs 1765. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 13073 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4450 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndiaShelterFinanceCorporationLtd_79307332_48455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Man Industries surges after strong Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/man-industries-surges-after-strong-q3-performance/1674020</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674020</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[EBITDA improved by 61.4% to Rs 136 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 84 crore in Q3 FY25.

EBITDA improved by 61.4% to Rs 136 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 84 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin was 16.2% in Q3 FY26, reflecting the highest consolidated quarterly margin achieved by the company to date. This strong performance was driven by a favourable product and geographic mix. The company maintained a net cash position of around Rs 38 crore as of 31 December 2025, reflecting a healthy balance sheet. The company’s executable order book stood at around Rs 4,000 crore, providing healthy revenue visibility over the next 6–12 months and underpinning growth momentum in the coming quarters. Man Industries’ strategic capacity expansion initiatives in Saudi Arabia and Jammu are progressing as planned, with key civil works and major equipment installations largely completed. The Saudi facility is expected to commence commercial production by Q1 FY27, strengthening the company’s regional footprint, while the Jammu facility remains on track for commissioning by Q2 FY27. The company added that the outlook for the year remains strong, supported by steady order execution and healthy order inflows, and reiterated its full-year revenue guidance of Rs 3,600–3,700 crore, implying 15–20% year-on-year growth in its core business. Nikhil Mansukhani, managing director, MAN Industries (India), said, "We are pleased to report our highest-ever quarterly EBITDA margins, reflecting the strength of our strategy, disciplined execution, and continued focus on operational efficiency. With a record order book, steady progress on our capacity expansions in Saudi Arabia and Jammu, and an expanding global footprint, we are well positioned for the next phase of growth. Our emphasis on value-added products, prudent capital allocation, and customer diversification will continue to support sustainable performance and strengthen our leadership in the global line pipe industry.” Man Industries is a leading manufacturer and exporter of large-diameter carbon steel line pipes for various high-pressure transmission applications for gas, crude oil, petrochemical products, and potable water.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ManInds_64315062574_1369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE PAT rises 15% QoQ to Rs 2,408 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-pat-rises-15-qoq-to-rs-2408-crore/1674021</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674021</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 2,408 crore in Q3 FY26, up 15% QoQ from Rs 2,098 crore in Q2 FY26, but down 37% YoY compared with Rs 3,834 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, profit after tax stood at Rs 2,408 crore in Q3 FY26, up 15% QoQ from Rs 2,098 crore in Q2 FY26, but down 37% YoY compared with Rs 3,834 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit after tax margin improved to 54% in Q3 FY26 from 39% in Q2 FY26, though lower than 64% in Q3 FY25. Profit on sale of investment in associates was nil during the quarter, compared with Rs 1,201 crore in Q2 FY26 and Rs 1,155 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income came in at Rs 4,395 crore in Q3 FY26, rising 6% QoQ from Rs 4,160 crore in Q2 FY26, but declining 9% YoY from Rs 4,807 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 3,925 crore, up 7% QoQ, while falling 10% YoY. Operating EBITDA surged 92% QoQ to Rs 2,851 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,484 crore in the previous quarter. On a year-on-year basis, EBITDA declined 16% from Rs 3,398 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA margin improved sharply to 73% in Q3 FY26 from 40% in Q2 FY26, though lower than 78% reported a year ago. Revenue from transaction charges stood at Rs 3,033 crore in Q3 FY26, registering 9% QoQ growth, led by higher volumes across the equity cash market and derivatives segments. Revenue from data feed and terminal services came in at Rs 121 crore, up 5% QoQ, while revenue from listing services rose 25% QoQ to Rs 111 crore, reflecting increased listing-related activity. Total expenses declined sharply to Rs 1,234 crore in Q3 FY26, translating into a 48% QoQ decline, while increasing 14% YoY. In Q3FY26, the cash market trading segment recorded an average daily traded volume (ADTVs) of Rs 99,023 crore (up by 3% QoQ). The ADTV for equity futures segment in Q3FY26 stood at Rs 1,51,744 crore (up by 8% QoQ); while the ADTV for equity options (premium value) stood at Rs 53,248 crore (up by 15% QoQ). National Stock Exchange of India, which began operations in 1994, was the country’s first exchange to introduce electronic trading and has consistently ranked as India’s largest exchange by equity turnover since 1995, based on SEBI data. It operates a fully integrated business model spanning listings, trading, clearing and settlement, indices, market data, technology solutions and financial education, while overseeing regulatory compliance of market participants. Globally, NSE was the world’s largest derivatives exchange by trading volume in calendar year 2024 and ranked second worldwide in the equity segment by number of trades.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India secured preferential access to US$30 trillion US market, says government]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-secured-preferential-access-to-us30-trillion-us-market-says-government/1674019</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674019</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[A latest government update has noted that India secured preferential access to a USD 30 trillion US market following the US-India trade deal framework.

A latest government update has noted that India secured preferential access to a USD 30 trillion US market following the US-India trade deal framework. Textiles & apparel gain tariff cuts from 50% to 18%, with silk securing 0% duty access in a USD 113 billion U.S. market. Machinery exports see tariffs reduced to 18%, opening opportunities in a USD 477 billion U.S. market· USD 1.36 billion of Indian agricultural exports receive zero additional US duty access. Key products including spices, tea, coffee, fruits, nuts and processed foods gain zero-duty treatment while highly sensitive sectors such as dairy, meat, poultry and cereals remain fully protected. The India–U.S. Bilateral Trade Agreement marks a major milestone in India’s global trade engagement, securing sustained preferential access for Indian exports in the U.S. market valued at over $30 trillion. The agreement delivers comprehensive tariff rationalisation, zero-duty access across large product categories, enhanced digital and technology cooperation, and a carefully calibrated framework to safeguard India’s farmers, MSMEs and domestic industry. With India’s total exports to the United States standing at USD 86.35 billion in 2024, the agreement significantly enhances competitive access across key sectors including textiles, leather, gems and jewellery, agriculture, machinery, home décor, pharmaceuticals, and technology-driven industries. India’s export base of USD 86.35 billion to the United States in 2024 now benefits from major tariff restructuring. Reciprocal Tariffs (RT) were earlier as high as 50% on several Indian products. These have now been substantially reduced. Of the total exports, USD 40.96 billion were subject to Reciprocal Tariffs. Under the agreement, tariffs on USD 30.94 billion of these exports have been reduced from 50% to 18%, while tariffs on another USD 10.03 billion have been reduced from 50% to zero. This means a substantial share of Indian goods entering the U.S. market will now face either sharply lower tariffs or completely duty-free access, significantly improving price competitiveness. Additional structural duty relief ensures zero reciprocal duty access for USD 1.04 billion under the exemption category. Within this, agricultural products valued at USD 1.035 billion have been assured zero Reciprocal Tariff by the United States. This provides stability and predictability for Indian agricultural exporters and ensures that key farm products continue to enjoy uninterrupted market access. Additional Structural Duty Relief assures zero reciprocal duty for USD 28.30 billion under Section 232 (end-use basis). For these products, additional duties that earlier could go up to 50% have been reduced to zero. The agreement creates a clear tariff differential in favour of India. While duties on Indian products have been lowered, several competing suppliers continue to face elevated tariffs in the US market, including China (35%), Vietnam (20%), Bangladesh (20%), Malaysia (19%), Indonesia (19%), Philippines (19%), Cambodia (19%) and Thailand (19%).

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/hands-people-woman-working_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Modis Navnirman Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/modis-navnirman-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1674017</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674017</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro Pratik Sales Ltd, Manugraph India Ltd, Vindhya Telelinks Ltd and BN Agrochem Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 February 2026.

Euro Pratik Sales Ltd, Manugraph India Ltd, Vindhya Telelinks Ltd and BN Agrochem Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 February 2026. Modis Navnirman Ltd lost 14.80% to Rs 338 at 14:19 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 470 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 831 shares in the past one month. Euro Pratik Sales Ltd tumbled 12.99% to Rs 244.25. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 50726 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 52058 shares in the past one month. Manugraph India Ltd crashed 8.97% to Rs 14.2. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 445 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 532 shares in the past one month. Vindhya Telelinks Ltd corrected 7.41% to Rs 1155. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2856 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 624 shares in the past one month. BN Agrochem Ltd fell 6.48% to Rs 270.05. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 8627 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2751 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ModisNavnirman_97754619_76794.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Goldiam International jumps after Q3 PAT spurts 37% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/goldiam-international-jumps-after-q3-pat-spurts-37-yoy/1674015</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674015</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit stood at Rs 68.4 crore in Q3 FY26, up 37% YoY from Rs 49.8 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, the company's net profit stood at Rs 68.4 crore in Q3 FY26, up 37% YoY from Rs 49.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 18% YoY to Rs 339.7 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 288 crore in the year-ago quarter, aided by strong export demand despite tariff-related concerns. EBITDA stood at Rs 90.8 crore in Q3 FY26, up 28.2% YoY from Rs 70.8 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin expanded to 26.7%, compared with 24.6% a year ago. PAT margin improved to 20.1% from 17.3% in the corresponding quarter last year. The board proposed an interim dividend of Rs 2.75 per share. Cash and cash equivalents, including investments, stood at Rs 504.1 crore as of 31 December 2025, underscoring a strong liquidity position. Lab-grown diamond jewellery exports contributed 90.5% to overall export sales in Q3 FY26, up sharply from 80% in Q3 FY25. Online revenue contribution also rose meaningfully, accounting for 31.6% of total revenue during the quarter. Around 65% of finished jewellery inventory as of 31 December 2025 was held with customers for sale in subsequent months. The order book stood at approximately Rs 180 crore. During Q3 FY26, ORIGEM, Goldiam’s B2C lab-grown diamond jewellery brand, recorded revenue of Rs 5.65 crore. Around 6% of total finished inventory was held under ORIGEM. During the quarter, the company signed LOIs for 20 additional ORIGEM stores. Goldiam plans to open 12-14 new stores by March 2026, taking the total store count to 24-26 by the end of FY26, with another 15 stores planned in the first half of the next financial year. Executive chairman Rashesh Bhansali said the company’s B2B jewellery export business continues to deliver consistent growth and margins, supported by higher wallet share from existing customers, addition of new large-format US retailers, and expansion into Europe, the Middle East and Australia. Managing director Anmol Bhansali said ORIGEM is seeing strong traction, especially in premium malls, and that the national store rollout strategy is gaining momentum. Goldiam International is an integrated manufacturer and exporter of fine diamond jewellery, supplying leading retailers and wholesalers primarily in the US. The company recently made a foray into India retail for lab grown diamond jewellery under the brand name ORIGEM.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GoldiamIntl_52606926993_4545.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty continues to trade in positive terrain]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-continues-to-trade-in-positive-terrain/1674014</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674014</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks continued to trade with major gains in the mid-afternoon trade buoyed by optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues.

The domestic equity benchmarks continued to trade with major gains in the mid-afternoon trade buoyed by optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues. Sentiments further lifted by key agreements signed between India-Malaysia. Investors will monitor ongoing Q3 earnings season. The Nifty traded above the 25,850 mark. Consumer durables shares rallied for second consecutive trading session. At 14:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 461.13 points or 0.55% to 84,041.53. The Nifty 50 index added 168.40 points or 0.66% to 25,861.10. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 1.50% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 2.27%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,036 shares rose and 1,208 shares fell. A total of 188 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 1.52% to 12.12. India-Malaysia sign key agreements Prime Minister (PM) Narendra Modi visited Malaysia from 7 February to 8 February 2026 and held bilateral talks with Malaysian PM Anwar Ibrahim. The wide-ranging talks during the two-day official visit, marked a significant step in strengthening the Comprehensive Strategic Partnership between India and Malaysia. India and Malaysia has signed 11 Memorandums of Understanding (MoUs) and exchanged several bilateral documents across a broad range of sectors during Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s two-day official visit to Kuala Lumpur. The agreements, signed in the presence of PM Modi and his Malaysian counterpart Anwar Ibrahim following delegation-level talks, span trade and investment, semiconductors, digital economy, healthcare, security cooperation and peacekeeping, officials said. The two leaders launched Malaysia-India Digital Council (MLDC) and backed NPCI–PayNet payment link, paving way to introduce India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) system in Malaysia. This initiative will simplify cross-border payments for businesses and travellers and strengthen financial ties between the two economies. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index climbed 3.25% to 37,621.10. The Index jumped 4.24% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Kalyan Jewellers India (up 13.79%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (up 6.52%), Whirlpool of India (up 5.19%), Amber Enterprises India (up 4.98%) and Voltas (up 4.46%), Bata India (up 3.46%), Blue Star (up 2.9%), Dixon Technologies (India) (up 2.52%), Titan Company (up 2.23%) and V-Guard Industries (up 2.18%) surged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.33% to 6.755 compared with previous session close of 6.733. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6700 compared with its close of 90.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement advanced 1.35% to Rs 157,543. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.25% to 97.39. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.59% to 4.228. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement declined 60 cents or 0.88% to $67.45 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Axiscades Technologies hit the upper circuit of 5% after its subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, secured a domestic supply order worth around Rs 80 crore from Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL). Brahmaputra Infrastructure surged 7% after the company has received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from the North Frontier Railway (NF Railway), Maligaon, Assam, for the construction of a Road Over Bridge (RoB) project. Bajel Projects rallied 5.49% after the company secured an ultra-mega order from Power Grid Corporation of India (PGCIL) through its special purpose vehicle Vindhyachal Varanasi Transmission.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Shipping Corporation of India Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-shipping-corporation-of-india-ltd-counter/1674012</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674012</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, JK Tyre & Industries Ltd, IFCI Ltd, Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 09 February 2026.

Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, JK Tyre & Industries Ltd, IFCI Ltd, Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 09 February 2026. Shipping Corporation of India Ltd saw volume of 621.25 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 21.38 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 29.06 lakh shares. The stock increased 18.67% to Rs.263.22. Volumes stood at 10.24 lakh shares in the last session. Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd saw volume of 545.88 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.01 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 60.56 lakh shares. The stock increased 13.49% to Rs.431.55. Volumes stood at 51.08 lakh shares in the last session. JK Tyre & Industries Ltd clocked volume of 54.01 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.46 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 9.89 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.77% to Rs.567.30. Volumes stood at 11.81 lakh shares in the last session. IFCI Ltd witnessed volume of 1685.74 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.42 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 310.87 lakh shares. The stock increased 8.49% to Rs.65.29. Volumes stood at 256.7 lakh shares in the last session. Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd recorded volume of 171.67 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.17 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 33.21 lakh shares. The stock gained 12.78% to Rs.279.67. Volumes stood at 19.31 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SCI_79641479387_2347.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tea exports spike 9.5% in 2025, output gains 5%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tea-exports-spike-95-in-2025-output-gains-5/1674009</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674009</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[A latest update from Tea Board of India showed that tea production has increased marginally in the past year, as compared to that of 2024.

A latest update from Tea Board of India showed that tea production has increased marginally in the past year, as compared to that of 2024. Domestic tea production in 2025 (Jan-Dec) revealed that the country as a whole produced 1369.98 million kg (mkg) of tea, as compared to 1303.53 mkg in 2024. This reflects a rise of 66.45 mkg or 5% in 2025. While production edged higher, India’s tea exports also climbed to a record high in 2025, buoyed by a sharp rise in shipments to Iraq and China, even as geopolitical trade currents remain unsettled. Total Tea exports rose by 9.5% to 280.4 mkg last year, compared with 256.17 mkg in 2024, despite a temporary blip in the US due to elevated tariffs. Iraq emerged as the top destination for the Indian variety. In terms of earnings, unit prices edged up sharply on weakness in Indian Rupee. The per kg export price stood at Rs 302.73 in 2025, up 8.20% on year, pushing up the total export earnings by 18.43% to Rs 8488 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/sugar-please-1481728_silver.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[G R Infra gains as Q3 PAT jumps 38% YoY to Rs 232 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/g-r-infra-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-38-yoy-to-rs-232-cr/1674007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674007</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 35.91% YoY to Rs 2,039.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 35.91% YoY to Rs 2,039.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 314.93 crore in Q3 FY26, up 35.38% as against Rs 232.62 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 36.19% to Rs 1,893.28 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,390.13 crore in Q3 FY25. Employee benefit expenses were at Rs 169.24 crore (up 21.13% YoY), while the cost of material consumed stood at Rs 113.59 crore (up 24.07% YoY) during the period under review. On a consolidated basis, the company’s net profit fell 1.46% to Rs 258.74 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 262.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue form operations jumped 36.22% year on year to Rs 2,308.27 crore in Q3 FY26. On a segmental revenue basis, revenue from build, operate, and transfer (BOT)/annuity projects fell 6.50% YoY to Rs 1,245.75 crore, while revenue from engineering, procurement, and construction zoomed 342.76% YoY to Rs 920.56 crore in Q3 FY26. GR Infraprojects is engaged in the construction of infrastructure facilities on an engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) and build, operate, and transfer (BOT) basis.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GRInfraprojectsLtd_18239026_35408.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade with significant gains; European mrkt advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-with-significant-gains-european-mrkt-advance/1674000</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674000</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major gains in the afternoon trade buoyed by optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with major gains in the afternoon trade buoyed by optimism over the recently concluded India-US trade agreement and positive global cues. Sentiments further lifted by key agreements signed between India-Malaysia. Investors will monitor ongoing Q3 earnings season. The Nifty traded near the 25,850 mark. All the sectoral indices on the NSE were traded in green with Media, PSU Bank and consumer durables shares leading the rally. At 13:25 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 423.23 points or 0.51% to 84,000.72. The Nifty 50 index added 149.70 points or 0.58% to 25,844.35. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 1.40% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 2.06%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,034 shares rose and 1,166 shares fell. A total of 188 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rose 1.71% to 12.15. Gainers & Losers: State Bank of India (up 6.89%), Shirram Finance (up 4.02%), Grasim Industries (up2.89%), Tata Steel (up 2.53%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 2.14%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Max Healthcare (down 1.50%), ICICI Bank (down 1%), Infosys (down 0.73%), ITC (down 0.68%) and HDFC Bank (down 0.48%) were the major Nifty50 losers. State Bank of India has rallied 6.89% after the bank reported 24.49% jump in net profit to Rs 21,028 crore on a 9.69% increase in total income to Rs 1,40,915 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Steel added 2.53% after the steelmaker reported a sharp 723.14% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 2688.70 crore on 6.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 56,646.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. India-Malaysia sign key agreements Prime Minister (PM) Narendra Modi visited Malaysia from 7 February to 8 February 2026 and held bilateral talks with Malaysian PM Anwar Ibrahim. The wide-ranging talks during the two-day official visit, marked a significant step in strengthening the Comprehensive Strategic Partnership between India and Malaysia. India and Malaysia has signed 11 Memorandums of Understanding (MoUs) and exchanged several bilateral documents across a broad range of sectors during Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s two-day official visit to Kuala Lumpur. The agreements, signed in the presence of PM Modi and his Malaysian counterpart Anwar Ibrahim following delegation-level talks, span trade and investment, semiconductors, digital economy, healthcare, security cooperation and peacekeeping, officials said. The two leaders launched Malaysia-India Digital Council (MLDC) and backed NPCI–PayNet payment link, paving way to introduce India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) system in Malaysia. This initiative will simplify cross-border payments for businesses and travellers and strengthen financial ties between the two economies. Stocks in Spotlight: Hi-Tech Pipes added 5.40% after the company announced the commencement of commercial production at its Sikandrabad, Unit-III (Uttar Pradesh) greenfield manufacturing facility. The Sikandrabad facility hosts a production capacity of 0.12 million tons. It would specialise in the production on ERW pipes and hollow sections. The company has reported 14.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.38 crore despite a 24.6% increase in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,069.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Ganesha Ecosphere surged 17.60% after the company delivered a decisive sequential recovery in Q3 FY26. On a sequential basis, Ganesha Ecosphere returned to profitability in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit at Rs 4.75 crore compared with a loss of Rs 0.50 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations eased 1.7% QoQ to Rs 357.22 crore. On a year-on-year basis, consolidated net profit declined 84% YoY from Rs 29.71 crore in Q3 FY25, while revenue from operations fell 10.2% YoY from Rs 397.80 crore. Shipping Corporation of India soared 16.46% after the company reported a 436.24% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 404.97 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 75.52 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 22.5% year-on-year to Rs 1,611.67 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Kalyan Jewellers India zoomed 12.82% after its consolidated net profit surged 90.24% to Rs 416.29 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by a 42.17% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 10,343.4 crore compared to the same period last year. JK Tyre & Industries rallied 5.46% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 294.96% to Rs 207.75 crore on a 14.95% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 4,222.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ram Ratna Wires rallied 9.83% after the company reported a 73.1% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 31.28 crore on 43.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,277.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atul Auto surged 10.23% after the company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 98.06% to Rs 15.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7.75 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations grew by 18.39% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 230.86 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: European market advanced as investors are awaited for the earnings report from UniCredit. Asian markets advanced on Monday, led by a surge in Japanese stocks following Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi’s historic landslide election victory. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party captured a two-thirds supermajority in the 465-seat lower house, public broadcaster NHK reported. A decisive win for Takaichi could be the “best outcome” for markets over the medium term, as strategic investments and tax reform bolster equities, said Sree Kochugovindan, media report said. Japanese stocks have hit several highs over the past few months, driven by the so-called 'Takaichi trade' as markets expect the prime minister’s economic policies — seen as growth‑focused continuation of Abenomics — to boost equities, while weakening the yen as she pushes for a looser monetary policy and higher government spending. U.S. President Donald Trump congratulated Takaichi on her victory in a TruthSocial post. Last Friday in the U.S., stocks surged as tech names recovered following several days of heavy selling in the sector and bitcoin rebounded following a rout that took the popular cryptocurrency down more than 50% from its high in October last year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 1,206.95 points, or 2.47%, closing at 50,115.67. Friday marked the first time the Dow exceeded the 50,000 level. The S&P 500 jumped 1.97% and ended at 6,932.30, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 2.18% to 23,031.21. With those moves, the S&P 500 climbed back into the green for 2026. Even with Friday’s rise, the S&P 500 posted a 0.1% decline for the week, while the Nasdaq fell 1.8% on the week. The 30-stock Dow rose 2.5% week to date, benefiting from some rotation into some economically cyclical stocks even as the overall market was weighed down by tech selling.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[State Bank of India surges after Q3 PAT rises over 24% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/state-bank-of-india-surges-after-q3-pat-rises-over-24-yoy-in-q3/1674002</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674002</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 45,190 crore, up 9.04% YoY.

Net interest income for the period under review was Rs 45,190 crore, up 9.04% YoY. Net interest margin was 3.12% for the December 2025 period as against 3.15% for the December 2024 period. The bank has received a one-time dividend income of nearly Rs 2,200 crore from SBI Mutual Fund during the quarter, along with treasury gains of approximately Rs 3,280 crore. Operating expenses rose by 21.08% to Rs 30,687 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 28,935 crore in the December 2024 quarter. Accordingly, the public sector bank registered an operating profit of Rs 32,862 crore in Q3 FY26, up 39.54% YoY. Total provisions expanded by 77.71% to Rs 11,834 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6,659 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 249 crore, up by 22% from Rs 204 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross NPAs declined to 1.57% as of 31 December 2025, from 2.07% as of 31 December 2024. Net NPAs fell to 0.39% as of 31 December 2025 from 0.53% as of 31 December 2024. The provision coverage ratio (PCR) (including AUCA) as on 31 December 2025 was at 92.37%. AUCA or advance under collection account (AUCA) is a dummy account maintained by SBI in which written off loan accounts are transferred. The bank had a deposit base of Rs 57,01,309 crore as on 31 December 2025, up 9.02% YoY. Gross advances of the bank as on 31 December 2025 were Rs 46,83,508 crore, up 15.14% YoY. Capital adequacy ratio (CAR) as at the end of Q3 FY26 stood at 14.04%. The bank’s management has reportedly guided for maintaining domestic NIMs above 3% and expects cost-to-income ratio to stay around 50%. Following the earnings announcement, domestic brokerages have reportedly raised their target prices for this stock. A domestic research house has reportedly maintained its ‘buy’ rating with a revised target of Rs 1,200 as against the previous target of Rs 1,035, valuing the bank at 1.5x September 2027 adjusted book value. Another domestic brokerage has lifted its target to Rs 1,300 from Rs 1,035 earlier, citing the bank’s raised credit growth guidance of 13% to 15% for FY26. State Bank of India is engaged in providing a wide range of products and services to individuals, commercial enterprises, large corporates, public bodies, and institutional customers. The Government of India held 55.50% stake in the bank as on 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StBkofIndia_57185891_1375.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axiscades Technologies hits the roof after arm bags Rs 80-cr HAL order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axiscades-technologies-hits-the-roof-after-arm-bags-rs-80-cr-hal-order/1673991</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673991</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order entails the supply of mission computers and smart display units and will be executed over multiple years.

The order entails the supply of mission computers and smart display units and will be executed over multiple years. As per the company’s disclosure, the contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related-party transactions. Bengaluru-based Axiscades Technologies is an end-to-end technology and product engineering company operating across aerospace, defence and ESAI domains, with capabilities spanning the full product development lifecycle. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 88.82% year-on-year to Rs 23.13 crore in Q2 FY26 from Rs 12.25 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 12.97% YoY to Rs 299.06 crore. In dollar terms, revenue stood at $31.6 million, up 9.3% YoY.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AXISCADESEngg_38496178544_21304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-state-petronet-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1673983</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673983</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat State Petronet Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Gujarat State Petronet Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 313.5, up 2.37% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.54% on the day, quoting at 25832.9. The Sensex is at 83979.52, up 0.48%. Gujarat State Petronet Ltd has risen around 2.32% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Gujarat State Petronet Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 6.09% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36451.7, up 0.34% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 4.58 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.98 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 24.32 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujStPetronet_95223652929_24065.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1673984</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673984</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy India Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Hitachi Energy India Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 22368, up 2.27% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.54% on the day, quoting at 25832.9. The Sensex is at 83979.52, up 0.48%. Hitachi Energy India Ltd has gained around 28.34% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Hitachi Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 6.09% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36451.7, up 0.34% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.81 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.4 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 22400, up 2.1% on the day. Hitachi Energy India Ltd is up 82.94% in last one year as compared to a 10.48% jump in NIFTY and a 13.9% jump in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 110.86 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HitachiEnergyIndiaLimited_51485438_74646.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Spirits Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-spirits-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1673985</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1673985</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[United Spirits Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

United Spirits Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1398.9, up 1.59% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is up around 0.54% on the day, quoting at 25832.9. The Sensex is at 83979.52, up 0.48%. United Spirits Ltd has gained around 5.37% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which United Spirits Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 1.66% in last one month and is currently quoting at 51882.75, down 0.03% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.35 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 9.44 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1402, up 1.73% on the day. United Spirits Ltd is down 1.45% in last one year as compared to a 10.48% jump in NIFTY and a 5.45% jump in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 57.29 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnitedSpirits_20574926747_8036.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>