<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:17:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee Falls]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-falls/1662089</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662089</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 89.9050 per Dollar on Friday (26 December 2025), versus its previous close of 89.8400 per Dollar on Wednesday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper vaults around 40% this year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-vaults-around-40-this-year/1662085</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662085</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures continued to surge today.

COMEX Copper futures continued to surge today. Firm equities and weak US dollar are pushing the metal up in thin year end trades. COMEX Copper futures are up 2.60% at $5.72 per pound right now. Copper has rallied by more than 40% this year, poised for the biggest annual gain since 2009, driven higher by rising tech demand, supply constraints, and tariff uncertainty. The general undertone remains supportive for global economy and generous demand for electric vehicles. Electric Vehicles (EV) sales in 2025 are expected to exceed 20 million worldwide to represent more than one-quarter of cars sold worldwide, according to IEA. Electric car sales exceeded 17 million globally in 2024, reaching a sales share of more than 20%. Copper has managed to deal with the recent wave of slightly tepid Chinese economic data forcefully due to the surge in demand from EV segment. Weak US dollar and record high US equities also boosted the red metal as a break above $5 per pound extended.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volatility set to persist into year-end as investors eye key data for direction]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volatility-set-to-persist-into-year-end-as-investors-eye-key-data-for-direction/1662083</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662083</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equity markets head into the holiday-shortened week with consolidation dominating sentiment, as the Nifty50 and Sensex trimmed weekly gains amid profit-taking and thin year-end trading volumes.

Indian equity markets head into the holiday-shortened week with consolidation dominating sentiment, as the Nifty50 and Sensex trimmed weekly gains amid profit-taking and thin year-end trading volumes. Benchmarks rose marginally over the week but saw profit booking at record highs, reflecting investor caution in the absence of fresh catalysts. The rupee remained stable near 89.83 against the U.S. dollar, aided by state-bank interventions, even as the Chinese yuan outperformed, highlighting divergent currency dynamics that could impact import costs and FII flows. Globally, surging gold prices reached record highs, prompting shifts in investor positioning and risk sentiment that may influence risk assets. On the policy front, India and New Zealand finalized a free trade agreement, underscoring efforts to diversify export markets amid global trade uncertainties. Given muted liquidity, markets may remain range-bound, with select cyclicals and exporters offering relative value while investors await clearer macro cues in early 2026. In India, the Industrial Production data for the month of November would be announced on Monday (29 December 2025). The Industrial production in India increased 0.4% year-on-year in October 2025, following an upwardly revised 4.6% gain in September. It marks the smallest annual growth rate since August 2024 when industrial output stalled. On Tuesday (30 December 2025), the M3 Money Supply figures for the week ended on December 12 would be made public. The Money Supply M3 in India increased to Rs 291,363.75 billion in the week ending November 28 from Rs 289,454.93 billion two weeks before. On Wednesday (31 December 2025), the government budget value for November 2025 would be announced. India recorded a government budget deficit of Rs 825,144 tens of million in October of 2025. India’s external debt position at the end of third quarter for FY26 would be made public on the same day. The external debt in India increased to $747200 million in the second quarter of 2025 from $736300 million in the first quarter of 2025. On Friday (02 January 2026), the final reading for the HSBC Manufacturing PMI for December would be unveiled. The HSBC India Manufacturing PMI eased to 55.7 in December 2025 from 56.6 in November, marking the weakest improvement in manufacturing conditions since December 2023, according to preliminary estimates. The Foreign Exchange Reserves for the week ended on December 26 would be made public on the same day. Foreign Exchange Reserves in India increased to $688,950 million in December 12 from $687,260 million in the previous week. In China, PMI data releases would be in focus, with the NBS Manufacturing PMI, NBS Non-Manufacturing PMI and the RatingDog Manufacturing PMI would be released on Wednesday (31 December 2025). China’s official NBS Manufacturing PMI edged up to 49.2 in November 2025 from October’s six-month low of 49.0. China’s official NBS Non-Manufacturing PMI slipped to 49.5 in November 2025 from 50.1 in the previous month, pointing to the lowest figure since December 2022 and the first decline in nearly three years. The RatingDog China General Manufacturing PMI fell to 49.9 in November 2025 from 50.6 in the previous month, hitting its lowest level since July. In United States, the Dallas Fed Manufacturing Index for December 2025 would be released on Monday (29 December 2025). The Dallas Fed’s general business activity index for Texas manufacturing fell to -10.4 in November 2025, from -5 in the prior, signaling a fourth consecutive monthly contraction in manufacturing activity and the steepest since June. Monday would also see the release of advanced estimates of Goods Trade Balance for the month of November. The US trade deficit in goods narrowed by $17.3 billion from the previous month to $85.5 billion in August 2025, according to an advance estimate. Imports fell 7.0% month-on-month to $261.6 billion, while exports fell 1.3% to $176.1 billion. On Wednesday (31 December 2025), the FOMC Minutes for its December meeting would be made public. The Federal Reserve cut the federal funds rate by 25 bps to a range of 3.5%–3.75% in its December 2025 meeting, following similar reductions in September and October. The API Crude Oil Stock Change for the week ended on December 26 would be made public would also be released on Wednesday. US crude oil inventories increased by 2.4 million barrels in the week ending December 19th, 2025, marking the first build after four weeks of draws and following the sharpest decrease since June of 9.3 million-barrel the previous week. The Initial Jobless Claims for the week ended on December 27 would also be announced on the same day. Initial jobless claims in the US fell by 10,000 from the previous week to 214,000 on the period ending December 20th, around the commonly volatile holiday season for new claims.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bank credit growth stays steady at 11.60% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bank-credit-growth-stays-steady-at-1160-on-year/1662081</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662081</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The bank credit growth in India continues to remain resilient, reflecting sustained lending momentum across key segments of the economy.

The bank credit growth in India continues to remain resilient, reflecting sustained lending momentum across key segments of the economy. As per the latest data released by the Reserve Bank of India, total bank credit stood at Rs 201.3 lakh crore as of 12 December 2025, registering a year-on-year growth of 11.60%. Credit growth has consistently remained above 10% in recent months, indicating stable demand conditions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee weaknes near 90 per US dollar mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-weaknes-near-90-per-us-dollar-mark/1662079</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662079</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee continued to slide today amid a modest spell of weakness in the local equities and thin activity in world markets.

Indian rupee continued to slide today amid a modest spell of weakness in the local equities and thin activity in world markets. INR has been falling rising near three-week high against the US dollar and INR tested a one-week low of 89.94 per US dollar. Overall mood in local currency market remains cautious after sustained fall in INR this year. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has said that it will conduct $10 billion USD/INR Buy/Sell Swap auction for a tenure of three years. The auction will take place on January 13. INR shed 20 paise to 89.90, down 10 paise on the day. On NSE, USD/INR futures rose 0.13% to 89.89. The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts today as profit booking in a holiday-truncated week and sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) weighed on market sentiment. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 367.25 points or 0.43% to 85,041.45. The Nifty 50 index lost 99.80 points or 0.38% to 26,042.30.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-1-1236488_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty dips below 26,050 as FII outflows and profit booking weigh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-dips-below-26050-as-fii-outflows-and-profit-booking-weigh/1662064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662064</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks slipped into the red on Tuesday, as profit booking in a holiday-shortened week and relentless FII selling sapped investor confidence.

Domestic equity benchmarks slipped into the red on Tuesday, as profit booking in a holiday-shortened week and relentless FII selling sapped investor confidence. The Nifty closed below the 26,050 mark, pulled down by losses in IT and auto stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 367.25 points or 0.43% to 85,041.45. The Nifty 50 index lost 99.80 points or 0.38% to 26,042.30. Bajaj Finance (down 1.3%), ICICI Bank (down 0.65%) and HDFC Bank (down 0.52%) were major drags today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.18% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.34%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,745 shares rose and 2,456 shares fell. A total of 186 shares were unchanged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.44% to 6.567 as compared with the previous close of 6.538. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8200 compared with its close of 89.7100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement gained 0.99% to Rs 1,39,467. Silver prices continued rising and hit another high after notching a record Wednesday. Spot silver rose more than 4% on Friday to reach an all-time high of $74.89 per ounce. Silver has rallied over 159% year to date. Metal prices have soared this year amid shaky investor sentiment on riskier assets, as fears of an AI bubble and uncertainty over U.S. Fed rate cuts mount. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 97.71. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.51% to 4.151. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 13 cents or 0.21% to $61.95 a barrel. Global Markets: European market remained closed on Friday on account of the Boxing Day holiday, while Asian market ended mixed, with several regional exchanges shut for the holiday. Meanwhile, core consumer prices in Tokyo rose 2.3% in December from a year earlier, according to government data Friday. The core CPI, which strips out volatile fresh food costs, remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target, reinforcing the case for more interest rate hikes. The latest reading was below the 2.8% increase in November. Tokyo’s inflation numbers are widely considered to be a leading indicator of nationwide trends. U.S. equity futures ticked slightly higher in early Asian hours, after the S&P 500 closed at a new record for the second straight day on Wednesday stateside. The broad market index advanced 0.32%, ending the session at 6,932.05. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 288.75 points, or 0.60%, and also posted a closing record of 48,731.16. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.22% and settled at 23,613.31. Stocks in Spotlight: Railway stocks rallied sharply on Friday as renewed optimism ahead of Union Budget 2026 sparked fresh buying interest across the sector. Rail Vikas Nigam surged 12.22%, while RailTel Corporation of India 6.03%. Indian Railway Finance Corporation advanced 9.92%. Manufacturing-linked names also gained, with Titagarh Rail Systems rising 4.96% and Texmaco Rail & Engineering up 4.59%. RITES rose 4.10% and Ircon International gained 4.87%. Among other stocks, Jupiter Wagons climbed 2.07%, while Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation advanced 3.72%. Market participants are positioning for higher government capital expenditure on rail infrastructure, rolling stock expansion and network modernisation, a trend that has historically supported railway-linked stocks in the run-up to the Budget. Panacea Biotec surged 13.54% after it received an award from the United Nations International Children’s Emergency Fund (UNICEF) for the supply of its WHO pre-qualified pentavalent vaccine, Easyfive-TT, for 2023–2027. Vikran Engineering rose 4.40% after securing an order worth Rs 459.20 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy for the engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) of a 400 MW AC solar power project at Chitrakoot-1 in Uttar Pradesh. Strides Pharma Science slipped 2.71% after its step-down subsidiary, Strides Pharma Inc. USA (SPI), received four observations from the USFDA following a routine inspection of its formulations facility in Chestnut Ridge, New York. Apollo Micro Systems climbed 1.71% after the company received orders amounting to Rs 100.24 crore from a private company for the supply of Unmanned Aerial Systems. NMDC advanced 1.51% after the company signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Colorado School of Mines, USA, to establish a framework for research collaboration in mining, mineral processing, metallurgy, and AI/ML in mining. Ola Electric Mobility jumped 2.32% after its subsidiary, Ola Electric Technology, secured incentives worth Rs 366.78 crore under the Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for automobiles and auto components (PLI-Auto) for FY25. Lenskart Solutions shed 0.62%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary, Lenskart Solutions Pte. Ltd., Singapore, would invest 3 billion Korean Won for acquiring 123,945 preference shares or 29.24% of the share capital of iiNeer Corp., Ltd. Dilip Buildcon rose 2.23% after the company announced that it has secured a letter of award (LOA) for a significant road construction project in Bihar. Concord Control Systems fell 1.31%. The company, through its wholly owned subsidiary Advanced Rail Controls, secured an order worth Rs 56.58 crore from Indian Railways.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices snap 2-week losses; broader mrkt outperforms ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-snap-2-week-losses-broader-mrkt-outperforms/1662061</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662061</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks posted minor gains during the truncated week, snapping a two-week losing streak, supported by India-New Zealand trade deal, encouraging economic data and robust response for a recent IPO.

The key equity benchmarks posted minor gains during the truncated week, snapping a two-week losing streak, supported by India-New Zealand trade deal, encouraging economic data and robust response for a recent IPO. Mid- and small-cap stocks outperformed, while stock-specific action remained active on the back of order wins, acquisitions, and strategic partnerships. Further, the market will now track developments around the India-US trade deal, FII activity, rupee movement, crude oil prices and the upcoming corporate earnings season. In the week ended on Friday, 26 December 2025, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 112.09 points or 0.13% to settle at 85,041.45. The Nifty 50 index added 75.90 points or 0.29% to settle at 26,042.30. The BSE Mid-Cap index advanced 0.37% to close at 46,721.04. The BSE Small-Cap added 1.02% to end at 51,318.60. Weekly Index Movement: The domestic equity benchmarks closed higher on Monday, extending gains for a second straight session. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 638.12 points or 0.75% to 85,576.48. The Nifty 50 index gained 206 points or 0.79% to 26,172.40. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.3% and 1.38%, respectively. Benchmark equity indices ended Tuesday’s session largely flat as volatility persisted around the weekly expiry of Nifty futures. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 42.64 points or 0.05% to 85,524.84. The Nifty 50 index rose 4.75 points or 0.02% to 26,177.15. Domesic equity benchmarks slipped into the red on Wednesday in a quiet, pre-Christmas session marked by light volumes and subdued risk-taking. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 116.14 points or 0.14% to 85,408.70. The Nifty 50 index fell 35.05 points or 0.13% to 26,142.10. The stock market was closed on Thursday, 25 December 2025 on account of Christmas. The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts on Friday as profit booking in a holiday-truncated week and sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) weighed on market sentiment while investors preferred to stay on the sidelines ahead of upcoming earnings announcements. India-New Zealand Agreement: India and New Zealand have concluded a comprehensive and forward looking Free Trade Agreement, marking a significant economic and strategic step in India’s Indo Pacific engagement. The pact opens up opportunities for Indian service providers across high value sectors such as IT, professional services, education, finance, tourism and construction. As part of the agreement, New Zealand has committed to facilitate $20 billion of investments into India over the next 15 years, supporting manufacturing, infrastructure, innovation and jobs, while also enabling Indian companies to expand their presence in New Zealand and the wider Pacific region. Economy: The Index of Eight Core Industries rose 1.8% year-on-year in November, driven by higher output of cement, steel, fertilisers and coal. Cement production grew 14.5%, fertilisers 5.6%, steel 6.1% and coal 2.1%, while crude oil output fell 3.2% and natural gas production declined 2.5%. The index tracks eight sectors that together account for over 40% of the weight in the Index of Industrial Production. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro (L&T) shed 0.71%. The company announced that its Hydrocarbon Onshore business vertical (L&T Onshore) has secured a major engineering, procurement, construction and commissioning (EPCC) order from Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL). Belrise Industries surged 10.01%. The company announced a strategic agreement with Israel-based Plasan Sasa. Under the agreement, the two companies will jointly identify and pursue defence-related business opportunities in India. Varun Beverages rose 2.85%. The company shared details of its proposed acquisition of South Africa based Twizza Proprietary. The company said the acquisition will be executed through its wholly owned subsidiary in South Africa. The proposed transaction involves the purchase of 100% equity in Twizza at an enterprise value of about ZAR 2,095 million, or roughly Rs 1,118.7 crore. Vikran Engineering jumped 13.14%. The company announced a major solar EPC order win. The company has secured a work order worth Rs 2,035.26 crore from Onix Renewables to set up 600 MW AC solar power projects across multiple locations in Maharashtra. The order will be executed on a turnkey EPC basis. Sunita Tools rose 2.9%. The company announced a strategic memorandum of understanding with a Middle East-based partner to support an upcoming defence order. Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals gained 0.49%. The company announced that it has received an order worth Rs 46.20 crore from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company (MSEDCL). The order covers 2,000 solar water pumping systems, with a total work order value of Rs 46,20,48,229. Antony Waste Handling Cell rose 0.64%. The company announced that its arm, Antony Lara Enviro Solutions, has secured a contract worth Rs 329.45 crore for the development of a mixed solid waste processing plant in Maharashtra. Global Markets: UK economy grew by 0.1% in ⁠the July-to-September period of this year, the Office for National Statistics said on Monday, in line with its initial estimate. Singapore's inflation in November remained steady at 1.2%. Core inflation in the city-state, which strips out prices of private transport and accommodation, also came in at 1.2%, compared to expectations of 1.3%. The People’s Bank of China kept its 1-year and 5-year loan prime rates unchanged at 3% and 3.5% respectively The annual inflation rate in the U.S. eased to 2.7% in November 2025, marking its lowest level since July. The reading was lower than the 3% recorded in September, offering further relief on the inflation front. US GDP grew 4.3% in third quarter compared with 3.8% growth recorded in Second quarter. This is also the highest quarterly GDP growth in the US economy in the past 2 years.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty December futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-december-futures-trade-at-premium/1662057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662057</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty December 2025 futures closed at 26,058, a premium of 15.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,215.55 in the cash market.

The Nifty December 2025 futures closed at 26,058, a premium of 15.7 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 26,215.55 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index lost 99.80 points or 0.38% to 26,042.30. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.43% to 9.15. HDFC Bank, Infosys and Vedanta were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The December 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 30 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers ends with minor cuts; Nifty settles below 26,050 marks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-ends-with-minor-cuts-nifty-settles-below-26050-marks/1662056</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662056</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today as profit booking in a holiday-truncated week and sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) weighed on market sentiment.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with modest losses today as profit booking in a holiday-truncated week and sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) weighed on market sentiment. The Nifty settled below the 26,050 mark. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 367.25 points or 0.43% to 85,041.45. The Nifty 50 index lost 99.80 points or 0.38% to 26,042.30. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.18% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.34%. The market breadth was negative. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Metal index (up 0.59%), the Consumer Durable index (up 0.34%) and the Nifty FMCG (up 0.03%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 1.03%), the Nifty Media index (down 0.62%) and the Nifty Auto index (down 0.52%), underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.44% to 6.567 as compared with the previous close of 6.538. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8200 compared with its close of 89.7100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement gained 0.99% to Rs 1,39,467. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 97.71. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.51% to 4.151. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 13 cents or 0.21% to $61.95 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets remained closed on Friday on account of the Boxing Day holiday, while Asian markets ended mixed, with several regional exchanges also shut for the holiday. Silver prices continued rising and hit another high after notching a record Wednesday. Spot silver rose more than 4% on Friday to reach an all-time high of $74.89 per ounce. Silver has rallied over 159% year to date. Metal prices have soared this year amid shaky investor sentiment on riskier assets, as fears of an AI bubble and uncertainty over U.S. Fed rate cuts mount. Meanwhile, core consumer prices in Tokyo rose 2.3% in December from a year earlier, according to government data Friday. The core CPI, which strips out volatile fresh food costs, remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target, reinforcing the case for more interest rate hikes. The latest reading was below the 2.8% increase in November. Tokyo’s inflation numbers are widely considered to be a leading indicator of nationwide trends. The Australia and Hong Kong markets were closed for the holiday. U.S. equity futures ticked slightly higher in early Asian hours, after the S&P 500 closed at a new record for the second straight day on Wednesday stateside. The broad market index advanced 0.32%, ending the session at 6,932.05. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 288.75 points, or 0.60%, and also posted a closing record of 48,731.16. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.22% and settled at 23,613.31.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index falls 1.03%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-falls-103/1662055</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662055</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index ended down 1.03% at 38572.3 today.

Nifty IT index ended down 1.03% at 38572.3 today. The index has gained 3.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Coforge Ltd shed 3.71%, LTIMindtree Ltd dropped 2.07% and Mphasis Ltd slipped 1.43%. The Nifty IT index has fallen 12.00% over last one year compared to the 9.65% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Media index has dropped 0.62% and Nifty Metal index gained 0.59% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has dropped 0.38% to close at 26042.3 while the SENSEX has dropped 0.43% to close at 85041.45 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 367 pts lower; Nifty ends below 26,050 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-367-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-26050-mark/1662054</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662054</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts today as profit booking in a holiday-truncated week and sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) weighed on market sentiment, while investors preferred to stay on the sidelines ahead of upcoming earnings announcements.

The key equity barometers ended with modest cuts today as profit booking in a holiday-truncated week and sustained selling by foreign institutional investors (FIIs) weighed on market sentiment, while investors preferred to stay on the sidelines ahead of upcoming earnings announcements. The Nifty settled below the 26,050 mark. IT, media and auto stocks declined, while metal, consumer durables and FMCG advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 367.25 points or 0.43% to 85,041.45. The Nifty 50 index lost 99.80 points or 0.38% to 26,042.30. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.18% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.34%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,749 shares rose and 2,449 shares fell. A total of 181 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index fell 1.03% to 38,572.30. The index dropped 2.32% in the past three trading sessions. Coforge (down 3.75%), LTIMindtree (down 2.08%), Mphasis (down 1.41%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 1.21%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.1%), Persistent Systems (down 0.82%), HCL Technologies (down 0.74%), Wipro (down 0.63%), Infosys (down 0.43%) and Oracle Financial Services Software (down 0.13%) tumbled. Stocks in Spotlight: Panacea Biotec surged 13.75% after it received an award from the United Nations International Children’s Emergency Fund (UNICEF) for the supply of its WHO pre-qualified pentavalent vaccine, Easyfive-TT, for 2023–2027. Vikran Engineering rose 4.56% after securing an order worth Rs 459.20 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy for the engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) of a 400 MW AC solar power project at Chitrakoot-1 in Uttar Pradesh. Strides Pharma Science slipped 2.71% after its step-down subsidiary, Strides Pharma Inc. USA (SPI), received four observations from the USFDA following a routine inspection of its formulations facility in Chestnut Ridge, New York. Apollo Micro Systems climbed 1.79% after the company received orders amounting to Rs 100.24 crore from a private company for the supply of Unmanned Aerial Systems. NMDC advanced 1.34% after the company signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Colorado School of Mines, USA, to establish a framework for research collaboration in mining, mineral processing, metallurgy, and AI/ML in mining. Ola Electric Mobility jumped 2.23% after its subsidiary, Ola Electric Technology, secured incentives worth Rs 366.78 crore under the Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for automobiles and auto components (PLI-Auto) for FY25. Lenskart Solutions shed 0.95%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary, Lenskart Solutions Pte. Ltd., Singapore, would invest 3 billion Korean Won for acquiring 123,945 preference shares or 29.24% of the share capital of iiNeer Corp., Ltd. Dilip Buildcon rose 3.13% after the company announced that it has secured a letter of award (LOA) for a significant road construction project in Bihar. Concord Control Systems fell 1.13%. The company, through its wholly owned subsidiary Advanced Rail Controls, secured an order worth Rs 56.58 crore from Indian Railways. Sayaji Hotels shed 0.02%. The company said that it has entered into a 15-year agreement with SPJ Recreational Centre to manage and operate a new 5-star hotel in Takve Khurd, Taluka Maval, near Wet and Joy Park, Pune, Maharashtra. Global Markets: European markets remained closed on Friday on account of the Boxing Day holiday, while Asian shares ended mixed, with several regional exchanges also shut for the holiday. Silver prices continued rising and hit another high after notching a record Wednesday. Spot silver rose more than 4% on Friday to reach an all-time high of $74.89 per ounce. Silver has rallied over 159% year to date. Metal prices have soared this year amid shaky investor sentiment on riskier assets, as fears of an AI bubble and uncertainty over U.S. Fed rate cuts mount. Meanwhile, core consumer prices in Tokyo rose 2.3% in December from a year earlier, according to government data Friday. The core CPI, which strips out volatile fresh food costs, remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target, reinforcing the case for more interest rate hikes. The latest reading was below the 2.8% increase in November. Tokyo’s inflation numbers are widely considered to be a leading indicator of nationwide trends. The Australia and Hong Kong markets were closed for the holiday. U.S. equity futures ticked slightly higher in early Asian hours, after the S&P 500 closed at a new record for the second straight day on Wednesday stateside. The broad market index advanced 0.32%, ending the session at 6,932.05. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 288.75 points, or 0.60%, and also posted a closing record of 48,731.16. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.22% and settled at 23,613.31.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD falls near 1.1800 mark amid thin trades overall]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-falls-near-11800-mark-amid-thin-trades-overall/1662053</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662053</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro is trading in a lax manner today, giving up a bit after hitting three-month top against the US dollar amid thin trades.

Euro is trading in a lax manner today, giving up a bit after hitting three-month top against the US dollar amid thin trades. European markets ended Wednesday's shortened session on a flat note and capped upside in Euro too. Mood remains tepid today as several markets were closed for Christmas and Boxing Day holidays. Markets in Germany, France, the UK, and Switzerland are shut today and EUR/USD pair is currently quoting at 1.1815, down marginally on the day. EUR/INR futures are currently trading at 105.69, down 0.28% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Currency in circulation spikes 9.6% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/currency-in-circulation-spikes-96-on-year/1662052</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662052</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation rose 1.2% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 39.13 lakh crore as on December 15, 2025.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has reported that currency in circulation rose 1.2% on the fortnightly basis to stand at Rs 39.13 lakh crore as on December 15, 2025. The central bank stated further that the overall reserve money rose 0.2% on the week to Rs 47.95 lakh crore. Currency in circulation spiked 9.6% on a year ago basis compared to 6.1% rise at the same time last year. In the current fiscal year, the currency in circulation edged up 5.1% so far while the reserve money has contracted 0.10%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Midwest climbs after brokerage initiates coverage with buy call]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/midwest-climbs-after-brokerage-initiates-coverage-with-buy-call/1662039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662039</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The brokerage highlighted Midwest's position as India’s largest producer and exporter of Black Galaxy granite, backed by a vertically integrated model and 20 operating mines.

The brokerage highlighted Midwest's position as India’s largest producer and exporter of Black Galaxy granite, backed by a vertically integrated model and 20 operating mines. Strong historical performance, with revenue CAGR of over 21% and EBITDA CAGR above 44% over the past five years, underpins the positive view. Looking ahead, revenue and EBITDA are expected to grow at a CAGR of 36% and 47%, respectively, over FY25-28, driven by the Quartz and HMS segments, while adjusted PAT is seen rising at a 56% CAGR. Improving cash flows are also expected to reduce net debt-to-EBITDA below 1x. The target price is based on a valuation of 13x FY28 estimated EV/EBITDA. Midwest (ML) is engaged in the exploration, mining, processing, marketing, distribution, and export of natural stones. The company is a producer and exporter of black galaxy granite, a unique granite variety known for its sparkling golden flakes. On a consolidated basis, Midwest's net profit rose 86.82% to Rs 27.78 crore while net sales rose 12.38% to Rs 158.69 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. The stock was listed on the exchanges on 24 October 2025, debuting at Rs 1,165.10, a premium of 9.4% to the issue price of Rs 1,065. The stock is currently up 57.93% over its IPO price and 44.37% over its listing price. Midwest’s IPO was subscribed 87.89 times. The issue opened for bidding on 15 October 2025, and closed on 17 October 2025, with a price band of Rs 1,014 to Rs 1,065 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MidwestLtd_60188168_94066.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Pipavav Port Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-pipavav-port-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1662037</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662037</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Coforge Ltd, V I P Industries Ltd, JSW Holdings Ltd and HFCL Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 December 2025.

Coforge Ltd, V I P Industries Ltd, JSW Holdings Ltd and HFCL Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 26 December 2025. Gujarat Pipavav Port Ltd crashed 4.90% to Rs 182.3 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 71315 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.37 lakh shares in the past one month. Coforge Ltd tumbled 4.15% to Rs 1665.3. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 89508 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 53796 shares in the past one month. V I P Industries Ltd lost 4.14% to Rs 391.25. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.65 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21.2 lakh shares in the past one month. JSW Holdings Ltd shed 4.07% to Rs 19475. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 355 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 882 shares in the past one month. HFCL Ltd fell 3.88% to Rs 61.71. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 92.26 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.24 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujPipavavPort_89824764870_12232.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold sparkles as rally above $4500 per ounce extends]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-sparkles-as-rally-above-4500-per-ounce-extends/1662036</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662036</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Gold futures jumped to a record high on Friday, witnessing excellent buying support on safe-haven demand and rising expectations of further interest rate cuts by the US Federal Reserve.

COMEX Gold futures jumped to a record high on Friday, witnessing excellent buying support on safe-haven demand and rising expectations of further interest rate cuts by the US Federal Reserve. The US dollar index is trading in a very lax manner and is down around 1.60% this month. COMEX Gold futures are up 1% at $4543 per ounce today per ounce, bouncing around 7% this month so far. Indian spot retail demand in thin right now and a meaningful pick-up could be seen only after the year-end. Meanwhile, the US President Donald Trump has said that he expects the next chairman of the US Federal Reserve to keep interest rates low and never disagree with him. This is keeping overall mood upbeat for the bullion counters. The MCX Gold futures are trading at Rs 139329 per 10 grams, up 0.89% on the day after hitting a high above Rs 139400 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Regency Ceramics Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/regency-ceramics-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1662035</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662035</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Creative Eye Ltd, Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd, Teamo Productions HQ Ltd and Adroit Infotech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 December 2025.

Creative Eye Ltd, Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd, Teamo Productions HQ Ltd and Adroit Infotech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 26 December 2025. Regency Ceramics Ltd tumbled 10.57% to Rs 43 at 14:00 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 90 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3235 shares in the past one month. Creative Eye Ltd crashed 9.85% to Rs 7.14. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 7110 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10039 shares in the past one month. Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd lost 9.74% to Rs 22.6. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 35 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 24.76 lakh shares in the past one month. Teamo Productions HQ Ltd shed 9.30% to Rs 0.78. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9.09 lakh shares in the past one month. Adroit Infotech Ltd slipped 7.30% to Rs 9.9. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.54 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12373 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RegencyCeramics_1874361855_831.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Concord Control rises after subsidiary bags order from Indian Railways ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/concord-control-rises-after-subsidiary-bags-order-from-indian-railways/1662034</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662034</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order covers the supply, installation and commissioning of locomotive wireless control systems, a safety-critical solution that enhances real-time communication, operational coordination, and control in locomotive operations.

The order covers the supply, installation and commissioning of locomotive wireless control systems, a safety-critical solution that enhances real-time communication, operational coordination, and control in locomotive operations. The contract further strengthens Concord’s execution pipeline, reinforcing its growing engagement with Indian Railways across multiple safety and control applications. With this addition, the company’s order book as on date is Rs. 450-plus crore. Gaurav Lath, joint managing director of Concord Control Systems, said: “This order strengthens Concord’s position as a leader in India’s railway technology journey. It shows the trust Indian Railways has in our capabilities in railway safety and electronic systems, and fits well with the country’s focus on safer and better rail infrastructure.” Concord Control Systems is a manufacturer of embedded electronic systems and critical electronic solutions, specializing in railway safety and control technologies.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ConcordControlSystemsLtd_63232532_77868.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at MMTC Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-mmtc-ltd-counter/1662026</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662026</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, Karur Vysya Bank Ltd, Indian Railway Catering & Tourism Corporation Ltd, Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 December 2025.

Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, Karur Vysya Bank Ltd, Indian Railway Catering & Tourism Corporation Ltd, Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 26 December 2025. MMTC Ltd witnessed volume of 589.56 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 32.74 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 18.01 lakh shares. The stock increased 10.79% to Rs.63.74. Volumes stood at 32.15 lakh shares in the last session. Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd recorded volume of 836.5 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.46 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 73.02 lakh shares. The stock gained 11.43% to Rs.385.20. Volumes stood at 125.11 lakh shares in the last session. Karur Vysya Bank Ltd recorded volume of 110.01 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 9.25 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 11.89 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.92% to Rs.267.40. Volumes stood at 13.85 lakh shares in the last session. Indian Railway Catering & Tourism Corporation Ltd saw volume of 61.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.21 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7.50 lakh shares. The stock increased 4.00% to Rs.706.85. Volumes stood at 11.44 lakh shares in the last session. Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd notched up volume of 1228.93 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.66 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 160.48 lakh shares. The stock rose 8.68% to Rs.132.03. Volumes stood at 275.8 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MMTC_69316024395_2292.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops over 426 pts; auto shares slide]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-over-426-pts-auto-shares-slide/1662028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662028</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade.

The headline equity benchmarks traded with modest cuts in mid-afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 26,050 mark. Auto shares extended losses for the second consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 426.32 points or 0.50% to 84,979.27. The Nifty 50 index lost 116.10 points or 0.44% to 26,026.65. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.11% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.22%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,721 shares rose and 2,403 shares fell. A total of 184 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index rose 0.49% to 27,750. The index jumped 1.54% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Uno Minda (down 1.53%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 1.11%), Hero MotoCorp (down 1.04%), Ashok Leyland (down 0.95%), Bajaj Auto (down 0.86%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 0.78%), TVS Motor Company (down 0.52%), Mahindra & Mahindra (down 0.42%), Exide Industries (down 0.31%) and Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 0.26%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was up 0.41% to 6.565 as compared with the previous close of 6.538. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.8425 compared with its close of 89.7100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement rose 0.89% to Rs 1,39,329. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.08% to 98.03. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.56% to 4.153. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement added 7 cents or 0.11% to $62.31 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Dilip Buildcon rose 3.80% after the company announced that it has secured a letter of award (LOA) for a significant road construction project in Bihar. Astra Microwave Products rose 2.38% after the company announced the execution of a memorandum of undertaking with state-run Bharat Electronics.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>