<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:44:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Energy zooms after Q3 PAT surges 90% YoY to Rs 261 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hitachi-energy-zooms-after-q3-pat-surges-90-yoy-to-rs-261-cr/1672555</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672555</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 402.02 crore during the quarter, up 118.42% YoY.

Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 402.02 crore during the quarter, up 118.42% YoY. Exceptional items of Rs 54.24 crore were related to labour code charges. Operating EBITDA surged 100.4% to Rs 338.4 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 168.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Operating EBITDA margin expanded 15.6% in Q3 FY26 as against 10.1% in Q3 FY25. During the quarter ended December 31, 2025, orders totaled Rs 2,477.6 crore, up 73.7% YoY excluding a large order during the same period of FY25. This was led by orders for transformers (power, traction, and dry) reactors, gas insulated switchgear (GIS) and air-insulated switchgear (AIS). In terms of segment- industries, datacenter and renewables were major contributors to the orderbook. During Q3FY26, exports grew, accounting for 29.8 percent of the total orders booked for the quarter. The company received export orders from utilities, data centers, from Southeast Asia, and Southern Africa, respectively. The order backlog stood at Rs 29,872.2 crore as of December 31, 2025, providing revenue visibility for several upcoming quarters. On the outlook front, the company said that the recent EU-India FTA strengthens clean-energy collaboration according to analysts, especially in renewables and green hydrogen, this is likely to boost opportunities for Indian energy firms through enhanced technology exchange and investment flows. It is also likely to create a more stable, climate-aligned trade framework. On this energy front, opportunities are growing as India moves toward its larger energy goals. But the challenge ahead is not only to supply electricity, but to manage it under more demanding conditions. Capacity, control, and coordination will determine whether the power system can keep pace with industrial complexity and urban growth. N Venu, managing director & CEO, Hitachi Energy India, said, “Our Q3 results highlight the increasing pace of electrification in India and the world, with global electricity demand projected to surge over 70 percent. AI's power intensive growth demands strategic infrastructure investments, and we are proud to be at the forefront, powering AI-ready data centers and the sustainable energy future ahead. In India, this huge focus on electrification also signals robust capacity expansion, grid reliability, and inclusive access to meet ambitious targets like 2,000 kWh per capita consumption by 2030. These trends offer a clear glimpse of our nation's evolving energy needs, both immediate and long-term, and position our company for sustained leadership in delivering reliable, affordable, and sustainable power.” Hitachi Energy India provides product, system, software, and service solutions across the entire power value chain. The portfolio includes an extensive range of high-voltage products, transformers, grid automation products, and power quality products and systems.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HitachiEnergyIndiaLimited_51485438_74646.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pitti Engineering slips as Q3 PAT slides 30% QoQ to Rs 28 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pitti-engineering-slips-as-q3-pat-slides-30-qoq-to-rs-28-cr/1672543</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672543</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit fell by 1.9%, despite a 15% increase in net sales in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

On a year-on-year basis, the company’s net profit fell by 1.9%, despite a 15% increase in net sales in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 39.69 crore, up 2.7% from Rs 38.66 crore reported in the corresponding quarter last year. Reported EBITDA rose 20.8% YoY to Rs 80.9 crore, with an EBITDA margin of 16.9% recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Akshay S. Pitti, MD & CEO, said, “Our performance in Q3 FY26 remained strong, with total income rising 15% Y-o-Y to Rs 484 crore, driven by consistent execution across operations. Adjusted EBITDA grew 25% to Rs 83 crore, while adjusted PAT grew by 4% Y-o-Y to Rs 30 crore. For 9MFY26, revenue increased 14% to Rs 1,447 crore, reflecting robust volume growth across our value-added product portfolio. Capacity utilization continues to be healthy, supported by strong order flows and execution across railways, power, industrial & mining, and oil & gas sectors. Our exports business remained steady, contributing 28% to 9MFY26 revenues despite global uncertainties and geopolitical tensions. Our capex plan remains on track, with announced investments aligned to anticipated future demand. This includes calibrated expansion across key facilities and value-added capabilities to ensure we are well-prepared to meet growing orders and strengthen our competitive position. As a strategic initiative, the Board has approved the merger of the wholly owned subsidiaries (Pitti Industries & Dakshin Foundry) with the Company to streamline administrative, operational, and corporate structures. This consolidation is aimed at enhancing efficiencies and generating synergies across the organization. Looking ahead, we remain focused on disciplined execution, calibrated capacity expansion, and strengthening our presence across key end segments. With clear demand visibility and ongoing investments in value-added capabilities, the company is well-positioned to deliver sustainable medium-term growth.” Pitti Engineering is engaged in the manufacturing of electrical steel laminations, motor cores, sub-assemblies, die-cast rotors, press tools, and machining of metal components.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PittiEngg_80997893620_3497.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen holds ahead of election; Set for 1% weekly loss ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-holds-ahead-of-election-set-for-1-weekly-loss/1672519</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672519</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen hovered around 156.7 per dollar in electronic trading on Friday as investors positioned ahead of this weekend’s lower house elections.

The Japanese yen hovered around 156.7 per dollar in electronic trading on Friday as investors positioned ahead of this weekend’s lower house elections. Despite the stability, the currency is set for a weekly loss of more than 1%, weighed down by expectations that Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi will secure voter support for higher government spending and possible tax cuts, intensifying concerns over Japan’s fiscal outlook. Uncertainty surrounding how the government plans to fund its policy agenda has kept investors cautious, while attention also turns to Japan’s Q4 GDP data due next week, which is expected to show a rebound from the previous quarter’s contraction. Adding to the pressure, the US dollar remained firm near a two-week high, as markets reassessed the outlook for US monetary policy. The greenback has gained momentum since President Donald Trump nominated Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve Chair. Warsh is widely viewed as favoring a tighter policy stance, including maintaining higher interest rates for longer and reducing the Fed’s balance sheet.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India-US trade deal fully safeguards India’s agricultural interests: Union Minister for Agriculture & Farmers’ Welfare]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-us-trade-deal-fully-safeguards-indias-agricultural-interests-union-minister-for-agriculture-farmers-welfare/1672516</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672516</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Minister for Agriculture & Farmers’ Welfare and Rural Development, Shivraj Singh Chouhan, firmly stated that the agreement fully safeguards India’s agricultural interests, particularly those of the farm and dairy sectors.

Union Minister for Agriculture & Farmers’ Welfare and Rural Development, Shivraj Singh Chouhan, firmly stated that the agreement fully safeguards India’s agricultural interests, particularly those of the farm and dairy sectors. He underlined that under the leadership and guidance of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, the deal reflects a new benchmark of diplomacy, development and dignity, with the Prime Minister making it clear from the outset that farmers’ interests are non-negotiable. He reiterated that India’s staple grains, fruits, major crops, millets and dairy products remain completely secure and face no threat whatsoever. He emphasized that the interests of small and large farmers alike have been fully protected, and that the agreement will create fresh opportunities rather than risks for Indian agriculture. The Minister assured that no sudden or disruptive entry of foreign products will take place in the Indian market. He stressed that no market segment has been opened in a manner that could harm Indian farmers, and all major crops, food grains, fruits and dairy products remain shielded. On the confusion triggered by a recent tweet from the US Treasury Secretary about increased access for American farm products, Chouhan said that Commerce Minister Shri Piyush Goyal has already clarified the facts in Parliament. He reiterated that India has not opened its markets in any way that puts pressure on domestic farmers, and that the protections for key agricultural commodities remain intact. Highlighting the export potential unlocked by the agreement, Chouhan noted that India already exports rice to many countries, including the United States, and recently recorded exports worth around ₹63,000 crore. He stated that reduced tariffs will directly benefit India’s rice, spices and textile exports, and that growth in textile exports will help millions of cotton-growing farmers. The Minister affirmed that the deal is unequivocally in the interest of Indian farmers and opens up new export avenues, despite the misinformation being spread by the opposition.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/farm-produce-2-1325387_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NCC slides after Q3 PAT tumbles 37% YoY to Rs 122 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ncc-slides-after-q3-pat-tumbles-37-yoy-to-rs-122-cr/1672499</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672499</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 8.91% YoY to Rs 4,868.29 crore during the third quarter of FY26.

Revenue from operations fell 8.91% YoY to Rs 4,868.29 crore during the third quarter of FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 181.59 crore in Q3 FY26, down 32.75% from Rs 270.03 crore posted in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. In Q3 FY26, revenue from the construction segment was Rs 4,826.58 crore, reflecting an 8.68% YoY decline, while revenue from the real estate segment stood at Rs 41.71 crore, down 28.84% YoY. During the quarter, the company’s EBITDA slipped by 1.13% to Rs 436 crore, down from Rs 441 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous fiscal. As of 31 December 2025, NCC’s consolidated order book stood at Rs 79,571 crore, reflecting a 43% increase year-on-year. NCC is engaged in the infrastructure sector, primarily in the construction of industrial and commercial buildings, housing projects, roads, bridges and flyovers, water supply and environment projects, mining, power transmission lines, irrigation and hydrothermal power projects, etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NCC_71121013216_2598.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends recovery ahead of RBI policy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-recovery-ahead-of-rbi-policy/1672493</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672493</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee extends recovery in opening trades on Friday on the back of improving sentiments and FII inflows following US-India trades deal.

The Indian rupee extends recovery in opening trades on Friday on the back of improving sentiments and FII inflows following US-India trades deal. Easing crude oil prices from elevated levels are also seen supporting the counter. However, dollar strength and muted local equities could cap upside in the counter.Asian stock markets are trading mostly lower on Friday, following the broadly negative cues from Wall Street overnight, hurt by continued weakness in technology stocks which mirror their peers on the tech-heavy Nasdaq amid concerns about valuations and the impact of artificial intelligence. INR opened at Rs 90.28 per dollar and hit a high of 90.18 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee appreciated 13 paise to close at 90.34 against the US dollar. Meanwhile investors shift their focus to RBI monetary policy scheduled for the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TACL gains on securing multi-year orders worth over Rs 1,000 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tacl-gains-on-securing-multi-year-orders-worth-over-rs-1000-crore/1672498</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672498</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders, set to be executed over the next five years with commercialization beginning in FY27, span all major product lines, including gaskets, heat shields, forging components, hoses and anti-vibration parts, and chassis components.

The orders, set to be executed over the next five years with commercialization beginning in FY27, span all major product lines, including gaskets, heat shields, forging components, hoses and anti-vibration parts, and chassis components. The company secured approximately Rs 250 crore from its gaskets and heat shields business, including Rs 110 crore from exports. The forgings business received around Rs 500 crore in export orders, mainly from a new European client. Its JV, Marelli Talbros Chassis Systems, won approximately Rs 90 crore in export orders for BIW components for luxury vehicles, SUVs, and EVs, while Talbros Marugo Rubber secured around Rs 170 crore in domestic orders for hoses and anti-vibration parts. Talbros Automotive Components is engaged in the business of manufacturing gaskets and forging. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 1.3% to Rs 23.10 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 23.41 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 1% YoY to Rs 213.15 crore in the quarter ended 31 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TalbrosAuto_18421500249_549.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge lower in early trade; breadth negative]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-lower-in-early-trade-breadth-negative/1672489</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672489</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor losses in early trade as investors remained cautious ahead of the Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI) crucial monetary policy decision due later today.

The domestic equity indices traded with minor losses in early trade as investors remained cautious ahead of the Reserve Bank of India’s (RBI) crucial monetary policy decision due later today. The Nifty traded below the 25,600 level. Barring private bank shares, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the red. At 09:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tanked 123.88 points or 0.14% to 83,213.84. The Nifty 50 index fell 65.40 points or 0.26% to 25,577.40. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.69% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index tanked 0.93%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,128 shares rose and 1,821 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 2,150.51 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,129.82 crore in the Indian equity market on 05 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharti Airtel rose 0.13%. The company reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Berger Paints fell 1.72% after it has reported 8.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 271.16 crore despite 0.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2983.97 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. FSN E-Commerce (Nykaa) added 3.82% after its consolidated net profit surged 142.4% to Rs 63.31 crore on 26.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2973.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel had started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced today. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.66% to 6.651 compared with previous session close of 6.651. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1800 compared with its close of 90.3400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.0.4% to Rs 150,341. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.11% to 97.86. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.67% to 4.180. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 19 cents or 0.28% to $67.74 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian market edged lower as South Korea led the losses on Friday, following the tech-driven sell off on Wall Street. South Korea’s market, which is heavily weighted in favor of companies in the chip and automotive industries, have seen sharp swings in the past week as sentiment over tech stocks sours. Pharmaceutical stocks in Japan also slumped on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled his website offering discounted prescription medicines. On the commodities front, spot silver prices continued their decline, falling 1.63% after crashing about 13% on Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 1.20%, while the S&P 500 lost 1.23%, pushing it into negative territory for the year. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite posted the biggest decline, dropping 1.59%. Tech giant Alphabet came under pressure after reporting fourth-quarter results and flagging a sharp rise in artificial intelligence spending, with capital expenditure totaling $185 billion for 2026. Qualcomm slid more than 8% after posting a weaker forecast because of a global memory shortage.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-mutual-funds-picture-id157281690_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Properties Ltd Spikes 1.16%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-properties-ltd-spikes-116/1672486</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672486</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Godrej Properties Ltd rose 1.16% today to trade at Rs 1709.4.

Godrej Properties Ltd rose 1.16% today to trade at Rs 1709.4. The BSE Realty index is up 0.2% to quote at 6405.04. The index is down 9.37 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Lodha Developers Ltd increased 0.71% and Phoenix Mills Ltd added 0.66% on the day. The BSE Realty index went down 10.17 % over last one year compared to the 6.65% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Godrej Properties Ltd has lost 20.1% over last one month compared to 9.37% fall in BSE Realty index and 2.01% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 2164 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 61038 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 2522.55 on 05 Feb 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 1476.05 on 01 Feb 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejPropert_34796940031_15613.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd Falls 2.46%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/national-aluminium-company-ltd-falls-246/1672487</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672487</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[National Aluminium Company Ltd lost 2.46% today to trade at Rs 355.

National Aluminium Company Ltd lost 2.46% today to trade at Rs 355. The BSE Metal index is down 0.59% to quote at 38991.32. The index is up 2.62 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Hindustan Zinc Ltd decreased 1.71% and Tata Steel Ltd lost 0.89% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 38.09 % over last one year compared to the 6.65% surge in benchmark SENSEX. National Aluminium Company Ltd has added 0.71% over last one month compared to 2.62% gain in BSE Metal index and 2.01% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 48542 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 16.17 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 431.6 on 29 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 140 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NatlAluminium_39819539035_2304.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests flat start for equities ahead of RBI's monetary policy announcement]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-flat-start-for-equities-ahead-of-rbis-monetary-policy-announcement/1672473</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672473</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 18.50 points, suggesting a muted start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were down 18.50 points, suggesting a muted start for the Nifty 50 today. The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel had started its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday. The decision of RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 2,150.51 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 1,129.82 crore in the Indian equity market on 05 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs bought shares worth Rs 694.76 so far in February (till 05 February 2026). This follows their cash sales of Rs 38740.12 in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian market edged lower as South Korea led the losses on Friday, following the tech-driven sell off on Wall Street. South Korea’s market, which is heavily weighted in favor of companies in the chip and automotive industries, have seen sharp swings in the past week as sentiment over tech stocks sours. Pharmaceutical stocks in Japan also slumped on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled his website offering discounted prescription medicines. On the commodities front, spot silver prices continued their decline, falling 1.63% after crashing about 13% on Thursday. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 1.20%, while the S&P 500 lost 1.23%, pushing it into negative territory for the year. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite posted the biggest decline, dropping 1.59%. Tech giant Alphabet came under pressure after reporting fourth-quarter results and flagging a sharp rise in artificial intelligence spending, with capital expenditure totaling $185 billion for 2026. Qualcomm slid more than 8% after posting a weaker forecast because of a global memory shortage. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks closed deep in the red on Thursday, breaking a three-day winning streak as investors locked in profits at stretched valuations. The rally, fuelled by optimism around the India-US trade deal, ran into selling as caution crept in ahead of the Reserve Bank of India’s monetary policy decision due on Friday. Weakness was not limited to frontline stocks, with the broader market also sliding under pressure. The Nifty 50 slipped below the 25,650 mark, dragged down by sharp losses in metal, consumer durables and auto stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex slumped 503.76 points or 0.60% to 83,313.93. The Nifty 50 index fell 133.20 points or 0.52% to 25,642.80. Over the past three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex advanced 3.20%, while the Nifty gained 3.29%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IRB Infra’s board to consider bonus issue, interim dividend on 13 February 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/irb-infras-board-to-consider-bonus-issue-interim-dividend-on-13-february-2026/1672469</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672469</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the board will also review and take on record the company’s consolidated and standalone unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025.

According to an exchange filing, the board will also review and take on record the company’s consolidated and standalone unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The proposed bonus issue will be subject to approval from the company’s shareholders and other requisite regulatory approvals. The company further informed that 19 February 2026, has been fixed as the record date to determine the eligibility of shareholders for the interim dividend, if declared by the board. IRB is India's first integrated multinational transport infrastructure developer in the roads & highways segment. The company has a strong track record of constructing, tolling, operating, and maintaining around 19,000 lane kms pan-India in its existence of more than 25 years in India. The company reported a 41% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.82 crore on a 10.42% increase in total revenue from operations to Rs 1,751.02 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of IRB Infrastructure Developers rose 0.47% to end at Rs 42.47 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IRBInfraDevl_42061995161_28365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Bharti Airtel, Nykaa, Tata Motors PV, LIC, Berger Paints]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-nykaa-tata-motors-pv-lic-berger-paints/1672468</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1672468</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Earnings Today Tata Steel, Baazar Style Retail, Shipping Corporation of India, Lemon Tree Hotels, Whirlpool of India, Sun TV Network, Shree Cement, Sonata Software, BEML, BLS International Services, Bosch, Centum Electronics, CESC, Crompton Greaves, JK Tyre & Industries, Jana Small Finance Bank, Jubilant Pharmova, Kalpataru, Kalyan Jewellers India will declare their result later today.

Earnings Today Tata Steel, Baazar Style Retail, Shipping Corporation of India, Lemon Tree Hotels, Whirlpool of India, Sun TV Network, Shree Cement, Sonata Software, BEML, BLS International Services, Bosch, Centum Electronics, CESC, Crompton Greaves, JK Tyre & Industries, Jana Small Finance Bank, Jubilant Pharmova, Kalpataru, Kalyan Jewellers India will declare their result later today. Stocks to Watch: Bharti Airtel reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Berger Paints reported 8.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 271.16 crore despite 0.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2983.97 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. FSN E-Commerce (Nykaa)’s consolidated net profit surged 142.4% to Rs 63.31 crore on 26.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2973.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles reported consolidated net loss of Rs 3,486 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net profit of Rs 5406 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC)’s consolidated net profit climbed 17.5% YoY to Rs 12,930.44 crore in Q3 FY26. Total income jumped 15.7% YoY to Rs 236,776.30 crore during the quarter. Bharti Hexacom recorded a 48.7% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 481.29 crore on 4.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,359.90 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hero Motocorp’s consolidated net profit climbed 19.6% to Rs 1438.88 crore on 20.7% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 12,328.38 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>