<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IEX slides after APTEL defers hearing on power market coupling]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/iex-slides-after-aptel-defers-hearing-on-power-market-coupling/1664099</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664099</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The tribunal was hearing IEX’s plea seeking the withdrawal of the Central Electricity Regulatory Commission’s (CERC) July 2025 direction on day-ahead market (DAM) coupling.

The tribunal was hearing IEX’s plea seeking the withdrawal of the Central Electricity Regulatory Commission’s (CERC) July 2025 direction on day-ahead market (DAM) coupling. Market coupling is an economic model used in energy markets to create a single, uniform price for electricity across different trading platforms or exchanges, diluting IEX's dominant position. At the scheduled hearing on 9 January 2026, APTEL concluded proceedings for the day and deferred further hearing in the market coupling case to Monday, 19 January 2026. Ahead of the hearing, CERC issued a circular clarifying that its July 2025 communication should be treated as a “direction” rather than an “order.” In its petition, IEX has argued that the CERC direction is arbitrary, violates principles of natural justice, and would result in a loss of market share without delivering any tangible benefits. During an earlier hearing on 28 November, IEX had cited a Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) report alleging that certain CERC officials had indulged in insider trading. Meanwhile, the company clarified that media reports on the market coupling issue were based on a routine hearing before APTEL and that no fresh order had been passed. IEX further stated that the stock price movement was market-driven and that all developments, including CERC’s corrigendum to its earlier direction, had already been disclosed to the exchanges. IEX is India's premier electricity exchange providing a nationwide, automated trading platform for physical delivery of electricity, renewable power, renewable energy certificates and energy saving certificates. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 13.9% to Rs 123.35 crore on 10.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 153.92 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndianEnergyExchangeLtd_3642743015_70961.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JPY/INR futures tumble over half a percent ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jpyinr-futures-tumble-over-half-a-percent/1664097</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664097</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures climbed 0.24% to end at 90.26.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures climbed 0.24% to end at 90.26. GBP/INR and EUR/INR edge lower to settle at 121 and 105.19 respectively. JPY/INR futures tumble over half a percent to end at 57.40.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper up around 3.50% this week]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-up-around-350-this-week/1664098</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664098</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures marked a strong rebound today after a slide in last session as the UN World Economic Situation and Prospects 2026 predicted that global economic output will grow by 2.7% this year, marginally below the 2.8% estimated for 2025 but still maintaining a steady bias amid trade uncertainty and geopolitical unrest.

COMEX Copper futures marked a strong rebound today after a slide in last session as the UN World Economic Situation and Prospects 2026 predicted that global economic output will grow by 2.7% this year, marginally below the 2.8% estimated for 2025 but still maintaining a steady bias amid trade uncertainty and geopolitical unrest. COMEX Copper had lost around 1% yesterday but moved up 1.66% to $5.89 per pound today. The metal is up around 3.50% for this week. MCX Copper futures are trading at Rs 1278 per kg, up 0.66% on the day after hitting a high around Rs 1290 per kg. Equities edged up in Asia and Europe as DOW held near record highs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee droops further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-droops-further/1664094</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664094</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.2600 per Dollar on Friday (09 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.0300 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Coking Coal subscribed 8.08 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-coking-coal-subscribed-808-times/1664093</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664093</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 2,80,50,57,000 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Friday (9 January 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) received bids for 2,80,50,57,000 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Friday (9 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 8.08 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The offer is a pure offer-for-sale (OFS) of up to 46.57 crore equity shares of face value Rs 10 each by Coal India. At the upper price band of Rs 23 per equity share Caol India will raise Rs 1,071 crore. The IPO includes a reservation of up to 2.32 crore equity shares for eligible employees and up to 4.66 crore shares for eligible shareholders of Coal India under the shareholder reservation portion. Ahead of the IPO, Bharat Coking Coal on 8 January 2026, the company raised Rs 273.13 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 11.87 crore shares at Rs 23 each to 15 anchor investors. Bharat Coking Coal (BCCL) produces coking coal, non-coking coal, and washed coal. BCCL is India壮 largest producer of coking coal and operates primarily in the Jharia coalfields of Jharkhand and the Raniganj coalfields of West Bengal. It is the wholly-owned subsidiary of Coal India and was conferred with Mini Ratna status in 2014. The primary product is coking coal, catering to the steel and power industries. BCCL had an estimated coking coal reserve of approximately 7,910 million tonnes (mt) as of 01 Apri 2024. It accounted for 58.50% of the total domestic coking coal production in India in FY 2025. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 123.88 crore and sales of Rs 5,659 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends week deep in red on global geopolitical, tariff concerns]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-week-deep-in-red-on-global-geopolitical-tariff-concerns/1664066</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664066</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks ended the week on major losses, with all trading sessions closing in the red, as investors grappled with a confluence of global and domestic headwinds.

Domestic equity benchmarks ended the week on major losses, with all trading sessions closing in the red, as investors grappled with a confluence of global and domestic headwinds. Sentiment was dampened by escalating geopolitical tensions following U.S. military action in Venezuela, renewed concerns over potential U.S. tariffs, and persistent foreign institutional investor outflows. Adding to the volatility was a mixed set of Q3 earnings and business updates, which failed to provide clear directional cues. As a result, investors remained cautious, leading to broad-based selling and extended losses across the week. In the week ended on Friday, 09 January 2025, the S&P BSE Sensex dropped 2,185.77 points or 2.55% to settle at 83,576.24. The Nifty 50 index plunged 645.25 points or 2.45% to settle at 25,683.30. The BSE Mid-Cap index fell 2.59% to close at 46,304.80. The BSE Small-Cap index tumbled 3.86% at 49,912.11. Weekly Index Movement: Domestic equity market ended marginally lower on Monday after a choppy session. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 322.39 points or 0.38% to 85,439.62. The Nifty 50 index dropped 78.25 points or 0.30% to 26,250.30. Frontline equity benchmarks ended lower for a second straight session on Tuesday as risk sentiment weakened across markets. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 376.28 points or 0.44% to 85,063.34. The Nifty 50 index dropped 71.60 points or 0.27% to 26,178.70. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 0.81% while the Nifty fell 0.56%. Domestic equity benchmarks ended lower on Wednesday, extending losses for a third consecutive session. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 120.20 points or 0.12% to 84,961.14. The Nifty 50 index dropped 37.95 points or 0.14% to 26,140.75. In three consecutive sessions, the Sensex declined 0.93% while the Nifty fell 0.71%. Bears clawed deeper into Dalal Street as equity benchmarks slid for a fourth straight session on Thursday, with relentless selling. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 780.18 points or 0.92% to 84,180.96. The Nifty 50 index dropped 263.90 points or 1.01% to 25,876.85. In four consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 1.84% while the Nifty fell 1.71%. The key equity benchmarks ended with major losses on Friday, extending losses for a fifth straight session. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 604.72 points or 0.72% to 83,576.24. The Nifty 50 index dropped 193.55 points or 0.75% to 25,683.30. In five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%. US and Venezuela Situation: The U.S. launched a military operation in Venezuela over the weekend, resulting in the arrest of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores. The couple is set to appear before a New York court on drug-related charges. President Donald Trump stated that the U.S. is now in control of Venezuela and warned of potential further military action. The UN Security Council is scheduled to meet today to discuss the U.S. intervention, which UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres called a dangerous precedent. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves increased by $3.29 billion to $696.61 billion in the week ended December 26, 2025, according to the Reserve Bank of India’s Weekly Statistical Supplement released on January 2. Foreign currency assets (FCAs), the largest component of the reserves, stood at $559.61 billion, registering a marginal weekly increase of $184 million, the data showed. Gold reserves increased sharply by $2.96 billion during the week to $113.32 billion, contributing the most to the overall rise in reserves. India’s Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) with the International Monetary Fund rose by $60 million to $18.80 billion. The country’s reserve position in the IMF increased by $93 million to $4.88 billion as of December 26. India’s services sector growth slowed in December, with the HSBC India Services PMI Business Activity Index easing to 58.0 from 59.8 in November, marking the weakest expansion since January while still indicating solid growth. The Composite PMI Output Index also softened to 57.8 from 59.7 in November but remained well above its long-run average, pointing to continued overall economic expansion at a moderated pace. Stocks in Spotlight: Reliance Industries dropped 7.35%. Despite the company strongly denying reports that Russian Urals crude shipments were headed to its Jamnagar refinery. Reliance said it has not received any Russian crude for nearly three weeks and expects none in January, reiterating that it halted the use of Russian oil at its export-oriented unit in November 2025 amid rising geopolitical and regulatory risks, including US tariff threats under Donald Trump. The company also flagged inaccuracies in vessel tracking data and said it is shifting to diversified, non-Russian crude sourcing to avoid sanctions risks and maintain access to global markets. Trent fell 9.82%. The company’s Q3 FY26 business update showed steady but slowing momentum. While standalone revenue rose 17% YoY to Rs 5,220 crore and nine-month revenue increased 18% YoY, investors were concerned about flat sequential growth and a moderation compared with the stronger growth seen in recent quarters. HDFC Bank slipped 6.24%. Despite reporting double-digit loan growth in the December quarter. While advances rose 12% YoY and deposits grew 11.5%, investor concerns centred on the loan-deposit ratio, which increased to nearly 99%, well above management’s near-term target of below 90%. The elevated ratio has renewed worries over deposit constraints and raised questions about the bank’s ability to sustain above-industry growth in the coming financial year. Titan Company rallied 3.62%. The company’s domestic consumer businesses recorded around 40% year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26, with jewellery emerging as the biggest contributor. The jewellery portfolio posted about 41% YoY growth, supported by strong wedding and festive demand and improved performance across gold studded jewellery and gold coins. IndusInd Bank slipped 2.41%. The bank reported a 3.8% decline in deposits to Rs 3,94,022 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 4,09,438 crore as of 31st December 2024. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) declined 3.27%. The company said it has received a supply order from the Corps of Electronics and Mechanical Engineers (EME) of the Indian Army for overhaul, upgrade, and obsolescence management of the indigenous Pinaka Multi-Rocket Launcher Systems. GM Breweries plunged 10.48%. The company reported a 91.22% surge in standalone net profit of Rs 42.01 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 21.97 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased 21.89% YoY to Rs 202.14 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. KSH International lost 4.99%. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 129.02% to Rs 29.59 crore on a 50.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 712.14 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Kalyan Jewellers India added 2.12%. The company’s consolidated revenue climbed approximately 42% YoY, driven by robust festive demand, strong same-store sales growth (SSSG), and sharp traction in its digital platform, Candere. JSW Steel slipped 1.77%. The company recorded consolidated steel production of 7.48 million tonnes in Q3 FY26, marking a 6% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared with 7.03 million tonnes in Q3 FY25. AVG Logistics shed 0.39%. The company announced a strategic partnership with Nestlé India and Ashok Leyland to develop a green supply chain corridor. Under the partnership, AVG Logistics will deploy 50 CNG powered trucks to service Nestlé India, creating a dedicated green corridor aimed at improving efficiency while lowering environmental impact. The company said the fleet is expected to cover around 2.75 lakh kilometres per month and reduce carbon emissions by about 1.1 lakh kg of CO₂ annually. Global Markets: The Eurozone inflation stood at 2% in December, according to flash data from Eurostat, easing from 2.1% in November and aligning with the European Central Bank’s (ECB) target. Core inflation, which excludes volatile components such as energy, food, alcohol, and tobacco, moderated to 2.3% in December from 2.4% in the previous month. Services inflation also cooled, easing to 3.4% from 3.5% in November. The ECB kept its key deposit facility rate unchanged at 2% in December, extending its pause for a fourth consecutive meeting, after last cutting rates in June. Germany’s unemployment rate remained unchanged at 6.3% in December 2025, according to data released Wednesday by the Federal Employment Agency. China’s consumer prices rose 0.8% year-on-year, according to data from the National Bureau of Statistics, following a 0.7% increase in November. U.S. authorities reportedly said that Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were flown to New York following the operation and charged with narco-terrorism conspiracy and other crimes. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. US President Donald Trump has discussed a range of options, including potential military measures, to acquire Greenland, with the White House describing the move as a national security priority. Meanwhile U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tariff jitters extend selloff; Sensex drops 605 pts, Nifty below 25,700]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tariff-jitters-extend-selloff-sensex-drops-605-pts-nifty-below-25700/1664065</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664065</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Key equity benchmarks ended sharply lower for a fifth straight session, with the Nifty closing below 25,700, as investor caution intensified ahead of a US Supreme Court ruling on the legality of American tariffs.

Key equity benchmarks ended sharply lower for a fifth straight session, with the Nifty closing below 25,700, as investor caution intensified ahead of a US Supreme Court ruling on the legality of American tariffs. An early attempt at a rebound quickly fizzled, with indices turning decisively lower within minutes of the open. Sentiment also remained under pressure amid sustained foreign institutional investor selling, weak global cues and firm crude oil prices. Auto and consumer durables stocks led the decline, while energy, IT and PSU bank shares bucked the trend and closed higher. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 604.72 points or 0.72% to 83,576.24. The Nifty 50 index dropped 193.55 points or 0.75% to 25,683.30. In five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%. ICICI Bank (down 2.09%), Bajaj Finance (down 1.08%) and HDFC Bank (down 0.81%) dragged the Nifty lower today. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 0.90% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.74%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,062 shares rose and 3,104 shares fell. A total of 176 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 3.06% to 10.93. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper remained unchanged at 6.630 In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1675 compared with its close of 89.9025 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.46% to Rs 138,375. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.19% to 99.06. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.07% to 4.188. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 17 cents or 0.27% to $62.16 a barrel. Global Markets: European market advanced on Friday as investors assessed evolving economic cues and rising social pressures across the region. Most Asian market ended higher. China’s consumer prices rose 0.8% year-on-year, according to data from the National Bureau of Statistics, following a 0.7% increase in November. In the U.S., investors are awaiting two key catalysts on Friday. First, the Supreme Court could issue a ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump’s tariffs, which could have an impact on trade policy and the nation’s fiscal situation. Second, the December jobs report will be out on Friday morning. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose while the Nasdaq Composite came under pressure as investors moved away from technology stocks. The Dow Jones Industrial Average climbed 270.03 points, or 0.55%, and ended at 49,266.11; the S&P 500 advanced 0.01% and closed at 6,921.46, while The tech-heavy Nasdaq dropped 0.44% and settled at 23,480.02. Stocks in Spotlight: Indian Energy Exchange shares slumped 7.76%. The company clarified that media reports on the market coupling case were based on a routine hearing before Electricity Appellate Tribunal, with no fresh order passed. IEX said the move was market driven and all developments, including Central Electricity Regulatory Commission’s corrigendum on its earlier directions, have already been disclosed. Elecon Engineering Company dropped 15.79% after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 33.1% to Rs 71.99 crore despite a 4.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 551.74 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JSW Steel rose 0.35%. The company recorded consolidated steel production of 7.48 million tonnes in Q3 FY26, marking a 6% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared with 7.03 million tonnes in Q3 FY25. Power Grid Corporation of India shed 0.37%. The company has been declared as successful bidder under tariff based competitive bidding (TBCB) for the development of 3GW transmission system in Davanagere, Karnataka. Brahmaputra Infrastructure added 2.11% after the company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from the Office of the Chief Engineer, PWD (R&B), Jammu, for balance work related to the construction of the new Legislature Complex at Jammu. Bharat Heavy Electricals rose 0.88% after the company announced a major order win worth around Rs 5,400 crore, snapping the previous session’s sharp decline. Highway Infrastructure rose 0.81%. The company announced that it has entered into a contract agreement worth Rs 328.77 crore with the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI). Ravindra Energy fell 1.51%. The company has received 13 letter of award (LOA) from Hubli Electricity Supply Company (HESCOM) for setting up aggregate capacity of 62 MW(AC) solar power generators (SPGs) project in Karnataka. Indo Tech Transformers fell 2.21%. The company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 64.99 crore from ReNew Wind Energy (Jamb) for the manufacture and supply of six 220 kV-165 MVA transformers. Power Mech Projects shed 0.37%. The company’s wholly owned subsidiary, PM Green, secured an order worth Rs 3,126 crore from West Bengal State Electricity Distribution Company (WBSEDCL). IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 2,75,39,11,800 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:40 IST on Friday (9 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 7.94 times. The issue opened for bidding on today (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles sharply lower amid sharp sell-off in equities ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-sharply-lower-amid-sharp-sell-off-in-equities/1664064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664064</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee fell sharply today back beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark tracking sharp selloff in domestic equities and sustained firmness in dollar overseas.

The Indian rupee fell sharply today back beyond Rs 90 per dollar mark tracking sharp selloff in domestic equities and sustained firmness in dollar overseas. The benchmark BSE Sensex plummeted 604.72 points, or 0.72 percent, to 83,576.24, with selling seen across the board. The broader NSE Nifty index fell 193.55 points, or 0.75 percent, to 25,683.30. Besides, elevated global crude oil prices and persistent foreign fund outflows amid rising geopolitical tensions also weighed down the local unit. The rupee declined 26 paise to settle at 90.16 (provisional) against the US dollar. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened higher at 89.88 but lost ground through the day to settle at 90.16 (provisional) against the US dollar, down 26 paise from its previous close. During the day, the local currency traded between 89.88 and 90.25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bargain hunting may aid rebound, but global headwinds to cap gains]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bargain-hunting-may-aid-rebound-but-global-headwinds-to-cap-gains/1664063</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664063</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity market may attempt a rebound in the coming week, supported by bargain hunting after the recent sharp correction.

The domestic equity market may attempt a rebound in the coming week, supported by bargain hunting after the recent sharp correction. However, upside is likely to remain limited as global trade jitters, political uncertainty from Washington and persistent foreign fund outflows continue to weigh on sentiment. A key trigger will be the much awaited US Supreme Court verdict on the legality of tariffs imposed by former President Donald Trump. Markets are closely watching whether the court strikes down the tariffs fully or only in part. A ruling declaring the tariffs illegal could trigger a relief rally in Indian equities, as India has been among the worst affected, with cumulative tariffs of up to 50%. Uncertainty around India-US trade relations has intensified after the Trump administration linked higher tariffs to India’s purchases of Russian crude. The proposed bilateral trade agreement remains stuck despite multiple rounds of negotiations, keeping the trade outlook clouded. Fears of even steeper tariffs under US sanctions legislation have added to volatility. Persistent selling by foreign institutional investors remains another overhang. FIIs have been net sellers for several sessions, exacerbating the recent slide in benchmark indices amid adverse global cues. From a technical perspective, analysts note that the market has breached key short term support levels, reinforcing near term caution. While oversold indicators suggest the possibility of a technical bounce, a sustained recovery would depend on the market reclaiming critical resistance levels. A decisive break below recent lows could open the door to deeper downside. On the domestic macro front, market will track a busy economic calendar. December CPI inflation data due on Monday, January 12, will be closely watched for trends in food prices and implications for the Reserve Bank of India’s policy stance. Consumer price inflation had risen to 0.71% YoY in November 2025, from a record low of 0.25% in October. Attention then shifts to Wednesday, January 14, with the release of December WPI data. Wholesale food prices had declined 2.60% YoY in November, moderating from a sharper 5.04% fall in October. On Thursday, January 15, markets will track December trade data, including exports, imports and the trade balance. The trade deficit had narrowed to $24.53 billion in November 2025, compared with $31.92 billion a year earlier, according to preliminary estimates. December unemployment data will also be in focus, offering cues on labour market conditions and consumer demand. The unemployment rate fell to 4.7% in November, the lowest level since at least 2018. Globally, investors will navigate a packed macro calendar. On Tuesday, January 13, the spotlight will be on US December inflation data, with both headline and core CPI readings watched closely for signals on the Federal Reserve’s rate trajectory. Attention then shifts to China on Wednesday, January 14, with December trade data due, offering insights into global demand trends. Later on Wednesday, the focus returns to the US with producer price inflation (PPI) readings for October and November, followed by November retail sales data. The day will conclude with December existing home sales, providing further cues on the health of the US economy amid elevated interest rates.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-premium/1664060</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664060</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 25,810.80, a premium of 127.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,683.30 in the cash market.

The Nifty 27 January 2026 futures closed at 25,810.80, a premium of 127.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,683.30 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index tanked 193.55 points or 0.75% to 25,683.30. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 3.06% to 10.93. Indian Energy Exchange, HDFC Bank and Vodafone Idea were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks tumble for 5th day; IT shares rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-tumble-for-5th-day-it-shares-rally/1664058</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664058</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fifth straight session, as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S.

The key equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fifth straight session, as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on the legality of American tariffs. The Nifty settled below the 25,700 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 604.72 points or 0.72% to 83,576.24. The Nifty 50 index dropped 193.55 points or 0.75% to 25,683.30. In five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 0.90% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.74%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 3.06% to 10.93. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 0.40%), the Nifty IT index (up 0.28%) and the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 0.18%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Realty index (down 2.26%), the Nifty Auto index (down 1.15%) and the Nifty Cosumer Durables index (down 1.14%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper remained unchanged at 6.630 In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.1675 compared with its close of 89.9025 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.46% to Rs 138,375. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.19% to 99.06. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.07% to 4.188. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 17 cents or 0.27% to $62.16 a barrel. Global Markets: European markets advanced on Friday as investors assessed evolving economic cues and rising social pressures across the region. Asian markets ended higher, despite China’s consumer prices rose 0.8% year-on-year, according to data from the National Bureau of Statistics, following a 0.7% increase in November. In the U.S., investors are awaiting two key catalysts on Friday. First, the Supreme Court could issue a ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump’s tariffs, which could have an impact on trade policy and the nation’s fiscal situation. Second, the December jobs report will be out on Friday morning. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose while the Nasdaq Composite came under pressure as investors moved away from technology stocks. The Dow Jones Industrial Average climbed 270.03 points, or 0.55%, and ended at 49,266.11; the S&P 500 advanced 0.01% and closed at 6,921.46, while The tech-heavy Nasdaq dropped 0.44% and settled at 23,480.02.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index registers a drop of 2.26%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-registers-a-drop-of-226/1664057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664057</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index closed down 2.26% at 874 today.

Nifty Realty index closed down 2.26% at 874 today. The index has added 1.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Godrej Properties Ltd fell 4.94%, Anant Raj Ltd slipped 3.50% and DLF Ltd dropped 3.11%. The Nifty Realty index has decreased 12.00% over last one year compared to the 9.17% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Auto index has slid 1.15% and Nifty FMCG index has slid 1.08% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has declined 0.75% to close at 25683.3 while the SENSEX has declined 0.72% to close at 83576.24 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dow-jones-2-1458944_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 605 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,700 level; VIX spurts 3.06%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-605-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25700-level-vix-spurts-306/1664056</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664056</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fifth straight session, as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S.

The key equity benchmarks ended with major losses today, extending losses for a fifth straight session, as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on the legality of U.S. tariffs, which have weighed on markets in recent sessions. The Nifty settled below the 25,700 level. Oil & gas, IT and PSU bank shares advanced while realty, auto and consumer durables shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 604.72 points or 0.72% to 83,576.24. The Nifty 50 index dropped 193.55 points or 0.75% to 25,683.30. In five consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex declined 2.54% while the Nifty fell 2.45%. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 0.90% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.74%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,069 shares rose and 3,101 shares fell. A total of 184 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 3.06% to 10.93. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Bharat Coking Coal received bids for 2,43,23,01,000 shares as against 34,69,46,500 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:35 IST on Friday (9 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 7.01 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (9 January 2026) and it will close on Tuesday (13 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 21 and 23 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 600 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 2.26% to 874. The index declined 3.86% in the four consecutive trading session. Godrej Properties (down 4.91%), Anant Raj (down 3.73%), DLF (down 3.13%), Lodha Developers (down 2.59%) and Oberoi Realty (down 2%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 1.59%), Brigade Enterprises (down 1.12%), Sobha (down 0.68%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Elecon Engineering Company dropped 16.22% after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 33.1% to Rs 71.99 crore despite a 4.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 551.74 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JSW Steel rose 0.49%. The company recorded consolidated steel production of 7.48 million tonnes in Q3 FY26, marking a 6% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared with 7.03 million tonnes in Q3 FY25. Power grid Corporation of India shed 0.10%. The company has been declared as successful bidder under tariff based competitive bidding (TBCB) for the development of 3GW transmission system in Davanagere, Karnataka. Brahmaputra Infrastructure added 2.11% after the company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from the Office of the Chief Engineer, PWD (R&B), Jammu, for balance work related to the construction of the new Legislature Complex at Jammu. Highway Infrastructure rose 0.02%. The company announced that it has entered into a contract agreement worth Rs 328.77 crore with the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI). Ravindra Energy fell 1.51%. The company has received 13 letter of award (LOA) from Hubli Electricity Supply Company (HESCOM) for setting up aggregate capacity of 62 MW(AC) solar power generators (SPGs) project in Karnataka. Indo Tech Transformers fell 2.21%. The company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 64.99 crore from ReNew Wind Energy (Jamb) for the manufacture and supply of six 220 kV–165 MVA transformers. Power Mech Projects shed 0.35%. The company’s wholly owned subsidiary, PM Green, secured an order worth Rs 3,126 crore from West Bengal State Electricity Distribution Company (WBSEDCL). Global Markets: European shares traded higher on Friday as investors assessed evolving economic cues and rising social pressures across the region. Asian markets ended higher as investors digested China inflation data, with consumer prices rising 0.8% year-on-year in December, according to figures released by the National Bureau of Statistics, following a 0.7% increase in November. In the U.S., investors are awaiting two key catalysts on Friday. First, the Supreme Court could issue a ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump’s tariffs, which could have an impact on trade policy and the nation’s fiscal situation. Second, the December jobs report will be out on Friday morning. Overnight in the U.S., the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose while the Nasdaq Composite came under pressure as investors moved away from technology stocks. The Dow Jones Industrial Average climbed 270.03 points, or 0.55%, and ended at 49,266.11; the S&P 500 advanced 0.01% and closed at 6,921.46, while The tech-heavy Nasdaq dropped 0.44% and settled at 23,480.02

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bullion heads for weekly gain of 3% amid geopolitical uncertainty]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bullion-heads-for-weekly-gain-of-3-amid-geopolitical-uncertainty/1664052</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664052</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures rose to around $4,482 per ounce in Asian trade, snapping a two-day losing streak as safe-haven demand strengthened amid escalating geopolitical tensions.

Gold futures rose to around $4,482 per ounce in Asian trade, snapping a two-day losing streak as safe-haven demand strengthened amid escalating geopolitical tensions. The metal is set for a weekly gain of more than 3%, supported by uncertainty linked to the US incursion in Venezuela, a diplomatic standoff between China and Japan, and the ongoing Russia-Ukraine conflict. Meanwhile, the dollar index climbed toward 99 ahead of the US jobs report, reflecting expectations of a resilient labor market and shaping views on the Federal Reserve’s policy outlook. In the domestic market, MCX gold futures traded higher by about 0.6% at ₹138,615 per 10 grams, tracking global strength and risk-averse sentiment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Elecon Engineering Company Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/elecon-engineering-company-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1664049</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664049</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Energy Exchange Ltd, Manappuram Finance Ltd, Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd and Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 January 2026.

Indian Energy Exchange Ltd, Manappuram Finance Ltd, Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd and Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 09 January 2026. Elecon Engineering Company Ltd lost 15.61% to Rs 424.05 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 5.79 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.2 lakh shares in the past one month. Indian Energy Exchange Ltd tumbled 7.26% to Rs 139.2. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 177.1 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8.69 lakh shares in the past one month. Manappuram Finance Ltd crashed 6.77% to Rs 288.4. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6.39 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.76 lakh shares in the past one month. Thangamayil Jewellery Ltd corrected 6.11% to Rs 3651. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 36831 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10829 shares in the past one month. Transformers & Rectifiers India Ltd plummeted 5.50% to Rs 275.8. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 17.08 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9.78 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EleconEnggCo_20976911796_152.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ravindra Energy gains after bagging 62 MW solar projects from HESCOM ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ravindra-energy-gains-after-bagging-62-mw-solar-projects-from-hescom/1664047</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664047</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the project, the company will develop 62 MW (AC) projects spread across 13 HESCOM sub-stations.

Under the project, the company will develop 62 MW (AC) projects spread across 13 HESCOM sub-stations. HESCOM will enter into a 25 (Twenty-Five) years Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with the company at an average tariff of Rs 2.95 per unit. The estimated capital expenditure for the project is approximately Rs 225 crore. The projects are scheduled to be commissioned within 12 months from the signing of the PPA. Ravindra Energy is principally engaged in selling solar pumps, setting up of solar generation power plant (ground mount & rooftop) & generation and sale of power. The company’s consolidated net profit surged to Rs 30.79 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 1.15 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales jumped 672.3% YoY to Rs 120.33 crore in Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RavindraEnergyLtd_33336001143_6582.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shankara Building Products Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shankara-building-products-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1664043</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664043</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[N K Industries Ltd, Naksh Precious Metals Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 January 2026.

N K Industries Ltd, Naksh Precious Metals Ltd, Rollatainers Ltd and JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 09 January 2026. Shankara Building Products Ltd crashed 13.06% to Rs 110.15 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 47486 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 25093 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd lost 9.99% to Rs 66.96. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 127 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62 shares in the past one month. Naksh Precious Metals Ltd tumbled 9.98% to Rs 5.77. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4821 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 68353 shares in the past one month. Rollatainers Ltd fell 9.60% to Rs 1.79. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.4 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.96 lakh shares in the past one month. JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd pared 9.48% to Rs 10.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 33363 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 22423 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ShankaraBuildingProductsLtd_44449259665_28590.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tanvi Foods jump on incorporation of UK subsidiary]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tanvi-foods-jump-on-incorporation-of-uk-subsidiary/1664044</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664044</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the UK subsidiary was incorporated on 8 January 2026, with an initial paid up capital of GBP 1,000.

The company said the UK subsidiary was incorporated on 8 January 2026, with an initial paid up capital of GBP 1,000. Tanvi Foods (India) will hold a 51% stake by subscribing to 510 shares of GBP 1 each, with the investment to be made in cash. The new subsidiary will focus on frozen and ready to eat Indian food products, including frozen samosas, and is aimed at tapping the growing demand for ethnic and convenience foods in the UK. The company said the move will help strengthen its international presence and replicate the business model of its US arm, Tanvi Foods USA Inc., in the UK market. Tanvi Foods said the incorporation does not involve any acquisition and that there is no promoter interest in the subsidiary. The company added that all future transactions between the parent and the subsidiary will be conducted at arm’s length and in compliance with applicable laws in India and the UK. Tanvi Foods (India) is engaged in the processing and manufacture of corn based food products such as corn samosas, corn patties and spring rolls, and also trades in fresh and frozen corn and related products. On a consolidated basis, Tanvi Foods (India)'s net profit surged 282.35% to Rs 0.65 crore on 9.33% increase in net sales to Rs 48.29 crore in H1FY26 over H1FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TanviFoodsIndiaLtd_33349110964_69448.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AuSom Enterprise jumps 21% in four days]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ausom-enterprise-jumps-21-in-four-days/1664045</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664045</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shares of AuSom Enterprise surged 21.1% in four trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 109 on 5 January 2026.

Shares of AuSom Enterprise surged 21.1% in four trading sessions from its recent closing low of Rs 109 on 5 January 2026. The stock hit an all-time high of Rs 132 today. On the BSE, 0.89 lakh shares have been traded so far, compared with an average daily volume of 7,431 shares over the past two weeks. The stock had outperformed the market over the past month, rising 20.82% as against the Sensex's 1.37% drop. The stock had outperformed the market over the three months, rising 22.85% as against the Sensex's 1.62% jump. The counter had also outperformed the market in the past year, soaring 30.56% as against Sensex's 7.58% rise. On the technical front, the stock's daily RSI (relative strength index) stood at 83.352. The RSI oscillates between zero and 100. Traditionally, the RSI is considered overbought when above 70 and oversold when below 30. On the daily chart, the stock was trading above its 50-day, 100-day, and 200-day simple moving average (SMA), placed at 80.80, 77.33, and 42.35, respectively. These levels will act as crucial support zones in the near term. AuSom Enterprise is engaged in trading in the financial and commodity markets, along with the manufacturing and trading of jewellery. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 6.7% to Rs 1.81 crore on a 5014.2% surge in total income to Rs 122.23 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AusomEnter_45506933337_2386.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 651 pts; consumer durables shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-651-pts-consumer-durables-shares-decline/1664039</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1664039</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in the mid- afternoon as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S.

The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in the mid- afternoon as investors remained cautious ahead of a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on the legality of U.S. tariffs, which have weighed on markets in recent sessions. The Nifty traded near the 25,650 mark. Consumer durables shares extended losses for second consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 651.25 points or 0.77% to 83,539.71. The Nifty 50 index dropped 223.30 points or 0.87% to 25,653.95. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index tanked 1.13% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index declined 1.79%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 965 shares rose and 3,126 shares fell. A total of 180 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index declined 1.28% to 37,548.90. The index fell 2.05% in for the two consecutive trading session. Amber Enterprises India (down 2.7%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (down 2.68%), V-Guard Industries (down 2.23%), PG Electroplast (down 1.69%), Kajaria Ceramics (down 1.3%), Blue Star (down 1.3%), Whirlpool of India (down 1.23%), Kalyan Jewellers India (down 1.22%), Cera Sanitaryware (down 1.19%) and Titan Company (down 0.92%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.15% to 6.640 compared with previous session close of 6.630. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2275 compared with its close of 89.9025 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rose 0.46% to Rs 138,364. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.16% to 99.03. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.12% to 4.190. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement added 57 cents or 0.92% to $62.56 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Indo Tech Transformers fell 2.13%. The company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 64.99 crore from ReNew Wind Energy (Jamb) for the manufacture and supply of six 220 kV–165 MVA transformers. Waaree Energies shed 2.68%. The company said that it has received a one-time order from a renowned domestic customer engaged in owning, developing, and operating renewable power projects in India for the supply of 105 MW solar modules in FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>