<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:37:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Government approves wheat exports of 25 lakh metric tonnes, allows additional wheat product and sugar exports ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/government-approves-wheat-exports-of-25-lakh-metric-tonnes-allows-additional-wheat-product-and-sugar-exports/1676863</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676863</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India has approved the export of 25 Lakh Metric Tonnes (LMT) of wheat along with an additional 5 LMT of wheat products, taking a decisive and farmer-centric step to stabilise domestic markets and ensure remunerative returns to producers.

The Government of India has approved the export of 25 Lakh Metric Tonnes (LMT) of wheat along with an additional 5 LMT of wheat products, taking a decisive and farmer-centric step to stabilise domestic markets and ensure remunerative returns to producers. Wheat stock availability with private entities during 2025–26 stands at approximately 75 LMT, which is nearly 32 LMT higher compared to the corresponding period last year. This substantial year-on-year increase indicates a comfortable supply position in the country. Furthermore, as on 1st April 2026, total wheat availability in the central pool with FCI is projected at around 182 LMT thus ensuring that export permissions will not impact domestic food security requirements. Wheat acreage in Rabi 2026 has also increased to about 334.17 lakh hectares compared to 328.04 lakh hectares last year. In view of higher stock availability, softening prices, expected higher production, and the need to prevent distress sales during peak arrivals, the Government’s decision to permit export of 25 LMT of wheat and 5 LMT wheat products will help stabilise domestic prices, improve market liquidity, ensure efficient stock rotation, and further strengthen farmers’ income while national food security. Along with this, to facilitate sugar exports, Government of India has decided to allow export of an additional 5 LMT of sugar to willing sugar mills during the current Sugar Season 2025–26. Earlier, the Government had permitted export of 15 LMT of sugar during the current Sugar Season 2025–26 vide order dated 14.11.2025. As per information furnished by sugar mills, only about 1.97 LMT of sugar has been exported up to 31.01.2026. In addition, approximately 2.72 LMT of sugar has been contracted for export by sugar mills as on date. The additional export quantity of 5 LMT shall be made available to willing sugar mills subject to the condition that at least 70% of their allocated quantity is exported by 30 June 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/coworker-carrying-cardboard-box-in-warehouse-picture-id5207_commodities.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee Falls]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-falls/1676862</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676862</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 90.6900 per Dollar on Friday (13 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.6300 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WPI data, PMI figures, international trade numbers to remain in focus]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wpi-data-pmi-figures-international-trade-numbers-to-remain-in-focus/1676856</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676856</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equities head into the next trading week under marked pressure and elevated volatility after a sharp late-week sell-off.

Indian equities head into the next trading week under marked pressure and elevated volatility after a sharp late-week sell-off. Domestic benchmarks ended the week on a significantly weaker note, with the Nifty dipping below 25,500 and the Sensex dropping over 1,000 pts amid broad-based weakness, including tech and cyclical stocks. Retail inflation in India rose to 2.75% in January, the first print under a revamped CPI series and within the RBI’s target band — a factor that may temper expectations of near-term monetary easing. The rupee remained under strain, trading weaker against the U.S. dollar amid risk-off sentiment. Globally, markets retreated from record highs as concerns around tech earnings and cautious positioning ahead of U.S. inflation data weighed on sentiment. With macro headwinds and policy uncertainties lingering, large-caps and defensive sectors could remain in foucs as investors continue to monitor global inflation cues and earnings signals for directional clarity. In India, Wholesales Price Index data for the month of January would be released on Monday (16 February 2026). India’s wholesale prices increased 0.83% year-on-year in December 2025, rebounding from a 0.32% drop recorded in November. This marked the first increase in three months and the fastest pace since April, mainly supported by faster rises in manufacturing prices. The Balance of Trade data for January 2026 would also be announced on the same day. The merchandise trade balance in India widened to $25 billion in December of 2025 from $20.6 billion in the corresponding period of the previous year, marking the sharpest trade gap for the month on record. Imports rose by 8.8% from the previous year to $63.6 billion while exports grew by 1.8% to $38.5 billion. On Wednesday (18 February 2026), the M3 Money Supply figures for the week ended on February 06 would be made public. Money Supply M3 in India increased to 322144.23 INR Billion in the week ending December 31 from 246833.33 INR Billion two weeks before. On Friday, the Manufacturing PMI, the Services PMI and the Composite PMI for the month of February would be released. The HSBC India Manufacturing PMI rose to 55.4 in January 2026 from 55.0 in December, but was revised lower from the initial estimate of 56.8. The reading still indicates a solid improvement in operating conditions at the start of the year. The HSBC India Services PMI was revised lower to 58.5 in January 2026 from a preliminary estimate of 59.3. However, the latest figure remained above the December reading of 58.0, which marked the softest expansion in 11 months, supported by faster growth in output and new business. India’s Composite PMI by HSBC came in at 58.4 in January 2026, below the flash print of 59.5 yet higher than December’s 11-month low of 57.8. The figure points to a solid pace of expansion, driven by improved momentum among goods producers and service providers. In China, the preliminary reading for the current account deficit for the fourth quarter would be announced on Saturday (14 February 2026). China’s current account surplus jumped to a record $198.7 billion in the third quarter of 2025, exceeding an initial estimate of $195.6 billion and up sharply from $157.4 billion in the same period last year. On Monday (16 February 2026), the year-to-date (YTD) FDI data for the period ended in January 2026 would be made public. Foreign direct investment (FDI) into China fell 9.5% to CNY 747.77 billion in 2025, following a sharp 24.7% decline in 2024 and marking the third consecutive year of contraction. On Tuesday (24 February 2026), the loan prime rate for one-year and five-year tenors would be unveiled. The People’s Bank of China (PBoC) kept key lending rates at record lows for an eighth consecutive month in January after earlier reductions to the central bank’s relending and rediscount facility rates had already taken effect. The one-year loan prime rate (LPR) remained at 3.0%, while the five-year LPRwas unchanged at 3.5%. In the United States, the ADP Employment Change Weekly figures would be announced on Tuesday (17 February 2026). US private employers added an average of 6,500 jobs per week in the four weeks ending January 24, 2026, up from 5,000 in the prior period, according to ADP Research. Tuesday would also see the release of the NAHB Housing Market Index for the month of February. The NAHB/Wells Fargo Housing Market Index fell to 37.0 in January 2026, down from 39.0 in December. On Wednesday (18 February 2026), the Industrial Production data for the month of January would be made public. Industrial production in the United States rose 0.4% month-over-month in December, the same as in November. On Thursday (19 February 2026), the FOMC Minutes from the latest US Federal Reserve Meeting would be made public. The Fed left the federal funds rate unchanged at the 3.5%–3.75% target range in its January 2026 meeting after three consecutive rate cuts last year that pushed borrowing costs to their lowest level since 2022. The Balance of Trade data for the month of December would also be released on Thursday. The trade deficit in the US widened sharply to $56.8 billion in November 2025, the highest in four months, compared to a $29.2 billion gap in October which was the lowest since 2009. On Friday (20 February 2026), the Core Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) Price Index for the month of December would be announced. The US personal consumption expenditures (PCE) price index excluding food and energy increased by 0.2% month over month in November 2025, unchanged from October, according to delayed data from the Bureau of Economic Analysis (BEA). Friday would also see the release of advanced estimates for the fourth quarter GDP. The US economy expanded at an annualized rate of 4.4% in Q3 2025, slightly above the initial estimate of 4.3% and marking the strongest GDP growth since Q3 2023.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Week Ahead<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper sees sustained stress, breaks under $6 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-sees-sustained-stress-breaks-under-6-mark/1676805</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676805</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures saw an accelerated correction today as elevated inventories and stressed equities weighed on the red metal.

COMEX Copper futures saw an accelerated correction today as elevated inventories and stressed equities weighed on the red metal. The counter currently trades at $5.70 per pound, down 1.36% on the day and testing around one-week low. Copper had lost around 3% in last session amid a hefty drop in the US equities. The US markets tumbled on concerns about the impact of the artificial intelligence. The Nasdaq plunged 2% and S&P 500 lost 1.6% yesterday. The Dow slumped 1.3% too. AI jitters weighed on Asian markets too. Shanghai Composite index fell 1.26%. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index tanked 1.72%. Japanese NIKKEI 225 index lost 1.21%. European stocks are witnessing mixed moves ahead of weekend. MCX Copper also saw hefty losses, particularly after the Rs 1200 per kg mark gave up. The counter currently trades at Rs 1190 per kg, down 1.35% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-3321166__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR edges lower tracking negative trend in domestic equities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-edges-lower-tracking-negative-trend-in-domestic-equities/1676803</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676803</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee consolidated in a narrow range and settled for the day 3 paise lower at 90.64 (provisional) against the US dollar on Friday, tracking the strength of the American currency in the overseas market and a negative trend in domestic equities.

The Indian rupee consolidated in a narrow range and settled for the day 3 paise lower at 90.64 (provisional) against the US dollar on Friday, tracking the strength of the American currency in the overseas market and a negative trend in domestic equities. The dollar index was oscillating on either side of 97 mark amid improved US data but awaiting inflation data later in the day. Indian shares tumbled on Friday to extend losses from the previous session as investors fretted about the impact AI could have on revenues and profit margins of financial, transportation and logistics and even commercial real estate companies. The talk around AI has added to uncertainty about how fast traditional service models might change. Ongoing U.S.-Iran tensions and dwindling hopes for Fed rate cuts also kept investors on edge ahead of the U.S. Labor Department's report on consumer price inflation for January later in the day that could shed additional clues on the likely path of interest rates. The benchmark BSE Sensex plunged 1,048.16 points, or 1.25 percent, to 82,626.76 while the NSE Nifty index plummeted 336.10 points, or 1.30 percent, to 25,471.10.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end with major losses; Nifty tumbles below 25,500 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-with-major-losses-nifty-tumbles-below-25500-level/1676802</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676802</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian equity benchmarks ended the week lower, weighed down by heavy selling in IT stocks and fading hopes of near-term US rate cuts after stronger-than-expected US jobs data.

Indian equity benchmarks ended the week lower, weighed down by heavy selling in IT stocks and fading hopes of near-term US rate cuts after stronger-than-expected US jobs data. Markets had begun the week on a firm footing, supported by FII inflows, optimism around the India–US trade agreement and positive Asian cues, but sentiment turned cautious mid-week ahead of key global triggers. In the week ended on Friday, 13 February 2025, the S&P BSE Sensex tanked 953.64 points or 1.14% to settle at 82,626.76. The Nifty 50 index fell 222.6 points or 0.86% to settle at 25,471.10. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index fell 1.58% to close at 16,030.52. The BSE 250 Small-Cap index declined 1.50% to close at 6,350.84. Weekly Index Movement: The key equity benchmarks closed sharply higher on Monday. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 485.35 points or 0.58% to 84,065.75. The Nifty 50 index rallied 173.60 points or 0.68% to 25,867.30. The key equity benchmarks closed with moderate gains on Tuesday. The S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 208.17 points or 0.25% to 84,273.92. The Nifty 50 index rallied 67.85 points or 0.26% to 25,935.15. The key domestic indices ended almost flat on Wednesday. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 40.28 points or 0.05% to 84,233.64. The Nifty 50 index rose 18.70 points or 0.07% to 25,953.85. Benchmark indices closed sharply lower on Thursday. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 558.72 points or 0.66% to 83,674.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 146.65 points or 0.57% to 25,807.20. The key equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday. The S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 1,048.16 points or 1.25% to 82,626.76. The Nifty 50 index tanked 336.10 points or 1.30% to 25,471.10. Economy: India's retail inflation stood at 2.75% in January 2026 under the new Consumer Price Index (CPI) series with base year 2024=100. The corresponding inflation rates were 2.73% for rural areas and 2.77% for urban areas. This is the first retail inflation released by the government under the new CPI series. Meanwhile, the central government’s net direct tax collections, after accounting for refunds, stood at Rs 19.43 lakh crore so far this fiscal year, up 9.4% from a year earlier. Net corporate tax collection rose 14.51% to Rs 8.90 lakh crore, while taxes from non-corporates, including individuals and Hindu Undivided Families (HUFs), rose 5.91 % to about Rs 10.03 lakh crore. India-Malaysia sign key agreements: Prime Minister (PM) Narendra Modi visited Malaysia from 7 February to 8 February 2026 and held bilateral talks with Malaysian PM Anwar Ibrahim. The wide-ranging talks during the two-day official visit, marked a significant step in strengthening the Comprehensive Strategic Partnership between India and Malaysia. India and Malaysia has signed 11 Memorandums of Understanding (MoUs) and exchanged several bilateral documents across a broad range of sectors during Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s two-day official visit to Kuala Lumpur. The agreements, signed in the presence of PM Modi and his Malaysian counterpart Anwar Ibrahim following delegation-level talks, span trade and investment, semiconductors, digital economy, healthcare, security cooperation and peacekeeping, officials said. The two leaders launched Malaysia-India Digital Council (MLDC) and backed NPCI–PayNet payment link, paving way to introduce India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) system in Malaysia. This initiative will simplify cross-border payments for businesses and travellers and strengthen financial ties between the two economies. Stocks in Spotlight: State Bank of India has rallied 12.41%. The bank reported 24.49% jump in net profit to Rs 21,028 crore on a 9.69% increase in total income to Rs 1,40,915 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The bank has received a one-time dividend income of nearly Rs 2,200 crore from SBI Mutual Fund during the quarter, along with treasury gains of approximately Rs 3,280 crore. Kalyan Jewellers India zoomed 10.04%. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 90.24% to Rs 416.29 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by a 42.17% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 10,343.4 crore compared to the same period last year. Atul Auto surged 11.40%. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 98.06% to Rs 15.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 7.75 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations grew by 18.39% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 230.86 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Sterlite Technologies rose 14.70%. The company said its board approved the issuance of up to 45.3 crore convertible warrants to promoter Twin Star Overseas on a preferential basis at Rs 110 per warrant, aggregating Rs 498.3 crore. Each warrant is convertible into one equity share within 18 months from the date of allotment. On a fully diluted basis, Twin Star Overseas’ shareholding is expected to increase to 47.75% from 42.9%, subject to full conversion of the warrants and shareholder approval. As on December 2025, total promoter shareholding in the company stood at 44.44%. Shanti Gold International soared 6.06%. The company reported a 127.97% rise in net profit to Rs 40.08 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 17.58 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operation for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs. 636.93 crore, as against Rs. 303.22 crore in Q3 FY25, reflecting a 110.06% growth on a year-on-year basis. Eicher Motors rallied 12.44%. The company reported a 21.38% year-on-year (YoY) increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,170.50 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations surged 22.94% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,114.04 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) shed 1.22%. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 32.62% to Rs 3,931.30 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,964.31 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total income increased by 26.93% year on year to Rs 39,639.45 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Britannia Industries gained 1.26%. The company’s consolidated net profit stood at Rs 679.96 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.89% YoY from Rs 581.69 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit rose 3.89% from Rs 654.47 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations increased 9.45% YoY to Rs 4,885.23 crore, compared with Rs 4,463.30 crore in the year-ago quarter. Sequentially, revenue grew 2.80% from Rs 4,752.17 crore. Lenskart Solutions surged 10.57%. The company reported 237.9% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 132.7 crore on a 37.4% rise in revenue to Rs 2,307.7 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Global Markets: The China's consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. In U.S, December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat following a 0.6% increase in November, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ January nonfarm payrolls report showed job growth of 130,000 in January. Media reports suggested that the job growth gains for January were estimated to be around 55,000. Jobs growth in December was downwardly revised to 48,000.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - The Week That Was<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures linger below $63 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-oil-futures-linger-below-63-per-barrel/1676757</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676757</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures lingered below $63 per barrel on Friday, extending a second consecutive weekly retreat as persistent oversupply concerns dominated market sentiment.

WTI crude oil futures lingered below $63 per barrel on Friday, extending a second consecutive weekly retreat as persistent oversupply concerns dominated market sentiment. The International Energy Agency projected a record 2026 surplus of 3.7 million barrels per day and revised downwards its global oil demand forecast, citing inventory accumulation in 2025 at the fastest pace since the pandemic. Oil lost around 3% in last session and is holding near one-week low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Friday the 13th rattles Dalal Street; Nifty slips below 25,500 in broad sell-off]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/friday-the-13th-rattles-dalal-street-nifty-slips-below-25500-in-broad-sell-off/1676758</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676758</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Benchmark indices closed sharply lower on Friday as widespread selling pressure dominated the session.

Benchmark indices closed sharply lower on Friday as widespread selling pressure dominated the session. Indices traded with a negative bias throughout the day, with the lack of fresh domestic catalysts keeping sentiment subdued. The Nifty settled below the 25,500 mark, reflecting sustained weakness across sectors. All NSE sectoral indices ended in the red. IT stocks extended losses amid ongoing concerns over AI-led disruption, while private banks, metals and energy shares also witnessed significant selling pressure. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,048.16 points or 1.25% to 82,626.76. The Nifty 50 index tanked 336.10 points or 1.30% to 25,471.10. Reliance Industries (down 2.09%), HDFC Bank (down 1.81%) and ICICI Bank (down 1.01%) were major Nifty drags today. Broader markets also witnessed heavy selling, with the BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 1.58% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 1.50%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,253 shares rose and 2,960 shares fell. A total of 155 shares were unchanged. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.10% to 6.679 compared with previous session close of 6.686. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6500 compared with its close of 90.6100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.74% to Rs 153,970. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.15% to 97.07. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.39% to 4.120. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 29 cents or 0.43% to $67.81 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently down by 189 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. Most European shares declined on Friday as investors digested more quarterly earnings as well as an overnight slide in U.S. technology shares. Data released earlier Friday showed that German wholesale prices rose by 1.2% in January compared with the same month last year. Asian indices ended lower, tracking Wall Street declines, as fears over artificial intelligence disruption drove the S&P 500 to a third straight day of losses. All eyes are on U.S. inflation data due later in the day. Certain pockets of the U.S. stock market have been hit this year by the release of AI tools that threaten to automate tasks performed by some companies—or at least risk eating into their profit margins. Overnight on Wall Street, US stocks fell sharply Thursday as the market punished companies seen as potential losers from artificial-intelligence technology. The S&P 500 fell 108.71 points to 6,832.76. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 669.42 to 49,451.98, and the Nasdaq Composite sank 469.32 to 22,597.15. Stocks in Spotlight: The Nifty Metal index declined 3.31% to 11,872.80, after having gained 3% over the previous five trading sessions. Among constituents, Hindalco Industries dropped 6.08%, National Aluminium Company fell 5.42%, Hindustan Copper declined 5.16% and Hindustan Zinc slipped 4.91%. Vedanta lost 4.11%, Jindal Stainless fell 4.10% and Adani Enterprises declined 3.83%. Welspun Corp dropped 3.63%, NMDC fell 3.42% and Lloyds Metals and Energy declined 2.66%. Tata Steel slipped 2.47%, Jindal Steel and Power fell 1.65% and JSW Steel declined 1.51%, while APL Apollo Tubes and Steel Authority of India fell 1.02% and 0.84%, respectively. Engineers India rallied 11.64% after the company reported a sharp jump in revenue and profitability for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net sales rose 58.29% YoY to Rs 1,210.24 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 764.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, revenue increased 31.36% from Rs 921.29 crore in Q2 FY26. Net profit surged 219.30% YoY to Rs 347.17 crore, up from Rs 108.73 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PAT jumped 315.82% from Rs 83.49 crore. Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) declined 3.17%. The company reported 1.60% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 8,371.85 crore in Q3 FY2, compared with Rs 8,239.92 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations declined 6.43% YoY to Rs 31,546.51 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Hindalco Industries tumbled 5.77% after the company reported 45% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 2,049 crore despite a 14% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 66,521 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Info Edge (India) fell 0.30%. The company reported a 23.11% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 246.45 crore on 13.85% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 764.55 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Honasa Consumer gained 0.82% after reporting a strong operational and financial performance for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a reported basis, consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% YoY from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit after tax stood at Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, up 92.9% YoY from Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY25. Indian Hotels Company declined 1.59%. The company consolidated net profit jumped 55.10% to Rs 903.23 crore on 12.91% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,841.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. NIBE tumbled 6.01% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 18.87 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 1.94 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 60.3% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 59.08 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Lupin shed 0.50%. The company reported 37.46% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,175.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 855.16 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1676752</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676752</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,481 a premium of 9.9 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,471.10 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,481 a premium of 9.9 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,471.10 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index tanked 336.10 points or 1.30% to 25,471.10. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 13.36% to 13.29. Infosys (Infy), Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and HDFC Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 1,048 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,500 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-1048-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25500-level/1676749</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676749</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, weighed down by a steep sell-off in IT stocks that dented investor sentiment amid rising concerns over AI-led disruption and its potential impact on traditional outsourcing models.

The key equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, weighed down by a steep sell-off in IT stocks that dented investor sentiment amid rising concerns over AI-led disruption and its potential impact on traditional outsourcing models. The Nifty closed below the 25,500 mark. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, tumbled 1,048.16 points or 1.25% to 82,626.76. The Nifty 50 index tanked 336.10 points or 1.30% to 25,471.10. The broader market underperformed the headline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 1.58% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 1.50%. The market breadth was weak. Among the sectoral indices, the PSU Bank index (down 0.68%), the Nifty Media index (down 0.76%) and the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.85%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Metal index (down 3.31%), the Nifty Realty index (down 2.23%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 1.88%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.10% to 6.679 compared with previous session close of 6.686. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6500 compared with its close of 90.6100 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement rose 0.74% to Rs 153,970. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.15% to 97.07. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.39% to 4.120. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 29 cents or 0.43% to $67.81 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares advanced on Friday as investors awaited U.S. inflation data, due later today. Asian markets ended lower, tracking Wall Street declines, as fears over artificial intelligence disruption drove the S&P 500 to a third straight day of losses. Certain pockets of the U.S. stock market have been hit this year by the release of AI tools that threaten to automate tasks performed by some companies—or at least risk eating into their profit margins. Overnight on Wall Street, US stocks fell sharply Thursday as the market punished companies seen as potential losers from artificial-intelligence technology. The S&P 500 fell 108.71 points to 6,832.76. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 669.42 to 49,451.98, and the Nasdaq Composite sank 469.32 to 22,597.15.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index declines 3.31%, NIFTY Tumbles 1.30% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-declines-331-nifty-tumbles-130/1676714</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676714</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index ended down 3.31% at 11872.8 today.

Nifty Metal index ended down 3.31% at 11872.8 today. The index is up 2.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, NMDC Ltd slipped 6.27%, Hindalco Industries Ltd dropped 5.74% and National Aluminium Company Ltd shed 5.52%. The Nifty Metal index is up 42.00% over last one year compared to the 10.59% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Commodities index is down 2.24% and Nifty Realty index has slid 2.23% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has slid 1.30% to close at 25471.1 while the SENSEX is down 1.25% to close at 82626.76 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background-picture-i_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers tumble over 1%; metal shares slide ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-tumble-over-1-metal-shares-slide/1676713</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676713</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with substantial losses today as sentiment weakened following after US-based artificial intelligence startup Anthropic introduced a tool targeted at corporate legal teams, raising concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models.

The key equity benchmarks ended with substantial losses today as sentiment weakened following after US-based artificial intelligence startup Anthropic introduced a tool targeted at corporate legal teams, raising concerns about the long-term implications for outsourcing-driven IT business models. Investors adopted a risk-off approach. Traders will monitor upcoming US CPI data due later today. The Nifty closed below the 25,500 mark. All the sectoral indices on the NSE ended in red, led by losses in metal, realty, and FMCG shares. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,048.16 points or 1.25% to 82,626.76. The Nifty 50 index tanked 336.10 points or 1.30% to 25,471.10. The broader market underperformed the headline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index dropped 1.58% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index slipped 1.50%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,320 shares rose and 2,881 shares fell. A total of 167 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 13.36% to 13.29. Buzzing Index: The Metal index declined 3.42% to 11858.85. The index jumped 3% in the past five trading sessions. NMDC (down 6.36%), National Aluminium Company (down 5.56%), Hindalco Industries (down 5.53%), Hindustan Copper (down 5.12%), Hindustan Zinc (down 4.95%), Jindal Stainless (down 4.58%), Vedanta (down 4.2%), Welspun Corp (down 3.57%), Adani Enterprises (down 3.29%) and Lloyds Metals & Energy (down 2.95%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Lupin shed 0.50%. The company reported 37.46% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,175.55 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 855.16 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 24.26% year-on-year to Rs 7,167.52 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) declined 3.06%. The company reported 1.60% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 8,371.85 crore in Q3 FY2, compared with Rs 8,239.92 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations declined 6.43% YoY to Rs 31,546.51 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Hindalco Industries tumbled 5.77% after the company reported 45% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 2,049 crore despite a 14% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 66,521 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Info Edge (India) fell 1.50%. The company reported a 23.11% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 246.45 crore on 13.85% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 764.55 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Honasa Consumer gained 0.82% after reporting a strong operational and financial performance for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. On a reported basis, consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 602 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% YoY from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit after tax stood at Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, up 92.9% YoY from Rs 26 crore in Q3 FY25. Indian Hotels Company declined 1.59%. The company consolidated net profit jumped 55.10% to Rs 903.23 crore on 12.91% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,841.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. NIBE tumbled 6.54% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 18.87 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 1.94 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 60.3% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 59.08 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: Most European market advanced as investors awaited U.S. inflation data, due later today. The Asia-Pacific ended lower Friday, tracking Wall Street declines, as fears over artificial intelligence disruption drove the S&P 500 to a third straight day of losses. Certain pockets of the U.S. stock market have been hit this year by the release of AI tools that threaten to automate tasks performed by some companies—or at least risk eating into their profit margins. Overnight on Wall Street, US stocks fell sharply Thursday as the market punished companies seen as potential losers from artificial-intelligence technology. The S&P 500 fell 108.71 points to 6,832.76. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 669.42 to 49,451.98, and the Nasdaq Composite sank 469.32 to 22,597.15.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold reclaims ground as liquidity pressures ease across markets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-reclaims-ground-as-liquidity-pressures-ease-across-markets/1676705</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676705</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold futures staged a measured rebound during the mid-European session, recovering from earlier dips toward the $4,900 per ounce mark after suffering a sharp $150-plus selloff in the previous session amid broad-based risk liquidation.

Gold futures staged a measured rebound during the mid-European session, recovering from earlier dips toward the $4,900 per ounce mark after suffering a sharp $150-plus selloff in the previous session amid broad-based risk liquidation. The earlier plunge was driven by forced selling across asset classes, as investor’s unwound positions in precious metals to raise liquidity. The dollar index hovered near 97, extending its sideways consolidation for a fourth consecutive session, as markets awaited the release of the January US CPI report—widely seen as pivotal for refining expectations around Federal Reserve policy. Recent robust US nonfarm payrolls underscored labor market resilience, prompting markets to reassess the timing of rate cuts, with expectations shifting toward a first reduction in July rather than June. In domestic trade, MCX April gold futures advanced nearly 1% to Rs 154,160 per 10 grams, reflecting cautious bargain-hunting amid heightened macro uncertainty.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Lokesh Machines bags Rs 6-cr order from Assam Rifles]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lokesh-machines-bags-rs-6-cr-order-from-assam-rifles/1676699</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676699</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order entails the supply of 9x19mm carbines along with accessories, essential spares, and gauges.

The order entails the supply of 9x19mm carbines along with accessories, essential spares, and gauges. Awarded by a domestic entity, the contract is scheduled to be executed within 90 days from the date of issuance of the Acceptance of Tender. Lokesh Machines is engaged in the business of manufacturing special purpose machines (SPM), general purpose machines/CNC lathes (GPM), connecting rods, and machining cylinder blocks and heads. On a standalone basis, Lokesh Machines' net profit declined 81.74% to Rs 0.63 crore, while net sales declined 33.05% to Rs 50.43 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024. The counter fell 1.15% to Rs 176.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LokeshMach_84321725333_13320.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Info Edge Q3 PAT climbs 23% YoY to Rs 246 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/info-edge-q3-pat-climbs-23-yoy-to-rs-246-cr/1676698</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676698</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax rose 10.82% YoY to Rs 378.42 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional item and tax rose 10.82% YoY to Rs 378.42 crore during the quarter. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 48.75 crore in Q3 FY26, primarily related to labour code compliance. The recruitment business's year-on-yearrevenue growth improved slightly in Q3, compared with Q2, while non-recruitment businesses also continued to grow and generated positive cash during the quarter The company reported a 11.8% year-on-year growth in standalone billings for the quarter, reaching Rs 747.2 crore. Billings in the recruitment business grew by 11.0%, while the non-recruitment portfolio, 99acres (real estate), Jeevansathi (matchmaking), and Shiksha (education), combined, recorded growth of 14.1%. The standalone business generated cash from operations (before taxes) of Rs 376.1 crore for the quarter. Hitesh Oberoi, managing director and chief executive officer, said, “Q3FY26 saw steady business growth and improved operating profitability, driven by the resilience of our Recruitment business amid an uncertain hiring environment. 99acres and Jeevansathi continued to build on their growth momentum while further gaining market share and strengthening their market positions.” Ambarish Raghuvanshi, CFO, said, “With steady revenue growth, our operating profit margins improved in the recruitment business sequentially by 300 basis points, and non-recruitment businesses combined also were cash positive.” Info Edge (India) is India's premier online classifieds company in recruitment, matrimony, real estate, education and related services. The scrip shed 0.88% to Rs 1,137 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InfoEdgIndia_32670259917_18844.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EID Parry Q3 PAT jumps 5% YoY to Rs 437 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eid-parry-q3-pat-jumps-5-yoy-to-rs-437-cr/1676643</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676643</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) rose 1.07% YoY to Rs 587.93 crore during the quarter.

Profit before tax (PBT) rose 1.07% YoY to Rs 587.93 crore during the quarter. Earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 were Rs. 895 crore, as compared to the Rs. 811 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. On the segmental front, the company’s revenue from the sugar business stood at Rs 1,103.22 crore (down 14.98% YoY), distillery came in at Rs 289.05 crore (down 0.17% YoY), consumer products stood at Rs 143.03 crore (down 39.46%), crop protection was at Rs 1,098.29 crore (up 72.78% YoY), and nutrient and allied business was at Rs 7,761.77 crore (up 21.9% YoY) during the period under review. On the other hand, the firm’s income from nutraceuticals was at Rs 61.91 crore (up 44.25% YoY), and revenue from cogeneration stood at Rs 36.59 crore (down 10.36% YoY) in Q3 FY26. Segment-wise, the farm inputs division continued to lead performance, recording a profit before interest and tax (PBIT) of Rs 741 crore for the quarter, up 3.35% from Rs 717 crore a year ago. Consolidated sugar operations, including refinery business, reported a loss before interest and tax of Rs 30 crore for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 as compared to a loss of Rs 59 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. The consolidated nutraceuticals division reported a loss before interest and tax of Rs 2 crore for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 as compared to Rs 5 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. EID Parry (India) is engaged in sugar, nutraceuticals, and ethanol production. It also has a significant presence in the farm inputs business, including biopesticides, through its subsidiary, Coromandel International. Shares of EID Parry (India) rose 0.95% to Rs 990.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EIDParry_79775166468_148.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SpiceJet Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/spicejet-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1676637</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676637</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Muthoot Finance Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd and Cohance Lifesciences Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026.

Muthoot Finance Ltd, Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd and Cohance Lifesciences Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 13 February 2026. SpiceJet Ltd lost 14.85% to Rs 17.38 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 330.6 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 85.37 lakh shares in the past one month. Muthoot Finance Ltd tumbled 11.52% to Rs 3600.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.52 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 27471 shares in the past one month. Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd crashed 10.00% to Rs 397.45. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 40861 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 18388 shares in the past one month. Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd corrected 9.74% to Rs 1615.8. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 63045 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21552 shares in the past one month. Cohance Lifesciences Ltd pared 9.16% to Rs 318.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.35 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 30582 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SpiceJet_3698663034_3367.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineers India rallies after Q3 PAT soars 219.30% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/engineers-india-rallies-after-q3-pat-soars-21930-yoy/1676640</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676640</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net sales rose 58.29% YoY to Rs 1,210.24 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 764.59 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net sales rose 58.29% YoY to Rs 1,210.24 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 764.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, revenue increased 31.36% from Rs 921.29 crore in Q2 FY26. Net profit surged 219.30% YoY to Rs 347.17 crore, up from Rs 108.73 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, PAT jumped 315.82% from Rs 83.49 crore. Profit before tax climbed 218.37% YoY to Rs 400.60 crore, compared with Rs 125.83 crore in Q3 FY25. Sequentially, PBT rose 174.52% from Rs 145.93 crore. Total expenditure increased 28.70% YoY to Rs 858.02 crore, while rising 7.05% sequentially. Development and construction costs declined 29.30% YoY to Rs 77.87 crore, while employee expenses rose 10.97% YoY to Rs 282.24 crore. Interest costs declined 6.25% YoY to Rs 0.60 crore, and depreciation increased 7.68% YoY to Rs 10.23 crore. Segment-wise, revenue from the consultancy and engineering projects segment stood at Rs 490.14 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 16.36% YoY increase from Rs 421.22 crore in the year-ago period. The turnkey projects segment reported revenue of Rs 720.10 crore, registering a sharp 109.73% YoY jump from Rs 343.37 crore in Q3 FY25. During the quarter, the company secured contracts worth over $350 million from Nigeria’s Dangote Group for the expansion of a mega refinery project, strengthening its international order book and execution pipeline. Engineers India, a Navratna public sector enterprise, is an engineering consultancy and EPC company. As on December 2025, Government of India held 51.32% stake in the company.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EngineersIndia_47008482189_12029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dilip Buildcon secures Rs 124 crore ATF pipeline project from PNGRB]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dilip-buildcon-secures-rs-124-crore-atf-pipeline-project-from-pngrb/1676635</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676635</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves setting up a Petroleum or Petroleum Product (Air Turbine Fuel/ATF) pipeline from Navgam, Gujarat to Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel International Airport, Gujarat.

The project involves setting up a Petroleum or Petroleum Product (Air Turbine Fuel/ATF) pipeline from Navgam, Gujarat to Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel International Airport, Gujarat. The contract, awarded by a domestic entity, is valued at Rs 124 crore (excluding GST) and will be executed over a period of 25 years. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding entity and the contract does not fall under related party transactions. Dilip Buildcon is presently in the business of development of infrastructure facilities on an Engineering Procurement and Construction basis (EPC) and undertakes contracts from various government and other parties and special purpose vehicles promoted by the company. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 22.8% to Rs 181.49 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 235.24 crore in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations fell 22.9% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1925.89 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Dilip Buildcon tanked 3.82% to Rs 435.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DilipBuildconLtd_92563827065_36662.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Regency Ceramics Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/regency-ceramics-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1676634</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1676634</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sharika Enterprises Ltd, Ruchira Papers Ltd, Genesys International Corporation Ltd and Tokyo Plast International Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026.

Sharika Enterprises Ltd, Ruchira Papers Ltd, Genesys International Corporation Ltd and Tokyo Plast International Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 13 February 2026. Regency Ceramics Ltd crashed 13.26% to Rs 41.2 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 817 shares in the past one month. Sharika Enterprises Ltd lost 11.24% to Rs 12. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 45606 shares in the past one month. Ruchira Papers Ltd tumbled 11.08% to Rs 112. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9779 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2959 shares in the past one month. Genesys International Corporation Ltd slipped 10.72% to Rs 302.45. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 2.62 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 62952 shares in the past one month. Tokyo Plast International Ltd shed 10.45% to Rs 98.5. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 4 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 547 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RegencyCeramics_1874361855_831.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>