<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:07:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge higher in early trade; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-strong/1666458</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666458</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with major gains in early trade, tracking a rally in global markets amid improved investor sentiment.

The key equity benchmarks traded with major gains in early trade, tracking a rally in global markets amid improved investor sentiment. The Nifty traded above the 25,350 mark. All the NSE sectoral indices traded in the green, with PSU bank, media and pharma stocks outperforming. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 687.49 points or 0.84% to 82,597.12. The Nifty 50 index rose 226.45 points or 0.90% to 25,374.70. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 1.48% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 1.54%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,575 shares rose and 506 shares fell. A total of 141 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,787.66 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 4,520.47 crore in the Indian equity market on 21 January 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: Eternal rose 5.86% after the company reported a 72.9% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 102 crore on 201.9% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 16,315 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Consumer jumped 9.13% after the company reported an 83.2% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 46.4 crore on 30.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 306 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dr Reddys Laboratories rose 3.13%. The company reported 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,210 crore on a 4.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 8,753 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.06% to 6.651 compared with previous session close of 6.655. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.5350 compared with its close of 91.6500 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement fell 0.37% to Rs 152,220. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.01% to 98.78. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.12% to 4.256. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement rose 8 cents or 0.12% to $65.32 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian markets rebounded on Thursday, tracking gains on Wall Street after U.S. President Donald Trump walked back on his threat to impose tariffs on European countries over Greenland. Trump also said at the World Economic Forum in Davos that he would not use force to acquire the Arctic island, calming nerves over a possible U.S. military action, adding that he had “formed the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland,” along with NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. Meanwhile, South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. U.S. equities leaped after Wednesday after President Donald Trump called off new Europe tariffs, saying a deal framework has been reached over Greenland. The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged 588.64 points, or 1.21%, to end at 49,007.23. The S&P 500 gained 1.16% and closed at 6,875.62, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.18% to settle at 23,224.82. Back in Washington, Supreme Court justices expressed skepticism about whether Trump has the authority to fire Lisa Cook as a Federal Reserve governor. During oral arguments Wednesday, Justice Brett Kavanaugh told a Trump administration lawyer that arguments the president can fire Cook without judicial review “would weaken, if not shatter, the independence of the Federal Reserve."

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Waaree Energies Ltd Spurts 7.38%, BSE Capital Goods index Rises 1.03%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/waaree-energies-ltd-spurts-738-bse-capital-goods-index-rises-103/1666457</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666457</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Waaree Energies Ltd rose 7.38% today to trade at Rs 2594.2.

Waaree Energies Ltd rose 7.38% today to trade at Rs 2594.2. The BSE Capital Goods index is up 1.03% to quote at 62482.68. The index is down 7.63 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Premier Energies Ltd increased 4.71% and Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd added 2.97% on the day. The BSE Capital Goods index went down 1.16 % over last one year compared to the 7.92% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Waaree Energies Ltd has lost 16.19% over last one month compared to 7.63% fall in BSE Capital Goods index and 3.58% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 26869 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 95429 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 3864.4 on 12 Sep 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 1808.65 on 07 Apr 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WaareeEnergiesLtd_42747859_39763.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests green start for equities after Trump retreats from proposed tariffs on Europe ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-green-start-for-equities-after-trump-retreats-from-proposed-tariffs-on-europe/1666450</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666450</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 48.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty January 2026 futures were up 48.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 1,787.66 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 4,520.47 crore in the Indian equity market on 21 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 34,041.21 so far in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: Asia market rebounded Thursday, tracking gains on Wall Street after U.S. President Donald Trump walked back on his threat to impose tariffs on European countries over Greenland. Trump also said at the World Economic Forum in Davos that he would not use force to acquire the Arctic island, calming nerves over a possible U.S. military action, adding that he had “formed the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland,” along with NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. Meanwhile, South Korea’s economy unexpectedly shrank 0.3% on a quarterly basis in the October to December period, its sharpest contraction since 2022. Gross domestic product grew 1.5% year on year, while full-year economic growth slowed to 1%, the weakest since 2020, when output contracted 0.7% during the pandemic. U.S. equities leaped after Wednesday after President Donald Trump called off new Europe tariffs, saying a deal framework has been reached over Greenland. The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged 588.64 points, or 1.21%, to end at 49,007.23. The S&P 500 gained 1.16% and closed at 6,875.62, while the Nasdaq Composite advanced 1.18% to settle at 23,224.82. Back in Washington, Supreme Court justices expressed skepticism about whether Trump has the authority to fire Lisa Cook as a Federal Reserve governor. During oral arguments Wednesday, Justice Brett Kavanaugh told a Trump administration lawyer that arguments the president can fire Cook without judicial review “would weaken, if not shatter, the independence of the Federal Reserve." Domestic Market: Domestic equities extended losses for a third straight session on Wednesday as global shocks and weak earnings hit risk appetite. The Sensex fell over 1,000 points intraday, while the Nifty 50 slipped below 25,000 for the first time since October. Selling was broad-based, with IT, chemicals and consumer durables under sharp pressure. Banking and financial stocks stayed weak, while defensive sectors offered limited support. Equities were weighed down by renewed global uncertainty after President Donald Trump’s remarks on Greenland, soft domestic earnings, a record-low rupee, and continued foreign investor selling. The S&P BSE Sensex dropped 270.84 points or 0.33% to 81,909.63. The Nifty 50 index lost 75 points or 0.30% to 25,157.50. In three trading sessions, the Sensex slipped 1.99% while the Nifty declined 2.09%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[CESC arm signs MoU with UP Govt for Rs 3,800-cr RE projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cesc-arm-signs-mou-with-up-govt-for-rs-3800-cr-re-projects/1666448</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666448</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the MoU, the company will set-up a 3 GW solar cell/module plant, 60 MW of solar power plant and ancillary units, research & development lab and other infrastructural facilities with an investment of around Rs 3,800 crore.

Under the MoU, the company will set-up a 3 GW solar cell/module plant, 60 MW of solar power plant and ancillary units, research & development lab and other infrastructural facilities with an investment of around Rs 3,800 crore. CESC is a fully-integrated electrical utility company. The company's other business segments include power, organized retailing, property development and business process outsourcing. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 20.4% to Rs 425 crore on 12.1% increase in net sales to Rs 5,267 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The scrip declined 1.29% to settle at Rs 145.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CESC_38062435381_99.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Eternal, Bajaj Consumer, Dr Reddys Lab, KEI Industries, PNB Housing]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-eternal-bajaj-consumer-dr-reddys-lab-kei-industries-pnb-housing/1666446</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666446</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Bandhan Bank and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 22 January 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Bandhan Bank and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 22 January 2026. Result Today: Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC, Adani Energy Solutions, Alivus Life Sciences, APL Apollo Tubes, Adani Total Gas, Bandhan Bank, BlueStone Jewellery and Lifestyle, Borana Weaves, Computer Age Management Services, Cigniti Technologies, Coforge, Cyient, DLF, Go Digit General Insurance, Gujarat State Petronet, Home First Finance Company India, Ideaforge Technology, IIFL Finance, Indian Bank, InterGlobe Aviation, Infobeans Technologies, Le Travenues Technology, Mphasis, Orient Electric, Premier Energies, Radico Khaitan, Steel Strips Wheels, Syngene International, Tanla Platforms, Ujjivan Small Finance Bank, V‑Mart Retail, Zee Entertainment Enterprises, Zensar Technologies will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Eternal reported a 72.9% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 102 crore on 201.9% surge in revenue from operations to Rs 16,315 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Consumer reported a 83.2% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 46.4 crore on 30.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 306 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dr Reddys Laboratories reported 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,210 crore on 4.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 8,753 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. KEI Industries reported a 42.5% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 235 crore on 19.5% jump in revenue to Rs 2,955 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY26. PNB Housing Finance reported a 7.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 520 crore on 9.1% rise in total income to Rs 2,121 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Anant Raj has reported 30.8% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 144 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 110 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased by 20% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 642 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-team-deal-on-a-stock-exchange-stock-traders-concep_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>