<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MSTC jumps on bagging three-year mandate from Coal India for NRS linkage auction services]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mstc-jumps-on-bagging-three-year-mandate-from-coal-india-for-nrs-linkage-auction-services/1679780</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679780</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the agreement, MSTC will manage the entire gamut of associated services for NRS linkage auctions, starting from conducting the auction to execution of agreements through its digital platform.

Under the agreement, MSTC will manage the entire gamut of associated services for NRS linkage auctions, starting from conducting the auction to execution of agreements through its digital platform. The mandate is valid for a period of three years. The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity. The financial consideration or size of the order cannot be quantified at this stage, the company said. MSTC clarified that neither its promoter nor promoter group has any interest in Coal India. The contract does not fall under related party transactions, it added. MSTC’s (formerly known as Metal and Scrap Trading Corporation) core activity is diversified mainly into providing e-auction/e-procurement services and trading of bulk products like ferrous and non-ferrous scrap, coke, finished steel, coal and petroleum products. Coal India is mainly engaged in mining and production of coal and also operates coal washeries. The major consumers of the company are the power and steel sectors. Consumers from other sectors include cement, fertilizers, and brick kilns. The scrip declined 1.50% to Rs 427.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MSTCLtd_79136707579_2291.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NBCC India bags Rs 775-cr redevelopment orders from DDA]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nbcc-india-bags-rs-775-cr-redevelopment-orders-from-dda/1679755</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679755</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The projects comprise the redevelopment of Old Rajinder Nagar staff quarters valued at Rs 437.79 crore and Safdarjung Development Area staff quarters valued at Rs 337.48 crore.

The projects comprise the redevelopment of Old Rajinder Nagar staff quarters valued at Rs 437.79 crore and Safdarjung Development Area staff quarters valued at Rs 337.48 crore. The order value excludes marketing fees, which will be determined at a later stage. Both contracts have been awarded in the normal course of business and will be executed under the project management consultancy (PMC) mode. The redevelopment will be undertaken on a self-sustainable model, wherein a portion of the built-up area (BUA) will be monetized to fund the project cost, while the balance BUA will be handed over for DDA staff use. The Old Rajinder Nagar project involves 117 dwelling units with an envisaged BUA of around 99,635 square meters. The Safdarjung Development Area project comprises 152 dwelling units with a tentative built-up area of 65,925 square meters. Final BUA approvals will be subject to a detailed survey and submission of the Detailed Project Report (DPR). The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the awarding authority, and the contracts do not qualify as related-party transactions. NBCC (India) operates in three major segments—project management consultancy, real estate, and engineering procurement & construction. The company's consolidated net profit advanced 38.5% to Rs 197.22 crore on a 7.6% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3,022.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of NBCC (India) shed 0.01% to Rs 94.03 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NBCC_1807915630_13166.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers opens lower in early trade; breadth negative]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-opens-lower-in-early-trade-breadth-negative/1679756</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679756</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in the early trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in the early trade. The Nifty traded below the 25,400 level. Chemical, FMCG and auto shares declined, while IT and consumer durabes stocks advanced. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 351.42 points or 0.43% to 81,897.19. The Nifty 50 index gained 126.90 points or 0.49% to 25,368.90. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index shed 0.24% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.46%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,288 shares rose and 1,610 shares fell. A total of 186 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,465.99 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,031.57 crore in the Indian equity market on 26 February 2026, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: NBCC (India) added 0.48%. The company said that it has secured a Rs 775 crore order from the Delhi Development Authority (DDA) for the redevelopment of staff quarters. Brigade Enterprises shed 0.38%. The company announced that the Brigade Group has partnered with Primus Senior Living to launch three senior living communities across Bengaluru and other geographies in South India. The upcoming projects will have an expected gross development value (GDV) of approximately Rs 750 crore. Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (GMDC) rose 0.69%. The company has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with NTPC to jointly explore opportunities in coal and lignite gasification and downstream utilization. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.13% to 6.699 compared with previous session close of 6.690. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9500 compared with its close of 90.9150 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement added 0.26% to Rs 160,001. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.08% to 97.66. The United States 10-year bond yield declined 0.37% to 4.002. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement lost 8 cents or 0.11% to $70.76 a barrel. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Friday, after U.S. stocks declined overnight as Nvidia shares tumbled despite a quarterly earnings beat. In Asian tech stocks, SK Hynix, which is a key supplier of high-bandwidth memory to Nvidia, dipped over 2%. Samsung Electronics, which has been a decades-old partner of Nvidia, was down 0.69%. Gold prices held broadly steady on Friday, with investors digesting the previous day's U.S.-Iran nuclear talks, while the dollar, hovering near three-week highs, pressured the yellow metal. An Omani mediator of U.S. and Iran nuclear talks has reportedly given an optimistic readout over the latest round of negotiations, but uncertainty still hung over energy markets with no sign of a breakthrough that would avert potential U.S. strikes. Following these developments, Brent crude futures settled down 10 cents, or 0.14%, to $70.75 a barrel. Overnight on Wall Street, the S&P 500 pulled back after the latest results from tech titan Nvidia and software giant Salesforce failed to boost the broader market. The broad market index fell 0.54% to end at 6,908.86, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.18% and closed at 22,878.38. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 17.05 points, or 0.03%, to settle at 49,499.20. Nvidia shares fell more than 5%, even after the chip giant posted fourth-quarter earnings and revenue that were higher than widely reported forescasts. On the other end, Salesforce, which has been one of the biggest victims of recent artificial intelligence disruption fears, rose 4% after the software company’s latest quarterly results were higher than widely reported forecasts on the top and bottom lines. However, the company issued a disappointing fiscal 2027 revenue forecast. Sentiment has been fragile in software and cybersecurity stocks this year as worries remain about the rapidly developing capabilities of AI products that could interfere with incumbent software vendors’ businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dee Development Engineers gains on bagging Rs 58-cr order for seamless pipes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dee-development-engineers-gains-on-bagging-rs-58-cr-order-for-seamless-pipes/1679754</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679754</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order has been awarded by a domestic entity, a joint venture between an Indian conglomerate and a foreign power sector major.

The order has been awarded by a domestic entity, a joint venture between an Indian conglomerate and a foreign power sector major. The name of the customer has not been disclosed due to commercial considerations. The contract, valued at Rs 58 crore, is scheduled to be executed by December 2026, the company said in a regulatory filing. This is the maiden order for seamless pipes to be manufactured at the company’s new facility in Anjar, Gujarat, signalling the commencement of commercial operations at the plant. The company clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group has any interest in the entity awarding the contract. It also stated that the order does not fall under related party transactions. DEE Development Engineers (DDEL) is an engineering company providing specialized process piping solutions for industries such as oil and gas, power (including nuclear), process industries, and chemicals through engineering, procurement, and manufacturing services. The company reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 18.28 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with a net loss of Rs 13.33 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales increased 77% YoY to Rs 298.67 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DeeDevelopmentEngineersLtd_25916295_34369.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ramco Systems Ltd Surges 16.78%, BSE Information Technology index Gains 1.45%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ramco-systems-ltd-surges-1678-bse-information-technology-index-gains-145/1679753</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679753</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Ramco Systems Ltd gained 16.78% today to trade at Rs 525.

Ramco Systems Ltd gained 16.78% today to trade at Rs 525. The BSE Information Technology index is up 1.45% to quote at 30103.98. The index is down 19.18 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Ksolves India Ltd increased 15.25% and Allied Digital Services Ltd added 4.26% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 21.32 % over last one year compared to the 10.2% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Ramco Systems Ltd has added 23.66% over last one month compared to 19.18% fall in BSE Information Technology index and 0.15% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 19128 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 681.8 on 12 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 27 Feb 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RamcoSystems_8823703642_12611.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests red start for equities; Asian markets trade mixed]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-red-start-for-equities-asian-markets-trade-mixed/1679747</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679747</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty March 2026 futures were down 21.00 points, suggesting a red start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty March 2026 futures were down 21.00 points, suggesting a red start for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,465.99 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 5,031.57 crore in the Indian equity market on 26 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have bought shares worth Rs 895.58 crore in the cash market so far in February (till 26 February 2026). This is in contrast to their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Friday, after U.S. stocks declined overnight as Nvidia shares tumbled despite a quarterly earnings beat. In Asian tech stocks, SK Hynix, which is a key supplier of high-bandwidth memory to Nvidia, dipped over 2%. Samsung Electronics, which has been a decades-old partner of Nvidia, was down 0.69%. Gold prices held broadly steady on Friday, with investors digesting the previous day's U.S.-Iran nuclear talks, while the dollar, hovering near three-week highs, pressured the yellow metal. An Omani mediator of U.S. and Iran nuclear talks has reportedly given an optimistic readout over the latest round of negotiations, but uncertainty still hung over energy markets with no sign of a breakthrough that would avert potential U.S. strikes. Following these developments, Brent crude futures settled down 10 cents, or 0.14%, to $70.75 a barrel. Overnight on Wall Street, the S&P 500 pulled back after the latest results from tech titan Nvidia and software giant Salesforce failed to boost the broader market. The broad market index fell 0.54% to end at 6,908.86, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.18% and closed at 22,878.38. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 17.05 points, or 0.03%, to settle at 49,499.20. Nvidia shares fell more than 5%, even after the chip giant posted fourth-quarter earnings and revenue that were higher than widely reported forescasts. On the other end, Salesforce, which has been one of the biggest victims of recent artificial intelligence disruption fears, rose 4% after the software company’s latest quarterly results were higher than widely reported forecasts on the top and bottom lines. However, the company issued a disappointing fiscal 2027 revenue forecast. Sentiment has been fragile in software and cybersecurity stocks this year as worries remain about the rapidly developing capabilities of AI products that could interfere with incumbent software vendors’ businesses. Domestic Market: The key equity benchmarks ended in sideways trend, as market participants monitored Prime Minster Narendra Modi’s visit to Israel. The visit comes amid heightened geopolitical tensions in the region, U.S. warnings, and evolving global diplomatic dynamics, adding a layer of caution to market sentiment. The Nifty briefly slipped into negative territory amid volatility surrounding the monthly F&O expiry before recovering marginally in the final hour to close little changed. Nifty ended near the 25,500 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex shed 27.46 points or 0.03% to 82,248.61. The Nifty 50 index rose 14.05 points or 0.06% to 25,496.55.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quality Power Electrical bags Rs 146-cr domestic order for HVDC reactors]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quality-power-electrical-bags-rs-146-cr-domestic-order-for-hvdc-reactors/1679742</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679742</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the orders have been awarded by a domestic entity.

The company said the orders have been awarded by a domestic entity. However, the name of the awarding entity has not been disclosed due to a non-disclosure agreement (NDA). The scope of work involves the supply of multiple HVDC reactors, and the orders are to be executed over a period of around 18 months. Quality Power clarified that neither the promoter nor the promoter group or group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the contracts. The company also confirmed that the orders do not fall under related party transactions. Quality Power Electrical Equipment is engaged in the business of energy transition equipment and power technologies. The company’s consolidated net profit zoomed 220.69% to Rs 62.76 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 19.57 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 291.27% to Rs 283.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 72.58 crore in Q3 FY25. The counter advanced 0.65% to end at Rs 904.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/QualityPowerElectricalEquipmentsLtd_48177673_54766.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: NBCC, Tata steel, Netweb Tech, Brigade Enterprises, BPCL, Hindalco]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-nbcc-tata-steel-netweb-tech-brigade-enterprises-bpcl-hindalco/1679741</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679741</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 27 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 27 February 2026. New listing: In the mainboard IPO segment, Gaudium IVF & Women Health is set to debut on the stock exchanges today. The public issue witnessed a healthy response, getting subscribed 7.27 times. The IPO price band was fixed at Rs 75–79 per share. Meanwhile, in the SME segment, Manilam Industries India is also scheduled to list on the bourses today. Its IPO was subscribed 4.22 times, with the price band set at Rs 65–69 per share. Stocks to Watch: NBCC said that it has secured a Rs 775 crore order from the Delhi Development Authority (DDA) for the redevelopment of staff quarters. Tata Steel said that it has acquired 262 crore shares in its arm, T Steel Holdings, for a total consideration of Rs 2,402 crore. Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (GMDC) has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with NTPC to jointly explore opportunities in coal and lignite gasification and downstream utilization. The MoU establishes a collaborative framework to assess the feasibility of gasifying coal from GMDC’s coal blocks in Odisha and lignite from its mining operations in Gujarat. Netweb Technologies announced that it has entered into a collaboration with Vertiv, a global critical digital infrastructure firm. MSTC has become the lowest bidder for a tender hosted by Coal India on the GeM portal for the appointment of an external service provider to conduct linkage auctions for the non-regulated sector (NRS) for three years. Brigade Enterprises announced that the Brigade Group has partnered with Primus Senior Living to launch three senior living communities across Bengaluru and other geographies in South India. The upcoming projects will have an expected gross development value (GDV) of approximately Rs 750 crore. Hindalco Industries has informed that due to the partial shutdown of the US federal government, the statutory timelines under the CFIUS review framework have been tolled, impacting the ongoing review process. At present, no definitive timeline is available for the conclusion of the shutdown. Accordingly, the CFIUS review and the related transaction remain temporarily halted. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary in Singapore named Bharat Petroleum Global Energy Services to establish an international trading desk for crude oil and natural gas. Indian Railway Finance Corporation said that the board will meet on March 9 to consider the declaration of a second interim dividend for the current financial year 2025–26 and to consider approval of the market borrowing program for the financial year 2026–27. GRE Renew Enertech has received multiple orders worth Rs 19.27 crore from domestic entities for the execution of engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) contracts on a turnkey basis in the ordinary course of its business operations. Greaves Cotton said that the company’s subsidiary, Greaves Electric Mobility, has announced its international expansion into Nepal, in partnership with STC Auto Solution. As part of this expansion, the company is launching its flagship product, Ampere Nexus. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services has entered into an agreement with Chennai Super Kings Cricket, Superking Ventures, and Saurashtra Cement. The company will offer its Zaggle Corporate Expense Cards to employees and associates of Chennai Super Kings Cricket and Superking Ventures.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>