<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge higher in early trade; breadth strong]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-higher-in-early-trade-breadth-strong/1662738</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662738</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices opened with slight gains in early trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark.

The key equity indices opened with slight gains in early trade as the Nifty traded above the 26,150 mark. Market activity is expected to stay range-bound in the absence of strong global economic triggers and due to the New Year holiday. Trading may witness volatility due to the expiry of the weekly Sensex derivatives contract. Auto stocks will be in focus as companies announce their monthly sales numbers. Media, auto and IT shares rally while FMCG, pharma and PSU Bank shares declined. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 98.47 points or 0.12% to 85,319.07. The Nifty 50 index added 36.90 points or 0.15% to 26,167.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.07% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.07%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 1,706 shares rose and 1,046 shares fell. A total of 139 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,492.04 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 6,542.14 crore in the Indian equity market on 31 December 2025, provisional data showed. Stocks in Spotlight: NBCC (India) advanced 1.15% after the company said it has secured multiple construction orders aggregating Rs 383 crore from Canara Bank and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Titagarh Rail Systems rose 0.83%. The company said its board has approved a business transfer agreement to transfer its Shipbuilding, Marine and Systems (SMS) business to its arm, Titagarh Naval Systems, in a transaction valued at Rs 114.9 crore, which will be executed in accordance with the terms of the pact. Dr Reddy’s Laboratories shed 0.87%. The company said its Switzerland-based arm has received a complete response letter (CRL) from the US Food and Drug Administration for the biologics license application of its proposed biosimilar AVT03. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.24% to 6.592 as compared with the previous close of 6.576. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9900 compared with its close of 89.8800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement shed 0.04% to Rs 135,390. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 98.28. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.65% to 4.177. In the commodities market, Brent crude for February 2025 settlement declined 49 cents or 0.80% to $60.84 a barrel. Global Markets: Both the US and major Asian markets will remain shut today on account of the New Year’s Day holiday. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back on Wednesday, though the index still closed out a bumper year. The broad market S&P 500 dipped 0.74% and closed at 6,845.50, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and ended at 23,241.99. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 303.77 points, or 0.63%, and settled at 48,063.29.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Time Technoplast bags Rs 51-cr supply order from HPCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/time-technoplast-bags-rs-51-cr-supply-order-from-hpcl/1662737</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662737</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order is for supply of rigid polymer packaging products, namely Conipack pails, to be delivered as per HPCL’s schedule.

The order is for supply of rigid polymer packaging products, namely Conipack pails, to be delivered as per HPCL’s schedule. Payments under the contract will be secured through an appropriate financial instrument. The supplies are to be dispatched in line with the delivery schedule over a period of up to two years. The company clarified that the order does not involve any promoter or promoter group interest and does not fall under related party transactions. Time Technoplast is a global manufacturer of polymer products with operations across multiple countries. Its portfolio spans industrial packaging solutions, lifestyle products, automotive components, infrastructure / construction related products, material handling solutions & composite cylinders. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Time Technoplast rose 17.04% to Rs 115.44 crore while net sales rose 10.3% to Rs 1,511.11 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Time Technoplast rose 0.49% to Rs 189 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimeTechnoplast_46114320009_27753.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd Spurts 14.78%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/optiemus-infracom-ltd-spurts-1478/1662735</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662735</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Optiemus Infracom Ltd gained 14.78% today to trade at Rs 580.

Optiemus Infracom Ltd gained 14.78% today to trade at Rs 580. The BSE Telecommunication index is up 0.53% to quote at 3139.3. The index is up 2.02 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, ADC India Communications Ltd increased 1.89% and Vodafone Idea Ltd added 1.86% on the day. The BSE Telecommunication index went up 9.36 % over last one year compared to the 8.6% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Optiemus Infracom Ltd has added 3.39% over last one month compared to 2.02% gain in BSE Telecommunication index and 0.14% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 9857 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 793 on 06 Jan 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 0 on 01 Jan 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OptiemusInfra_38144306001_5004.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Silver Touch Technologies Ltd Slides 1.6%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/silver-touch-technologies-ltd-slides-16/1662736</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662736</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Silver Touch Technologies Ltd fell 1.6% today to trade at Rs 1076.95.

Silver Touch Technologies Ltd fell 1.6% today to trade at Rs 1076.95. The BSE Information Technology index is down 0.15% to quote at 36679.82. The index is up 0.86 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Orient Technologies Ltd decreased 1.41% and Nucleus Software Exports Ltd lost 1.04% on the day. The BSE Information Technology index went down 15.21 % over last one year compared to the 8.6% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Silver Touch Technologies Ltd has added 40.19% over last one month compared to 0.86% gain in BSE Information Technology index and 0.14% rise in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 370 shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 16471 shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 1115.6 on 31 Dec 2025. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 621 on 06 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SilverTouchTechnologiesLtd_8102135951_71656.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pace Digitek gains as arm bags Rs 94-cr advance purchase order from BSNL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pace-digitek-gains-as-arm-bags-rs-94-cr-advance-purchase-order-from-bsnl/1662734</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662734</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order entails supply of 25,000 units of 100Ah/48V lithium-ion battery modules with battery management systems (BMS) along with associated accessories, and 2,500 IP55 racks for housing eight 48V/100Ah modules each, including required accessories such as cables for connecting master BMS and SMPS systems.

The order entails supply of 25,000 units of 100Ah/48V lithium-ion battery modules with battery management systems (BMS) along with associated accessories, and 2,500 IP55 racks for housing eight 48V/100Ah modules each, including required accessories such as cables for connecting master BMS and SMPS systems. The scope of the contract also includes a five-year annual maintenance contract (AMC) after the initial five-year warranty period for the supplied lithium-ion battery modules and accessories. Pace Digitek is a telecom infrastructure solutions provider with a significant focus on the telecom industry, including telecom tower infrastructure and optical fiber cables. The company’s consolidated net profit slipped 32.7% to Rs 64.08 crore on a 37% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 533.45 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PACEDIGITEKLIMITED_26475505_94643.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Utkarsh Small Finance Bank director Pramod Kumar Dubey resigns]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/utkarsh-small-finance-bank-director-pramod-kumar-dubey-resigns/1662733</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662733</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[His resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on 31 December 2025.

His resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on 31 December 2025. The bank noted that there is no inter-se relationship between its directors, and no further profile details were provided. Utkarsh Small Finance Bank engaged in providing banking and financial services and governed by the Banking. The company reported standalone net loss of Rs 348.46 crore in Q2 FY26 as against net profit of Rs 51.39 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 14% year on year (YoY) to Rs 937.32 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Utkarsh Small Finance Bank rose 0.41% to Rs 14.83 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UtkarshSmallFinanceBankLtd_93043978_72071.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zaggle gains on inking pact with Visa Worldwide to promote co-branded prepaid cards]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zaggle-gains-on-inking-pact-with-visa-worldwide-to-promote-co-branded-prepaid-cards/1662731</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662731</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the agreement, Visa will incentivise Zaggle to roll out and promote the co-branded prepaid card offerings.

Under the agreement, Visa will incentivise Zaggle to roll out and promote the co-branded prepaid card offerings. Although the contract has been awarded by an international entity, the transaction pertains to domestic operations. The project is proposed to be executed over a period of seven years. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services (Zaggle) is a leading player in spend management, with a differentiated value proposition and diversified user base. The company operates in the business-to-business-to-customer segment. It is one of the largest numbers of issued prepaid cards in India in partnership with its banking partners. Additionally, the company has a diversified portfolio of software as a service (SaaS) products, including tax and payroll software, and a wide touchpoint reach. The company’s standalone net profit surged 79.1% to Rs 33.24 crore on a 42.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 430.98 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ZagglePrepaidOceanServicesLtd_95613182_78337.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests flat opening for equities; major Asian markets shut on account of holiday]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-flat-opening-for-equities-major-asian-markets-shut-on-account-of-holiday/1662726</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662726</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were up 1.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty December 2025 futures were up 1.50 points, indicating a flat opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 3,492.04 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 6,542.14 crore in the Indian equity market on 31 December 2025, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 34,349.62 crore so far in December. This follows their cash sales of Rs 17,500.31 crore in November and Rs 2,346.89 crore in October. Global Markets: Both the US and major Asian markets will remain shut today on account of the New Year’s Day holiday. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back on Wednesday, though the index still closed out a bumper year. The broad market S&P 500 dipped 0.74% and closed at 6,845.50, while the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.76% and ended at 23,241.99. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 303.77 points, or 0.63%, and settled at 48,063.29. Domestic Market: Domestic equity indices rebounded on Wednesday, with the Sensex and Nifty breaking a four-session losing streak on the year’s final trading day. Bargain hunting lifted benchmarks despite continued foreign fund outflows. The Nifty closed near the 26,130 mark, driven by strength in energy and consumer durables stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex advanced 545.52 points or 0.64% to 85,220.60. The Nifty 50 index gained 190.75 points or 0.74% to 26,129.60. The 50 unit index slipped 0.91% in the past four sessions.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Precision Electronics secures Rs 3-cr defence supply order]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/precision-electronics-secures-rs-3-cr-defence-supply-order/1662724</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662724</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the contract, the company will supply masts and tripods along with related accessories, in line with the customer’s specifications.

Under the contract, the company will supply masts and tripods along with related accessories, in line with the customer’s specifications. Owing to confidentiality and commercial sensitivity, the name of the awarding entity has not been disclosed. The order has been awarded by a domestic government entity and is scheduled to be executed within the current financial year. The company clarified that the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions and that the promoter or promoter group has no interest in the awarding entity. Precision Electronics is a diverse telecom infrastructure enabler with active interest spanning telecom infrastructure development, system integration, and manufacture and supply of high-end telecom equipment. The company reported a standalone net loss of Rs 1.40 crore in Q2 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 1.17 crore in Q2 FY25. Net sales surged 48.4% year-on-year to Rs 15.15 crore in Q2 FY26. Shares of Precision Electronics shed 0.36% to Rs 192.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PrecElectronic_6758329937_2063.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Canara Bank, NBCC (India), Titagarh Rail Systems, Dr Reddy’s Laboratories, Time Technoplast]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-canara-bank-nbcc-india-titagarh-rail-systems-dr-reddys-laboratories-time-technoplast/1662723</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1662723</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Stocks to Watch: Canara Bank said Hardeep Singh Ahluwalia has been entrusted with the additional charge of managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective 1 January 2026, for a period of three months.

Stocks to Watch: Canara Bank said Hardeep Singh Ahluwalia has been entrusted with the additional charge of managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective 1 January 2026, for a period of three months. NBCC (India) said it has secured multiple construction orders aggregating Rs 383 crore from Canara Bank and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Titagarh Rail Systems said its board has approved a business transfer agreement to transfer its Shipbuilding, Marine and Systems (SMS) business to its arm, Titagarh Naval Systems, in a transaction valued at Rs 114.9 crore, which will be executed in accordance with the terms of the pact. Dr Reddy’s Laboratories said its Switzerland-based arm has received a complete response letter (CRL) from the US Food and Drug Administration for the biologics license application of its proposed biosimilar AVT03. Time Technoplast said it has received an order worth Rs 51 crore from Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd (HPCL) for the supply of goods. Hyundai Motor India said Unsoo Kim has resigned as managing director (MD) and director of the company, while shareholders have approved the appointment of Tarun Garg as the new managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective from 1 January 2026. Utkarsh Small Finance Bank said Pramod Kumar Dubey has resigned from his position as whole-time director (WTD) to pursue other career opportunities.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>