<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:25:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Q3 PAT rises 4% YoY; board clears Rs 15,000-cr fundraise ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-bank-q3-pat-rises-4-yoy-board-clears-rs-15000-cr-fundraise/1667440</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667440</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Operating profit before provisions and tax rose 3.84% YoY to Rs 5,379.77 crore during the quarter.

Operating profit before provisions and tax rose 3.84% YoY to Rs 5,379.77 crore during the quarter. Provision (other than tax) and contingencies increased 1.95% YoY to 809.58 crore during the quarter. Net interest income (NII) stood at Rs 7565 crore in Q3 FY26, up 5% compared with Rs 7,196 crore in Q3 FY25. Net Interest Margin (NIM) was 4.54% for Q3FY26 compared with 4.93% for Q3FY25. Operating expenses rose 8% to Rs 5,023 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 4,638 crore in Q3 FY25. Q3FY26. These expenses include an estimated incremental cost of Rs 96 crore arising from the implementation of the new Labour Code. Excluding this impact, operating expenses for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 4,927 crore, reflecting a 6% YoY increase. Credit cost (annualised) stood at 0.63% in Q3 FY26, compared with 0.68% in Q3 FY25. Total deposits at the end of the period grew 15% to Rs 542,638 crore for Q3FY26, from Rs 473,497 crore for Q3FY25. Average total deposits also increased 15% to Rs 526,025 crore for Q3FY26, from Rs 458,614 crore for Q3FY25. Average current deposits grew to Rs 75,596 crore for Q3FY26, up 14% from Rs 66,589 crore for Q3FY25. Net Advances increased 16% to Rs 480,673 crore as at December 31, 2025 from Rs 413,839 crore as at December 31, 2024. Asset quality continued to improve, with gross non-performing assets (GNPA) declining to 1.30% as on December 31, 2025, from 1.50% as on 31st December 2024 and net non-performing assets (NNPA) was 0.31% as on 31st December 2025 compared with 0.41% as of 31st December 2024. As at December 31, 2025, Provision Coverage Ratio stood at 76% as of 31st December 2025. The bank’s capital adequacy ratio under Basel III norms stood at 22.6% as of December 31, 2025, while the CET1 ratio was strong at 21.5%, including unaudited profits. Meanwhile, the company’s board approved a proposal to raise funds by way of issuance of unsecured, redeemable, non-convertible debentures (NCDs), on a private placement basis, for an amount up to Rs 15,000 crore, in one or more tranches / series, during FY 2026-27, subject to the approval of the members of the bank. Kotak Mahindra Bank is the part of the Kotak Group and has diversified operations covering commercial vehicle financing, consumer loans, corporate finance, and asset reconstruction. Through its subsidiaries, the bank is engaged in investment banking, equity broking, securities-based lending, and car finance. As on 31 st December 2025, the bank has a national footprint of 2,218 branches and 2,749 ATMs (incl. cash recyclers) and branches in GIFT City and DIFC (Dubai). The counter shed 0.85% to end at Rs 422.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KotakMahBank_47062626511_2330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ultratech Cement Q3 PAT climbs 27% YoY to Rs 1,725 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ultratech-cement-q3-pat-climbs-27-yoy-to-rs-1725-cr/1667434</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667434</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Pursuant to the implementation of the new labour code in the country with effect from 21st November, 2025, the company has recognised Rs 88 crore as an exceptional expense towards additional Gratuity and Leave Encashment obligations.

Pursuant to the implementation of the new labour code in the country with effect from 21st November, 2025, the company has recognised Rs 88 crore as an exceptional expense towards additional Gratuity and Leave Encashment obligations. Excluding the impact of labour code, profit after tax (PAT) jumped 32% YoY to Rs 1,792 crore during the quarter. Profit before tax (PBT) increased 34.99% YoY to Rs 2,283 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA stood at Rs 4,051 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 28.93% compared with Rs 3,142 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Consolidated cement sales volume stood at 38.87 mtpa, registering a 15% YoY growth. Domestic grey cement capacity volumes increased 15.4% YoY to 36.37 million tonnes per annum (MTPA). Overall capacity utilisation improved to 77% for the quarter, compared to 72% during the same period last year. UltraTech recorded a 29.4% growth in domestic grey cement volumes, excluding the sales volumes of India Cements and Kesoram from the corresponding previous period, as these entities were not part of the company for the entire period. “UltraTech” as a Cement brand grew 22.3% with the rapid improvement of quality of product from these acquired assets and integration of its marketing and logistics. Operating EBITDA per ton improved to Rs 1,051 excluding India Cements, improving from Rs 911/mt over the previous year. During the quarter, the company incurred capex of Rs 2,357 crore as part of its ongoing expansion programme and has reduced its net debt-to- EBITDA of 1.08x reflecting strong operating cash flows. UltraTech along with its subsidiary, India Cements, has initiated the next phase of its expansion, to add 22.8 mtpa of capacity, through a mix of brownfield and greenfield projects and work is progressing as scheduled. Post completion of this phase of expansion, the company will reach a capacity of 240.76 mtpa. The company also said that its cables and wires business is on track, with critical orders placed, civil work on the project site in progress and key team members being onboarded. It remains confident of meeting the committed launch timeline of Q3 FY27. UltraTech Cement is the cement flagship company of the Aditya Birla Group. It is the second-largest cement producer in the world, outside of China. During the December quarter, the company’s domestic grey cement capacity stood at 188.66 mtpa. Including its 5.4 mtpa cement capacity in the UAE, UltraTech’s total global cement capacity has reached 194.06 mtpa. The scrip rose 0.03% to settle at Rs 12,368.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UltraTechCem_63281629205_24951.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Granules India Q3 PAT climbs 28% YoY to Rs 150 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/granules-india-q3-pat-climbs-28-yoy-to-rs-150-cr/1667421</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667421</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue growth during the quarter was driven by Finished Dosages (FD) segment in North America and Europe.

Revenue growth during the quarter was driven by Finished Dosages (FD) segment in North America and Europe. Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 32.36% YoY to Rs 202.23 crore during the quarter. EBITDA stood at Rs 308.1 crore, registering the growth of 34% compared with Rs 230.3 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 22% in Q3 FY26 as against 20% in Q3 FY25. For Q3 FY26, Finished Dosages, Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients (API), Pharmaceutical Formulation Intermediates (PFI), and Peptides/CDMO contributed 76%, 11%, 11%, and 2% of revenue from operations, respectively. Net debt stood at Rs 1,015.1 crore and Net debt to EBITDA at 0.91x in Q3 FY26. Krishna Prasad Chigurupati, chairman & managing director of Granules India said, “Q3 has been one of our strongest quarters, reflecting disciplined execution of strategic growth initiatives and we are well positioned for sustained growth momentum. Our strong financial performance, on-going R&D investments, combined with advances in ESG stewardship and our expanding global supply footprint, reinforces our commitment to building a resilient, innovation-led pharmaceutical platform that delivers long-term value for all stakeholders.” Granules India is primarily involved in the manufacturing and sale of active pharmaceutical ingredients (APIs), pharmaceutical formulation intermediates (PFIs), and finished dosages (FDs). The scrip declined 1.09% to end at Rs 564.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GranulesIndia_74697683931_12632.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Piramal Finance registers PAT of Rs 401 crore Q3 FY26; AUM rises to Rs 96,690 crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/piramal-finance-registers-pat-of-rs-401-crore-q3-fy26-aum-rises-to-rs-96690-crore/1667420</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667420</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net interest income jumped 31% to Rs 1,227 crore in the December’25 quarter from Rs 940 crore recorded in the December’24 quarter.

Net interest income jumped 31% to Rs 1,227 crore in the December’25 quarter from Rs 940 crore recorded in the December’24 quarter. NIM expanded by 51 bps YoY during the quarter to 6.3%. Total income increased by 29% YoY to Rs 1,480 crore in Q3 FY26. Operating expenses for the period under review added up to Rs 821 crore, up 4% YoY. Accordingly, operating profit was Rs 659 crore for Q3 FY26, up 84% YoY. The NBFC has recorded 36% increase in provisions to Rs 370 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 272 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax for Q3 FY26 was Rs 328 crore as against Rs 91 crore in Q3 FY25. The company said that its asset quality remained stable, with GNPA at 2.6% and NNPA at 1.9% as on 31 December 2025. Total assets under management (AUM) grew by 23% YoY to Rs 96,690 crore as on 31 December 2025. The company’s networth at the end of December’25 period was Rs 27,872 crore, with cash and liquid investments of Rs 7,504 crore. Anand Piramal, chairman, Piramal Finance, said: “Q3 was another strong quarter, and it capped a very solid nine-month performance in FY26. We have also recently achieved a few important milestones. Earlier this month, we received a CRISIL AA+ rating for our long-term debt, which strengthens our ability to scale up responsibly and profitably. We also secured our inaugural DFI funding of $350 million from IFC and ADB — an important validation of our business model, governance and long-term direction. This partnership also diversifies our funding sources and supports our growth plans. Alongside growth, we remain focused on strengthening our balance sheet. We recently monetised our stake in Shriram Life Insurance for Rs 600crore, expected to close in Q4. The consistency we have seen across the last several quarters gives us confidence in our direction and our ability to deliver sustained growth and profitability.” Piramal Finance is a retail-led upper layer NBFC with a pan-India presence, having served over 5 million customers across 26 states. In retail lending, the company offers home loans, loans against property, used car loans, personal loans, digital loans and small business loans. In wholesale lending, the company provides asset-backed, data-driven solutions across real estate and select non-real estate sectors. The scrip had declined 1.53% to end at Rs 1792.95 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PiramalCapitalHousingFinanceLtd_18221962_1814.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HCL Tech to acquire 100% stake in Finergic Solutions for 19 million Singapore dollars]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hcl-tech-to-acquire-100-stake-in-finergic-solutions-for-19-million-singapore-dollars/1667416</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667416</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Founded in 2019, Finergic focuses on core banking and wealth management transformation and has a strong, well-established global presence.

Founded in 2019, Finergic focuses on core banking and wealth management transformation and has a strong, well-established global presence. The company had recorded revenue of 12.6 million Singapore dollars in the year ended 31 December 2024. HCL Technologies stated that by integrating Finergic’s specialized transformation strategy, consulting and wealth-architecture capabilities, the company would accelerate the delivery of next-generation, platform-enabled wealth management solutions anchored by advanced AI-native workflows. These capabilities will complement the company’s existing global experience supporting clients in Temenos products, including more than 40 global banks. The 100% stake in Finergic has been acquired for a cash consideration of 19 million Singapore dollars. The transaction is expected to close by 30 April 2026. Srinivasan Seshadri, chief growth officer and global head - Financial Services, HCLTech, said: "With Finergic’s focused domain expertise, HCLTech is strategically positioned to strengthen its digital services capabilities in wealth management. This transformative transaction enables us to deliver advanced capabilities, foster innovation and unlock substantial synergies—empowering our clients to realize greater business outcomes across the financial services landscape." HCL Technologies is a global technology company, delivering industry-leading capabilities centered around digital, engineering, cloud and AI, powered by a broad portfolio of technology services and products. The company's consolidated net profit declined 3.75% to Rs 4,076 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,235 crore in Q2 FY26. However, revenue from operations increased 6.04% to Rs 33,872 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 31,942 crore posted in Q2 FY26. The scrip had gained 0.23% to close at Rs 1706.60 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HCLTechnologies_63631997_5656.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI MF announces change in benchmark under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mf-announces-change-in-benchmark-under-its-scheme/1667411</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667411</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced change in the benchmark of UTI Multi Asset Allocation Fund .

UTI Mutual Fund has announced change in the benchmark of UTI Multi Asset Allocation Fund . with effect from, February 28, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in name of Benchmark of UTI Multi Asset Allocation Fund Scheme Name Existing Benchmark Revised Benchmark UTI Multi Asset Allocation Fund 65% BSE 200 TRI, 25% CRISIL Composite Bond Index, 10% Prices of Gold 65% BSE 200 TRI + 25% CRISIL Composite Bond Index + 7% Domestic Price of Gold + 2% Domestic Price of Silver + 1% iCOMDEX Composite Index

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Godrej Consumer clocks PAT of Rs 498 crore in Q3; records volume growth of 7.]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/godrej-consumer-clocks-pat-of-rs-498-crore-in-q3-records-volume-growth-of-7/1667408</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667408</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In constant currency terms, revenue grew by 7% YoY.

In constant currency terms, revenue grew by 7% YoY. The growth in revenue was aided by volume growth of 7%. The company’s standalone business delivered strong performance, with underlying volume growth of 9% YoY and sales growth of 11% YoY. In contrast, the Indonesia business posted a 3% YoY decline in sales, despite underlying volumes expanding at a mid-single-digit rate. Meanwhile, the Africa, USA, and Middle East businesses recorded robust growth, with sales rising 19% YoY in INR terms and 8% YoY in constant currency terms. Total operating expenditure for the period under review was Rs 4,155.01 crore, up 7.9% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 699.98 crore, up by 2.7% from Rs 681.70 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Sudhir Sitapati, managing director, and CEO, GCPL, said: "Q3 FY26 has been a quarter of strong, broad-based performance for Godrej Consumer Products Limited, fully aligned with our expectations and strategic priorities. For the year, we remain confident of achieving high single-digit revenue growth at a consolidated level. Our India business is expected to deliver continued growth performance while holding normative EBITDA margins in the coming quarter. GAUM continues to perform well and deliver on its stated objectives of double-digit revenue and profit growth for the year. At a consolidated level, while temporary macroeconomic and pricing pressures in Indonesia and Latin America may moderate full-year EBITDA growth, we remain confident in a robust exit trajectory and sustained profitability momentum into FY27." Godrej Consumer Products is an Indian consumer goods company. The company's products include soap, hair colorants, toiletries and liquid detergents. The scrip had shed 0.48% to end at Rs 1240.25 on the BSE on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GodrejConsumer_25192758531_21960.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nippon-india-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1667407</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667407</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 29 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes.

Nippon India Mutual Fund has announced 29 January 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under the following schemes. The amount of distribution (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Nippon India Power & Infra Fund – Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 4.50 Nippon India Power & Infra Fund – Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 5.00 Nippon India Retirement Fund - Wealth Creation Scheme – Regular Plan – IDCW Option & Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 1.50 each.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gandhar Oil Refinery Q3 PAT jumps 68% YoY to Rs 32 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gandhar-oil-refinery-q3-pat-jumps-68-yoy-to-rs-32-cr/1667406</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667406</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax climbed 67.93% to Rs 45.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 26.88 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax climbed 67.93% to Rs 45.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 26.88 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 59.1 crore, registering growth of 42.06% as compared with Rs 41.6 crore recorded in previous quarter same fiscal. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit soared 38.53% YoY to Rs 94.70 crore, while revenue increased 6.63% YoY to Rs 3,129.93 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Aslesh Parekh, joint managing director said, “We delivered a strong performance in Q3 FY26, supported by sustained domestic demand and our strategic focus on high-margin PHPO products. Despite global macroeconomic headwinds and logistical disruptions, we recorded sequential growth across all major financial indicators. Looking ahead, we remain optimistic about domestic demand and expect steady improvement in international logistics, further strengthening our confidence. Gandhar Oil Refinery India is a leading manufacturer of white oils by revenue with a growing focus on the consumer and healthcare end-industries. It is engaged in producing pharmaceutical, health care, and performance oil (PHPO), process insulating oil (PIO) and lubricants. The firm’s products are sold under flagship brand “Divyol”. The counter advanced 2.98% to Rs 163.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GandharOilRefineryIndiaLtd_37404581_38912.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1667405</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667405</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes: Mirae Asset Equity Savings Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.07 per unit.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes: Mirae Asset Equity Savings Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.07 per unit. Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.165 per unit. Mirae Asset Healthcare Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.92 per unit. Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 2.21 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quantum Nifty 50 ETF announces change in Face Value of Units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quantum-nifty-50-etf-announces-change-in-face-value-of-units/1667402</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667402</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Quantum Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Quantum Nifty 50 ETF from Rs.

Quantum Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Quantum Nifty 50 ETF from Rs. 10/- to Rs. 1/- of units, effective February 13, 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Face Value of Units of Quantum Nifty 50 ETF. Name of the Scheme Existing Face Value (Rs.) Proposed Face Value (Rs.) Quantum Nifty 50 ETF 10 1

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF announces change in Face Value of Units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/groww-gold-etf-and-groww-silver-etf-announces-change-in-face-value-of-units/1667400</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667400</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Groww Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF from Rs.

Groww Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF from Rs. 10/- to Rs. 1/- of units, effective February 06, 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Face Value of Units of Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF. Name of the Schemes Existing Face Value (Rs.) Proposed Face Value (Rs.) Groww Gold ETF 10 1 Groww Silver ETF 10 1

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BPCL Q3 PAT jumps 62% YoY to Rs 7,545 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bpcl-q3-pat-jumps-62-yoy-to-rs-7545-cr/1667336</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667336</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter.

Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Profit before tax (PBT) surged 63.43% YoY to Rs 10,093.99 crore during the quarter. Total expenses increased 4.17% YoY to Rs 1,27,279.21 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 53,680.89 crore (up 5.62% YoY), while employee benefits expenses declined 28.37% YoY to Rs 860.52 crore during the period under review. In Q3 FY26, refinery throughput stood at 10.51 million metric tonnes (MMT), up 10.16% from 9.54 MMT in Q3 FY25. Domestic sales increased 4.76% YoY to 14.07 MMT in Q3 FY26 compared with 13.43 MMT in Q3 FY25. Domestic market sales growth stood at 4.76% in Q3 FY26, compared with 3.95% in Q3 FY25. Export sales improved to 0.38 MMT in Q3 FY26 from 0.26 MMT in Q3 FY25. The average gross refining margin (GRM) of the corporation for the nine months ended 31 December 2025 stood at $9.68 per barrel, compared with $5.95 per barrel in the corresponding period last year. On the margins front, the company’s operating margin improved to 6.77% in Q3 FY26 from 3.75% in Q3 FY25, while the net profit margin rose to 5.26% from 2.98% during the same period. The board of directors, at its meeting held on 23 January 2026, declared a second interim dividend of Rs 10 per equity share of face value Rs 10 each (100%) for the financial year 2025–26. The dividend will be paid through electronic mode on or before 21 February 2026. The Board has fixed Monday, 2 February 2026, as the record date to determine shareholder eligibility for the dividend. Bharat Petroleum Corporation is a public sector company which is engaged in the business of refining crude oil and marketing petroleum products. The counter slipped 1.37% to Rs 349.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BPCL_78782939994_2290.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MCX Q3 PAT jumps 151% YoY to Rs 401 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mcx-q3-pat-jumps-151-yoy-to-rs-401-crore/1667272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667272</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Income from operations jumped 120.85% YoY to Rs 665.62 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Income from operations jumped 120.85% YoY to Rs 665.62 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 503.25 crore, registering a growth of 149.29% on a YoY basis. EBITDA increased 144% YoY to Rs 527 crore during the quarter. Average daily turnover (ADT) in the futures and options (F&O) segment rose to Rs 7,50,136 crore. Total expenses rose 56.38% YoY to Rs 192.40 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Employee benefits expense stood at Rs 44.42 crore (up 33.63% YoY), while finance costs declined 82.35% YoY to Rs 0.03 crore during the period under review. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit soared 88.84% YoY to Rs 801.78 crore, while revenue increased 72.04% YoY to Rs 1,413.06 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Praveena Rai, Managing Director & CEO, MCX said, “It gives me great pleasure to share our results for Q3 of FY 2026. This quarter’s results underscore our continued momentum and deepening participation across segments. Guided by the highest level of governance and compliance, we are enhancing product breadth and operational readiness for growth, delivering value to hedgers, investors and members while shaping the future of commodity derivatives.” MCX is India's largest commodity derivatives exchange with around 98% market share in commodity futures. It offers trading in a diverse range of commodities, spanning multiple segments including bullion, energy, metals and agri commodities, as well as sectoral commodity indices. The counter slipped 1.40% to Rs 2,282.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MultiCommExc_54258329132_25746.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>