<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:55:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahalaxmi Rubtech Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahalaxmi-rubtech-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1678710</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678710</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[TIL Ltd, Datamatics Global Services Ltd, Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd and Pavna Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026.

TIL Ltd, Datamatics Global Services Ltd, Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd and Pavna Industries Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 19 February 2026. Mahalaxmi Rubtech Ltd spiked 19.17% to Rs 230 at 09:05 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 910 shares in the past one month. TIL Ltd soared 17.40% to Rs 269.25. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 87729 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2730 shares in the past one month. Datamatics Global Services Ltd surged 13.21% to Rs 839. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6899 shares in the past one month. Radaan Mediaworks (I) Ltd advanced 12.54% to Rs 3.23. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 112 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5685 shares in the past one month. Pavna Industries Ltd rose 11.58% to Rs 26.49. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 57480 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21458 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahalaxmiRubtec_32623583074_4319.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Newgen Software Technologies Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/newgen-software-technologies-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1678708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678708</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Godrej Industries Ltd, Netweb Technologies India Ltd and Safari Industries (India) Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026.

Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Godrej Industries Ltd, Netweb Technologies India Ltd and Safari Industries (India) Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 19 February 2026. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd soared 13.90% to Rs 604.5 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 46.45 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.95 lakh shares in the past one month. Tata Investment Corporation Ltd spiked 9.03% to Rs 702.2. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 12.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 52576 shares in the past one month. Godrej Industries Ltd surged 5.63% to Rs 1040.1. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 31663 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3930 shares in the past one month. Netweb Technologies India Ltd jumped 5.58% to Rs 3561. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.72 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.47 lakh shares in the past one month. Safari Industries (India) Ltd added 4.31% to Rs 1881. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3540 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3394 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewgenSoftwareTechnologiesLtd_46602882106_13722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund Has Announced a Change in the Face Value of Certain ETFs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-mutual-fund-has-announced-a-change-in-the-face-value-of-certain-etfs/1678709</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678709</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced a change in the face value of units and creation unit size for certain of its Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) with effect from February 27, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Name of the Scheme Existing Provisions Revised Provisions Kotak Nifty Bank ETF Kotak Nifty India Consumption ETF Kotak Nifty Midcap 50 ETF Kotak Silver ETF Kotak Nifty 50 Value 20 ETF The face value of each unit offered under the Scheme shall be Rs.

Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced a change in the face value of units and creation unit size for certain of its Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) with effect from February 27, 2026 Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Name of the Scheme Existing Provisions Revised Provisions Kotak Nifty Bank ETF Kotak Nifty India Consumption ETF Kotak Nifty Midcap 50 ETF Kotak Silver ETF Kotak Nifty 50 Value 20 ETF The face value of each unit offered under the Scheme shall be Rs. 10 The face value of each unit offered under the Scheme shall be Rs. 1

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MCX rallies after easing additional margins on gold, silver futures]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mcx-rallies-after-easing-additional-margins-on-gold-silver-futures/1678707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678707</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In a circular, MCX stated that additional margin of 3% levied in Gold Futures (all contracts of all variants) and 7% levied in Silver Futures (all contracts of all variants) shall be withdrawn with effect from Thursday, February 19th, 2026.

In a circular, MCX stated that additional margin of 3% levied in Gold Futures (all contracts of all variants) and 7% levied in Silver Futures (all contracts of all variants) shall be withdrawn with effect from Thursday, February 19th, 2026. Earlier on 5 February 2026, the exchange had imposed additional margin to mitigate systematic risk. It levied an extra 4.5% margin on silver futures (all variants) and 1% on gold futures (all variants) effective 5 February 2026 (beginning of day). Subsequently, from 6 February 2026 (beginning of day), a further 2.5% margin was imposed on silver futures and 2% on gold futures contracts. MCX is India's largest commodity derivatives exchange, with around 98% market share in commodity futures. It offers trading in a diverse range of commodities, spanning multiple segments including bullion, energy, metals and agri commodities, as well as sectoral commodity indices. The company reported 150.63% year-on-year (YoY) surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 401.12 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 160.04 crore in Q3 FY25. Income from operations jumped 120.85% YoY to Rs 665.62 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MultiCommExc_54258329132_25746.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dr. Reddy’s Labs acquires 'Progynova' portfolio from UK's Mercury Pharma Group ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dr-reddys-labs-acquires-progynova-portfolio-from-uks-mercury-pharma-group/1678706</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678706</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Based in UK, the Mercury Pharma Group is a specialty pharmaceutical company.

Based in UK, the Mercury Pharma Group is a specialty pharmaceutical company. Progynova (estradiol valerate) is an oral hormone replacement therapy indicated for the treatment of estrogen deficiency symptoms and for the prevention of postmenopausal osteoporosis. Cyclo Progynova (estradiol valerate and norgestrel) is a combined hormone replacement therapy indicated for the treatment of estrogen deficiency symptoms, providing both estrogen and progestogen components. As per IQVIA MAT December 2025, the Progynova brand had recorded sales of Rs 100 crore. The company stated that this acquisition would strengthen Dr. Reddy’s gynaecology portfolio and mark its strategic entry into the hormone replacement therapy segment. The total cost of this acquisition of $32.15 million, which at the prevailing exchange rate of Rs 91.09 per dollar, translates to Rs 292.85 crore. M.V. Ramana, chief executive officer, branded markets (India and Emerging Markets), Dr. Reddy’s, said: "The acquisition will serve as the spearhead of our expansion into the HRT segment, strengthening our existing gynaecology portfolio in India. With our established market access, we are uniquely positioned to extend the reach of the acquired assets and deliver greater impact." Hyderabad-based Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories is a global pharmaceutical company. It offers a portfolio of products and services including APIs, generics, branded generics, biosimilars and OTC. The company had reported a 14.4% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,209.8 crore despite of 4.4% jump in revenue to Rs 8,716.8 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip rose 0.21% to currently trade at Rs 1283.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DrReddysLaboratoriesLtd_62585850_815.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITCONS E-Solutions gains as bags manpower outsourcing contract from UCIL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itcons-e-solutions-gains-as-bags-manpower-outsourcing-contract-from-ucil/1678704</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678704</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The contract involves deployment of 10 resources for manpower outsourcing services.

The contract involves deployment of 10 resources for manpower outsourcing services. The agreement is valued at Rs 43.14 lakh (Rs 43,14,220.86), inclusive of all duties and taxes, and will run for a period of one year from 26 February 2026 to 25 February 2027, unless extended by mutual consent. The company clarified that neither its promoter nor promoter group entities have any interest in the awarding entity, and the contract does not fall under related party transactions. ITCONS E-Solutions is engaged in the business of recruitment and staffing services. On a full-year basis, the company’s net profit surged 70.2% to Rs 3.25 crore on a 96.4% rise in net sales to Rs 55.98 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITCONSESolutionsLtd_70007426_78414.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GNG Electronics rises after inking pan-India distribution deals with Ingram Micro, Supertron Electronics ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gng-electronics-rises-after-inking-pan-india-distribution-deals-with-ingram-micro-supertron-electronics/1678702</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678702</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under this collaboration, Ingram Micro India and Supertron Electronics will distribute GNG’s range of professionally refurbished laptops, desktops and enterprise computing systems under the Company’s proprietary brand ‘Electronics Bazaar’.

Under this collaboration, Ingram Micro India and Supertron Electronics will distribute GNG’s range of professionally refurbished laptops, desktops and enterprise computing systems under the Company’s proprietary brand ‘Electronics Bazaar’. The association is expected to expand GNG’s reach across Tier-1, Tier-2 and Tier-3 markets in India, deepen enterprise and institutional penetration, and strengthen access to warranty-backed refurbished systems through established ICT distribution networks. The broader industry environment has supported increasing adoption of refurbished computers. Rising component costs, supply-side adjustments in the new PC market, and evolving enterprise procurement strategies have contributed to growing interest in professionally refurbished systems as a cost-efficient and scalable alternative. In this context, refurbished ICT devices are increasingly being integrated into structured procurement frameworks. Through these partnerships, GNG expects to enhance distribution velocity, improve geographic penetration, and further embed its products within organized channel ecosystems. GNG Electronics is India’s largest refurbisher of laptops and desktops and among the largest refurbishers of ICT devices globally. As of 31 March 2025, the company had a significant presence across India, the USA, Europe, Africa and the UAE. It follows a repair-over-replacement model and refurbished nearly 5.9 lakh devices in FY25, offering a portfolio of 5,840 SKUs spanning laptops, desktops, tablets, servers, smartphones, workstations and accessories. On a consolidated basis, the company's PAT stood at Rs 38.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 102.8% YoY from Rs 19.1 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations came in at Rs 487.2 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a strong 40.3% YoY growth over Rs 347.4 crore in Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GNGElectronicsLtd_47811715_91822.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 480 pts; realty shares slide]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-480-pts-realty-shares-slide/1678701</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678701</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning amid profit booking.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning amid profit booking. The Nifty traded below the 25,700 level. Realty shares declined after advancing in the past trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 479.99 points or 0.57% to 83,254.26. The Nifty 50 index fell 131.35 points or 0.51% to 25,688.85. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index slipped 0.49% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.16%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,656 shares rose and 2,114 shares fell. A total of 215 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 1.43% to 827.30. The index rose 0.62% in the past trading session. Lodha Developers (down 1.81%), Phoenix Mills (down 1.67%), DLF (down 1.67%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 1.52%), Godrej Properties (down 1.11%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.04%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.28%), and Sobha (down 0.09%) fell. Stocks in Spotlight: Tata Consultancy Services rose 0.77%. The company announced a multi-dimensional strategic partnership with OpenAI to drive AI-powered innovation across enterprise, consumer, and social sectors. B. L. Kashyap and Sons jumped 2.37% after it secured a contract worth Rs 300 crore from CRC Greens for a group housing project in Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) shed 0.52%. The company received a letter of acceptance (LoA) from Northern Railway for a project worth Rs 1,201.35 crore. Global Markets: Asian stocks rose on Thursday, supported by gains in technology giants on Wall Street, while lingering U.S.-Iran tensions kept oil prices on the boil. Hong Kong and mainland China markets remain closed for the Lunar New Year break. Oil prices edged higher as investors digested the latest developments between the U.S. and Iran. Vice President JD Vance reportedly said Tuesday that Iran failed to address U.S. red lines in this week’s nuclear talks and that military action is still a possibility. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 moved higher, supported by gains in key technology names, as traders weighed the release of the minutes from the Federal Reserve’s most recent policy meeting. The broad-based index climbed 0.56% to end at 6,881.31, while the Nasdaq Composite added 0.78% to settle at 22,753.63. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.26% to close at 49,662.66. Investors mulled over the minutes from the Fed’s January meeting, which revealed that participants largely approved of the central bank’s decision to leave its key interest rate unchanged at a range of 3.5% to 3.75%. However, officials were divided on the direction of monetary policy thereafter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Electronics to consider interim dividend on 27 Feb’26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-electronics-to-consider-interim-dividend-on-27-feb26/1678698</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678698</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company made the official announcement on 19 February 2026, after market hours.

The company made the official announcement on 19 February 2026, after market hours. Bharat Electronics (BEL) is a Navratna PSU under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India. It manufactures electronic products and systems for the army, navy, and air force. Its standalone net profit jumped 20.81% to Rs 1,590.06 crore on 23.72% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,121.98 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The company’s order book position stood at Rs 73,015 crore as of 1 January 2026. The counter slipped 1.05% to Rs 442.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatElectron_81586952923_2298.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD extends losing streak to test one-week low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-extends-losing-streak-to-test-one-week-low/1678696</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678696</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro slipped in last session, adding to recent set of losses.

Euro slipped in last session, adding to recent set of losses. Latest data showed that German economic confidence weakened in February after a strong rebound at the start of the year. The ZEW indicator of economic sentiment dropped to 58.3 in February from 59.6 in January, which was the highest since July 2021. This pulled EUR/USD pair towards 1.1800 mark. The pair fell around half a percent yesterday and currently quotes at 1.1805, almost unchanged on the day. This is the lowest level in nearly two-weeks for the EURO. On NSE, EUR/INR futures are currently quoting flat at 107.40.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growth-on-coin-pile-business-conceptual-picture-id489_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI releases Circular on Unique Transaction Identifier for OTC Derivative Transactions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-releases-circular-on-unique-transaction-identifier-for-otc-derivative-transactions/1678694</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678694</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India had issued a draft circular on Unique Transaction Identifier (UTI) for OTC Derivative Transactions on October 23, 2025, seeking feedback from banks, market participants and other interested parties.

The Reserve Bank of India had issued a draft circular on Unique Transaction Identifier (UTI) for OTC Derivative Transactions on October 23, 2025, seeking feedback from banks, market participants and other interested parties. UTI serves as a single unique reference for an OTC derivative transaction. It enables policy makers to obtain a comprehensive view of OTC derivatives market by facilitating global aggregation of transactions. Feedback received on the draft circular has been examined and consequent modifications have been suitably incorporated in the final directions. RBI has deferred the implementation of Unique Transaction Identifier (UTI) for all over-the-counter (OTC) derivatives to obtain a comprehensive view of the market to January 2027.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Arbitrage Fund announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-arbitrage-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1678695</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678695</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced 20 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option of Kotak Arbitrage Fund.

Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund has announced 20 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW) under the monthly IDCW option of Kotak Arbitrage Fund. The amount of IDCW on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Regular Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs 0.0459 Direct Plan – Monthly IDCW Option: Rs 0.0532

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-icici-prudential-life-insurance-company-ltd-counter/1678690</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678690</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Container Corporation Of India Ltd, Tata Chemicals Ltd, NCC Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 19 February 2026.

Tata Investment Corporation Ltd, Container Corporation Of India Ltd, Tata Chemicals Ltd, NCC Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 19 February 2026. ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd clocked volume of 17.82 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 30.51 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 58428 shares. The stock gained 1.03% to Rs.655.00. Volumes stood at 1.01 lakh shares in the last session. Tata Investment Corporation Ltd witnessed volume of 8.69 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 16.87 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 51512 shares. The stock increased 11.58% to Rs.718.65. Volumes stood at 48237 shares in the last session. Container Corporation Of India Ltd clocked volume of 4.09 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.94 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 45772 shares. The stock lost 0.65% to Rs.503.40. Volumes stood at 49527 shares in the last session. Tata Chemicals Ltd clocked volume of 3.54 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.35 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 42463 shares. The stock gained 0.70% to Rs.695.00. Volumes stood at 28094 shares in the last session. NCC Ltd registered volume of 14.26 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 6.89 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.07 lakh shares. The stock slipped 1.27% to Rs.147.55. Volumes stood at 1.5 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIPrudentialLifeInsuranceCompanyLtd_18603840404_22005.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index moves up to over a one-week high; Fed policymakers deeply divided on rate decision]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-moves-up-to-over-a-one-week-high-fed-policymakers-deeply-divided-on-rate-decision/1678689</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678689</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index is consolidating gains on Thursday morning in Asia following an over half a percent gain in the previous session that took the counter to its highest level in one and half weeks.

The dollar index is consolidating gains on Thursday morning in Asia following an over half a percent gain in the previous session that took the counter to its highest level in one and half weeks. The DXY that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is currently quoting at 97.69, nearly unchanged for the day. Minutes from the January FOMC meeting revealed on Wednesday that policymakers were deeply divided over the necessity and timing of further rate cuts amid concerns about inflation. Meanwhile, safe haven demand amid signs of rising tensions between the US and Iran is also supporting the greenback. US Vice President JD Vance reportedly said on Wednesday that Iran had failed to acknowledge key US demands in talks, after which Washington said it had agreed to give Tehran two weeks to close the gaps between the sides. Investors now turn to the upcoming jobless claims., PCE inflation and GDP reports for further guidance on the rates outlook.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-exchange-rate-544949__340_commodities.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zydus launches Anyra for treatment of major retinal disorders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zydus-launches-anyra-for-treatment-of-major-retinal-disorders/1678687</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678687</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has also entered into an agreement with Regeneron Pharmaceuticals, Inc.

The company has also entered into an agreement with Regeneron Pharmaceuticals, Inc. and Bayer. Anyra is indicated for the treatment of neovascular (wet) age-related macular degeneration (AMD), visual impairment due to macular edema secondary to retinal vein occlusion (branch RVO or central RVO), visual impairment due to diabetic macular oedema (DME), diabetic retinopathy (DR), and visual impairment due to myopic choroidal neovascularisation (mCNV). With this launch, Zydus reinforces its commitment to advancing ophthalmic care and expanding access to high-quality, affordable biologics for patients across India. Presently, more than 100 million people in India are living with diabetes, making it one of the largest diabetic populations globally. Diabetic Retinopathy (DR) affects an estimated 7–8 million individuals, with many progressing to vision-threatening stages such as DME. Wet AMD impacts approximately 1.5– 2 million elderly patients, while retinal vein occlusions affect over 2 million individuals. Collectively, these conditions represent a large patient pool requiring timely anti-VEGF therapy to prevent irreversible vision loss. As chronic retinal diseases require repeated intravitreal injections over extended periods, affordability and continuity of treatment are of concern. Enhanced access to such therapies improves treatment adherence, reduces preventable blindness, and lowers long-term disease burden. Dr. Sharvil P. Patel, Managing Director, Zydus Lifesciences, said, “At Zydus, we are committed to making advanced biologics accessible to patients who need them most. ANYRA™ is a transformative step for affordable retinal care in India. By delivering a high-quality, indigenously developed Aflibercept 2 mg, we are expanding patient access to critical therapies with advanced biologics. Our focus remains on enabling patient-centric outcomes by leveraging science, health and innovation.” Separately, the company received final approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for Bosentan tablets for oral suspension, 32 mg (USRLD: Tracleer Tablets for Oral Suspension, 32 mg). The drug is indicated for the treatment of pulmonary arterial hypertension (PAH), specifically to improve exercise ability and reduce clinical worsening in children (aged 3 years and older) with idiopathic or congenital PAH. It is a dual endothelin receptor antagonist that lowers high blood pressure in the lungs, typically administered based on body weight. The product will be manufactured at the group’s formulation facility at SEZ, Ahmedabad. According to IQVIA MAT December 2025 data, Bosentan 32 mg tablets recorded annual sales of $9.3 million in the United States. The group now holds 432 approvals and has filed 505 ANDAs since the commencement of its filing process in FY2003–04. Zydus Lifesciences operates as an integrated pharmaceutical company with business encompassing the entire value chain in the research, development, production, marketing and distribution of pharmaceutical products. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 7.7% to Rs 1,102.64 crore on 32.3% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,780.40 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Zydus Lifesciences rose 0.48% to Rs 914.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CadilaHealth_93490673476_20883.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Edelweiss Gold ETF FOF  Announces Extension of NFO period]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/edelweiss-gold-etf-fof-announces-extension-of-nfo-period/1678686</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678686</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Edelweiss Mutual Fund has announced that New Fund Offer (NFO) Period of the Scheme has been modified as follows: Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Name of the Scheme Existing closing date of NFO Revised closing date of NFO Edelweiss Gold ETF FOF February 23, 2026 February 26, 2026

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TCS rises on partnering with OpenAI for advancing AI transformation]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tcs-rises-on-partnering-with-openai-for-advancing-ai-transformation/1678682</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678682</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[This partnership spans multiple high-impact areas, including powering AI-led innovation across Tata Group companies, joint efforts to drive AI transformation across industries globally, and setting up AI infrastructure.

This partnership spans multiple high-impact areas, including powering AI-led innovation across Tata Group companies, joint efforts to drive AI transformation across industries globally, and setting up AI infrastructure. Unde the partnership, several thousand Tata Group employees will get access to Enterprise ChatGPT. In addition, TCS will leverage OpenAI’s Codex to boost software engineering outcomes. Further, TCS and OpenAI will jointly enable Indian and global enterprises to transform with AI-powered solutions specific to their organizational context. Through this collaboration, TCS will help its customers accelerate AI-led transformation by deploying, integrating, and scaling OpenAI’s advanced AI platforms worldwide. Additionally, TCS’ HyperVault unit and OpenAI have agreed to a multi-year partnership to develop AI infrastructure in India. In the initial phase, TCS will develop AI infrastructure with 100MW capacity, with an option to scale to 1 GW. N Chandrasekaran, Chairman, Tata Sons, said, “This deep collaboration between OpenAI and Tata Group marks a major milestone in India’s vision to become a global leader in AI. We are pleased to partner with OpenAI to create state-of-the-art AI infrastructure in India. This is a unique opportunity for OpenAI and TCS to transform industries. Together we will skill India’s youth and empower them to succeed in the AI era." TCS is a digital transformation and technology partner of choice for industry-leading organizations worldwide. The company had reported an 11.74% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 10,657 crore, despite 1.96% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,087 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TCS_30661368_5400.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Currency Market shut for trading]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-currency-market-shut-for-trading/1678681</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678681</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The currency market is shut for trading today (19 February 2026), on account of local holiday for Chatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Jayanti.

The currency market is shut for trading today (19 February 2026), on account of local holiday for Chatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Jayanti. Trading will resume tomorrow (20th February 2026).

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's oilmeal exports tumble 42% on year in Jan-26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-oilmeal-exports-tumble-42-on-year-in-jan-26/1678679</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678679</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Solvent Extractors’ Association of India has announced that India’s export of oilmeals for the month of January 2026 is provisionally reported at 260,123 tons compared to 452,352 tons in Jan., 2025 i.e.

The Solvent Extractors’ Association of India has announced that India’s export of oilmeals for the month of January 2026 is provisionally reported at 260,123 tons compared to 452,352 tons in Jan., 2025 i.e. down by 42%. The overall export of oilmeals during Apr.’25 to Jan.’26 reported at 3,235,862 tons compared to 3,603,030 tons during the same period of last year i.e. down by 10%. Soybean meal exports slumped 22.10% this fiscal while Rapeseed meal exports tumbled around 2.82%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TIL hits the roof as board to review fundraising proposal on 23 Feb’26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/til-hits-the-roof-as-board-to-review-fundraising-proposal-on-23-feb26/1678678</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678678</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company will raise capital by way of a rights issue, preferential allotment, qualified institutional placement, or any other permissible mode and or combination thereof, through the issuance of equity shares, equity-linked securities, warrants, and or any other eligible securities.

The company will raise capital by way of a rights issue, preferential allotment, qualified institutional placement, or any other permissible mode and or combination thereof, through the issuance of equity shares, equity-linked securities, warrants, and or any other eligible securities. Earlier, on 16 February 2026, the company’s board approved the acquisition of a 60% stake in Tulip Compression (TCPL) - a fast-growing clean energy solutions provider. The move marks the company’s accelerated entry into the clean energy manufacturing ecosystem. Established in 1944, TIL (formerly Tractors India) manufactures material handling and infrastructure equipment. Headquartered in Kolkata with a pan-India presence, it is renowned for its robust, high-quality products and innovative design. The company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 6.85 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 3.70 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 7.5% YoY to Rs 73.23 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TIL_10169275963_569.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>