<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:25:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound softens after tepid service sector data, FTSE eases from record high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-softens-after-tepid-service-sector-data-ftse-eases-from-record-high/1663632</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663632</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound fell yesterday, coming off a two and half month high despite Uk equities hitting record highs.

British Pound fell yesterday, coming off a two and half month high despite Uk equities hitting record highs. The UK service sector continued to see subdued growth at the end of the fourth quarter, final survey results from S&P Global showed on Tuesday. The S&P Global Services Purchasing Managers' Index posted 51.4 in December, up slightly from 51.3 in November. The flash score was 52.1. GBP/USD pair moved down 0.30% in last session and currently quotes down marginally at 1.3495. UK stocks are in red today with the benchmark FTSE100 index giving up half a percent on the day. On NSE, GBP/INR futures are trading at 121.43, down 0.52% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/grass-picture-id487784251_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/california-software-company-ltd-partly-paidup-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663631</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663631</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Balu Forge Industries Ltd, Orient Technologies Ltd, Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd and Orient Ceratech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 07 January 2026.

Balu Forge Industries Ltd, Orient Technologies Ltd, Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd and Orient Ceratech Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 07 January 2026. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup crashed 10.87% to Rs 4.59 at 14:28 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 2750 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2110 shares in the past one month. Balu Forge Industries Ltd tumbled 10.33% to Rs 523.25. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 9.56 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 32396 shares in the past one month. Orient Technologies Ltd lost 9.45% to Rs 392.1. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5.44 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10.33 lakh shares in the past one month. Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd fell 9.09% to Rs 38. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 56836 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14138 shares in the past one month. Orient Ceratech Ltd plummeted 7.30% to Rs 47. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 92215 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 27364 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/>]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Oswal Agro Mills appoints Shreya Choudhary as CFO]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/oswal-agro-mills-appoints-shreya-choudhary-as-cfo/1663628</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663628</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shreya Choudhary is a member of the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India and a commerce graduate with strong experience in financial management, direct and indirect taxation, and financial reporting across diverse industries.

Shreya Choudhary is a member of the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India and a commerce graduate with strong experience in financial management, direct and indirect taxation, and financial reporting across diverse industries. As Whole-time Director & CEO of Oswal Agro Mills Limited, she will oversee overall operations, strategic planning, and financial management, supporting informed decision-making and sustainable growth. Oswal Agro Mills is engaged in the trading and development of real estate and trading of goods. The company also deploys its surplus funds by extending interest-bearing inter-corporate deposits. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 13.7% to Rs 1.77 crore on a 73.5% surge in total income to Rs 4.72 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Oswal Agro Mills shed 0.07% to Rs 58.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OswalAgroMills_13872677394_425.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Tata Elxsi Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-tata-elxsi-ltd-counter/1663626</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663626</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Elecon Engineering Company Ltd, Tata Technologies Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, Syngene International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 07 January 2026.

Elecon Engineering Company Ltd, Tata Technologies Ltd, Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd, Syngene International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 07 January 2026. Tata Elxsi Ltd clocked volume of 18.27 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 17.8 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.03 lakh shares. The stock gained 10.00% to Rs.5,879.50. Volumes stood at 92573 shares in the last session. Elecon Engineering Company Ltd clocked volume of 102.73 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 16.59 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.19 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.62% to Rs.511.05. Volumes stood at 4.48 lakh shares in the last session. Tata Technologies Ltd clocked volume of 70.16 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 15.16 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4.63 lakh shares. The stock gained 4.85% to Rs.680.65. Volumes stood at 3.89 lakh shares in the last session. Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd clocked volume of 140.22 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.72 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 16.09 lakh shares. The stock gained 3.97% to Rs.520.00. Volumes stood at 19.89 lakh shares in the last session. Syngene International Ltd saw volume of 20.05 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.61 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.03 lakh shares. The stock dropped 0.02% to Rs.655.55. Volumes stood at 3.94 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataElxsi_727602529_2322.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 307 pts; realty shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-307-pts-realty-shares-decline/1663627</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663627</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with significant losses in the mid- afternoon trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with significant losses in the mid- afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 26,100 level. Realty shares extended losses for second consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 306.71 points or 0.36% to 84,756.63. The Nifty 50 index dropped 86.30 points or 0.33% to 26,093.35. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.28% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.02%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,915 shares rose and 2,190 shares fell. A total of 187 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 0.78% to 907.20. The index fell 1.11% in for the second consecutive trading session. Prestige Estates Projects (down 1.99%), SignatureGlobal India (down 1.9%), Sobha (down 1.39%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.23%), DLF (down 1.18%), Phoenix Mills (down 0.54%), Brigade Enterprises (down 0.49%), Lodha Developers (down 0.22%) declined. On the other hand, Anant Raj (up 1.04%), Godrej Properties (up 0.33%) added. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.12% to 6.620 compared with previous session close of 6.612. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 89.9300 compared with its close of 90.1800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement shed 0.48% to Rs 138,416. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.01% to 98.60. The United States 10-year bond yield fell 0.77% to 4.148. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 45 cents or 0.74% to $60.25 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: PTC Industries fell 1.90%. The company announced that it has received a prestigious order from the Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre (VSSC), a key centre of the Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO) to supply grade Titanium Ingots. Tata Power Company fell 1.71%. The company said that TP Solar has manufactured 940 MW of DCR solar cells in Q3 FY26 as compared with 196 MW of cells manufactured in the corresponding period last year, thereby registering an increase of nearly 5x on YoY basis.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-mutual-funds-picture-id157281690_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T incorporates wholly owned subsidiary SuFin]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-incorporates-wholly-owned-subsidiary-sufin/1663619</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663619</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said the intimation follows the receipt of the certificate of incorporation from the Ministry of Corporate Affairs on 7 January 2026.

The company said the intimation follows the receipt of the certificate of incorporation from the Ministry of Corporate Affairs on 7 January 2026. SuFin has been incorporated to engage in wholesale trade through e-commerce and will primarily continue the existing SuFin business currently operated by L&T, subject to terms to be agreed in the future. Larsen & Toubro, along with its nominee shareholders, has subscribed to 100% of the equity share capital of SuFin Limited, amounting to Rs 5 lakh. Consequently, the entire shareholding of the new entity is held by L&T. SuFin has an authorised share capital of Rs 5 lakh, comprising 50,000 equity shares of Rs 10 each. The subscribed and paid-up capital of Rs 5 lakh has been fully subscribed by Larsen & Toubro along with its nominee shareholders. Larsen & Toubro is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services. The company reported a 15.6% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,926.09 crore on a 10.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 67,983.53 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Larsen & Toubro rose 0.04% to currently trade at Rs 4,143 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India Ratings and Research revises ratings outlook of Jindal Stainless to ‘positive’ ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-ratings-and-research-revises-ratings-outlook-of-jindal-stainless-to-positive/1663618</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663618</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘IND A1+’.

The agency has also affirmed the company’s short-term rating at ‘IND A1+’. India Ratings and Research stated that the outlook revision reflects the agency’s expectation of a likely increase in the scale of operations over FY26-FY28 on the back of a sustained improvement in the sales volume, maintaining of the EBITDA per tonne around Rs 20,000, and continued high-capacity utilisation. The ratings also factor in the JSL group’s strong business profile, backed by an increase in the proportion of value-added products, improved group’s financial flexibility, sustained comfortable credit metrics and diversified product mix. It also considers the diversified sourcing strategies that reduce exposure to volatility in nickel prices, and adequate liquidity. The EBITDA per tonne is likely to sustain in the medium term on the back of improved product mix, cost-saving measures, operating leverage and business synergies. India Ratings expects JSL's financial profile to remain comfortable over FY26-FY28, supported by healthy cash flows and low incremental debt requirement. However, the ratings are constrained by the group’s exposure to volatility in raw material prices as well as realisations, and the threat of low-cost imports. India Ratings further said that a sustained increase in the scale of operations while maintaining EBIDTA per tonne and net adjusted leverage remaining below 2.0x could lead to a positive rating action. However, a lower-than-expected scale of operations or a material reduction in the group’s profitability, leading to a significant decline in the EBITDA per tonne and/or higher-than-expected debt, leading to the net adjusted leverage exceeding 2.0x, on a sustained basis, could lead to a negative rating action. Jindal Stainless has been a leader in the stainless-steel industry in India for the last 50 years. It manufactures stainless steel in flat products in austenitic, ferritic, martensitic and duplex grades. The company had reported 32% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 806.94 crore on a 11.41% increase in revenue to Rs 10,892.78 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip shed 0.83% to currently trade at Rs 854.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JindalStain_15230115440_24610.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-petroleum-corporation-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1663607</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663607</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 368.8, down 0.54% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 26098.7. The Sensex is at 84796.27, down 0.31%.Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd has added around 3.15% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 3.63% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35849.15, down 0.42% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 18.67 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 56.89 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 370, down 0.59% on the day. Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd jumped 28.59% in last one year as compared to a 10.17% rally in NIFTY and a 1.54% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 7.42 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BPCL_78782939994_2290.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd drops for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-petroleum-corporation-ltd-drops-for-fifth-straight-session/1663608</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663608</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today.

Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd fell for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 478.65, down 0.77% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 26098.7. The Sensex is at 84796.27, down 0.31%.Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd has gained around 7.33% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 3.63% in last one month and is currently quoting at 35849.15, down 0.42% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 14.04 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 37.2 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 480.1, down 0.83% on the day. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd jumped 22.31% in last one year as compared to a 10.17% rally in NIFTY and a 1.54% spurt in the Nifty Energy index. The PE of the stock is 7.02 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HPCL_59291502793_2305.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITC Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itc-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1663609</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663609</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ITC Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

ITC Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 340.45, down 0.58% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 26098.7. The Sensex is at 84796.27, down 0.31%.ITC Ltd has lost around 15.37% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which ITC Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 2.01% in last one month and is currently quoting at 53561.95, down 0.22% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 192.97 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 316.7 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 342.1, down 0.61% on the day. ITC Ltd tumbled 24.27% in last one year as compared to a 10.17% rally in NIFTY and a 6.18% fall in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 21.54 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITC_29088800077_301.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[D B Corp Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/d-b-corp-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1663610</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663610</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[D B Corp Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today.

D B Corp Ltd dropped for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 254.25, down 0.18% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.31% on the day, quoting at 26098.7. The Sensex is at 84796.27, down 0.31%.D B Corp Ltd has added around 5.32% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which D B Corp Ltd is a constituent, has increased around 3.99% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1456.6, down 0.38% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 12380 shares today, compared to the daily average of 72406 shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 13.17 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DBCorp_72647549474_28589.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PTC Inds bags Titanium Ingots supply order from VSSC]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ptc-inds-bags-titanium-ingots-supply-order-from-vssc/1663611</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663611</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The order involves the conversion of 40 tonnes of Grade 1 Titanium sponge into Ti-6Al-4V Titanium alloy ingots, produced using a Double Vacuum Arc Remelting (Double VAR) process, meeting the stringent quality and purity requirements of space and aerospace applications.

The order involves the conversion of 40 tonnes of Grade 1 Titanium sponge into Ti-6Al-4V Titanium alloy ingots, produced using a Double Vacuum Arc Remelting (Double VAR) process, meeting the stringent quality and purity requirements of space and aerospace applications. The said order is expected to be executed in 1 year. Vacuum Arc Remelting (VAR) is a critical secondary melting process used for producing aerospace-grade Titanium alloys. The value of the purchase order is reasonably significant and is expected to positively impact the company’s revenue, the exact order value has not been disclosed due to confidentiality clauses applicable to contracts placed by VSSC, a centre operating under the Department of Space (DoS), Government of India. PTC Industries is a leading Indian manufacturer of precision metal components for critical applications. Through its wholly owned subsidiary Aerolloy Technologies, the company is manufacturing and supplying titanium and superalloy castings for aerospace and defence applications within India as well as for exports. The company reported 4.79% growth in consolidated net profit to Rs 18.14 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 17.31 crore posted in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations surged 72.21% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 124.63 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. The counter shed 0.23% to Rs 17,829.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PTCInds_85881590_5380.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 26,100 level; broader market outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-26100-level-broader-market-outperforms/1663606</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663606</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade amid mixed global cues and renewed concerns over US tariffs and geopolitical tensions.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade amid mixed global cues and renewed concerns over US tariffs and geopolitical tensions. The Nifty traded below the 26,100 level. Auto, realty and oil & gas shares declined, while IT and consumer durables shares advanced. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 338.29 points or 0.40% to 84,725.05. The Nifty 50 index dropped 105.80 points or 0.40% to 26,072.75. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.09% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.16%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,838 shares rose and 2,229 shares fell. A total of 172 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Titan Company (up 4.26%), Jio Financial Services (up 1.56%), HCL Technologies (up 1.63%), Infosys (up 1.29%) and Wipro (up 1.28%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Cipla (down 4.40%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 3.33%), Max Healthcare Institute (down 2.24%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 2.30%), and Mahindra & Mahindra (down 1.70%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Info Edge (India) rose 1.48% after it posted strong performance in its recruitment segment, which saw revenues increase 10.99% YoY to Rs 548.3 crore on 31 December 2025, up from Rs 494 crore in the same period last year. Kalyan Jewellers India jumped 3.36% after the company’s consolidated revenue climbed approximately 42% YoY, driven by robust festive demand, strong same-store sales growth (SSSG), and sharp traction in its digital platform, Candere. Titan Company rose 4.28% after its domestic consumer businesses recorded around 40% year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26, with jewellery emerging as the biggest contributor. The jewellery portfolio posted about 41% YoY growth, supported by strong wedding and festive demand and improved performance across gold studded jewellery and gold coins. Lodha Developers shed 0.28%. The company reported pre-sales of Rs 5,620 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 25% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 4,510 crore in Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets open mixed territory on Wednesday as regional market jitters grow over U.S. President Donald Trump’s threat to annex Greenland. Asian shares traded mixed, with regional defense stocks snapping a two-day winning streak on Wednesday, as investors continued to assess geopolitical risks after the U.S. attack on Venezuela and renewed rhetoric over Greenland. White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt reportedly said on Tuesday that President Donald Trump and his team were considering “a range of options” in order to acquire Greenland—including “utilizing the U.S. Military.” The statement further escalates the Trump administration’s already aggressive rhetoric about Greenland, which the president has long sought to make a part of the United States. U.S. crude futures fell 1.3% to $56.39 per barrel after U.S. President Donald Trump said that Venezuela would transfer between 30 million and 50 million barrels of oil to the United States. The remarks followed a weekend operation in which U.S. forces seized former leader Nicolás Maduro. Overnight in the United States, stocks advanced as investors appeared to look past the Venezuela operation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Power's step-down subsidiary produced 940 MW of solar modules in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-powers-step-down-subsidiary-produced-940-mw-of-solar-modules-in-q3/1663605</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663605</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Module production stood at 990 MW versus 927 MW in the same period last year, reflecting an approximately 7% year-on-year growth.

Module production stood at 990 MW versus 927 MW in the same period last year, reflecting an approximately 7% year-on-year growth. For the period from April 2025 to December 2025, TP Solar manufactured 2.8 GW of DCR solar cells and 2.9 GW of solar modules. Out of 2.9 GW modules, 2.4GW were DCR Modules and balance 0.5 GW were ALMM modules. TP Solar operates one of India’s largest single-location state of the art, 4.3 GW Solar Cell and Module manufacturing facility in Tirunelveli, Tamil Nadu. TP Solar is the solar manufacturing arm and a wholly owned subsidiary of Tata Power Renewable Energy, which is a subsidiary of The Tata Power Company. Tata Power Company is primarily engaged in the generation, transmission, and distribution of electricity. It aims to produce electricity entirely through renewable sources. The company also manufactures solar rooftops and plans to build 1 lakh EV charging stations by 2025. Tata Power is India’s largest vertically integrated power company. The company’s consolidated net profit dipped 0.8% to Rs 919.44 crore, while revenue from operations declined 1% to Rs 15,544.91 crore in Q2 FY26 compared with Q2 FY25. The scrip fell 1.73% to currently trade at Rs 379.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataPowerCo_38377109932_554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Meesho slumps after shareholder lock-in expiry]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/meesho-slumps-after-shareholder-lock-in-expiry/1663604</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663604</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Around 10.99 crore shares, or nearly 2% of the company’s outstanding equity, have reportedly become eligible for trading following the end of the lock-in.

Around 10.99 crore shares, or nearly 2% of the company’s outstanding equity, have reportedly become eligible for trading following the end of the lock-in. However, this does not necessarily indicate immediate selling, as the expiry only allows these shares to be traded. Meesho made its stock market debut on 10 December 2025. The stock is up 56.04% over its IPO price of Rs 111 and has gained 7.44% from its listing price of Rs 161.20. Post listing, the stock had surged 57.97% from its listing price to hit a record high of Rs 254.65 on 18 December 2025, before witnessing profit-taking. The stock is currently down about 32% from its peak levels. The company’s initial public offering had seen strong investor interest, with the issue subscribed 79.03 times. The IPO was open for subscription between December 3 and December 5, with a price band of Rs 105 to Rs 111 per share. Meesho plans to utilise the IPO proceeds to strengthen its cloud infrastructure, invest in technology and AI talent, scale up marketing and brand-building initiatives, pursue inorganic growth opportunities and meet general corporate requirements. The company operates a multi-sided e-commerce platform connecting consumers, sellers, logistics partners and content creators. Order fulfilment is managed through its in-house logistics arm, Valmo, as well as third-party logistics partners. For the quarter ended September 2025, Meesho reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 700.72 crore, while revenue stood at Rs 5,577.54 crore. Its net merchandise value per annual transacting seller grew at a CAGR of 16.86% between FY23 and FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MeeshoLtd_15936426_77963.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rabi acreage edges up 2.65% on year]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rabi-acreage-edges-up-265-on-year/1663602</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663602</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The total area sown under rabi crops in current winter season has edged up by 16.4 lakh hectares or 2.65% on year to 634.14 lakh hectares as on January 2 this year, data released by the Ministry of Agriculture and Farmers Welfare showed.

The total area sown under rabi crops in current winter season has edged up by 16.4 lakh hectares or 2.65% on year to 634.14 lakh hectares as on January 2 this year, data released by the Ministry of Agriculture and Farmers Welfare showed. The area under wheat has moved up to 334.17 lakh hectares, up 1.86% on year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/agriculture-1551091__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Radico Khaitan Ltd spurts 2.85%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/radico-khaitan-ltd-spurts-285/1663598</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663598</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Radico Khaitan Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Radico Khaitan Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 3217.9, up 2.85% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.37% on the day, quoting at 26081.2. The Sensex is at 84749.13, down 0.37%. Radico Khaitan Ltd has risen around 2.22% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Radico Khaitan Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 2.18% in last one month and is currently quoting at 53561.95, down 0.39% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.31 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 3 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 90.5 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RadicoKhaitan_11315875496_2153.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Britannia Industries Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/britannia-industries-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1663599</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663599</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Britannia Industries Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Britannia Industries Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 6195.5, up 1.08% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.37% on the day, quoting at 26081.2. The Sensex is at 84749.13, down 0.37%. Britannia Industries Ltd has gained around 5.95% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty FMCG index of which Britannia Industries Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.18% in last one month and is currently quoting at 53561.95, down 0.39% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.87 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.12 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 6220.5, up 0.96% on the day. Britannia Industries Ltd is up 27.48% in last one year as compared to a 10.1% jump in NIFTY and a 6.35% jump in the Nifty FMCG index. The PE of the stock is 64.09 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BritanniaInds_60979410361_93.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Wockhardt Ltd up for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wockhardt-ltd-up-for-third-consecutive-session/1663600</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663600</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Wockhardt Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Wockhardt Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1513.7, up 3.27% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.37% on the day, quoting at 26081.2. The Sensex is at 84749.13, down 0.37%. Wockhardt Ltd has gained around 15.08% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Wockhardt Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 2.29% in last one month and is currently quoting at 23126.85, up 0.13% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 6.09 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 9.18 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 168.77 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Wockhardt_86323674169_8021.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Info Edge gains on reporting strong recruitment revenue growth]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/info-edge-gains-on-reporting-strong-recruitment-revenue-growth/1663601</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663601</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s real estate platform, 99acres, also delivered healthy growth, with revenues climbing 14.42% YoY to Rs 117.4 crore, compared to Rs 102.6 crore in 31 December 2024.

The company’s real estate platform, 99acres, also delivered healthy growth, with revenues climbing 14.42% YoY to Rs 117.4 crore, compared to Rs 102.6 crore in 31 December 2024. Info Edge (India) is India's premier online classifieds company in recruitment, matrimony, real estate, education and related services. The company’s consolidated net profit soared 1,260.81% to Rs 316.39 crore on 14.92% increase in net sales to Rs 805.45 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/InfoEdgIndia_32670259917_18844.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>