<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian economy has experienced a virtuous cycle of accelerated growth and macroeconomic stability, says RBI Deputy Governor]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-economy-has-experienced-a-virtuous-cycle-of-accelerated-growth-and-macroeconomic-stability-says-rbi-deputy-governor/1679349</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679349</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian economy is not just growing at an accelerated pace, it is also depicting enhanced macroeconomic stability which is reflected in a whole host of economic outcomes becoming steadier, Poonam Gupta, Deputy Governor, Reserve Bank of India, has noted.

Indian economy is not just growing at an accelerated pace, it is also depicting enhanced macroeconomic stability which is reflected in a whole host of economic outcomes becoming steadier, Poonam Gupta, Deputy Governor, Reserve Bank of India, has noted. The economic outcomes now materialize within a narrower range, most notable of which are aggregate economic growth - overall as well as growth across sectors - and inflation, she opined in a speech titled Perspectives on India’s Growth: Last Four Decades to the Present. High, stable and accelerating growth, and more predictable economic outcomes have become the hallmarks of the Indian economy. The Indian economy, with its macroeconomic stability, policy consistency, a large and diversified demand base consisting of domestic consumption as well as exports, and a diversified production base is assured of a continuously improving economic trajectory. This is in contrast to a more modest economic promise of most other Emerging and Developing Economies, for they lack one or more of these enabling factors. An economy is typically assessed to be macroeconomically stable if specific outcomes (commonly, inflation, current account deficit, fiscal deficit, quality of public debt and deficit, and those pertaining to the financial sector) are seen to be sustainable, growth supportive, and not indicative of excessive underlying risks or overheating. For India, most of these indicators have remained in a healthy range over the last four decades with notable improvement in recent years. Inflation has both moderated over time and has become more stable, especially under the flexible inflation targeting (FIT) regime. Average annual CPI inflation in India has declined from close to 10 per cent in the 1990s to about 6 per cent a year in the subsequent two decades; to below 5 per cent in the last four years; and is likely to remain benign in the coming months. Inflation has also declined relative to other countries. India’s inflation differential has narrowed vis-à-vis advanced economies (AEs) and other emerging market and developing economies (EMDEs).

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/growth-951606__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee yields to losses]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-yields-to-losses/1679346</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679346</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed weaker at 91.0975 per Dollar on Tuesday (24 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.9175 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gaudium IVF and Women Health IPO subscribed 7.27 times]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gaudium-ivf-and-women-health-ipo-subscribed-727-times/1679345</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679345</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 10,63,50,489 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 10,63,50,489 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:30 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 7.27 times. The issue opened for bidding on Friday (20 February 2026) and it closed on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 189 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The IPO comprises a fresh issue of 1,13,92,500 equity shares, worth up to Rs 90 crore, and an offer for sale of 9,493,700 equity shares, aggregating up to Rs 75 crore, by Dr. Manika Khanna. The objectives for the fresh issue include Rs 50 crore for funding capital expenditure towards the establishment of new IVF centers, Rs 20 crore for repayment and prepayment of certain outstanding loans, and the remaining amount for general corporate purposes. The promoters and promoter group hold an aggregate of 6,13,85,084 equity shares, aggregating to 99.99% of the pre-offer issued and paid-up equity share capital. Their post-IPO shareholding is expected to be around 71.29%. Ahead of the IPO of Gaudium IVF and Women Health on 19 February 2026, the company raised Rs 49.50 crore from anchor investors by allotting 62.65 lakh shares at Rs 79 each to 4 anchor investors. Gaudium IVF and Women Health (est. 2015) is an India-based fertility chain operating 30+ centers under a hub-and-spoke model. It offers IVF, ICSI, IUI, fertility preservation, and related gynecology services. IVF contributes approximately 69% of revenue, with a success rate of 58.74% and average revenue per patient of Rs 2.58 lakh. The company plans to add 19 new centers over FY26–FY28 to expand its footprint. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 4.28 crore and income from operations of Rs 49.50 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shree Ram Twistex IPO subscribed 75%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shree-ram-twistex-ipo-subscribed-75/1679338</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679338</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 79,76,880 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 79,76,880 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.75 times. The issue opened for bidding on Monday (23 February 2026) and it closed on Wednesday (25 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 144 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The offer consists of an entirely fresh issue of 1.06 crore equity shares. At the upper price band of Rs 104, the company intends to raise Rs 110.24 crore. Shree Ram Twistex to utilise proceeds from the IPO for setting up a 4.2 MW wind power plant for captive use at the expense of Rs 39 crore. Further, Rs 14.89 crore will be used for repayment of certain borrowings, Rs 44 crore for working capital requirements, and the balance towards general corporate purposes. Shree Ram Twistex manufactures cotton yarns, including compact ring spun, combed, and carded varieties for knitting, weaving, and value-added yarns like slub and lycra blends. Operating on a B2B model, it supplies domestic textile manufacturers and exporters, with exports contributing 6–10% of revenue. The Gujarat-based facility has 17 spinning machines and five warehouses with 9,855 MT storage capacity. For the six months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 7 crore and income from operations of Rs 132.08 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery subscribed 59%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pngs-reva-diamond-jewellery-subscribed-59/1679334</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679334</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 33,83,488 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer, , according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026).

PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 33,83,488 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer, , according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.56 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. The IPO comprises a fresh issue of equity shares worth up to Rs 380 crore. The objectives for the fresh issue include Rs 286.56 for funding expenditure towards setting-up of 15 new stores, Rs 35.4 crore for marketing and promotional expenses, and remaining amount for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery on 23 February 2026, the company raised Rs 920.99 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 87.46 lakh shares at Rs 1,053 each to 41 anchor investors. P. N. Gadgil & Sons, its corporate promoter, divested its diamond business through a slump sale to PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery under a business transfer agreement (BTA). Following this transaction, PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery operates as a separate entity in the diamond jewellery segment. PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery offers different types of jewellery using diamonds, precious and semi-precious stones, which are studded into precious metals such as gold and platinum. The product offerings include rings, earrings, necklaces, pendants, solitaires, bangles, bracelets, mangalsutra, nose rings, and chains to cater to diverse customer segments and occasions. Prices start at around Rs 20,000 and go up to high-value jewellery pieces. As of September 30, 2025, the company had 13 distinct jewellery collections, including in-house design team and curated selections from third-party manufacturers and Karigars. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 20.13 crore and income from operations of Rs 156.72 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions subscribed 45%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/clean-max-enviro-energy-solutions-subscribed-45/1679333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679333</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The initial public offer (IPO) of Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions 97,59,106 received bids for 75,07,654 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (23 February 2026).

The initial public offer (IPO) of Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions 97,59,106 received bids for 75,07,654 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Monday (23 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.45 times. The issue opened for bidding on Monday (23 February 2026) and it will close on Wednesday (25 February 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 14 equity shares and in multiples thereof. The issue comprises fresh equity shares, aggregating Rs 1,200 crore, and an offer-for-sale (OFS) of equity shares, aggregating Rs 1900 crore. The OFS by the promoters include equity shares, aggregating Rs 216.799 crore by Kuldeep Jain, Rs 903.898 crore by BGTF One Holdings, and Rs 73 crore by KEMPINC LLP. The OFS by selling shareholders aggregate Rs 541.921 crore and by DSDG Holdings Rs 164.382 crore. Of the net proceeds, Rs 1122.674 crore will be used for repayment and/or pre-payment, in part or full,of all or certain outstanding borrowings and/or certain of subsidiaries, and balance for general corporate purposes. Total borrowings stood at Rs 10,121.46 crore as of 30 September 2025. Ahead of the IPO, Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions on 20 February 2026, the company raised Rs 920.99 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 87.46 lakh shares at Rs 1,053 each to 41 anchor investors. CleanMax is India‘s largest commercial and industrial (C&I) renewable energy provider, with 2799 MW of operational capacity portfolio as of 31 October 2025. Additionally, capacity of 3,044 MW was in an advanced stage, 3,172 MW contracted and 1,914 MW under development. With 15 years of experience since inception, CleanMax specializes in delivering net zero and decarbonization solutions, including supplying renewable power and energy services and carbon credit solutions across data centres, AI and technology industries and C&I enterprises across a range of sectors, including infrastructure, cement, steel, industrial manufacturing, FMCG, pharmaceuticals, real estate, and global capability centres. The company’s s expertise spans across providing energy contracting, engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) services, and operation and maintenance (O&M) services of renewable energy plants including solar, wind and hybrid plants, within the customer‘s premises (onsite) and within inhouse-developed renewable energy (solar, wind and hybrid) farms (offsite). Renewable energy power sales revenue as a percentage of revenue from operations amounted to 77.09% and 74.03% in H1FY2026 and FY 2025. For the six month ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 15.44 crore and income from operations of Rs 932.95 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles near three-week low amid firm greenback overseas; Muted local shares weigh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-near-three-week-low-amid-firm-greenback-overseas-muted-local-shares-weigh/1679332</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679332</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee traded in a narrow range on Tuesday and settled 6 paise lower at 90.95 (provisional) against the US dollar amid a firm greenback and higher crude oil prices.

The Indian rupee traded in a narrow range on Tuesday and settled 6 paise lower at 90.95 (provisional) against the US dollar amid a firm greenback and higher crude oil prices. A sharp fall in domestic equity markets and uncertainties over the India-US trade deal further pressured the local unit, while foreign fund inflows lent some support. Indian shares came under heavy selling pressure on Tuesday, with concerns over tariffs, U.S.-Iran tensions and worries over AI-related disruptions keeping investors on edge. The benchmark BSE Senex ended the session down 1,068.74 points, or 1.28 percent, at 82,225.92 while the broader NSE Nifty index tumbled 288.35 points, or 1.12 percent, to 25,424.65. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 90.91 and traded in a narrow range of 90.91-90.97 due to possible intervention by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI). It ended the session at 90.95 (provisional), down 6 paise from its previous close and at its lowest level in nearly three weeks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty tumble as tariff concerns weigh; IT shares plunge ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-tumble-as-tariff-concerns-weigh-it-shares-plunge/1679331</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679331</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian benchmark indices suffered a major setback on Tuesday, as a brutal sell-off in the information technology sector dragged the market into the deep red.

Indian benchmark indices suffered a major setback on Tuesday, as a brutal sell-off in the information technology sector dragged the market into the deep red. The expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE intensified volatility. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 479.95 points or 0.58% to 83,294.66. The Nifty 50 index gained 141.75 points or 0.55% to 25,713. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively. The primary catalyst for the decline was a massive rout in IT heavyweights, triggered by fears of AI-led disruption after Anthropic’s "Claude Code" tool raised concerns about the long-term viability of the traditional labor-arbitrage model. Adding to the gloom were renewed global trade anxieties following U.S. President Donald Trump’s threats of universal tariffs and escalating geopolitical tensions that led the Brent crude towards the $72-per-barrel mark. By the closing bell, the carnage had wiped out over Rs 4 lakh crore in investor wealth, leaving only a few defensive sectors like metals and FMCG in positive territory. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.21% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index added 0.51%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.35% to 14.17. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.43% to 6.670 compared with the previous session close of 6.725. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9475 compared with its close of 90.9450 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.48% to Rs 160,810. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.10% to 97.84. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.035. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement added 16 cents or 0.22% to $71.65 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures are currently up 69 points, indicating a positive opening for equities on Wall Street today. European market declined while their Asian peers ended mixed on Tuesday as investors weighed renewed tariff threats from U.S. President Donald Trump and concerns that artificial intelligence could disrupt software companies. Trump posted on Truth Social Monday that any country that wants to “play games” with the Supreme Court decision “will be met with a much higher tariff.” The comments followed a Supreme Court decision Friday striking down tariffs enacted under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act. In response, Trump said he would impose a 15% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act. Investors in Asia were also assessing China’s loan prime rate (LPR) decision. China’s central bank on Tuesday kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged at 3% for the one-year LPR and 3.5% for the five-year LPR. Overnight on Wall Street, U.S. equities tumbled on Monday as investors grappled with persistent fears around artificial intelligence disruptions to various industries and President Donald Trump’s decision to raise his global tariffs. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 821.91 points, or 1.66%, to close at 48,804.06, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.13% and ended at 22,627.27. The S&P 500 shed 1.04% and closed at 6,837.75, putting it into the red once again for 2026. The 30-stock Dow was dragged down by IBM shares, which declined 13% on the heels of Anthropic outlining new programming capabilities for its Claude Code product. Software stocks such as Microsoft and CrowdStrike were under pressure yet again as AI disruption worries hovered over the market. However, software hasn’t been the only sector to be hit due to AI fears recently: Stocks linked to trucking and logistics, commercial real estate and financial services have similarly suffered losses this month. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharti Airtel slipped 2.91%. The telecom major said that it will capitalise its NBFC arm, Airtel Money, with Rs 20,000 crore over the next few years. HUDCO (down 2.11%), Piramal Pharma (down 1.42%), Tata Technologies (down 4.78%) and Torrent Power (down 0.49) declined after the National Stock Exchange (NSE) has decided to exclude these securities from the Futures & Options (F&O) segment with effect from 29 April 2026. IDFC First Bank added 1.31%. The company said the recent volatility in its share price followed the detection of a Rs 590-crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch. The bank added that reports regarding government de-empanelment are part of the ordinary course of business. Silver Touch Technologies declined 1.44%. The company announced that it has been selected by the FSSAI for a strategic digital transformation engagement. Shilpa Medicare fell 2.29%. The company said that its subsidiary Shilpa Biologicals and SteinCares have entered into a strategic licensing agreement to commercialize a biosimilar across Latin America. Under the agreement, SteinCares will hold exclusive rights to register, commercialize, and distribute the biosimilar across the region while Shilpa Biologicals will complete product development and provide long-term commercial manufacturing from its facility in Dharwad, India. Brahmaputra Infrastructure hit an upper circuit of 5% after it has emerged as the L-1 bidder for a National Highway project awarded by the Ministry of Road Transport & Highways (MoRTH), Government of India. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) fell 3.51%. The company said its Heavy Civil Infrastructure (HCI) and Heavy Engineering (HE) verticals have jointly secured a ‘significant’ order from the Department of Atomic Energy for the LIGO India Observatory in Maharashtra. Samvardhana Motherson International rose 1.11%. The company announced that it has launched a manufacturing facility in Sanand, Gujarat, dedicated to producing cutting-edge exterior lighting systems. The facility has been set up under a strategic joint venture with Marelli, namely Marelli Motherson Automotive Lighting India (MMLI). The joint venture strengthens the group’s capabilities in automotive component manufacturing. MMLI is a 50:50 partnership between Samvardhana Motherson International and Marelli Europe S.p.A. Signpost India rose 0.23%. The company has secured exclusive outdoor advertising rights from the Kolkata Municipal Corporation under the ‘Kolkata Streetscape Renaissance’ project in a Rs 450-crore, 10-year public-private partnership contract. Waaree Energies rallied 3.68% after the company announced that it has received an order to supply 500 MW of solar modules from a renowned domestic solar power developer and independent power producer (IPP). Indoco Remedies advanced 2.58% after it has received final approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) for Brivaracetam Oral Solution, 10 mg/mL. Caplin Point Laboratories slipped 1.08%. The company announced that its subsidiary, Caplin Steriles, has received final approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for Sodium Phosphates Injection USP. KEC International added 1.38% after the company announced that it has secured new orders worth Rs 1,002 crore across its Transmission & Distribution (T&D) and Cables & Conductors businesses. IPO Update: PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 32,03,072 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer, , according to stock exchange data at 16:12 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.56 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 10,50,76,629 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:12 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.54 times. The issue was subscribed 7.19 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it will close on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 69,88,032 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:12 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 1.54 times. The issue was subscribed 0.66 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 97,02,196 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:12 IST on Tuesday (24 February 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.44 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty March futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-march-futures-trade-at-premium/1679330</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679330</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 30 March 2026 futures closed at 25,613.80, a premium of 189.15 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,424.65 in the cash market.

The Nifty 30 March 2026 futures closed at 25,613.80, a premium of 189.15 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,424.65 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index fell 288.35 points or 1.12% to 25,424.65. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 0.12% to 14.15. HDFC Bank, Infosys and Tata Consultancy Services were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The March 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 30 March 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 1,069 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,450]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-1069-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25450/1679329</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679329</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended sharply lower today, breaking a two-day winning streak, as heavy selling in IT counters weighed on the market.

The key equity indices ended sharply lower today, breaking a two-day winning streak, as heavy selling in IT counters weighed on the market. Escalating geopolitical tensions, renewed tariff threats from former US President Donald Trump, and concerns over AI-driven disruptions in global technology stocks added to investor caution. Nifty ended below the 25,450 mark. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,068.74 points or 1.28% to 82,225.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 288.35 points or 1.12% to 25,424.65. In the past two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.40% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.76%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, shed 0.12% to 14.15. Among the sectoral indices, the Metal index (up 0.93%), the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 0.50%) and the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 0.29%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty IT index (down 4.74%), the Nifty Realty index (down 2.54%) and the Nifty Media index (down 1.31%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.43% to 6.670 compared with the previous session close of 6.725. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9475 compared with its close of 90.9450 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement shed 0.48% to Rs 160,810. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.10% to 97.84. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.22% to 4.035. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement added 16 cents or 0.22% to $71.65 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares declined on Tuesday as investors assessed the new global trading landscape after U.S. President Donald Trump’s latest tariff move. Asian markets ended mixed as investors weighed renewed tariff threats from U.S. President Donald Trump and concerns that artificial intelligence could disrupt software companies. Trump posted on Truth Social Monday that any country that wants to “play games” with the Supreme Court decision “will be met with a much higher tariff.” The comments followed a Supreme Court decision Friday striking down tariffs enacted under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act. In response, Trump said he would impose a 15% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act. Investors in Asia were also assessing China’s loan prime rate (LPR) decision. China’s central bank on Tuesday kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged at 3% for the one-year LPR and 3.5% for the five-year LPR. Overnight on Wall Street, U.S. equities tumbled on Monday as investors grappled with persistent fears around artificial intelligence disruptions to various industries and President Donald Trump’s decision to raise his global tariffs. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 821.91 points, or 1.66%, to close at 48,804.06, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.13% and ended at 22,627.27. The S&P 500 shed 1.04% and closed at 6,837.75, putting it into the red once again for 2026. The 30-stock Dow was dragged down by IBM shares, which declined 13% on the heels of Anthropic outlining new programming capabilities for its Claude Code product. Software stocks such as Microsoft and CrowdStrike were under pressure yet again as AI disruption worries hovered over the market. However, software hasn’t been the only sector to be hit due to AI fears recently: Stocks linked to trucking and logistics, commercial real estate, and financial services have similarly suffered losses this month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty IT Index registers a drop of 4.74%, NIFTY Crashes  1.12% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-it-index-registers-a-drop-of-474-nifty-crashes-112/1679326</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679326</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty IT index closed down 4.74% at 30053.5 today.

Nifty IT index closed down 4.74% at 30053.5 today. The index has lost 21.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, LTIMindtree Ltd fell 6.84%, Tech Mahindra Ltd slipped 6.63% and Persistent Systems Ltd dropped 6.34%. The Nifty IT index has decreased 24.00% over last one year compared to the 12.73% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Realty index has slid 2.54% and Nifty Services Sector index has slid 1.46% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has declined 1.12% to close at 25424.65 while the SENSEX has declined 1.28% to close at 82225.92 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finance-background-picture-id625756386_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Centum Electronics rises on HAL order for AESA radar systems for UH-M helicopters]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/centum-electronics-rises-on-hal-order-for-aesa-radar-systems-for-uh-m-helicopters/1679325</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679325</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Phase-1 order, valued at Rs 66 crore (Rs 78 crore gross), covers the design and development of AESA radar systems to be delivered over the next two financial years.

The Phase-1 order, valued at Rs 66 crore (Rs 78 crore gross), covers the design and development of AESA radar systems to be delivered over the next two financial years. These radar systems will enhance the helicopter’s ability to detect, classify, and track multiple maritime targets, boosting operational and surveillance capabilities in maritime environments. Upon successful completion of Phase-1, the programme is expected to move to Phase-2, which involves serial production and supply of AESA radar systems over five years. The indicative value of Phase-2 is Rs 500 crore (Rs 590 crore gross). Centum said the programme represents a major opportunity to demonstrate its system-level design, development, and manufacturing capabilities in advanced radar and mission-critical defence electronics, while strengthening its long-standing partnership with HAL. The company’s consolidated net profit surged 423.6% to Rs 24.19 crore, on a 21.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 324 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. Hindustan Aeronautics is engaged in the business of Manufacture of Aircraft and Helicopters and Repair, Maintenance of Aircraft and Helicopters. The company’s consolidated rose 29.6% to Rs 1,866.68 crore on 10.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7,698.80 crore in Q3FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip fell 1.59% to Rs 3,960 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CentumElectron_78895257939_4488.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benares Hotels appoints Sumit Deol as CEO]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benares-hotels-appoints-sumit-deol-as-ceo/1679323</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679323</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Sumit Singh Deol has pursued Hotel Management from IHM Chennai and joined IHCL in 2010 as a Restaurant Manager in Taj Coromandel, Chennai.

Sumit Singh Deol has pursued Hotel Management from IHM Chennai and joined IHCL in 2010 as a Restaurant Manager in Taj Coromandel, Chennai. He has vast experience in Food & Beverage and General Management. He has successfully led the teams at Taj Taal Kutir and Taj Coromandel, Chennai. He has been awarded various laurels. Benares Hotels (BHL) is a listed public company incorporated in 1971. Its portfolio comprises Taj Ganges and Taj Nadesar Palace, in Varanasi, as well as Ginger Gondia in Maharashtra. Since 2011, BHL has been a subsidiary of Indian Hotels Company (IHCL). The company’s standalone net profit increased 5.7% to Rs 14.33 crore on 7.1% increase in net sales to Rs 41.63 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.02% to Rs 9,501.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BenaresHotels_2930902456_1266.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market snaps two-day winning streak; Nifty settles below 25,450 marks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-snaps-two-day-winning-streak-nifty-settles-below-25450-marks/1679321</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679321</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity indices ended with sharp losses on Tuesday, snapping a two-day winning streak, dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters.

Domestic equity indices ended with sharp losses on Tuesday, snapping a two-day winning streak, dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters. Investor sentiment was dented after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened foreign nations with higher tariffs on goods exported to the United States. Meanwhile, the expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE added to market volatility. Nifty ended below the 25,450 mark. IT, realty and media shares declined, while metal, oil & gas and pharma stocks advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,068.74 points or 1.28% to 82,225.92. The Nifty 50 index fell 288.35 points or 1.12% to 25,424.65. In the past two consecutive trading session, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 0.95% and 1.01%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index slipped 0.40% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.76%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,455 shares rose and 2,766 shares fell. A total of 163 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery received bids for 30,18,496 shares as against 57,06,235 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.53 times. The issue opened for bidding on 24 February 2026 and it will close on 26 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 367 and 386 per share. Shree Ram Twistex received bids for 55,94,976 shares as against 1,06,00,000 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.53 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 95 and 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions received bids for 92,64,052 shares as against 2,18,23,329 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.42 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it will close on 25 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 1,000 and 1,053 per share. Gaudium IVF and Women Health received bids for 10,42,18,947 shares as against 1,46,20,340 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 7.13 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it will close on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 75 and 79 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index slumped 4.74% to 30,053.50. The index tumbled 9.13% in five consecutive trading sessions. LTIMindtree (down 6.88%), Tech Mahindra (down 6.48%), Persistent Systems (down 6.28%), HCL Technologies (down 6.07%), Coforge (down 5.95%), Mphasis (down 3.96%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 3.79%), Infosys (down 3.79%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 3.22%) and Wipro (down 2.84%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Bharti Airtel slipped 2.91%. The telecom major said that it will capitalize its NBFC arm, Airtel Money, with Rs 20,000 crore over the next few years. HUDCO (down 2.11%), Piramal Pharma (down 1.42%), Tata Technologies (down 4.78%) and Torrent Power (down 0.49) to be excluded from F&O The National Stock Exchange (NSE) has decided to exclude Housing & Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO), Piramal Pharma, Tata Technologies, and Torrent Power from the Futures & Options (F&O) segment with effect from 29 April 2026. IDFC First Bank added 1.31%. The company said the recent volatility in its share price followed the detection of a Rs 590-crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch. The bank added that reports regarding government de-empanelment are part of the ordinary course of business. Silver Touch Technologies declined 1.44%. The company announced that it has been selected by the FSSAI for a strategic digital transformation engagement. Shilpa Medicare fell 2.29%. The company said that its subsidiary Shilpa Biologicals and SteinCares have entered into a strategic licensing agreement to commercialize a biosimilar across Latin America. Under the agreement, SteinCares will hold exclusive rights to register, commercialize, and distribute the biosimilar across the region while Shilpa Biologicals will complete product development and provide long-term commercial manufacturing from its facility in Dharwad, India. Brahmaputra Infrastructure hit an upper circuit of 5% after it emerged as the L-1 bidder for a National Highway project awarded by the Ministry of Road Transport & Highways (MoRTH), Government of India. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) fell 3.51%. The company said its Heavy Civil Infrastructure (HCI) and Heavy Engineering (HE) verticals have jointly secured a ‘significant’ order from the Department of Atomic Energy for the LIGO India Observatory in Maharashtra. Samvardhana Motherson International rose 1.11%. The company announced that it has launched a manufacturing facility in Sanand, Gujarat, dedicated to producing cutting-edge exterior lighting systems. The facility has been set up under a strategic joint venture with Marelli, namely Marelli Motherson Automotive Lighting India (MMLI). The joint venture strengthens the group’s capabilities in automotive component manufacturing. MMLI is a 50:50 partnership between Samvardhana Motherson International and Marelli Europe S.p.A. Signpost India rose 0.23%. The company has secured exclusive outdoor advertising rights from the Kolkata Municipal Corporation under the ‘Kolkata Streetscape Renaissance’ project in a Rs 450-crore, 10-year public-private partnership contract. Waaree Energies rallied 3.68% after the company announced that it has received an order to supply 500 MW of solar modules from a renowned domestic solar power developer and independent power producer (IPP). Indoco Remedies advanced 2.58% after it received final approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) for Brivaracetam Oral Solution, 10 mg/mL. Caplin Point Laboratories slipped 1.08%. The company announced that its subsidiary, Caplin Steriles, has received final approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for Sodium Phosphates Injection USP. KEC International added 1.38% after the company announced that it has secured new orders worth Rs 1,002 crore across its Transmission & Distribution (T&D) and Cables & Conductors businesses. Global Markets: European shares declined on Tuesday as investors assessed the new global trading landscape after U.S. President Donald Trump’s latest tariff move. Asian markets ended mixed as investors weighed renewed tariff threats from U.S. President Donald Trump and concerns that artificial intelligence could disrupt software companies. Trump posted on Truth Social Monday that any country that wants to “play games” with the Supreme Court decision “will be met with a much higher tariff.” The comments followed a Supreme Court decision Friday striking down tariffs enacted under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act. In response, Trump said he would impose a 15% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act. Investors in Asia were also assessing China’s loan prime rate (LPR) decision. China’s central bank on Tuesday kept its benchmark lending rates unchanged at 3% for the one-year LPR and 3.5% for the five-year LPR. Overnight on Wall Street, U.S. equities tumbled on Monday as investors grappled with persistent fears around artificial intelligence disruptions to various industries and President Donald Trump’s decision to raise his global tariffs. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 821.91 points, or 1.66%, to close at 48,804.06, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.13% and ended at 22,627.27. The S&P 500 shed 1.04% and closed at 6,837.75, putting it into the red once again for 2026. The 30-stock Dow was dragged down by IBM shares, which declined 13% on the heels of Anthropic outlining new programming capabilities for its Claude Code product. Software stocks such as Microsoft and CrowdStrike were under pressure yet again as AI disruption worries hovered over the market. However, software hasn’t been the only sector to be hit due to AI fears recently: Stocks linked to trucking and logistics, commercial real estate, and financial services have similarly suffered losses this month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cartrade Tech Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/cartrade-tech-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1679312</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679312</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SpiceJet Ltd, Le Travenues Technology Ltd, L&T Technology Services Ltd and Affle 3i Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 February 2026.

SpiceJet Ltd, Le Travenues Technology Ltd, L&T Technology Services Ltd and Affle 3i Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 24 February 2026. Cartrade Tech Ltd crashed 10.03% to Rs 1800 at 14:45 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 24200 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 32887 shares in the past one month. SpiceJet Ltd lost 8.64% to Rs 14.48. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 221.03 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 120.74 lakh shares in the past one month. Le Travenues Technology Ltd tumbled 8.38% to Rs 164.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.83 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.5 lakh shares in the past one month. L&T Technology Services Ltd shed 8.22% to Rs 3155.2. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 11675 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 12715 shares in the past one month. Affle 3i Ltd pared 7.16% to Rs 1401. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 15556 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 34500 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Cartrade--Tech-Ltd_25528484_65036.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold retreats toward $5150 support after four-day rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-retreats-toward-5150-support-after-four-day-rally/1679311</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679311</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices slipped below $5200 per ounce on Tuesday, ending a four-session rally as investors locked in profits after prices touched four-year highs.

Gold prices slipped below $5200 per ounce on Tuesday, ending a four-session rally as investors locked in profits after prices touched four-year highs. A firmer U.S. dollar, up around 0.2%, added pressure by making bullion more expensive for overseas buyers. However, renewed trade uncertainty and rising geopolitical risks helped limit losses, keeping gold supported near lower levels. Fresh U.S. tariff threats and lingering global tensions sustained safe-haven demand. Meanwhile, markets also monitored developments around upcoming U.S.–Iran nuclear talks in Geneva. On the domestic front, MCX April gold futures traded lower by about 0.5% at Rs 160886 per 10 grams, with near-term support seen around Rs 159500–160000 and resistance near Rs 162000 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Alembic Pharma gets USFDA nod for antifungal ANDA]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/alembic-pharma-gets-usfda-nod-for-antifungal-anda/1679309</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679309</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug product (RLD), Jublia Topical Solution, 10%, of Bausch Health Americas, Inc.

The approved ANDA is therapeutically equivalent to the reference listed drug product (RLD), Jublia Topical Solution, 10%, of Bausch Health Americas, Inc. (Bausch). The said drug is indicated for the topical treatment of onychomycosis of the toenail(s) due to Trichophyton rubrum and Trichophyton mentagrophytes. According to IQVIA, Efinaconazole Topical Solution, 10%, has an estimated market size of $500 million for twelve months ending December 2025. The company has a cumulative total of 234 ANDA approvals (215 final approvals and 19 tentative approvals) from USFDA. Alembic Pharmaceuticals, a vertically integrated research and development company, is engaged in the manufacture and marketing of generic pharmaceutical products across global markets. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 3.9% to Rs 132.97 crore despite a 10.8% jump in net sales to Rs 1,876.31 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The counter fell 1.31% to Rs 757 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AlembicPharma_46538273359_40294.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indoco Remedies rises on USFDA approval for Brivaracetam oral solution]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indoco-remedies-rises-on-usfda-approval-for-brivaracetam-oral-solution/1679306</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679306</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The approval allows the company to market a generic version of Briviact 10 mg/mL oral solution, the reference listed drug (RLD) of UCB, Inc.

The approval allows the company to market a generic version of Briviact 10 mg/mL oral solution, the reference listed drug (RLD) of UCB, Inc. The company said its Brivaracetam Oral Solution has been determined to be bioequivalent and therapeutically equivalent to the RLD. The product will be manufactured at Indoco Remedies’ facility located at L-14, Verna Industrial Area, Verna, Goa – 403722, India. Brivaracetam Oral Solution (10 mg/mL) is a prescription antiepileptic drug indicated for the treatment of partial-onset seizures in patients aged one month and older. Aditi Panandikar, managing director (MD) said, “The ANDA approval for Brivaracetam is a significant milestone for us as we continue to strengthen our presence in the Regulated Markets. We are committed to offering innovative and affordable healthcare to patients worldwide.” Indoco Remedies is engaged in the manufacturing and marketing of Formulations and Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients. The Company caters to both Domestic and International markets. The company’s consolidated net loss of Rs 23.64 crore in Q3 FY26 as against net loss of Rs 27.30 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 7.9% year on year to Rs 434.34 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndocoRemedies_30015747980_12579.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AKI India Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aki-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1679305</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679305</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Yatra Online Ltd, Cropster Agro Ltd, EFC (I) Ltd and Shekhawati Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 February 2026.

Yatra Online Ltd, Cropster Agro Ltd, EFC (I) Ltd and Shekhawati Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 24 February 2026. AKI India Ltd crashed 17.05% to Rs 5.01 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 79751 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4724 shares in the past one month. Yatra Online Ltd tumbled 14.32% to Rs 122.65. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.95 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.19 lakh shares in the past one month. Cropster Agro Ltd lost 13.73% to Rs 11.5. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 59614 shares in the past one month. EFC (I) Ltd shed 9.97% to Rs 238.75. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 15.91 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 78569 shares in the past one month. Shekhawati Industries Ltd plummeted 9.85% to Rs 12.35. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 5313 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 16482 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AKIIndiaLtd_33238188821_72485.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade with major losses; auto shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-with-major-losses-auto-shares-decline/1679304</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679304</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with deep cuts in the mid-afternoon trade dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with deep cuts in the mid-afternoon trade dragged down by heavy selling in IT counters. Investor sentiment was dented after Trump has threatened foreign nations that if they side with the US Supreme Court's judgment, they may face higher tariffs on goods imported into the US, while the expiry of monthly F&O contracts on the NSE added to the volatility in the market. Nifty traded below 25,450 mark. Auto shares declined after advancing in the past two consecutive trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 1096.28 points or 1.32% to 82,197.91. The Nifty 50 index tanked 298.58 points or 1.15% to 25,414.65. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index fell 0.81% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index dropped 1.06%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,165 shares rose and 2,940 shares fell. A total of 187 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 2.99% to 14.59. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index fell 0.75% to 27,867.55. The index rose 1.23% in the past two consecutive trading session. Uno Minda (down 1.81%), Eicher Motors (down 1.37%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 1.31%), Bajaj Auto (down 1.17%), Exide Industries (down 1.15%), Mahindra & Mahindra (down 1.01%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 0.86%), Bosch (down 0.79%), Ashok Leyland (down 0.77%) and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 0.71%) declined. On the other hand, Bharat Forge (up 0.44%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 0.33%) and Hero MotoCorp (up 0.21%) edged higher. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper slipped 0.24% to 6.683 compared with the previous session close of 6.699. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9625 compared with its close of 90.8950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement slipped 0.56% to Rs 160,696. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.13% to 97.77. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.35% to 4.040. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 11 cents or 0.15% to $71.60 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Caplin Point Laboratories slipped 1.40%. The company announced that its subsidiary, Caplin Steriles, has received final approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for Sodium Phosphates Injection USP. KEC International added 0.60%. The company announced that it has secured new orders worth Rs 1,002 crore across its Transmission & Distribution (T&D) and Cables & Conductors businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>