<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:28:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[STT sting sends benchmarks into a tailspin, Nifty ends below 24,850]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stt-sting-sends-benchmarks-into-a-tailspin-nifty-ends-below-24850/1670106</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670106</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The benchmark equity indices witnessed a sharp sell-off during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of the Union Budget 2026 by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman.

The benchmark equity indices witnessed a sharp sell-off during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of the Union Budget 2026 by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman. While the speech remained broadly market-friendly at the macro level—maintaining the fiscal deficit glide path at 4.4% in FY26 and 4.3% in FY27, raising capital expenditure to around Rs 12.2 lakh crore, and reiterating a declining debt-to-GDP trajectory—the positives were overshadowed by a key negative for markets. The sharp increase in Securities Transaction Tax on derivatives emerged as the primary trigger for the sell-off. STT on futures was raised from 0.02% to 0.05%, while the levy on options was increased to 0.15%. The move sparked aggressive unwinding in stocks linked to capital market sector, with brokerages, exchanges and other high-beta F&O counters bearing the brunt of the selling during the single special session. Market opened on a mixed note, but failed to sustain early gains as the Budget speech progressed. Indices slipped into negative territory after investors digested the higher transaction costs. The Sensex fell below the 80,750 level, while the Nifty slipped under 24,850, dragged down by selling pressure in PSU banks, metal and energy stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,546 points or 1.88% to 80,722.94. The Nifty 50 index dropped 495.20 points or 1.96% to 24,825.45. Bharat Electronics (down 6.02%), State Bank of India (down 5.31%) and Reliance Industries (down 3.77%) were major Nifty drags today. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.91% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index slipped 1.61%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,759 shares rose and 2,375 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 10.72% to 15.10. Stocks in Spotlight: Shares of data centre and artificial intelligence-linked companies surged after the Union Budget 2026 unveiled long-term tax incentives aimed at attracting global cloud service providers to India. E2E Networks jumped 7.90%, while Anant Raj rose 5.44%. Netweb Technologies India gained 5.10%. Under the budget proposal, any foreign company providing cloud services to customers worldwide using data centre infrastructure located in India will be eligible for a tax holiday extending up to 2047. In addition, the government announced a safe harbour margin of 15% on cost for data centre services provided from India by related entities, offering greater tax certainty for multinational groups. Shares of companies operating in the Indian capital market dropped after Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced an increase in the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on both futures and options. Following the news, broker stocks tumbled, with Billionbrains Garage Ventures (Groww) down 5.11%, Nuvama Wealth Management sliding 7.28% and Angel One falling 8.61%. The only listed stock exchange, BSE was down 8.12%. GAIL (India) fell 2.90% after the company reported 19.5% drop in standalone net profit to Rs 1602.57 crore on a 2.5% fall in gross sales to Rs 34,075.81 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The muted revenue performance was driven primarily by lower realizations and volumes in LPG and liquid hydrocarbons, partially offset by resilient transmission income and higher ‘other’ revenues. Bajaj Auto fell 1.11%. The company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries rose 0.95%. The company has reported 16.03% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,368.81 crore on a 13.49% increase in revenue to Rs 15,520.54 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. VST Tillers Tractors advanced 1.17% after the company reported a 53.89% surge in total sales to 5,257 units in January 2026, up from 3,416 units sold in January 2025. Meesho fell 4.97% after the company's consolidated net loss widened to Rs 490.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 37.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) advanced 0.78% after the company reported a net turnover of Rs 480.03 crore for January 2026, marking a 17.32% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 409.16 crore recorded in January 2025. R R Kabel rose 0.69% after the company reported growth in profit and revenue for the December quarter. On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 72.4% YoY to Rs 118.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 68.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Relaxo Footwears fell 3.60% after the company reported a 19.6% decline in net profit to Rs 26.54 crore, despite a 0.2% rise in net sales to Rs 668.03 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Escorts Kubota added 3.38% after the company's Agri Machinery Business in January 2026 sold 9,799 tractors registering a growth of 46.9% as against 6,669 tractors sold in January 2025. Union Budget 2026: Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman used the Union Budget 2026 to underline a reform-heavy path built around fiscal consolidation, job creation and sharper global competitiveness. The Centre reiterated its medium-term debt sustainability goal, with the FRBM roadmap indicating a steady decline in the debt-to-GDP ratio and projecting central government debt at around 55.6% in BE 2026-27 versus 56.1% in RE 2025-26, framing the glide towards a sub 50% target by 2030 as a policy anchor rather than a hard statutory number. On the deficit side, the government stuck to its consolidation track, with the fiscal gap seen at 4.4% of GDP in RE FY26 and budgeted to narrow to 4.3% in BE FY27, a sequence that keeps the post pandemic promises on course while still giving room for capex-driven growth. On the expenditure and borrowing front, the Budget raised capital expenditure to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore for FY27, signalling another year of heavy public investment in infrastructure, especially in emerging tier 2 and tier 3 growth centres that are starting to look more like mini metros than satellite towns. To fund the gap, the Centre plans net market borrowing of Rs 11.54 lakh crore through dated securities, with the balance coming from small savings and other sources, in line with the glide path indicated in the Budget 2025 26 speech. That combination—slower deficit, still high capex and a calibrated borrowing programme—is meant to keep bond yields contained while nudging the baton from public to private capex over the medium term. Markets, however, zeroed in on the tax tweaks. On the indirect side, the Finance Bill, 2026 sharply increased the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives: STT on futures goes up from 0.02% to 0.05% of the traded value, while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium (and from 0.125% to 0.15% when options are exercised). That makes high-churn F&O strategies more expensive at the margin and nudges some speculative volume off the table, even as it modestly boosts revenue. On the direct tax side, the Income-tax Act, 2025 is slated to take full effect from 1 April 2026, with fresh slab structures, harmonised surcharge rules and a cleaned up TDS/TCS and penalty framework, all aimed at reducing litigation and making the law more “plain English” for taxpayers. The Budget also delivered compliance relief via Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rationalisation under the LRS and travel bucket. TCS on overseas tour packages has been pared down to a flat 2%, replacing the earlier structure that included higher 5–20% slabs and thresholds. Similarly, TCS on remittances under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme for education and medical treatment drops to 2% from 5%, with a higher trigger threshold, easing the cash flow pinch on families sending children abroad or paying for medical procedures. Alongside, the Bill tightens the architecture for revised and updated returns—allowing revised returns up to the end of the assessment year (or 12 months in the new Act), with a modest fee if filed late—while keeping the extended “updated return” window of up to four years, albeit at a steep additional tax to discourage strategic under reporting. For cross border and enforcement issues, the Budget has carved out a targeted Foreign Assets of Small Taxpayers Disclosure Scheme, 2026. The scheme ring fences smaller cases—undisclosed foreign assets and income up to defined ceilings—into a one time, time bound window where taxpayers can come clean by paying 30% tax plus a 100% penalty on that tax on previously untaxed foreign assets or income, or a flat Rs 1 lakh fee in benign cases where foreign assets bought out of already taxed income were not reported in the foreign asset schedule. In return, declarants get immunity from further tax, penalty and prosecution under the Black Money Act on the declared items. The exact opening and closing dates will be notified separately, but the policy signal is clear: clean up small legacy foreign asset issues before the information exchange net tightens further. On the business tax side, several structural tweaks stand out. First, supply of manpower is now explicitly included in the statutory definition of “work” for TDS purposes, putting manpower contracts clearly under the contractor TDS net at the familiar 1%-2% slabs depending on the payer’s status. Second, the Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) regime has been recalibrated. To encourage companies to shift to the new regime, set-off of brought forward MAT credit to be allowed to companies only in the new regime. Set-off using available MAT credit to be allowed to an extent of 1/4th of the tax liability in the new regime. MAT is proposed to be made final tax. There will be no further credit accumulation from 1st April 2026. The rate of final tax to be reduced to 14% from the current MAT rate of 15%. The brought forward MAT credit of taxpayers accumulated till 31st March 2026, will continue to be available to them for set-off as above. For non-resident and digital economy players, the government has doubled down on India as a data and cloud hub. Any foreign company that provides cloud services to customers globally by using data centre services from India to be provided Tax holiday till 2047. A safe harbour of 15% on cost to be provided if the company providing data centre services from India is a related entity. A safe harbour to non-residents for component warehousing in a bonded warehouse at a profit margin of 2% of the invoice value. The resultant tax of about 0.7 percent will be much lower than in competing jurisdictions. Exemption from income tax for 5 years to be provided to any non-resident who provides capital goods, equipment or tooling, to any toll manufacturer in a bonded zone. Exemption to global (non-India sourced) income of a non-resident expert, for a stay period of 5 years under notified schemes. Exemption from Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) to all non-residents who pay tax on presumptive basis. The Budget also rationalises a few smaller but high friction levies. On the collection side, TCS rate for sellers of specific goods namely alcoholic liquor, scrap and minerals will be rationalized to 2% and that on tendu leaves will be reduced from 5% to 2%. On capital markets, the long criticised buyback tax is being redesigned. Buyback for all types of shareholders to be taxed as capital gains. Promoters to pay an additional buyback tax, making effective tax 22% for corporate promoters and 30% for non-corporate promoters. Beyond taxes, the Budget leans hard into manufacturing, logistics and services as growth engines. Customs schedules have been overhauled to remove rate clutter, cut or eliminate basic customs duty on a basket of critical minerals and components for electronics, clean tech, batteries, telecom and shipping, and amend rates for shipbuilding, airports and select agri linked products, all with an eye on domestic value addition and supply chain resilience. Infrastructure plans—from PPP pipelines, a new asset monetisation plan and multimodal connectivity under PM Gati Shakti to continued support for Jal Jeevan, urban challenge funds and maritime corridors—are meant to keep the public investment cycle humming even as the deficit comes down. On the services and social side, the government has layered in measures such as a fresh Rs 10,000 crore fund of funds for startups, expanded skilling and research allocations, and sector specific pushes in tourism, medical tourism and urban livelihoods, framing the entire package as an attempt to deliver both hard infrastructure growth and more inclusive, employment rich development. Global Markets: On Friday, U.S stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at discount]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-discount/1670105</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670105</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 24,791.80 a discount of 33.65 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 24,825.45 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 24,791.80 a discount of 33.65 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 24,825.45 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index tumbled 495.20 points or 1.96% to 24,825.45. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 10.72% to 15.10. Bharat Electronics (BEL), Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and HDFC Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty ends below 24,850 mark; IT shares climb ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-ends-below-24850-mark-it-shares-climb/1670104</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670104</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices witnessed bloodbath during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of Union budget 2026 by Finance Minster Niramal Sitharaman, her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to do so.

The key equity indices witnessed bloodbath during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of Union budget 2026 by Finance Minster Niramal Sitharaman, her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to do so. The speech stayed largely market-friendly on the big picture – sticking to a fiscal deficit glide path of 4.4% in FY26 and 4.3% in FY27, lifting capex to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore, and reiterating a declining debt-to-GDP trajectory – which ordinarily would have reassured investors. But the sharp hike in Securities Transaction Tax on futures and options trades, with STT on futures lifted from 0.02% to 0.05% and on options to 0.15%, landed as a direct hit on the most active part of the market, triggering aggressive unwinding in brokerages, exchanges and high beta stocks tied to F&O volumes. F&O heavy counters bore the brunt during the single special session. Markets opened on a mixed note, but as the Budget speech progressed, indices failed to sustain early gains and slipped into negative territory after investors reacted to the unfavourable tax announcement. The Sensex fell below the 80,750 mark, while the Nifty slipped below 24,850. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,546 points or 1.88% to 80,722.94. The Nifty 50 index dropped 495.20 points or 1.96% to 24,825.45. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.91% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index slipped 1.61%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 10.72% to 15.10. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty IT index (up 0.57%), the Nifty Media index (down 1.80%) and the Nifty Private Bank index (down 1.22%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty PSU Bank index (down 5.57%), the Nifty Metal index (down 4.05%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 2.86%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Union Budget 2026 Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman used the Union Budget 2026 to underline a reform-heavy path built around fiscal consolidation, job creation and sharper global competitiveness. The Centre reiterated its medium-term debt sustainability goal, with the FRBM roadmap indicating a steady decline in the debt-to-GDP ratio and projecting central government debt at around 55.6% in BE 2026-27 versus 56.1% in RE 2025-26, framing the glide towards a sub 50% target by 2030 as a policy anchor rather than a hard statutory number. On the deficit side, the government stuck to its consolidation track, with the fiscal gap seen at 4.4% of GDP in RE FY26 and budgeted to narrow to 4.3% in BE FY27, a sequence that keeps the post pandemic promises on course while still giving room for capex-driven growth. On the expenditure and borrowing front, the Budget raised capital expenditure to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore for FY27, signalling another year of heavy public investment in infrastructure, especially in emerging tier 2 and tier 3 growth centres that are starting to look more like mini metros than satellite towns. To fund the gap, the Centre plans net market borrowing of Rs 11.54 lakh crore through dated securities, with the balance coming from small savings and other sources, in line with the glide path indicated in the Budget 2025 26 speech. That combination—slower deficit, still high capex and a calibrated borrowing programme—is meant to keep bond yields contained while nudging the baton from public to private capex over the medium term. Markets, however, zeroed in on the tax tweaks. On the indirect side, the Finance Bill, 2026 sharply increased the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives: STT on futures goes up from 0.02% to 0.05% of the traded value, while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium (and from 0.125% to 0.15% when options are exercised). That makes high-churn F&O strategies more expensive at the margin and nudges some speculative volume off the table, even as it modestly boosts revenue. On the direct tax side, the Income-tax Act, 2025 is slated to take full effect from 1 April 2026, with fresh slab structures, harmonised surcharge rules and a cleaned up TDS/TCS and penalty framework, all aimed at reducing litigation and making the law more “plain English” for taxpayers. The Budget also delivered compliance relief via Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rationalisation under the LRS and travel bucket. TCS on overseas tour packages has been pared down to a flat 2%, replacing the earlier structure that included higher 5–20% slabs and thresholds. Similarly, TCS on remittances under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme for education and medical treatment drops to 2% from 5%, with a higher trigger threshold, easing the cash flow pinch on families sending children abroad or paying for medical procedures. Alongside, the Bill tightens the architecture for revised and updated returns—allowing revised returns up to the end of the assessment year (or 12 months in the new Act), with a modest fee if filed late—while keeping the extended “updated return” window of up to four years, albeit at a steep additional tax to discourage strategic under reporting. For cross border and enforcement issues, the Budget has carved out a targeted Foreign Assets of Small Taxpayers Disclosure Scheme, 2026. The scheme ring fences smaller cases—undisclosed foreign assets and income up to defined ceilings—into a one time, time bound window where taxpayers can come clean by paying 30% tax plus a 100% penalty on that tax on previously untaxed foreign assets or income, or a flat Rs 1 lakh fee in benign cases where foreign assets bought out of already taxed income were not reported in the foreign asset schedule. In return, declarants get immunity from further tax, penalty and prosecution under the Black Money Act on the declared items. The exact opening and closing dates will be notified separately, but the policy signal is clear: clean up small legacy foreign asset issues before the information exchange net tightens further. On the business tax side, several structural tweaks stand out. First, supply of manpower is now explicitly included in the statutory definition of “work” for TDS purposes, putting manpower contracts clearly under the contractor TDS net at the familiar 1%–2% slabs depending on the payer’s status. Second, the Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) regime has been recalibrated: the MAT rate in the old corporate tax regime is trimmed to 14% and treated as a final tax, while companies moving into the new lower rate regime are allowed to use their legacy MAT credits under the old law, but with a tight 25% cap on the amount of MAT credit that can be set off against normal tax in any one year and a 15 year sunset for utilisation. That balances taxpayer expectations on MAT credit with the government’s desire to avoid MAT shielded “zero tax” years under the new regime. For non-resident and digital economy players, the government has doubled down on India as a data and cloud hub. Through amendments to the exemption schedules, qualifying foreign companies that deliver global cloud or data centre services by procuring capacity from “specified” Indian data centres—which themselves must be owned and operated by Indian companies, notified by the Centre and meet detailed conditions—can enjoy a long duration tax exemption on such income, available up to the tax year ending 31 March 2047. The idea is to attract global cloud majors to build onshore stacks on top of Indian owned infrastructure, without triggering immediate tax friction on the foreign service entity’s income sourced from those data centre services. The Budget also rationalises a few smaller but high friction levies. On the collection side, TCS rates on scrap and alcoholic liquor for human consumption are unified at 2%, down from higher earlier rates, giving a modest relief to cash flow sensitive sectors like metals trade and liquor distribution while keeping traceability intact. On capital markets, the long criticised buyback tax is being redesigned: rather than a blunt corporate level levy, the Bill proposes an additional capital gains tax on promoter level gains arising from buybacks, at differentiated rates for domestic and foreign promoters, while non promoter shareholders simply pay normal capital gains tax. That structure softens the blow for retail holders and aligns with the policy goal of penalising aggressive promoter buyback engineering more than ordinary investors. Beyond taxes, the Budget leans hard into manufacturing, logistics and services as growth engines. Customs schedules have been overhauled to remove rate clutter, cut or eliminate basic customs duty on a basket of critical minerals and components for electronics, clean tech, batteries, telecom and shipping, and amend rates for shipbuilding, airports and select agri linked products, all with an eye on domestic value addition and supply chain resilience. Infrastructure plans—from PPP pipelines, a new asset monetisation plan and multimodal connectivity under PM Gati Shakti to continued support for Jal Jeevan, urban challenge funds and maritime corridors—are meant to keep the public investment cycle humming even as the deficit comes down. On the services and social side, the government has layered in measures such as a fresh Rs 10,000 crore fund of funds for startups, expanded skilling and research allocations, and sector specific pushes in tourism, medical tourism and urban livelihoods, framing the entire package as an attempt to deliver both hard infrastructure growth and more inclusive, employment rich development. Numbers to Track: MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.02% to Rs 1,43,632, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement plunged 9% to Rs 2,65,652. Global Markets: On Friday, U.S stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashok Leyland’s January 2026 sales jump 27% YoY to 21,920 units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashok-leylands-january-2026-sales-jump-27-yoy-to-21920-units/1670100</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670100</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s total domestic sales rose 31% year-on-year to 20,079 units in January 2026.

The company’s total domestic sales rose 31% year-on-year to 20,079 units in January 2026. Domestic sales of medium and heavy commercial vehicles (M&HCV) increased 30% to 12,833 units, while light commercial vehicle (LCV) sales grew 33% to 7,246 units in January 2026 compared to the same month last year. Ashok Leyland is involved in the manufacture and sale of a broad range of commercial vehicles and also makes engines for industrial and marine applications, as well as forgings and castings. The company reported a marginal rise in standalone net profit to Rs 771.06 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 770.10 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 9.34% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 9,588.18 crore for the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of Ashok Leyland fell 3.84% to close at Rs 189.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokLeyland_6904859924_31.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Eicher Motors CV sales climb 25% YoY in January 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eicher-motors-cv-sales-climb-25-yoy-in-january-2026/1670099</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670099</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic sales increased by 23.6% to 9,729 units and total exports surged 55.8% to 701 units in January 2026 over January 2025.

Domestic sales increased by 23.6% to 9,729 units and total exports surged 55.8% to 701 units in January 2026 over January 2025. Further, the company’s monthly motorcycle sales in January 2026 stood at 1,04,322 units, which is higher by 14% compared with 91,132 units in the same month a year ago. Sales of motorcycle models with engine capacity up to 350 cc jumped 18% to 92,998 units, while sales of motorcycle models with engine capacity exceeding 350 cc declined 8% to 11,324 units in January 2026 over January 2025. The international business posted sales of 10,541 units in January 2026, registering a 5% rise compared with 10,080 units sold in the same period last year. Eicher Motors is the listed parent of Royal Enfield, the global leader in middleweight motorcycles. In addition to motorcycles, Eicher has a joint venture with Sweden's AB Volvo—Volvo Eicher Commercial Vehicles, which operates in India's commercial vehicle space. The company reported a 24.45% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,369.45 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 1,100.33 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Total revenue from operations surged 44.76% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,171.59 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Shares of Eicher Motors slipped 3.30% to Rs 6,887.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/EicherMotors_60312767308_151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty plunge amid STT hike in Budget 2026;  PSU Bank shares skid ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-plunge-amid-stt-hike-in-budget-2026-psu-bank-shares-skid/1670098</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670098</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices witnessed bloodbath during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of Union budget 2026 by Finance Minster Niramal Sitharaman, her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to do so.

The key equity indices witnessed bloodbath during the special trading session on Sunday following the presentation of Union budget 2026 by Finance Minster Niramal Sitharaman, her ninth consecutive Union Budget in the Lok Sabha, becoming the first finance minister in India to do so. The speech stayed largely market-friendly on the big picture – sticking to a fiscal deficit glide path of 4.4% in FY26 and 4.3% in FY27, lifting capex to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore, and reiterating a declining debt-to-GDP trajectory – which ordinarily would have reassured investors. But the sharp hike in Securities Transaction Tax on futures and options trades, with STT on futures lifted from 0.02% to 0.05% and on options to 0.15%, landed as a direct hit on the most active part of the market, triggering aggressive unwinding in brokerages, exchanges and high beta stocks tied to F&O volumes. F&O heavy counters bore the brunt during the single special session. Markets opened on a mixed note, but as the Budget speech progressed, indices failed to sustain early gains and slipped into negative territory after investors reacted to the unfavourable tax announcement. The Sensex fell below the 80,750 mark, while the Nifty slipped below 24,850. Barring IT index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE ended in red led by PSU Bank, metal and oil & gas stocks. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,546 points or 1.88% to 80,722.94. The Nifty 50 index dropped 495.20 points or 1.96% to 24,825.45. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.91% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index slipped 1.61%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,760 shares rose and 2,374 shares fell. A total of 182 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 10.72% to 15.10. MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.18% to Rs 1,43,400, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement plunged 8.91% to Rs 265,900. Union Budget 2026 Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman used the Union Budget 2026 to underline a reform-heavy path built around fiscal consolidation, job creation and sharper global competitiveness. The Centre reiterated its medium-term debt sustainability goal, with the FRBM roadmap indicating a steady decline in the debt-to-GDP ratio and projecting central government debt at around 55.6% in BE 2026-27 versus 56.1% in RE 2025-26, framing the glide towards a sub 50% target by 2030 as a policy anchor rather than a hard statutory number. On the deficit side, the government stuck to its consolidation track, with the fiscal gap seen at 4.4% of GDP in RE FY26 and budgeted to narrow to 4.3% in BE FY27, a sequence that keeps the post pandemic promises on course while still giving room for capex-driven growth. On the expenditure and borrowing front, the Budget raised capital expenditure to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore for FY27, signalling another year of heavy public investment in infrastructure, especially in emerging tier 2 and tier 3 growth centres that are starting to look more like mini metros than satellite towns. To fund the gap, the Centre plans net market borrowing of Rs 11.54 lakh crore through dated securities, with the balance coming from small savings and other sources, in line with the glide path indicated in the Budget 2025 26 speech. That combination—slower deficit, still high capex and a calibrated borrowing programme—is meant to keep bond yields contained while nudging the baton from public to private capex over the medium term. Markets, however, zeroed in on the tax tweaks. On the indirect side, the Finance Bill, 2026 sharply increased the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives: STT on futures goes up from 0.02% to 0.05% of the traded value, while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium (and from 0.125% to 0.15% when options are exercised). That makes high-churn F&O strategies more expensive at the margin and nudges some speculative volume off the table, even as it modestly boosts revenue. On the direct tax side, the Income-tax Act, 2025 is slated to take full effect from 1 April 2026, with fresh slab structures, harmonised surcharge rules and a cleaned up TDS/TCS and penalty framework, all aimed at reducing litigation and making the law more “plain English” for taxpayers. The Budget also delivered compliance relief via Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rationalisation under the LRS and travel bucket. TCS on overseas tour packages has been pared down to a flat 2%, replacing the earlier structure that included higher 5–20% slabs and thresholds. Similarly, TCS on remittances under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme for education and medical treatment drops to 2% from 5%, with a higher trigger threshold, easing the cash flow pinch on families sending children abroad or paying for medical procedures. Alongside, the Bill tightens the architecture for revised and updated returns—allowing revised returns up to the end of the assessment year (or 12 months in the new Act), with a modest fee if filed late—while keeping the extended “updated return” window of up to four years, albeit at a steep additional tax to discourage strategic under reporting. For cross border and enforcement issues, the Budget has carved out a targeted Foreign Assets of Small Taxpayers Disclosure Scheme, 2026. The scheme ring fences smaller cases—undisclosed foreign assets and income up to defined ceilings—into a one time, time bound window where taxpayers can come clean by paying 30% tax plus a 100% penalty on that tax on previously untaxed foreign assets or income, or a flat Rs 1 lakh fee in benign cases where foreign assets bought out of already taxed income were not reported in the foreign asset schedule. In return, declarants get immunity from further tax, penalty and prosecution under the Black Money Act on the declared items. The exact opening and closing dates will be notified separately, but the policy signal is clear: clean up small legacy foreign asset issues before the information exchange net tightens further. On the business tax side, several structural tweaks stand out. First, supply of manpower is now explicitly included in the statutory definition of “work” for TDS purposes, putting manpower contracts clearly under the contractor TDS net at the familiar 1%–2% slabs depending on the payer’s status. Second, the Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) regime has been recalibrated: the MAT rate in the old corporate tax regime is trimmed to 14% and treated as a final tax, while companies moving into the new lower rate regime are allowed to use their legacy MAT credits under the old law, but with a tight 25% cap on the amount of MAT credit that can be set off against normal tax in any one year and a 15 year sunset for utilisation. That balances taxpayer expectations on MAT credit with the government’s desire to avoid MAT shielded “zero tax” years under the new regime. For non-resident and digital economy players, the government has doubled down on India as a data and cloud hub. Through amendments to the exemption schedules, qualifying foreign companies that deliver global cloud or data centre services by procuring capacity from “specified” Indian data centres—which themselves must be owned and operated by Indian companies, notified by the Centre and meet detailed conditions—can enjoy a long duration tax exemption on such income, available up to the tax year ending 31 March 2047. The idea is to attract global cloud majors to build onshore stacks on top of Indian owned infrastructure, without triggering immediate tax friction on the foreign service entity’s income sourced from those data centre services. The Budget also rationalises a few smaller but high friction levies. On the collection side, TCS rates on scrap and alcoholic liquor for human consumption are unified at 2%, down from higher earlier rates, giving a modest relief to cash flow sensitive sectors like metals trade and liquor distribution while keeping traceability intact. On capital markets, the long criticised buyback tax is being redesigned: rather than a blunt corporate level levy, the Bill proposes an additional capital gains tax on promoter level gains arising from buybacks, at differentiated rates for domestic and foreign promoters, while non promoter shareholders simply pay normal capital gains tax. That structure softens the blow for retail holders and aligns with the policy goal of penalising aggressive promoter buyback engineering more than ordinary investors. Beyond taxes, the Budget leans hard into manufacturing, logistics and services as growth engines. Customs schedules have been overhauled to remove rate clutter, cut or eliminate basic customs duty on a basket of critical minerals and components for electronics, clean tech, batteries, telecom and shipping, and amend rates for shipbuilding, airports and select agri linked products, all with an eye on domestic value addition and supply chain resilience. Infrastructure plans—from PPP pipelines, a new asset monetisation plan and multimodal connectivity under PM Gati Shakti to continued support for Jal Jeevan, urban challenge funds and maritime corridors—are meant to keep the public investment cycle humming even as the deficit comes down. On the services and social side, the government has layered in measures such as a fresh Rs 10,000 crore fund of funds for startups, expanded skilling and research allocations, and sector specific pushes in tourism, medical tourism and urban livelihoods, framing the entire package as an attempt to deliver both hard infrastructure growth and more inclusive, employment rich development. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank Index tumbled 5.57% to 8,517.20. The index rose 0.06% in the past trading session. Bank of India (down 8.32%), Indian Bank (down 7.52%), Bank of Maharashtra (down 7.42%), Bank of Baroda (down 6.58%), Union Bank of India (down 6.3%), State Bank of India (down 5.47%), Canara Bank (down 4.32%), Indian Overseas Bank (down 3.59%), Central Bank of India (down 3.07%) and Punjab National Bank (down 2.88%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Auto fell 1.11%. The company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries rose 0.95%. The company has reported 16.03% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,368.81 crore on a 13.49% increase in revenue to Rs 15,520.54 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. VST Tillers Tractors advanced 1.17% after the company reported a 53.89% surge in total sales to 5,257 units in January 2026, up from 3,416 units sold in January 2025. Meesho fell 4.97% after the company's consolidated net loss widened to Rs 490.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 37.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) advanced 0.78% after the company reported a net turnover of Rs 480.03 crore for January 2026, marking a 17.32% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 409.16 crore recorded in January 2025. R R Kabel rose 0.69% after the company reported growth in profit and revenue for the December quarter. On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 72.4% YoY to Rs 118.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 68.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Relaxo Footwears fell 3.60% after the company reported a 19.6% decline in net profit to Rs 26.54 crore, despite a 0.2% rise in net sales to Rs 668.03 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Escorts Kubota added 3.38% after the company’s Agri Machinery Business in January 2026 sold 9,799 tractors registering a growth of 46.9% as against 6,669 tractors sold in January 2025. Global Markets: On Friday, U.S stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty PSU Bank Index declines 5.57%, NIFTY Tumbles 1.96% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-psu-bank-index-declines-557-nifty-tumbles-196/1670097</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670097</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty PSU Bank index ended down 5.57% at 8517.2 today.

Nifty PSU Bank index ended down 5.57% at 8517.2 today. The index is down 0.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Bank of India shed 8.32%, Indian Bank dropped 7.52% and Bank of Maharashtra fell 7.42%. The Nifty PSU Bank index is up 37.00% over last one year compared to the 6.78% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Metal index is down 4.05% and Nifty Commodities index has slid 3.31% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has slid 1.96% to close at 24825.45 while the SENSEX has dropped 1.88% to close at 80722.94 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gail (India) slips after weak Q3 numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gail-india-slips-after-weak-q3-numbers/1670094</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670094</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The muted revenue performance was driven primarily by lower realizations and volumes in LPG and liquid hydrocarbons, partially offset by resilient transmission income and higher ‘other’ revenues.

The muted revenue performance was driven primarily by lower realizations and volumes in LPG and liquid hydrocarbons, partially offset by resilient transmission income and higher ‘other’ revenues. Within the revenue mix, natural gas transmission revenue rose 0.5% YoY to Rs 2,476 crore, supported by largely stable pipeline throughput. In contrast, LPG transmission revenue declined 4.9% YoY to Rs 232 crore. Gas marketing revenue fell 1.3% YoY to Rs 27,924 crore, reflecting pressure on trading margins despite steady sales volumes. Petrochemicals revenue moderated 2.3% YoY to Rs 2,007 crore, while LPG and other liquid hydrocarbon revenues declined sharply by 39.6% YoY to Rs 850 crore, tracking lower volumes and realizations. The ‘others’ segment revenue for Q3 FY26 was Rs 541 crore, up 19.2% YoY. Excise duty charges rose 17.5% YoY to Rs 24.33 crore in the third quarter. Total operating expenditure for the period review was Rs 31,396.26 crore, down 2.2% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 2,030 crore, down by 59.6% from Rs 5,028.75 crore in Q3 FY25. GAIL (lndia) is the largest state-owned natural gas processing and distribution company in the country. It has a diversified business portfolio and has interests in the sourcing and trading of natural gas, production of LPG, liquid hydrocarbons and petrochemicals, transmission of natural gas and LPG through pipelines, etc.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GAILIndia_44377574438_12350.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Data centre, AI stocks rally after Budget offers tax sops for cloud services]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/data-centre-ai-stocks-rally-after-budget-offers-tax-sops-for-cloud-services/1670089</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670089</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[E2E Networks jumped 8.56%, while Anant Raj rose 6.57%.

E2E Networks jumped 8.56%, while Anant Raj rose 6.57%. Netweb Technologies India gained 5.27%, reflecting strong investor optimism around India's data centre and AI infrastructure theme. The rally followed Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's announcement of a major tax initiative to position India as a global hub for cloud services. Under the proposal, any foreign company providing cloud services to customers worldwide using data centre infrastructure located in India will be eligible for a tax holiday extending up to 2047. In addition, the government announced a safe harbour margin of 15% on cost for data centre services provided from India by related entities, offering greater tax certainty for multinational groups.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/E2ENetworksLtd_43382383477_72373.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Motor total monthly sales climb 29% YoY in January'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-motor-total-monthly-sales-climb-29-yoy-in-january26/1670092</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670092</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Two-wheeler sales surged 28% year-on-year in January 2026, rising to 494,195 units from 387,671 units in January 2025.

Two-wheeler sales surged 28% year-on-year in January 2026, rising to 494,195 units from 387,671 units in January 2025. Domestic two-wheeler sales grew 30%, increasing from 293,860 units in January 2025 to 383,262 units in January 2026. Motorcycle sales grew 26%, rising from 174,388 units in January 2025 to 219,188 units in January 2026. Scooter sales increased 30%, from 171,111 units in January 2025 to 222,926 units in January 2026. Electric vehicle (EV) sales rose 50%, increasing from 25,195 units in January 2025 to 37,756 units in January 2026. Three-wheeler sales surged 77%, rising from 9,952 units in January 2025 to 17,571 units in January 2026. The company’s total exports grew 21%, increasing from 101,055 units in January 2025 to 122,343 units in January 2026. Two-wheeler exports rose 18%, from 93,811 units in January 2025 to 110,933 units in January 2026. TVS Motor Company is a reputed global manufacturer of two-wheelers and three-wheelers, with four manufacturing facilities located in India and Indonesia. The company reported a 36.74% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 906.09 crore, on a 29.01% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 11,905.43 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. The stock slipped 2.47% to Rs 3,592.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSMotorCo_68147319859_8029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/multi-commodity-exchange-of-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1670082</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670082</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd, Hindustan Zinc Ltd, Bharat Dynamics Ltd and Muthoot Finance Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 01 February 2026.

Hindustan Copper Ltd, Hindustan Zinc Ltd, Bharat Dynamics Ltd and Muthoot Finance Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 01 February 2026. Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd lost 11.68% to Rs 2230 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 11.87 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.84 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Copper Ltd crashed 11.62% to Rs 606.75. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 95.94 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 55.73 lakh shares in the past one month. Hindustan Zinc Ltd tumbled 9.33% to Rs 570.15. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 36.16 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 15.24 lakh shares in the past one month. Bharat Dynamics Ltd corrected 8.49% to Rs 1407.05. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.78 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.05 lakh shares in the past one month. Muthoot Finance Ltd shed 7.92% to Rs 3524.55. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 52721 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 20071 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MultiCommExc_54258329132_25746.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Budget will give India’s Reform Express new energy and new momentum: PM]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/budget-will-give-indias-reform-express-new-energy-and-new-momentum-pm/1670076</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670076</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi today hailed the Budget 2026-2027 and described it as historic.

Prime Minister Narendra Modi today hailed the Budget 2026-2027 and described it as historic. Modi said, this budget is the foundation for country’s journey towards a Viksit Bharat by 2047. He said, the budget reflects the aspirations of 140 crore Indians and strengthens the reform journey and charts a clear roadmap for Viksit Bharat. He said, this year’s budget will give India’s Reform Express new energy and new momentum.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/budget-planning-and-allocating-money-concept-picture-id5081_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tokyo Plast International Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tokyo-plast-international-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1670075</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670075</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Eco Recycling Ltd, TransIndia Real Estate Ltd, B&B Triplewall Containers Ltd and Incredible Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 February 2026.

Eco Recycling Ltd, TransIndia Real Estate Ltd, B&B Triplewall Containers Ltd and Incredible Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 01 February 2026. Tokyo Plast International Ltd crashed 15.89% to Rs 100.05 at 14:22 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 1403 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 131 shares in the past one month. Eco Recycling Ltd tumbled 11.42% to Rs 391.4. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1.6 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 34264 shares in the past one month. TransIndia Real Estate Ltd lost 10.25% to Rs 24.52. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 13090 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5768 shares in the past one month. B&B Triplewall Containers Ltd shed 9.05% to Rs 181. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 0 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 382 shares in the past one month. Incredible Industries Ltd slipped 8.72% to Rs 37.14. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 124 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2001 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TokyoPlastInternationalLtd_60698755021_4159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices  trade in negative terrain; realty shares snap 4-day gains ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-in-negative-terrain-realty-shares-snap-4-day-gains/1670073</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670073</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in mid-afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium.

The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in mid-afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium. The move directly hit the most active part of the market, triggering aggressive unwinding in brokerages, exchanges and high beta stocks linked to F&O volumes. Nifty dropped below 25,100 level. Realty shares declined after rallying the past four trading sessions. At 14:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 814.83 points or 0.93% to 81,501.15. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 261.15 points or 1.03% to 25,059.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.27% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index slipped 1.11%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,820 shares rose and 2,234 shares fell. A total of 190 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 5.96% to 14.45. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 1.62% to 770.30. The index jumped 3.52% in the past four trading session. Godrej Properties (down 2.98%), DLF (down 2.89%), Sobha (down 2.64%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 2.2%) and Lodha Developers (down 1.91%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.69%), Phoenix Mills (down 1.09%), SignatureGlobal India (down 0.75%), Brigade Enterprises (down 0.26%) declined. Numbers to Track : MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.58% to Rs 1,44,400, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement declined 8.67% to Rs 2,66,623.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Anant Raj Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-anant-raj-ltd-counter/1670068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670068</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Intellect Design Arena Ltd, Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd, Angel One Ltd, BSE Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 01 February 2026.

Intellect Design Arena Ltd, Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd, Angel One Ltd, BSE Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 01 February 2026. Anant Raj Ltd witnessed volume of 208.91 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.91 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 26.40 lakh shares. The stock increased 8.70% to Rs.548.15. Volumes stood at 31.61 lakh shares in the last session. Intellect Design Arena Ltd notched up volume of 12.75 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.99 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.13 lakh shares. The stock slipped 3.22% to Rs.884.30. Volumes stood at 2.73 lakh shares in the last session. Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd witnessed volume of 8.75 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.32 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.64 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.34% to Rs.1,007.00. Volumes stood at 2.39 lakh shares in the last session. Angel One Ltd saw volume of 35.94 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.29 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.79 lakh shares. The stock dropped 8.46% to Rs.2,326.00. Volumes stood at 4.87 lakh shares in the last session. BSE Ltd recorded volume of 141.16 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 4.03 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 35.06 lakh shares. The stock lost 8.00% to Rs.2,573.30. Volumes stood at 38.06 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AnantRaj_28642833798_1538.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty trade lower; broader mrkt underperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-lower-broader-mrkt-underperforms/1670064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670064</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium.

The key equity indices traded with sharp losses in afternoon trade as investor sentiment weakened after the government announced an increase in the securities transaction tax (STT) on futures contracts to 0.05% while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium. Nifty skid below 25,050 mark after hitting day’s high of 25,440 in mid-morning trade. PSU Bank, oil & gas and realty shares declined while IT and consumer durables shares advanced At 13:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 542.62 points or 0.66% to 81,727.16. The Nifty 50 index tumbled 274.20 points or 0.79% to 25,087.30. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 Mid-Cap index declined 1.03% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index slipped 0.93%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,711 shares rose and 2,215 shares fell. A total of 217 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, rallied 5.02% to 14.32. MCX Gold futures for the 5 February 2026 settlement fell 4.58% to Rs 1,42,800, while MCX Silver futures for the 5 March 2026 settlement declined 8.79% to Rs 2,66,269. Gainers & Losers: Titan Company (up 3.45%), Wipro (up 3.14%), Max Healthcare Institute (up 2.74%), Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) (up 2.53%) and Sun Pharmaceutical Industries (up 1.22%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Hindalco Industries (down 4.70%), Coal India (down 3.99%), State Bank of India (down 3.98%), Bharat Electronics (BEL) (down 3.90%) and Oil & Natural Gas Corporations of India (ONGC) (down 3.62%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries rose 1.22% after it has reported 16.03% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,368.81 crore on a 13.49% increase in revenue to Rs 15,520.54 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Union Budget 2026 Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman used the Union Budget 2026 to underline a reform-heavy path built around fiscal consolidation, job creation and sharper global competitiveness. The Centre reiterated its medium-term debt sustainability goal, with the FRBM roadmap indicating a steady decline in the debt-to-GDP ratio and projecting central government debt at around 55.6% in BE 2026 27 versus 56.1% in RE 2025 26, framing the glide towards a sub 50% target by 2030 as a policy anchor rather than a hard statutory number. On the deficit side, the government stuck to its consolidation track, with the fiscal gap seen at 4.4% of GDP in RE FY26 and budgeted to narrow to 4.3% in BE FY27, a sequence that keeps the post pandemic promises on course while still giving room for capex-driven growth. On the expenditure and borrowing front, the Budget raised capital expenditure to about Rs 12.2 lakh crore for FY27, signalling another year of heavy public investment in infrastructure, especially in emerging tier 2 and tier 3 growth centres that are starting to look more like mini metros than satellite towns. To fund the gap, the Centre plans net market borrowing of Rs 11.54 lakh crore through dated securities, with the balance coming from small savings and other sources, in line with the glide path indicated in the Budget 2025 26 speech. That combination—slower deficit, still high capex and a calibrated borrowing programme—is meant to keep bond yields contained while nudging the baton from public to private capex over the medium term. Markets, however, zeroed in on the tax tweaks. On the indirect side, the Finance Bill, 2026 sharply increased the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives: STT on futures goes up from 0.02% to 0.05% of the traded value, while STT on options rises from 0.10% to 0.15% of the premium (and from 0.125% to 0.15% when options are exercised). That makes high-churn F&O strategies more expensive at the margin and nudges some speculative volume off the table, even as it modestly boosts revenue. On the direct tax side, the Income-tax Act, 2025 is slated to take full effect from 1 April 2026, with fresh slab structures, harmonised surcharge rules and a cleaned up TDS/TCS and penalty framework, all aimed at reducing litigation and making the law more “plain English” for taxpayers. The Budget also delivered compliance relief via Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rationalisation under the LRS and travel bucket. TCS on overseas tour packages has been pared down to a flat 2%, replacing the earlier structure that included higher 5–20% slabs and thresholds. Similarly, TCS on remittances under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme for education and medical treatment drops to 2% from 5%, with a higher trigger threshold, easing the cash flow pinch on families sending children abroad or paying for medical procedures. Alongside, the Bill tightens the architecture for revised and updated returns—allowing revised returns up to the end of the assessment year (or 12 months in the new Act), with a modest fee if filed late—while keeping the extended “updated return” window of up to four years, albeit at a steep additional tax to discourage strategic under reporting. For cross border and enforcement issues, the Budget has carved out a targeted Foreign Assets of Small Taxpayers Disclosure Scheme, 2026. The scheme ring fences smaller cases—undisclosed foreign assets and income up to defined ceilings—into a one time, time bound window where taxpayers can come clean by paying 30% tax plus a 100% penalty on that tax on previously untaxed foreign assets or income, or a flat Rs 1 lakh fee in benign cases where foreign assets bought out of already taxed income were not reported in the foreign asset schedule. In return, declarants get immunity from further tax, penalty and prosecution under the Black Money Act on the declared items. The exact opening and closing dates will be notified separately, but the policy signal is clear: clean up small legacy foreign asset issues before the information exchange net tightens further. On the business tax side, several structural tweaks stand out. First, supply of manpower is now explicitly included in the statutory definition of “work” for TDS purposes, putting manpower contracts clearly under the contractor TDS net at the familiar 1%–2% slabs depending on the payer’s status. Second, the Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) regime has been recalibrated: the MAT rate in the old corporate tax regime is trimmed to 14% and treated as a final tax, while companies moving into the new lower rate regime are allowed to use their legacy MAT credits under the old law, but with a tight 25% cap on the amount of MAT credit that can be set off against normal tax in any one year and a 15 year sunset for utilisation. That balances taxpayer expectations on MAT credit with the government’s desire to avoid MAT shielded “zero tax” years under the new regime. For non resident and digital economy players, the government has doubled down on India as a data and cloud hub. Through amendments to the exemption schedules, qualifying foreign companies that deliver global cloud or data centre services by procuring capacity from “specified” Indian data centres—which themselves must be owned and operated by Indian companies, notified by the Centre and meet detailed conditions—can enjoy a long duration tax exemption on such income, available up to the tax year ending 31 March 2047. The idea is to attract global cloud majors to build onshore stacks on top of Indian owned infrastructure, without triggering immediate tax friction on the foreign service entity’s income sourced from those data centre services. The Budget also rationalises a few smaller but high friction levies. On the collection side, TCS rates on scrap and alcoholic liquor for human consumption are unified at 2%, down from higher earlier rates, giving a modest relief to cash flow sensitive sectors like metals trade and liquor distribution while keeping traceability intact. On capital markets, the long criticised buyback tax is being redesigned: rather than a blunt corporate level levy, the Bill proposes an additional capital gains tax on promoter level gains arising from buybacks, at differentiated rates for domestic and foreign promoters, while non promoter shareholders simply pay normal capital gains tax. That structure softens the blow for retail holders and aligns with the policy goal of penalising aggressive promoter buyback engineering more than ordinary investors. Beyond taxes, the Budget leans hard into manufacturing, logistics and services as growth engines. Customs schedules have been overhauled to remove rate clutter, cut or eliminate basic customs duty on a basket of critical minerals and components for electronics, clean tech, batteries, telecom and shipping, and amend rates for shipbuilding, airports and select agri linked products, all with an eye on domestic value addition and supply chain resilience. Infrastructure plans—from PPP pipelines, a new asset monetisation plan and multimodal connectivity under PM Gati Shakti to continued support for Jal Jeevan, urban challenge funds and maritime corridors—are meant to keep the public investment cycle humming even as the deficit comes down. On the services and social side, the government has layered in measures such as a fresh Rs 10,000 crore fund of funds for startups, expanded skilling and research allocations, and sector specific pushes in tourism, medical tourism and urban livelihoods, framing the entire package as an attempt to deliver both hard infrastructure growth and more inclusive, employment rich development. Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Auto shed 0.87%. The company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. VST Tillers Tractors advanced 1.27% after the company reported a 53.89% surge in total sales to 5,257 units in January 2026, up from 3,416 units sold in January 2025. Meesho fell 4.97% after the company's consolidated net loss widened to Rs 490.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 37.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter. Steel Strips Wheels (SSWL) advanced 0.66% after the company reported a net turnover of Rs 480.03 crore for January 2026, marking a 17.32% year-on-year (YoY) increase compared to Rs 409.16 crore recorded in January 2025. R R Kabel rose 1.10% after the company reported growth in profit and revenue for the December quarter. On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 72.4% YoY to Rs 118.2 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 68.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Relaxo Footwears fell 2.06% after the company reported a 19.6% decline in net profit to Rs 26.54 crore, despite a 0.2% rise in net sales to Rs 668.03 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Escorts Kubota advanced 2.29% after the company’s Agri Machinery Business in January 2026 sold 9,799 tractors registering a growth of 46.9% as against 6,669 tractors sold in January 2025. Global Markets: On Friday, U.S stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Spot gold and silver dropped around 9% and 28%, respectively. Over the past year, gold and silver futures have soared about 67% and 142%, respectively. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Laurus Labs Ltd slips for fifth straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/laurus-labs-ltd-slips-for-fifth-straight-session/1670060</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670060</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Laurus Labs Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today.

Laurus Labs Ltd is down for a fifth straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 944.45, down 2.13% on the day as on 13:19 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.8% on the day, quoting at 25118.1. The Sensex is at 81829.23, down 0.54%.Laurus Labs Ltd has lost around 14.65% in last one month.Meanwhile, Nifty Pharma index of which Laurus Labs Ltd is a constituent, has eased around 5.07% in last one month and is currently quoting at 21715.1, down 0.37% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 11.2 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 23.57 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 948.75, down 2.06% on the day. Laurus Labs Ltd jumped 61.07% in last one year as compared to a 7.52% rally in NIFTY and a 1.28% spurt in the Nifty Pharma index. The PE of the stock is 65.08 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LaurusLabsLtd_52621883889_45955.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VST Tillers gains after reporting 54% YoY sales growth in January 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vst-tillers-gains-after-reporting-54-yoy-sales-growth-in-january-2026/1670058</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670058</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s power tiller sales grew by 54.91% to 4,810 units in January 2026, compared to 3,105 units in the same month last year.

The company’s power tiller sales grew by 54.91% to 4,810 units in January 2026, compared to 3,105 units in the same month last year. Tractor sales also grew 43.72% to 447 units in January 2026, up from 311 units sold in January 2025. VST Tillers Tractors is engaged in the manufacturing of power tillers and diesel engines. The company’s consolidated net profit declined 44.24% to Rs 24.98 crore in Q2 FY26, compared to Rs 44.80 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 11.19% year-on-year to Rs 315.15 crore for the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VSTTillTract_79364939960_2531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM announces allocation of Rs 10,000 crore over next five years under Biopharma Shakti]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-announces-allocation-of-rs-10000-crore-over-next-five-years-under-biopharma-shakti/1670057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670057</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman in her Budget 2026 speech announced allocation of Rs 10,000 crore over the next five years under the Biopharma Shakti.

Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman in her Budget 2026 speech announced allocation of Rs 10,000 crore over the next five years under the Biopharma Shakti. This will include a biopharma-focused network with three new National Institutes of Pharmaceutical Education and Research, popularly known as NIPERs, and upgrading seven existing ones.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/piggy-bank-with-doctors-stethoscope-picture-id490672108_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM proposes to reduce the tariff rate on all dutiable goods imported for personal use from 20% to 10% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-proposes-to-reduce-the-tariff-rate-on-all-dutiable-goods-imported-for-personal-use-from-20-to-10/1670056</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670056</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Union Minister for Finance and Corporate Affairs, Smt.

The Union Minister for Finance and Corporate Affairs, Smt. Nirmala Sitharaman, while presenting the Union Budget 2026-27 today in the Parliament announced that the proposals for Customs and Central Excise aim to further simplify the tariff structure, support domestic manufacturing, promote export competitiveness, and correct inversion in duty. Budget proposes to reduce the tariff rate on all dutiable goods imported for personal use from 20 per cent to 10 per cent to rationalize the customs duty structure. To provide relief to patients, particularly those suffering from cancer, the Budget proposes to exempt basic customs duty on 17 drugs or medicines. The Budget also proposes to add 7 more rare diseases for the purposes of exempting import duties on personal imports of drugs, medicines and Food for Special Medical Purposes (FSMP) used in their treatment. The Union Budget further proposes to revise provisions governing baggage clearance during international travel to address genuine concerns of passengers. The revised rules will enhance duty-free allowances and provide clarity in temporary carriage of goods brought in or taken out. Furthermore, the honest taxpayers will now be able to settle their dues and close cases by paying an additional amount in lieu of penalty, the Budget added.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>