<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:56:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashiana Housing Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashiana-housing-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1675187</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675187</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Brightcom Group Ltd, Sarthak Metals Ltd, Airan Ltd and Gulshan Polyols Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 11 February 2026.

Brightcom Group Ltd, Sarthak Metals Ltd, Airan Ltd and Gulshan Polyols Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 11 February 2026. Ashiana Housing Ltd spiked 15.07% to Rs 351.15 at 11-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 3.51 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2640 shares in the past one month. Brightcom Group Ltd soared 14.29% to Rs 13.76. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 35.54 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10.45 lakh shares in the past one month. Sarthak Metals Ltd surged 13.85% to Rs 91.38. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 10722 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1023 shares in the past one month. Airan Ltd advanced 13.11% to Rs 17.34. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 10579 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11251 shares in the past one month. Gulshan Polyols Ltd spurt 11.84% to Rs 163.85. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1.15 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4040 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshianaHousing_80521790060_2769.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HLE Glascoat slumps after weak Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hle-glascoat-slumps-after-weak-q3-performance/1675186</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675186</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While EBITDA declined by 10.8% to Rs 24.59 crore, EBITDA margin contracted by 440 basis points YoY to 7.5% in Q3 FY26.

While EBITDA declined by 10.8% to Rs 24.59 crore, EBITDA margin contracted by 440 basis points YoY to 7.5% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax and before exceptional items in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 6.83 crore, down by 40.1% from Rs 11.41 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company had an orderbook of Rs 653.39 crore as on 31 December 2025. The company said that it continues to receive enquiries for orders across all business segments. HLE Glascoat further said that it would undertake capital expenditure of upto Rs 25 crore to manufacture glass-fused tanks, silos and other allied products at its existing Silvassa manufacturing campus, based on the experience and knowledge of the Omeras business acquisition. Himanshu K. Patel, managing director, said: “The quarter highlighted exceptional performance in our Heat Transfer Equipment segment, which surged 151% year-on-year, alongside solid contributions from Glass Lined Products (24% growth) and Filtration and Drying Equipment (41% growth). Building on the Omeras acquisition completed in Q2, which expanded our footprint into Glass Fused Steel products with strong potential in Biogas Digestors, Large Storage Tanks, and Architectural Facades, we are now seeing early synergies and enhanced diversification. Looking ahead, the second half of the fiscal year typically contributes between 55% and 60% of our revenues. Omeras is expected to achieve breakeven by Q4 FY26, with meaningful contribution anticipated from FY27 onwards.” HLE Glascoat is engaged in the specialized business of manufacturing chemical process equipment. The company’s key product segment has been filtration and drying equipment. The flagship products in this segment are agitated nutsche filters and dryers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SwissGlascoat_47857861537_3646.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1675184</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675184</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PCBL Chemical Ltd, Eicher Motors Ltd, Banco Products (India) Ltd and Pricol Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 11 February 2026.

PCBL Chemical Ltd, Eicher Motors Ltd, Banco Products (India) Ltd and Pricol Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 11 February 2026. TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd soared 11.85% to Rs 120.62 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 18.24 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 37862 shares in the past one month. PCBL Chemical Ltd surged 9.38% to Rs 321.3. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 30.94 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.52 lakh shares in the past one month. Eicher Motors Ltd spiked 6.42% to Rs 7765. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.34 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8729 shares in the past one month. Banco Products (India) Ltd gained 6.09% to Rs 693.3. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 52295 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 26840 shares in the past one month. Pricol Ltd advanced 5.60% to Rs 617.5. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 38062 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21474 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSSupplyChainSolutionsLtd_13681781_28638.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI Aggressive Hybrid Fund announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-aggressive-hybrid-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1675183</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675183</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced 12 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under IDCW-Regular Plan and IDCW-Direct Plan of UTI Aggressive Hybrid Fund.

UTI Mutual Fund has announced 12 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under IDCW-Regular Plan and IDCW-Direct Plan of UTI Aggressive Hybrid Fund. The quantum of dividend will be Rs 0.9000 per unit or 9.00% on the face value of Rs 10 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/your-morning-ritual-picture-id172240980_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shriram Mutual Fund announces change in Key Personnel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shriram-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-key-personnel/1675177</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675177</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shriram Mutual Fund has announced that Ms.

Shriram Mutual Fund has announced that Ms. Vinita Kapoor has been appointed as Company Secretary with effect from February 06, 2026 (“Effective Date”). Details of Ms. Vinita Kapoor Age: 35 years Designation: Company Secretary, Qualification: B. Com, C.S., and LLB

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade near opening levels; auto shares gear up ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-near-opening-levels-auto-shares-gear-up/1675174</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675174</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices continued to trade with minor gains in the mid-morning trade, aided by recently signed the India-US interim trade deal and continued FPI inflows.

The key equity indices continued to trade with minor gains in the mid-morning trade, aided by recently signed the India-US interim trade deal and continued FPI inflows. Investors remained focused on corporate earnings as the Q3 results season gathered pace. The Nifty hovered above the 25,950 mark. Auto shares rallied for the third consecutive trading session. At 11:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 14.36 points or 0.02% to 84,288.28. The Nifty 50 index rose 22.82 points or 0.09% to 25,957.40. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.22% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.08%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,762 shares rose and 2,051 shares fell. A total of 228 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Fractal Analytics received bids for 43,58,016 shares as against 1,85,79,360 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.23 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 857 and 900 per share. Aye Finance received bids for 82,03,404 shares as against 4,55,32,785 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 0.18 times. The issue opened for bidding on 9 February 2026 and it closed on 11 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 122 and 129 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index rose 2.08% to 28,759.50. The index climbed 4.51% in the three consecutive trading sessions. Eicher Motors (up 6.51%), Samvardhana Motherson International (up 4.16%), TVS Motor Company (up 2.63%), Mahindra & Mahindra (up 2.34%), Ashok Leyland (up 2.04%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (up 1.52%), Maruti Suzuki India (up 1.47%), Bosch (up 1.38%), Tube Investments of India (up 1.23%) and Uno Minda (up 0.95%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: United Breweries (UBL) rose 0.39%. The company reported a 110.7% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 81.15 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 38.52 crore in Q3 FY25.Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 3.62% YoY to Rs 2,072.72 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Reliance Industries rose 0.29%. The company said that its FMCG arm Reliance Consumer Products (RCPL) has acquired leading health foods maker Southern Health Foods. RCPL has acquired 100% equity stake in Southern Health Foods (SHFPL) for an aggregate cash consideration of Rs 156.42 crore from the existing shareholders of SHFPL. Global Markets: Asia market advanced on Wednesday, continuing their rally even as China's consumer price index rose 0.2% in January from a year earlier, China’s National Bureau of Statistics data showed Wednesday. That’s below the widely reported forecast of 0.4% increase, a sign of continued deflationary pressure in the absence of stronger stimulus. Japan’s markets are closed for a public holiday. In U.S, December retail sales report showed that consumer spending was flat following a 0.6% increase in November, missing the 0.4% monthly gain that was widely expected. Overnight, the S&P 500 slipped on Tuesday as investors reacted to weaker-than-expected retail sales data and grew concerned about the threat artificial intelligence poses to the financial sector. The broad-based index lost 0.33% and ended at 6,941.81, while the Nasdaq Composite slipped 0.59% and closed at 23,102.47. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 52.27 points, or 0.10%, posting a closing record of 50,188.14. Financial stocks also took a hit Tuesday after tech platform Altruist launched a new AI-powered tax planning tool. Shares of LPL Financial declined 8.3%, while shares of Charles Schwab dropped 7.4% and Morgan Stanley dipped more than 2%. Investors await the release of big jobs report due on Wednesday, and the consumer price index data on Friday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RIL's consumer division acquires Southern Health Foods ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rils-consumer-division-acquires-southern-health-foods/1675145</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675145</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Based in Tamil Nadu, Southern Health Foods is key player in several health focused foods categories like packaged healthy foods including millets, oats, multi-grain products, health mixes, breakfast cereals, dry fruits, among others.

Based in Tamil Nadu, Southern Health Foods is key player in several health focused foods categories like packaged healthy foods including millets, oats, multi-grain products, health mixes, breakfast cereals, dry fruits, among others. Its flagship brand Manna is widely known for its healthy offerings in many emerging packaged foods categories like millet flour, baby foods and multigrain drink mix. RCPL has acquired 100% equity stake in Southern Health Foods (SHFPL) for an aggregate cash consideration of Rs 156.42 crore from the existing shareholders of SHFPL. The company stated that the addition of Manna adds further strength to RCPL’s foods and staples portfolio that includes brands like Udhaiyam, Independence and SiL, through building a strong business vertical in the growing millet-based foods segment. T. Krishnakumar, director, Reliance Consumer Products, said, "Manna is one of the most trusted names in the health focused foods market in Tamil Nadu with noticeable presence in the adjoining states. It is known for healthy offerings like millet-based staples and mixes, drinks and baby food. With our strong distribution, R&D and supply chain capabilities, Manna would be made available in other geographies - eventually making it a household name across the country.” Reliance Industries is India's largest private sector company. Its activities span hydrocarbon exploration and production, petroleum refining and marketing, petrochemicals, advanced materials and composites, renewables (solar and hydrogen), retail and digital services. The conglomerate had reported 1.6% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 22,290 crore on 10% increase in gross revenue to Rs 293,829 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip rose 0.13% to currently trade at Rs 1460.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RelianceInds_29114129325_476.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Edelweiss Mutual Fund announces change in scheme name]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/edelweiss-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-scheme-name/1675073</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675073</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Edelweiss Mutual Fund has announced change in scheme name under the following scheme, with effect from 16 March 2026.

Edelweiss Mutual Fund has announced change in scheme name under the following scheme, with effect from 16 March 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Changes in Scheme Name: Existing Scheme Name Revised Scheme Name Edelweiss Income Plus Arbitrage Active Fund of Funds Edelweiss Income Plus Arbitrage Omni Fund of Funds

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[United Breweries Q3 PAT spurts 111% YoY to Rs 81 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/united-breweries-q3-pat-spurts-111-yoy-to-rs-81-cr/1675072</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675072</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 3.62% YoY to Rs 2,072.72 crore in the December 2025 quarter.

Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 3.62% YoY to Rs 2,072.72 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Profit before exceptional items and tax rose to Rs 151.02 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 87.08 crore a year ago. The company had reported an exceptional loss of Rs 18.73 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous fiscal year, mainly due to severance pay and provisions made towards the impact of the newly notified labour codes, which are regulatory-driven and non-recurring in nature. United Breweries reported a 4% YoY increase in net sales in Q3 FY26, driven by premiumization and a favorable price mix. Premium volumes continued to outpace the overall portfolio (YTD +23%), taking year-to-date net sales growth to 6%. Gross margin improved sharply to 45.3% in Q3, the highest level in the last three years, expanding 222 bps YoY, aided by positive price mix, portfolio localization, and operational excellence. On a year-to-date basis, gross margin stood at 43.4%, up 12 bps YoY. EBIT surged 86% YoY during the quarter, aided by strong margin expansion and early benefits from the productivity and cost-effectiveness program. The productivity and cost-effectiveness program, launched earlier in the year and continuing through FY27, is expected to deliver gross savings of 3–6% of the total cost base over time, with a substantial portion planned for strategic reinvestment to support sustained growth, premiumization, and category building. Brand investments remained strong, resulting in the highest portfolio brand power in the last three years. During the quarter, the company strengthened its innovation pipeline with the launch of Kingfisher Smooth in Rajasthan and Karnataka in January 2026, aimed at reviving category growth and expanding its presence in the strong beer segment. United Breweries (UBL) is engaged in the business of manufacturing and selling beer and non-alcoholic beverages. Shares of United Breweries rose 0.39% to Rs 1,621.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnitedBreweries_49738308528_23220.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Grover Jewells carves a glittering path in market debut]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-grover-jewells-carves-a-glittering-path-in-market-debut/1675070</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675070</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 96, a premium of 9.09% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 96, a premium of 9.09% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 100.80 and a low of Rs 91.40. About 23.98 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Grover Jewells' IPO was subscribed 12.79 times. The issue opened for bidding on 4 February 2026 and it closed on 6 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 83 to Rs 88 per equity share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 38,44,800 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 73.50% from 100% pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for working capital requirements, issue related expenses and for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Grover Jewells on 3 February 2026, raised Rs 9.61 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 10.92 lakh shares at Rs 88 per share to 5 anchor investors. Delhi-based Grover Jewells is engaged in the manufacturing and designing of wholesale gold jewellery. The company offers a wide range of plain gold, studded, and semi-finished jewellery, primarily in 22 Karat, 20 Karat, and 18 Karat gold. It operates through two showrooms located in Karol Bagh and Chandni Chowk, Delhi, providing both hallmarked and non-hallmarked jewellery. The company’s manufacturing activities are divided into machine-made chain manufacturing and casting jewellery production, enabling it to cater to high-volume demand as well as contemporary, fashion-oriented designs with consistent quality and timely delivery. Grover Jewells classifies its sales into wholesale, retail, and consumer segments and has established a strong B2B network across around 20 states in India, along with an international presence through exports to Australia and the U.A.E. As of 31 December 2025, the company had a total of 78 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 473.18 crore and net profit of Rs 10.45 crore for the period ended 31 October 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GROVERJEWELLSLIMITED_47286717_96146.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ZF Commercial Vehicle gains as Q3 PAT jumps 12% YoY to Rs 140 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/zf-commercial-vehicle-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-12-yoy-to-rs-140-cr/1675069</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675069</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s revenue from operations jumped 11.68% YoY to Rs 1,074.91 crore in Q3 FY26.

The company’s revenue from operations jumped 11.68% YoY to Rs 1,074.91 crore in Q3 FY26. Total expenses rose 11.25% YoY to Rs 910.50 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of material consumed was at Rs 595.82 crore (up 9.89% YoY) and employee benefits expenses stood at Rs 145.77 crore (up 3.78% YoY) during the period under review. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 186.51 crore, up 16.19%, compared with Rs 160.51 crore recorded in the same period last year. ZF Commercial Vehicle Control Systems India, part of ZF Group Commercial Vehicle Solutions Division, is a market leader for advanced braking systems, conventional braking products and related air assisted technologies and systems in India. The company provides industry-leading solutions in the autonomous, connected and electric (ACE) domains to commercial vehicle industry in India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/WABCOIndia_78056282939_28069.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Brandman Retail hits the ground running on listing day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-brandman-retail-hits-the-ground-running-on-listing-day/1675068</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675068</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 183, a premium of 3.98% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 183, a premium of 3.98% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 192.15 and a low of Rs 183. About 24.74 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Brandman Retail's IPO was subscribed 76.21 times. The issue opened for bidding 4 February 2026 and it closed 6 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 167 to Rs 176 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 48,91,200 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for funding capital expenditure for expansion of the new retail network by launching 15 exclusive brand outlets (EBOs) and multi-brand outlets (MBOS), working capital requirements for new EBOs and MBOs, working capital requirements for existing EBOs and MBOs and general corporate expenses. Ahead of the IPO, Brandman Retail on 3 February 2026, raised Rs 24.49 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 13.92 lakh shares at Rs 176 per share to 6 anchor investors. Brandman Retail is engaged in the distribution and retail of premium international brands through non-exclusive distribution agreements. Its sales are conducted through multiple channels, including Exclusive Brand Outlets (EBOs) operated under specific brand arrangements, Multi-Brand Outlets (MBOs) under its trademark Sneakrz, e-commerce marketplaces, and its own website. In addition to offline stores, the company has entered into agreements with footwear retailers under which it supplies products to stores, which are then sold to end customers through both online and offline channels. This multi-channel presence enables the company to cater to customers across physical retail formats as well as digital platforms. As of 31 December 2025, the company had 161 full-time employees on its payroll. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 95.31 crore and net profit of Rs 19.67 crore for the period ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BRANDMANRETAILLIMITED_10662190_94670.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Ather Energy Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-ather-energy-ltd-counter/1675065</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675065</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HEG Ltd, Eicher Motors Ltd, Craftsman Automation Ltd, Jubilant Foodworks Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 11 February 2026.

HEG Ltd, Eicher Motors Ltd, Craftsman Automation Ltd, Jubilant Foodworks Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 11 February 2026. Ather Energy Ltd clocked volume of 41.14 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 21.92 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.88 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.16% to Rs.725.95. Volumes stood at 48489 shares in the last session. HEG Ltd witnessed volume of 10.62 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 16.31 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 65121 shares. The stock dropped 4.30% to Rs.537.05. Volumes stood at 68145 shares in the last session. Eicher Motors Ltd saw volume of 1.2 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 15.56 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 7725 shares. The stock increased 6.52% to Rs.7,772.15. Volumes stood at 8763 shares in the last session. Craftsman Automation Ltd witnessed volume of 51722 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.45 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6121 shares. The stock increased 3.20% to Rs.8,097.35. Volumes stood at 500 shares in the last session. Jubilant Foodworks Ltd witnessed volume of 3.94 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7.67 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 51400 shares. The stock dropped 1.22% to Rs.547.00. Volumes stood at 77348 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AtherEnergyLtd_32132763_75556.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI comes up with measures to strengthen cooperative banks’ financial health ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-comes-up-with-measures-to-strengthen-cooperative-banks-financial-health/1675064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675064</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI), in consultation with the Government of India, has announced that loans sanctioned by banks to National Cooperative Development Corporation (NCDC) w.e.f.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI), in consultation with the Government of India, has announced that loans sanctioned by banks to National Cooperative Development Corporation (NCDC) w.e.f. January 19, 2026, for on-lending to cooperative societies are eligible for classification as priority sector lending under the respective categories. These apply to banks other than Regional Rural Banks, Urban Cooperative Banks, Small Finance Banks and Local Area Banks. These loans are for purposes and activities as laid down in the Master Direction on Priority Sector Lending, 2025. The Government of India and RBI have taken various measures to strengthen cooperative banks’ financial health, governance and digital inclusion along with enhancing deposit security, credit availability and prudent regulation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PM GatiShakti Network Planning Group evaluates infrastructure projects worth Rs 16.10 Lakh Crore ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pm-gatishakti-network-planning-group-evaluates-infrastructure-projects-worth-rs-1610-lakh-crore/1675059</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675059</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Network Planning Group (NPG), constituted under the PM Gati Shakti National Master Plan (PMGS-NMP) framework, evaluates the critical infrastructure projects of the Central Government to ensure integrated planning, multimodality, inter-modality, synchronization of eﬀorts, last mile connectivity, comprehensive development in and around the project location, data-driven decision makings, etc at the planning stage.

The Network Planning Group (NPG), constituted under the PM Gati Shakti National Master Plan (PMGS-NMP) framework, evaluates the critical infrastructure projects of the Central Government to ensure integrated planning, multimodality, inter-modality, synchronization of eﬀorts, last mile connectivity, comprehensive development in and around the project location, data-driven decision makings, etc at the planning stage. As on date, 352 infrastructure projects with total estimated cost of Rs 16.10 Lakh Crore have been evaluated through the NPG mechanism. Out of these 352 projects, 201 projects have been sanctioned - out of which, 167 projects are under implementation. Ministry of Finance, Department of Expenditure through Part-II (for PM Gati Shakti related expenditure) of the "Scheme for Special Assistance to States for Capital Investment for 2022-23" made a provision of Rs 5000 crores for disbursement among the States for infrastructure development in the form of 50 years interest-free loan. Details of projects of the States, approved under the Part-II of the “Scheme for Special Assistance to the States for Capital Investment” and funds allocated.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/trend-1445464__340__stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,950 mark; consumer durables shares jump]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25950-mark-consumer-durables-shares-jump/1675057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675057</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices continued to trade with minor gains in the morning trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from foreign portfolio investors (FPIs).

The key equity indices continued to trade with minor gains in the morning trade, buoyed by optimism over the India-US interim trade deal and inflows from foreign portfolio investors (FPIs). Market participants are assessing ongoing Q3 result season. The Nifty hovered above the 25,950 mark. Consumer durables shares rallied for fourth consecutive trading session. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 40.69 points or 0.05% to 84,314.61. The Nifty 50 index rose 17.90 points or 0.07% to 25,953.05. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index shed 0.31% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.07%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,719 shares rose and 1,928 shares fell. A total of 219 shares were unchanged. Result Today: Mahindra & Mahindra(up 2.32%), LG Electronics India(down 1.29%), Lenskart Solutions(down 0.47%), Ashok Leyland(up 1.74%), Aarey Drugs & Pharmaceuticals(up 1.37%), Amagi Media Labs(up 1.40%), Amara Raja Energy & Mobility(down 0.33%), AstraZeneca Pharma India(up 0.64%), Avanti Feeds(up 0.88%), CARE Ratings(down 0.49%), Carraro India(down 1.27%), Divis Laboratories(up 0.65%), Godrej Industries(down 1.16%), Max Financial Services(down 0.43%), Patanjali Foods(up 0.11%), TBO Tek(down 0.30%), and Yatra Online (up 1.28%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index advanced 0.81% to 38,064.45. The index jumped 5.47% in the four consecutive trading sessions. Whirlpool of India (up 3.01%), Titan Company (up 1.55%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (up 1.51%), V-Guard Industries (up 1%), Amber Enterprises India (up 0.87%), Kajaria Ceramics (up 0.76%), Voltas (up 0.32%), Blue Star (up 0.2%) and Century Plyboards (India) (up 0.06%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Jubilant FoodWorks shed 0.98%. The company reported 68.6% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 72.9 crore on a 13.3% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2,437.2 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Power Mech Projects declined 4.11%. The company reported a 14.6% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 93.99 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 82.03 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (net sales) rose 6.1% YoY to Rs 1,419.56 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 1,337.97 crore in the corresponding period last year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Apollo Hospitals gains after Q3 PAT jumps 35% YoY to Rs 502 cr; board declares Rs 10 interim dividend]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apollo-hospitals-gains-after-q3-pat-jumps-35-yoy-to-rs-502-cr-board-declares-rs-10-interim-dividend/1675034</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675034</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) increased 27.19% YoY to Rs 682 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) increased 27.19% YoY to Rs 682 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. EBITDA grew by 26.64% to Rs 965 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 762 crore in Q3 FY25. This includes Apollo 24/7 costs of Rs 124 crore during the quarter (including Rs 38 crore in non-cash ESOP charges), compared to Rs 141 crore in Q3 FY25. On a segmental front, revenue from Healthcare Services rose 14% YoY to Rs 3,183 crore. Revenue from Apollo Health and Lifestyle (AHLL) stood at Rs 467 crore, up 20% YoY, while revenue from Apollo HealthCo reached Rs 2,827 crore, also up 20% YoY. As on 31 December 2025, Apollo Hospitals had 8,072 operating beds across the network (excluding AHLL & managed beds). The overall occupancy for hospitals was at 67% in Q3FY26 vs 68% in the same period in the previous year. Dr. Prathap C Reddy, Chairman, Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd. said, “Q3FY26 reflects the fundamental strength and clinical depth of Apollo’s integrated care model. Across our network, teams are consistently delivering strong outcomes through disciplined execution in patient safety, quality, and experience. This quarter, sustained investments in advanced clinical capability translated into meaningful progress across key specialties from Apollo OMR completing 150 robotic joint replacement surgeries in its first 150 days, to the expansion of our stroke care network in Chennai with nine advanced stroke labs, strengthening rapidaccess care and outcomes. We further reinforced our differentiated leadership in neurosciences with the launch of a dedicated Centre of Excellence for Parkinson’s disease and Deep Brain Stimulation care in Chennai, strengthened comprehensive oncology care through the ‘Save My Stomach’ early detection programme at Apollo Cancer Centres, and expanded high-acuity capability with a dedicated heart and lung transplant unit in Karnataka. In parallel, partnerships such as the MoU with Coal India reflect Apollo’s vision to expand access to standardized, high-quality healthcare by building integrated preventive and tertiary care pathways for large workforce populations. Apollo’s transplant programme reflects the depth, scale, and discipline of our clinical systems. As one of the world’s busiest solid organ transplant programmes, our teams now perform an average of five solid organ transplants each day. Cumulatively, we have completed more than 21,000 kidney transplants and over 5,000 liver transplants—becoming the first hospital group in India and the region to reach this landmark—along with 159 heart transplants and 232 lung transplants. These outcomes are the result of standardized clinical pathways, multidisciplinary expertise, and a sustained commitment to patient safety, ethics, and long-term outcomes. The Union Budget provides an important tailwind to India’s aspiration to become a global destination for healthcare. The proposal to support states in establishing five regional medical hubs through public– private partnership is a strategic step toward building a high-quality, well-coordinated Medical Value Travel ecosystem. At Apollo, we view Medical Value Travel as a long-term national mission that reflects India’s depth of clinical expertise, outcomes excellence, and cost advantage. We will continue to work closely with policymakers and state partners to strengthen international patient pathways, expand high-acuity capacity, and ensure seamless coordination across pre-travel evaluation, clinical care, and post-discharge followup.” The board has declared an interim dividend of Rs 10 per share for the financial year 2026. The record date for the same has been fixed as February 16 and it will be paid on or before February 27. Apollo Hospitals was established in 1983 by Dr. Prathap C Reddy, renowned architect of modern healthcare in India. As the nation’s first corporate hospital, Apollo Hospitals is acclaimed for pioneering the private healthcare revolution in the country. Apollo Hospitals has emerged as Asia’s foremost integrated healthcare services provider and has a robust presence across the healthcare ecosystem, including Hospitals, Pharmacies, Primary Care & Diagnostic Clinics and several Retail Health models.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ApolloHospitals_45306952472_636.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR extends upside amid weak dollar, FPI inflows]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-extends-upside-amid-weak-dollar-fpi-inflows/1675007</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675007</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee is regaining momentum in opening trades on Wednesday tracking dollar weakness overseas and cheering return of foreign investment inflows.

The Indian rupee is regaining momentum in opening trades on Wednesday tracking dollar weakness overseas and cheering return of foreign investment inflows. INR opened at Rs 90.56 per dollar and hit a high of 90.46 so far during the day. Yesterday, rupee pared initial losses and settled on a positive note, higher by 9 paise at 90.57 against the US dollar, supported by positive cues from domestic equities. NIFTY50 index extended the upmove as United States and India reached a framework for an Interim Agreement on reciprocal trade. The index has zoomed near 26000 mark today and is keeping INR supported. The benchmark BSE Sensex rose by 208.17 points, or 0.25 percent, to 84,273.92, extending its rally into a third consecutive session. The broader NSE Nifty index ended up 67.85 points, or 0.26 percent, at 25,935.15 amid the weekly expiry of options contracts. Meanwhile, US dollar index tanked in global markets yesterday and was trading under 97 mark, lingering near one-week low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jubilant FoodWorks posts nearly 69% YoY rise in Q3 PAT; store count rises to 3,594 outlets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jubilant-foodworks-posts-nearly-69-yoy-rise-in-q3-pat-store-count-rises-to-3594-outlets/1675009</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1675009</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While operating EBITDA improved by 20% to Rs 482.3 crore, operating EBITDA margin expanded by 110 basis points YoY to 19.8% in Q3 FY26.

While operating EBITDA improved by 20% to Rs 482.3 crore, operating EBITDA margin expanded by 110 basis points YoY to 19.8% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 115.26 crore, up by 57.2% from Rs 73.30 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Jubilant FoodWorks said that it has recorded a strong performance in Q3 FY26 marked by double digit revenue growth, robust margin expansion fuelled by improved operational efficiency, and accelerated store expansion across markets. The store network increased by 114 net new stores, which was the highest quarterly store additions during the last 4 quarters, taking the total store count to 3,594 across brands and geographies. The India business reported revenue from operations of Rs 1,801.5 crore, a growth of 11.8% YoY. It was driven by a 5.0% LFL growth in Domino’s, high double-digit growth in Popeyes, new additions to the menu and rapid expansion of store network in India. During the quarter, the company added 78 net new stores across all brands, including 75 new Domino’s and 5 new Popeyes stores, ending the quarter with 2,528 stores in India. The Turkey business continued to record high growth in topline. The revenue from operations increased by 15% YoY to Rs 580.1 crore. Sri Lanka and Bangladesh businesses also continued to report strong topline growth YoY. Net addition of 36 stores across all brands, ending the period with 1,066 stores in the international markets Shyam S. Bhartia, chairman and Hari S. Bhartia, co-chairman, Jubilant FoodWorks, commented: “We are elated with our performance in the quarter gone by. Our consolidated topline continues to grow at a very healthy rate. Our margins at all levels have improved significantly over last year. We are also delighted with our Turkey business, which is now servicing the acquisition debt obligations through its own cash flows. Sri Lanka and Bangladesh businesses also continue to deliver strong growth.” Jubilant FoodWorks ranks among the leading emerging markets’ food-tech companies. Its Group network comprises 3,594 stores across six markets – India, Turkey, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Azerbaijan and Georgia. The scrip shed 0.14% to currently trade at Rs 552.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JubilantFood_44171671816_14548.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Mech Projects Q3 PAT rises 15% YoY to Rs 94 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-mech-projects-q3-pat-rises-15-yoy-to-rs-94-cr/1674992</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1674992</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (net sales) rose 6.1% YoY to Rs 1,419.56 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 1,337.97 crore in the corresponding period last year.

Revenue from operations (net sales) rose 6.1% YoY to Rs 1,419.56 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 1,337.97 crore in the corresponding period last year. Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 123.86 crore in Q3 FY26, up 2.1% from the Rs 121.32 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 6.78% to Rs 1,309.10 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 1,225.98 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of raw material consumed stood at Rs 233.26 crore (up 8.84% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 191.86 crore (up 11.85% YoY) during the period under review. Power Mech Projects is an engineering and construction company providing integrated service in erection, testing, and commissioning (ETC) of boilers, turbines, and generators and balance of plant (BOP), civil works, and operation and maintenance (O&M). The counter slipped 3.56% to Rs 2,191.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerMechProj_11108641403_34787.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>