<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:26:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Panacea Biotec rallies on bagging international vaccine supply contract]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/panacea-biotec-rallies-on-bagging-international-vaccine-supply-contract/1661993</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661993</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the revision, the contract value for 2026 has been increased by $2.55 million (around Rs 23 crore) to $16.8 million, while the 2027 allocation rises by $2.70 million (around Rs 24 crore) to $15.18 million.

Under the revision, the contract value for 2026 has been increased by $2.55 million (around Rs 23 crore) to $16.8 million, while the 2027 allocation rises by $2.70 million (around Rs 24 crore) to $15.18 million. Additionally, an extra award for 2027 worth $3.68 million (about Rs 33 crore) has been included, taking the total incremental value to $8.93 million (roughly Rs 80 crore) for the two years. The international supply contract will be executed as per orders received from UNICEF during CY2026 and CY2027. UNICEF is expected to publish details of the award, including supplier name, vaccine, duration, total value, and awarded prices per product on its official website. Panacea Biotec said the award does not involve any promoter or promoter group interest. Panacea Biotec is a research-based biotechnology companies engaged in the business of research, development, manufacture, and marketing of vaccines in India and international markets. The company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 13.92 crore in Q2 FY26 as against a net profit of Rs 4.80 crore in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 4.2% year on year to Rs 141.13 crore in Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PanaceaBiotec_58339392041_12420.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Launches Integrated Renewable Energy and Green Hydrogen Policies to Boost Clean Energy Transition]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-launches-integrated-renewable-energy-and-green-hydrogen-policies-to-boost-clean-energy-transition/1661992</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661992</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Gujarat government unveiled policies on renewable energy and green hydrogen with an aim to establish the state as a clean energy hub, to diversify its portfolio in the sector with the larger goal of addressing the challenges posed by climate change.

The Gujarat government unveiled policies on renewable energy and green hydrogen with an aim to establish the state as a clean energy hub, to diversify its portfolio in the sector with the larger goal of addressing the challenges posed by climate change. These policies - 'Integrated Renewable Energy Policy 2025' and 'Gujarat Green Hydrogen Policy 2025' - seek to ensure a rapid transition towards clean and sustainable energy systems.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/euro-1863441__340_economy.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slides 266 pts; IT shares lag]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slides-266-pts-it-shares-lag/1661991</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661991</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning trade as investors stayed cautious ahead of upcoming corporate earnings announcements.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest losses in mid-morning trade as investors stayed cautious ahead of upcoming corporate earnings announcements. The Nifty traded below the 26,100 level. IT shares extended losses for the third consecutive trading session. At 11:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 266.31 points or 0.31% to 85,142.39. The Nifty 50 index lost 76.30 points or 0.29% to 26,064.75. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.10%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index remained flat. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,810 shares rose and 2,059 shares fell. A total of 204 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 0.78% to 38,669.10. The index dropped 2.07% in the past three trading sessions. Coforge (down 2.28%), LTIMindtree (down 1.1%), Tech Mahindra (down 1.02%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 0.92%), HCL Technologies (down 0.79%), Mphasis (down 0.61%), Oracle Financial Services Software (down 0.34%), Infosys (down 0.25%), and Wipro (down 0.01%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: NMDC advanced 1.51% after the company has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Colorado School of Mines, USA, to establish a framework for research collaboration in mining, mineral processing, metallurgy and AI/ML in mining. NBCC (India) climbed 3.96% after the state-owned construction firm announced key developments spanning overseas real estate and domestic infrastructure projects. Global Markets: Asian markets traded mixed on Friday, with several exchanges in the region closed for the Boxing Day holiday. Silver prices continued rising and hit another high after notching a record Wednesday. Spot silver rose more than 4% on Friday to reach an all-time high of $74.89 per ounce. Silver has rallied over 159% year to date. Metal prices have soared this year amid shaky investor sentiment on riskier assets, as fears of an AI bubble and uncertainty over U.S. Fed rate cuts mount. Meanwhile, core consumer prices in Tokyo rose 2.3% in December from a year earlier, according to government data Friday. The core CPI, which strips out volatile fresh food costs, remained above the Bank of Japan’s 2% target, reinforcing the case for more interest rate hikes. The latest reading was below the 2.8% increase in November. Tokyo’s inflation numbers are widely considered to be a leading indicator of nationwide trends. The Australia and Hong Kong markets were closed for the holiday. U.S. equity futures ticked slightly higher in early Asian hours, after the S&P 500 closed at a new record for the second straight day on Wednesday stateside. The broad market index advanced 0.32%, ending the session at 6,932.05. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 288.75 points, or 0.60%, and also posted a closing record of 48,731.16. The Nasdaq Composite advanced 0.22% and settled at 23,613.31.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality IPO wraps up with 5.21x subscription ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-kidney-and-super-speciality-ipo-wraps-up-with-521x-subscription/1661986</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661986</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 6,89,69,088 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer.

Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality received bids for 6,89,69,088 shares as against 1,32,26,880 shares on offer. The issue was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of equity shares, aggregating up to Rs 250.8 crore. The objectives of the fresh issue are to utilize Rs 77 crore towards the acquisition of Parekh’s Hospital in Ahmedabad; Rs 12.4 crore will be used for part-payment of the purchase consideration for the already acquired Ashwini Medical Centre; Rs 10.78 crore is earmarked for the acquisition of additional shareholding in the subsidiary, Harmony Medicare, located in Bharuch; Rs 30.09 crore towards funding its capital expenditure requirements; Rs 6.82 crore will be utilized for the purchase of robotics equipment for Gujarat Kidney & Super Specialty Hospital in Vadodara; Rs 1.2 crore will be used for the repayment and/or prepayment of certain outstanding borrowings; and the remaining proceeds will be used for general corporate purposes. The promoters are Dr. Pragnesh Yashwantsinh Bharpoda, Dr. Bhartiben Pragnesh Bharpoda, Dr. Yashwantsingh Motisinh Bharpoda and Anitaben Yashwantsinh Bharpoda. The promoters and promoter group hold an aggregate of 5,63,33,900 equity shares, aggregating to 99.1% of the pre-offer issued and paid-up equity share capital. Their post IPO shareholding is expected to be around 71.45%. Ahead of the IPO, Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality on 22 December 2025, the company raised Rs 100.01 crore from anchor investors, by allotting 87.73 lakh shares at Rs 114 each to 10 anchor investors. Gujarat Kidney & Super Speciality specializes in providing multispeciality healthcare services, including secondary and tertiary care, across multiple locations in Gujarat, India. The company operates seven multispeciality hospitals and four pharmacies with a total bed capacity of 490 beds, an approved capacity of 455 beds, and an operational capacity of 340 beds. Comprehensive medical care is provided across a range of specialty and super-specialty services. Treatment is offered across areas such as internal medicine, general surgery, nephrology, urology, cardiology, and orthopedics, while also focusing on advanced super-specialty care including renal transplantation, vascular surgery, and hematology among others. Healthcare services are categorized as secondary services, which are surgical services, and tertiary Services, which are super speciality surgical services. Central, state and local government bodies contributed 5.46% to its revenue, Insurers through third party administrators 13.9%, and Self-payers and others 80.64% in Q1 FY2026. For the three month ended 30 June 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 4.84 crore and income from operations of Rs 15.26 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBI to conduct USD/INR Buy/Sell swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of three years]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rbi-to-conduct-usdinr-buysell-swap-auction-of-usd-10-billion-for-a-tenor-of-three-years/1661984</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661984</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) will be conducting a USD/INR Buy/Sell swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of three years.

The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) will be conducting a USD/INR Buy/Sell swap auction of USD 10 billion for a tenor of three years. The auction will take place on January 13, 2026.RBI noted that Authorized Dealers Category – I (AD Category-I) banks will be the eligible entities to participate in the auction.The swap is in the nature of a simple buy/sell foreign exchange swap from the Reserve Bank side. A bank shall sell US dollars to the Reserve Bank and simultaneously agree to buy the same amount of US dollars at the end of the swap period.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Railway Ministry officially notifies hike in train ticket prices ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railway-ministry-officially-notifies-hike-in-train-ticket-prices/1661983</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661983</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Railway Ministry has officially notified a hike in train ticket prices by 1 paise per km for ordinary class beyond a journey of 215 km, and 2 paise per km for non-AC classes of mail/express trains and AC classes of all trains.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Page Industries Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-page-industries-ltd-counter/1661981</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661981</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SRF Ltd, Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, Indian Energy Exchange Ltd, Titagarh Rail Systems Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 26 December 2025.

SRF Ltd, Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, Indian Energy Exchange Ltd, Titagarh Rail Systems Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 26 December 2025. Page Industries Ltd notched up volume of 25068 shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 40.63 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 617 shares. The stock slipped 0.64% to Rs.36,364.20. Volumes stood at 634 shares in the last session. SRF Ltd witnessed volume of 1.54 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 8.33 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 18490 shares. The stock increased 1.05% to Rs.3,130.25. Volumes stood at 2801 shares in the last session. Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd registered volume of 48.78 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 7.61 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.41 lakh shares. The stock rose 11.95% to Rs.387.00. Volumes stood at 10.28 lakh shares in the last session. Indian Energy Exchange Ltd recorded volume of 6.61 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 3.47 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.91 lakh shares. The stock lost 1.62% to Rs.136.90. Volumes stood at 3.15 lakh shares in the last session. Titagarh Rail Systems Ltd notched up volume of 3.79 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 3.32 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.14 lakh shares. The stock rose 5.36% to Rs.900.80. Volumes stood at 3.1 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PageIndustries_21473837488_12521.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEBI enhances Basic Services Demat Account framework]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sebi-enhances-basic-services-demat-account-framework/1661980</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661980</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In order to enhance the Basic Services Demat Account (BSDA) framework, Securities Exchange Board of India or SEBI has decided to exclude Zero Coupon Zero Principal (ZCZP) bonds and delisted securities from the valuation threshold used to determine BSDA eligibility.

In order to enhance the Basic Services Demat Account (BSDA) framework, Securities Exchange Board of India or SEBI has decided to exclude Zero Coupon Zero Principal (ZCZP) bonds and delisted securities from the valuation threshold used to determine BSDA eligibility. This is likely to improve BSDA facility to make investing simpler for investors and reduce the compliance burden for depository participants (DPs).

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/globe-on-top-of-financial-papers-picture-id184927604_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JK Cement declared preferred bidder for Kishanpura Limestone Block in Rajasthan]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jk-cement-declared-preferred-bidder-for-kishanpura-limestone-block-in-rajasthan/1661979</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661979</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The announcement came after the company participated in the e-auction conducted by the Government of Rajasthan.

The announcement came after the company participated in the e-auction conducted by the Government of Rajasthan. The limestone block, located in Tehsil Deh and Nagaur, District Nagaur, covers an area of 483 hectares and has a G3 level of exploration. The company received the information on 23 December 2025, at around 7:30 PM and the official announcement was made on 24 December 2025, after market hours. JK Cement is one of India’s leading manufacturers of grey cement and one of the leading white cement manufacturers in the world. The company is engaged in the manufacturing and selling of cement and allied products. The company reported a 50.52% tumble in consolidated net profit to Rs 160.53 crore on a 9.94% drop in revenue from operations to Rs 3,019.20 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q1 FY26. On a year-on-year (YoY) basis, the company’s net profit rose 27.6%, while revenue grew 17.9% in Q2 FY26. The counter rose 0.40% to Rs 5,715.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JKCements_26301288730_17136.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR eases further as rising crude oil weighs]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-eases-further-as-rising-crude-oil-weighs/1661978</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661978</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian rupee continued to ease today amid a modest spell of weakness in the local equities and thin activity in world markets.

Indian rupee continued to ease today amid a modest spell of weakness in the local equities and thin activity in world markets. INR has been falling rising near three-week high against the US dollar. Quarter and year end trades saw steady demand for the dollar and INR dropped 14 paise to 89.85 per US dollar. There is a modest pick-up in the WTI Crude oil futures, weighing the INR down despite weakness in the US dollar. The US dollar index trades well under 98 mark today, holding around ten-week low. On the NSE, USD/INR futures are quoting at 89.83, up 0.06% on the day after a firm start as it quoted well above 89.90 mark in the early moves.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/photo-businessman-working-with-generic-design-notebook-onli_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NMDC gains after inking MoU with Colorado School of Mines for mining research]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nmdc-gains-after-inking-mou-with-colorado-school-of-mines-for-mining-research/1661977</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661977</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The agreement primarily outlines the collaborative research, implementation mechanisms, Intellectual property sharing, duration, arbitration, termination and confidentiality provisions.

The agreement primarily outlines the collaborative research, implementation mechanisms, Intellectual property sharing, duration, arbitration, termination and confidentiality provisions. Further, no special rights are agreed between the parties like, right to appoint directors , preferential rights to subscribe to shares in the event of a capital issuance, or rights related to changes in capital structure. The Colorado School of Mines is not related to NMDC’s promoter, promoter group, or group companies and the MoU does not constitute a related party transaction. NMDC is engaged in exploration and production of iron ore along with diamond production and sale of sponge iron and generation and sale of wind power. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 40.2% to Rs 1,698.86 crore on a 29.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 6,378.11 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NMDC_85653440841_12059.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEBI eases procedure for issuing duplicate securities, hikes limit to Rs 10 lakh ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sebi-eases-procedure-for-issuing-duplicate-securities-hikes-limit-to-rs-10-lakh/1661976</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661976</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has simplified the process for issuing duplicate securities certificates.

Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has simplified the process for issuing duplicate securities certificates. In a circular, the market regulator doubled the monetary threshold for the simplified documentation process to Rs 10 lakh from the earlier Rs 5 lakh. Following this, investors whose lost or damaged securities are valued up to Rs 10 lakh will now have to submit fewer documents to get duplicate certificates. SEBI said this is aimed at reducing compliance hassles and removing inconsistencies that existed due to different practices followed by companies and registrar and transfer agents (RTAs).

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty below 26,100 level; media shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-below-26100-level-media-shares-decline/1661974</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661974</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in morning trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with minor losses in morning trade. The Nifty traded below the 26,100 level. Media shares declined after gaining in the previous four trading sessions. At 10:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 197.39 points or 0.23% to 85,211.31. The Nifty 50 index fell 50 points or 0.19% to 26,092.10. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index added 0.19% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index rose 0.09%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,848 shares rose and 1,839 shares fell. A total of 211 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Media index fell 0.28% to 1,415.75. The index rose 1.62% in the past four trading sessions. PVR Inox (down 1.15%), Zee Entertainment Enterprises (down 0.56%), Nazara Technologies (down 0.46%), Sun TV Network (down 0.1%) fell. On the other hand, Network 18 Media & Investments (up 1.15%), D B Corp (up 1.09%) and Tips Music (up 0.52%) edged higher. Stocks in Spotlight: Ola Electric Mobility jumped 3.59% after its subsidiary, Ola Electric Technology, secured incentives worth Rs 366.78 crore under the Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for automobiles and auto components (PLI-Auto) for FY25. Vikran Engineering rose 4.66% after securing an order worth Rs 459.20 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy for the engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) of a 400 MW AC solar power project at Chitrakoot-1 in Uttar Pradesh.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/electronic-screen-of-stock-data-numbers-picture-id175408488_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NBCC (India) jumps on Dubai foray, Mumbai Port redevelopment MoU]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nbcc-india-jumps-on-dubai-foray-mumbai-port-redevelopment-mou/1661973</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661973</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[NBCC said it has entered the international real estate market by commencing overseas operations in Dubai through its wholly owned subsidiary, NBCC Overseas Real Estate LLC.

NBCC said it has entered the international real estate market by commencing overseas operations in Dubai through its wholly owned subsidiary, NBCC Overseas Real Estate LLC. The subsidiary has acquired a prime land parcel measuring 14,776.80 sq ft in Dubai Mainland for AED 15 million, which will be developed as a mixed-use project. Separately, the company received in-principle approval from Mumbai Port Trust to be engaged as the executing agency at an agency charge of 7% of the project cost. The scope of work includes planning, design, execution and supervision of multiple projects such as a CGO Complex, an iconic building, a multi-level car parking facility and an international convention centre, along with maintenance of port infrastructure. In this regard, NBCC has signed a memorandum of understanding with the Mumbai Port Authority on 23 December 2025, for the development of a CGO Complex on 25 acres of Mumbai Port land on a turnkey, deposit-work basis. Under the agreement, NBCC will act as the project management consultant for the proposed development. The company said the MoU has been executed in the normal course of business. NBCC (India) is in business and operates in three major segments, namely project management consultancy, real estate, and engineering procurement & construction. As on September 2025, the Government of India held 61.75% in the company. The company's consolidated net profit advanced 25.21% to Rs 156.68 crore on an 18.99% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,910.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NBCC_1807915630_13166.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Royal Orchid Hotels signs new upscale property in Gwalior]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/royal-orchid-hotels-signs-new-upscale-property-in-gwalior/1661971</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661971</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The hotel will be operated under a management agreement, in line with the group’s asset-light growth strategy.

The hotel will be operated under a management agreement, in line with the group’s asset-light growth strategy. Strategically located near the Gwalior airport, the upcoming Regenta Gwalior will be Royal Orchid & Regenta Hotels’ second property in the city and the third in Madhya Pradesh, further strengthening the chain’s presence in the state. The hotel will be developed in two phases. Phase I will comprise 71 rooms along with multiple banquet and event spaces catering to weddings, corporate meetings, social functions and MICE requirements. Phase II will add 30 more rooms, increasing the overall inventory and reinforcing the property’s position in one of Madhya Pradesh’s growing hospitality markets. The property is owned by Hoshiyar Singh Tomar through Oakwood Hotel and is expected to cater to business travellers, transit passengers and tourists visiting Gwalior’s cultural and historical attractions. Its proximity to the airport, industrial zones and key landmarks such as the Gwalior Fort and prominent city temples is likely to enhance its appeal among both leisure and corporate guests. Chander K. Baljee, chairman & MD, Royal Orchid Hotels, said, “Gwalior is an important cultural and economic centre, witnessing rising demand for quality hospitality. Signing Regenta Gwalior aligns with our commitment to expand in highpotential markets across India. We are confident that this new property will offer exceptional value and become a preferred address for travelers arriving in the region.” Sharing his views on the partnership, Hoshiyar Singh Tomar, Owner, Oakwood Hotel, said, “We are delighted to collaborate with Royal Orchid Hotels to bring the renowned Regenta experience to Gwalior. With its strategic location and thoughtfully planned phases, this property will redefine hospitality standards in the city. We look forward to a successful association and welcoming guests soon.” Royal Orchid Hotels operates and manages hotels/resorts and provides related services through its portfolio of hotel properties. The company’s consolidated net profit dropped 42.9% to Rs 4.28 crore on a 12.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 79.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Royal Orchid Hotels fell 0.48% to Rs 403.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RoyalOrchHotel_11218221105_22048.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Strides Pharma slides as US arm receives 4 USFDA observations for New York facility]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/strides-pharma-slides-as-us-arm-receives-4-usfda-observations-for-new-york-facility/1661972</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661972</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the current Good Manufacturing Practices (cGMP) inspection was conducted by the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) at the facility between 17 December and 23 December 2025.

In an exchange filing, the company said the current Good Manufacturing Practices (cGMP) inspection was conducted by the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) at the facility between 17 December and 23 December 2025. At the conclusion of the inspection, the regulator issued a Form 483 containing four observations. The company clarified that the observations are procedural in nature and are not expected to have any impact on the supply of its commercial products. SPI will submit a comprehensive response to the USFDA within the stipulated timeframe and expressed confidence in addressing all the observations to the regulator’s satisfaction. Strides Pharma further stated that it will keep the stock exchanges informed of any further developments in this matter. The official announcement was made on 24 December 2025, after market hours. Strides Pharma Science is a global pharmaceutical company headquartered in Bangalore, India. It develops and manufactures a wide range of niche and technically complex pharmaceutical products. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 81.98% to Rs 131.52 crore on a 4.62% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,220.83 crore in Q2 Sept 2025 over Q2 Sept 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/StridesPharma_63459406134_16996.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Railway stocks rally ahead of Union Budget 2026 on capex hopes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/railway-stocks-rally-ahead-of-union-budget-2026-on-capex-hopes/1661970</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661970</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rail Vikas Nigam surged 9.16%, while RailTel Corporation of India 6.63%.

Rail Vikas Nigam surged 9.16%, while RailTel Corporation of India 6.63%. Indian Railway Finance Corporation advanced 6.30%. Manufacturing-linked names also gained, with Titagarh Rail Systems rising 4.91% and Texmaco Rail & Engineering up 4.59%. RITES rose 4.26% and Ircon International gained 4.25%. Among other stocks, Jupiter Wagons climbed 2.14%, while Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation advanced 1.66%. Market participants are positioning for higher government capital expenditure on rail infrastructure, rolling stock expansion and network modernisation, a trend that has historically supported railway-linked stocks in the run-up to the Budget. The broader rally reflects expectations that the upcoming Budget will continue to prioritise railways as a key pillar of India’s infrastructure push.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/railway-1136359__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ola Electric rallies after arm secures PLI-Auto incentives worth Rs 367-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ola-electric-rallies-after-arm-secures-pli-auto-incentives-worth-rs-367-cr/1661968</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661968</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company has received a sanction order from the Ministry of Heavy Industries, Government of India.

The company has received a sanction order from the Ministry of Heavy Industries, Government of India. The sanction pertains to the demand incentive for the determined sales value for FY2024-25, and authorises a payment of Rs 366.78 crore to be released through Industrial Finance Corporation of India (IFCI), the designated financial institution for disbursement under the scheme The PLI-Auto Scheme is a flagship initiative of the Government of India aimed at strengthening domestic manufacturing, encouraging advanced automotive technologies, and enhancing India’s global competitiveness in the auto and auto components sector. Ola Electric spokesperson said, “The sanction of Rs 366.78 crore under the PLI-Auto Scheme is a strong endorsement of Ola Electric’s manufacturing capabilities and our commitment to building world-class EV technology in India. This incentive recognises our sustained efforts in scaling domestic production, deepening localisation, and driving innovation across the electric mobility value chain. We remain committed to supporting the Government of India’s vision of making India a global hub for advanced automotive manufacturing and clean mobility.” Ola Electric Mobility is a leading Indian electric vehicle (EV) manufacturer engaged in the integrated development of EV technology and components, including battery cells. Its manufacturing facility, the Ola Futurefactory in Tamil Nadu, produces EVs and key components and is positioned as one of India’s major EV hubs. On a consolidated basis, Ola Electric reported a net loss of Rs 418 crore in Q2 September 2025, compared with a net loss of Rs 495 crore a year earlier. Net sales fell 43.16% YoY to Rs 690 crore in the quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OlaElectricMobilityLtd_81720871_75559.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Supreme Industries bags Rs 54 crore repeat order from BPCL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/supreme-industries-bags-rs-54-crore-repeat-order-from-bpcl/1661969</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661969</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order is for the supply of approximately 2,00,000 composite LPG cylinders of 10 kg capacity.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order is for the supply of approximately 2,00,000 composite LPG cylinders of 10 kg capacity. The contract will be valid for a period of six months from the date of placement of the LoA and may be extended for an additional six months at the sole discretion of BPCL. The company further clarified that neither its promoters nor members of the promoter group have any interest in BPCL. It also stated that the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. Supreme Industries is engaged mainly in the production of plastic products and operates in various product categories like plastic piping systems, cross-laminated films & products, protective packaging products, industrial molded components, molded furniture, storage & material handling products, performance packaging films, and composite LPG cylinders. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 20.3% to Rs 164.74 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 206.60 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 5.3% YoY to Rs 2,393.87 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. The counter shed 0.34% to Rs 3,309.90 on the BSE. Bharat Petroleum Corporation is a public sector company which is engaged in the business of refining crude oil and marketing petroleum products. The company reported a 168.74% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 6,442.53 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 2,397.23 crore posted in Q2 FY25. Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 2.09% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,04,912.47 crore in the September 2025 quarter. The counter shed 0.72% to Rs 363 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SupremeInds_28660861665_541.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikran Engineering gains after bagging Rs 459-cr order from NTPC Renewable Energy]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikran-engineering-gains-after-bagging-rs-459-cr-order-from-ntpc-renewable-energy/1661948</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1661948</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said it has received the award of contract for inland transportation, insurance, installation, testing and commissioning, along with guarantee tests, under the Balance of System (BoS) package for the development of a 400 MW grid-connected solar PV project in Chitrakoot.

In an exchange filing, the company said it has received the award of contract for inland transportation, insurance, installation, testing and commissioning, along with guarantee tests, under the Balance of System (BoS) package for the development of a 400 MW grid-connected solar PV project in Chitrakoot. The total order is valued at Rs 459.20 crore and is to be executed within a period of 12 months. The company also clarified that neither its promoters nor members of the promoter group have any interest in the awarding authority. It added that the transaction does not fall under related-party transactions as per applicable regulatory norms. Rakesh Markhedkar, chairman and managing director, Vikran Engineering, said, “Securing this order from NTPC Renewable Energy is a strong endorsement of Vikran Engineering’s EPC capabilities and execution track record in the renewable energy sector. This project aligns with our strategic focus on expanding our footprint in utility-scale solar infrastructure while contributing meaningfully to India’s clean energy transition.” Vikran Engineering is a diversified EPC player. The company provides end-to-end turnkey solutions spanning conceptualization, design, supply, installation, testing, and commissioning, enabling it to capture the full value chain of project execution. On a standalone basis, net profit of Vikran Engineering rose 339.42% to Rs 9.14 crore while net sales increased 10.71% to Rs 176.29 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VikranEngineeringLtd_15725401_76742.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>