<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:30:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[An undervalued rupee advantageous as it offsets the impact of higher American tariffs on Indian goods: Economic Survey]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/an-undervalued-rupee-advantageous-as-it-offsets-the-impact-of-higher-american-tariffs-on-indian-goods-economic-survey/1668769</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668769</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Economic Survey document noted that the Indian rupee underperformed in 2025.

The Economic Survey document noted that the Indian rupee underperformed in 2025. India runs a trade deficit in goods. Its net trade surplus in services and remittances is not enough to offset it. India depends on foreign capital flows to maintain a healthy balance of payments. When they run drier, rupee stability becomes a casualty, it noted. The rupee’s valuation does not accurately reflect India’s stellar economic fundamentals. In other words, the rupee, therefore, is punching below its weight, the Survey stated as INR holds near record low of around Rs 92 per dollar mark currently. It does not hurt to have an undervalued rupee in these times, as it offsets to some extent the impact of higher American tariffs on Indian goods, and there is no threat of higher inflation from higher-priced crude oil imports now, the Economic survey noted. However, it does cause investors to pause. Meanwhile, the survey further stated that widened BOP deficit, coupled with market uncertainty over the outcome of a trade deal with the US, has exerted pressure on the Indian Rupee, causing it to weaken. Between April 1 and January 22, 2026, the Indian rupee depreciated by approximately 6.5 per cent against the US dollar. However, the movement in the INR has been orderly. Over the medium to long term, exchange rate dynamics are expected to be guided by structural fundamentals, such as productivity gains, export diversification towards higher-value goods and services, deeper integration into GVCs and a stable policy environment rather than short-term fluctuations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper soars to fresh high as break above $6 mark holds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-soars-to-fresh-high-as-break-above-6-mark-holds/1668752</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668752</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures soared above $6 per pound today, rising in tune with the overall metals with fresh mining worries boosting the counter.

COMEX Copper futures soared above $6 per pound today, rising in tune with the overall metals with fresh mining worries boosting the counter. Capstone Copper’s Mantoverde copper and gold mine in northern Chile said on Wednesday it presented a new contract offer to workers in a bid to end a strike that began in early January, after talks over new labor contracts broke down. The counter has zoomed to a fresh high currently trades at $6.29 per pound, up 6.20% on the day. MCX Copper has jumped 8.57% to trade at Rs 1435 per kg. Meanwhile, in equities, Shanghai Composite index rose 0.16% while Hong Kong's Hang Seng index added 0.51%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index edged up slightly. European stocks are mostly supported. The US stocks ended mixed yesterday after US Fed announced its decision to leave rates unchanged following recent reduction in borrowing costs.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR settles near Rs 92/$ mark; selling pressure from foreign funds and risk-off sentiment in global markets weigh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-settles-near-rs-92-mark-selling-pressure-from-foreign-funds-and-risk-off-sentiment-in-global-markets-weigh/1668746</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668746</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee settled near its all-time closing low at 91.99 (provisional) against the US dollar, amid selling pressure from foreign funds and risk-off sentiment in global markets.

The Indian rupee settled near its all-time closing low at 91.99 (provisional) against the US dollar, amid selling pressure from foreign funds and risk-off sentiment in global markets. Rupee hit its all-time intra-day low of 92 against the US dollar amid geopolitical uncertainty and foreign outflows. Moreover, a surge in crude oil prices weighed on the rupee. Nevertheless, dollar weakness helped limit downside in the counter. At the interbank foreign exchange, the rupee opened at 91.95 and touched an early high of 91.82, but pared gains to touch an intra-day low of 92 against the greenback. Benchmark indexes reversed early losses as the Economic Survey's First Advance Estimates put FY26 real GDP growth at 7.4 percent and Gross Value Added (GVA) growth at 7.3 percent, "reaffirming India's status as the fastest-growing major economy for the fourth consecutive year". "India is an oasis of economic performance in the global scenario. The growth numbers stand out in comparison to any other part of the world," Chief Economic Adviser V.A. Anantha Nageswaran said. The benchmark BSE Sensex gained 221.69 points, or 0.27 percent, to end the session at 82,566.37, after having fallen to a low of 81,707.94 earlier. The broader NSE Nifty index dipped to an intraday low of 25,159.80 before reversing course to close up 76.15 points, or 0.30 percent, at 25,418.90 ahead of the ahead of the Union Budget due this weekend.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India’s external sector placed comfortably, Forex reserves cover over 11 months of imports ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-external-sector-placed-comfortably-forex-reserves-cover-over-11-months-of-imports/1668743</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668743</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Economic Survey has stated India’s external sector is placed comfortably in the short run.

Economic Survey has stated India’s external sector is placed comfortably in the short run. Forex reserves cover over 11 months of imports as of 16 January 2026 and approximately 94.0 per cent of the external debt outstanding as of the end of September 2025, offering a comfortable liquidity cushion. The pursuit of a diversified trade strategy, as evidenced by the signing of trade agreements with the UK, Oman, and New Zealand and the EU, and active negotiations with US, bodes well for India’s exports. However, global developments are complicating the outlook in the medium term. A proliferation of immigration controls across countries typically favoured by Indian emigrants may cap the growth in remittances. Global trade is being increasingly influenced by geopolitical alignments and economic statecraft, which in turn may impact India’s exports.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/plant-growing-from-coin-jar-picture-id622446130_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee slumps]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-slumps/1668741</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668741</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 92.1500 per Dollar on Thursday (29 January 2026), versus its previous close of 92.0850 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Swiggy Q3 net loss widens to Rs 1,065 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/swiggy-q3-net-loss-widens-to-rs-1065-cr/1668731</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668731</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Despite the loss, the company recorded strong top-line growth, with revenue from operations rising 53.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,148 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Despite the loss, the company recorded strong top-line growth, with revenue from operations rising 53.96% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 6,148 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Total expenses climbed 48.99% YoY to Rs 7,298 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,898 crore in Q3 FY25. Advertising and sales promotion expenses surged 47.53% YoY to Rs 1,108 crore, while delivery and related charges increased 36.02% YoY to Rs 1,533 crore. Employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 673 crore (up 2.43% YoY) and finance costs climbed 111.53% YoY to Rs 55 crore during the quarter. The company’s pre-tax loss also stood at Rs 1,065 crore in Q3 FY26, against a pre-tax loss of Rs 799 crore in Q3 FY25. Swiggy said its Food Delivery business saw an acceleration in growth, with gross order value (GOV) rising 20.5% year-on-year to Rs 8,959 crore. Monthly transacting users (MTUs) increased 22% YoY to 18.1 million. Adjusted EBITDA margin improved to 3.0% of GOV, up 56 basis points YoY and 22 bps sequentially, the highest in the last two years, reflecting stronger user engagement through new use cases and improved affordability without compromising growth or profitability. Instamart’s GOV more than doubled, rising 103% YoY to Rs 7,938 crore. The company added 34 dark stores during the quarter, taking the total network to 1,136 stores across 131 cities, covering 4.8 million sq ft. Average order value rose 39.7% YoY to Rs 746, driven by traction in the Maxxsaver basket-building proposition and expansion of non-grocery categories. Contribution margin improved to -2.5% sequentially, aided by larger basket sizes, optimisation of customer incentives and operating leverage. Overall, the quick commerce business reported a loss of Rs 908 crore for the quarter, while adjusted EBITDA margin improved to -11.4% from -12.1% in Q2. Sriharsha Majety, MD & Group CEO of Swiggy, said, “the company continues to accelerate user growth and gross order value in food delivery, defying broader concerns of a sector slowdown, while significantly improving operating margins. He said the quick commerce opportunity remains in its early stages, with Swiggy focused on deepening wallet share and expanding differentiated assortments to drive engagement and order values. Majety added that the successful qualified institutional placement has strengthened the balance sheet and provides long-term capital to support sustained investments in growth and innovation, with the company maintaining a disciplined approach to capital allocation as it works towards contribution margin breakeven.” Swiggy is India’s pioneering on-demand convenience platform, catering to millions of consumers each month. Founded in 2014, its mission is to elevate the quality of life for the urban consumer by offering unparalleled convenience, enabled by over 6.9 lakh delivery partners. With an extensive footprint in food delivery, Swiggy Food collaborates with over 2.7 lakh restaurants across 720+ cities. Shares of Swiggy rose 1.17% to end at Rs 327.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SwiggyLtd_23318367_68148.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[An undervalued rupee advantageous as it offsets the impact of higher American tariffs on Indian goods: Economic Survey]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/an-undervalued-rupee-advantageous-as-it-offsets-the-impact-of-higher-american-tariffs-on-indian-goods-economic-survey/1668729</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668729</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Economic Survey document noted that the Indian rupee underperformed in 2025.

The Economic Survey document noted that the Indian rupee underperformed in 2025. India runs a trade deficit in goods. Its net trade surplus in services and remittances is not enough to offset it. India depends on foreign capital flows to maintain a healthy balance of payments. When they run drier, rupee stability becomes a casualty, it noted. The rupee’s valuation does not accurately reflect India’s stellar economic fundamentals. In other words, the rupee, therefore, is punching below its weight, the Survey stated as INR holds near record low of around Rs 92 per dollar mark currently. It does not hurt to have an undervalued rupee in these times, as it offsets to some extent the impact of higher American tariffs on Indian goods, and there is no threat of higher inflation from higher-priced crude oil imports now, the Economic survey noted. However, it does cause investors to pause. Meanwhile, the survey further stated that widened BOP deficit, coupled with market uncertainty over the outcome of a trade deal with the US, has exerted pressure on the Indian Rupee, causing it to weaken. Between April 1 and January 22, 2026, the Indian rupee depreciated by approximately 6.5 per cent against the US dollar. However, the movement in the INR has been orderly. Over the medium to long term, exchange rate dynamics are expected to be guided by structural fundamentals, such as productivity gains, export diversification towards higher-value goods and services, deeper integration into GVCs and a stable policy environment rather than short-term fluctuations.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks grind higher on budget buzz, Nifty reclaims 25,400]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-grind-higher-on-budget-buzz-nifty-reclaims-25400/1668708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668708</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic equity benchmarks closed with modest gains on Thursday, rising for the third straight session, as bargain buying and supportive economic signals helped offset expiry-led volatility.

Domestic equity benchmarks closed with modest gains on Thursday, rising for the third straight session, as bargain buying and supportive economic signals helped offset expiry-led volatility. Both the Sensex and the Nifty bounced back sharply from intraday lows to finish higher on the Sensex monthly F&O expiry day. Sentiment was buoyed by the Economic Survey’s FY27 growth outlook of 6.8%-7.2% and by foreign institutional investors turning buyers on Wednesday after a 15-session selling streak. With investor attention squarely on the Union Budget 2026 due on February 1, the Nifty ended above the 25,400 level, supported by strength in metal and private banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 221.69 points or 0.27% to 82,566.37. The Nifty 50 index added 76.15 points or 0.30% to 25,418.90. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 1.26% while the Nifty rose 1.48%. Larsen & Toubro (up 3.66%), Axis Bank (up 3.32%) and ICICI Bank (up 1.2%) supported the indices today. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 0.10%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.19%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,706 shares rose and 2,533 shares fell. A total of 159 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.14% to 13.37. Economic Survey 2025-2026: The Economic Survey 2025-26, tabled in Parliament on January 29 ahead of the February 1 Union Budget, highlighted both improving macro fundamentals and a clear shift in India’s export strategy as exporters steadily reduce their reliance on the US amid tariff-related uncertainties. The survey noted that while the India-US trade agreement remains under discussion, export data for April to November FY26 show a pivot towards West Asia, Europe, Africa, and parts of Asia to sustain growth. Sectors such as gems and jewelry, marine products, auto components, and textiles saw weaker demand from the US, but this was offset by stronger shipments to alternative markets, while pharmaceuticals remained resilient with healthy growth led by Africa, Latin America and Europe. On the broader economy, the survey said the fiscal deficit has sharply improved from 9.2% of GDP in FY21 to 4.8% in FY25 and is budgeted at 4.4% in FY26, while real GDP growth for FY26 is estimated at a robust 7.4%, driven largely by domestic demand. Looking ahead, the Indian economy is expected to grow 6.8%-7.2% in FY27, supported by strong macro fundamentals and ongoing regulatory reforms, underscoring a combination of internal strength and strategic diversification on the global trade front. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signaling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.01% to 6.702 as compared with the previous close of 6.703. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9800 compared with its close of 91.9975 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 5.29% to Rs 174,650. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.02% to 96.37. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.09% to 4.255. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement rose 1.40 cents or 2.05% to $69.80 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares traded higher, while Asian markets ended higher, as investors digested mixed mega-cap tech earnings on Wall Street and the Federal Reserve’s decision to keep rates unchanged. Investors will be keeping an eye on developments in Indonesia after the benchmark Jakarta Composite dropped over 1% on Wednesday after index provider MSCI had issued a statement warning of a potential downgrade of the country to frontier-market status. Meanwhile, Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 reached a milestone level, hitting 7,000 for the first time, before pulling back as the Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged and upped its economic growth assessment. The broad market index ended the day down 0.01% at 6,978.03. Earlier, the S&P 500 was up 0.3% on the day, hitting an all-time intraday high of 7,002.28. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.02% to close at 49,015.60. The Nasdaq Composite outperformed and gained 0.17%, settling at 23,857.45. Stocks in Spotlight: The Nifty Metal index jumped 3.07% to 12,478.05. The index gained 8.71% in three consecutive trading sessions. Hindustan Copper surged 20%, followed by National Aluminium Company up 5.48% and Tata Steel gaining 4.49%. Jindal Steel & Power rose 4.34%, while Vedanta advanced 4.13%. NMDC climbed 3.79% and Hindalco Industries added 2.89%. Gains were more modest in JSW Steel, which rose 1.93%, Steel Authority of India up 1.19%, and Hindustan Zinc higher by 1.1%. Adani Enterprises edged up 1.07%, while Jindal Stainless ended marginally higher by 0.24%. Larsen & Toubro added 3.66% after the company reported a 17.78% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 2,832.08 crore on 8.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 37,902.84 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Balu Forge Industries surged 10% after the company announced its induction into the NATO supply chain. The company said it has been certified as a supplier of high-precision, mission-critical defence components for NATO member states. The induction allows Balu Forge to manufacture and supply artillery shell bodies and complex forged components for global defence platforms. eClerx Services rose 5.80% after the company posted a strong set of Q3 FY26 numbers and announced a 1:1 bonus issue. On a consolidated basis, net profit increased 40.1% YoY to Rs 191.8 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 137.2 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit after tax rose 4.8% from Rs 183.19 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations grew 25.4% YoY to Rs 1,070.3 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 853.8 crore a year ago. Sequentially, revenue rose about 6.5% QoQ from Rs 1,004.85 crore in Q2 FY26. The company's board has recommended the issue of bonus equity shares in the ratio of 1:1, subject to shareholder approval via postal ballot, a move that further buoyed investor sentiment. Canara Bank declined 4.75%. The Bank reported standalone net profit jumped 25.61% to Rs 5,155.11 crore on a 10.43% increase in total income to Rs 39,880.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Net interest income (NII) rose 1.13% to Rs 9,252 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 9,149 crore in Q3 FY25. SBI Cards and Payment Services fell 1.82%. The company has reported 45% jump in net profit to Rs 557 crore on a 12% increase in total income to Rs 5,353 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Cards-in-force grew by 8% to 2.18 crore as of Q3 FY26 as against 2.02 crore as of Q3 FY25. New accounts volume stood at 864K in Q3 FY26 as compared to 1,175K in Q3 FY25. Heritage Foods tumbled 8.60% after the company reported 20% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 346 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 431 crore in Q3 FY25. Gland Pharma surged 6.75% after the company reported 27.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 261.48 crore on a 22.5% rise in net sales to Rs 1695.36 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. ASK Automotive climbed 3.33% after the company reported an 21.29% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 79.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 18.48% YoY to Rs 1,084.22 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers gained 2.52% after the company reported 74% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 171 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 98 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased to Rs 1,896 crore during the period under review, up 49% YoY.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id51_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vedanta Q3 PAT climbs 61% YoY to Rs 5,710 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vedanta-q3-pat-climbs-61-yoy-to-rs-5710-crore/1668773</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668773</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 36.95% YoY to Rs 23,369 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 36.95% YoY to Rs 23,369 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before exceptional items and tax soared 62.61% YoY to Rs 4,945 crore in Q3 FY26. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 199 crore during the quarter under review. EBITDA jumped 34% to Rs 15,171 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 11,284 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 41% in Q3 FY26, compared with 34% in Q3 FY25. Depreciation and amortisation rose 2% YoY to Rs 2,725 crore. This was lower due to accounting treatment as required under Ind AS 105 following the NCLT demerger order dated 16 December 2025. The YoY increase was primarily due to major capitalisation and higher production at Zinc India. Investment income declined 5% YoY due to a change in the investment mix, but rose 7% quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) owing to higher interest income from income tax refunds. On the balance sheet front, gross debt stood at Rs 80,709 crore as of 31 December 2025, while net debt was Rs 60,624 crore. Net debt-to-EBITDA ratio improved to 1.23x from 1.40x in Q3 FY25. Cash and cash equivalents remained strong at Rs 20,085 crore. The company follows a board-approved investment policy and invests in high-quality debt instruments, including mutual funds, bonds, and bank fixed deposits. Arun Misra, executive director, Vedanta, said, “Q3 FY26 has been a landmark quarter for Vedanta, delivering our highest-ever EBITDA of Rs 15,171 crore, with two of our businesses achieving their best-ever financial results. Aluminium posted its strongest EBITDA margin of $1,268 per ton, supported by record alumina and aluminium production. Zinc India recorded its highest-ever quarterly EBITDA of Rs 6,064 crore, driven by record mined and refined metal output, with silver contributing 44% of overall profit. Zinc International also reported a 28% YoY increase in production, led by Gamsberg achieving its highest-ever recovery. Our Oil & Gas business reached a major milestone with India’s first subsea template installation, while our Thermal Power business delivered 188% YoY EBITDA growth with a 62% increase in sales volumes. The Steel and Ferrochrome Business also achieved record production of steel billets at 285 kt, and ferrochrome output up 32% YoY. Alongside the landmark approval for the demerger into five pure-play entities, these results demonstrate our strong operational momentum and readiness to unlock long-term value as we advance Vedanta’s 2.0 journey”. Ajay Goel, chief financial officer, Vedanta, said, “This has been a remarkable quarter for Vedanta. We delivered our highest-ever quarterly PAT of Rs 7,807 crore, marking a strong 60% YoY growth. Our Q3 revenue stood at a record Rs 45,899 crore, up 19% YoY, while EBITDA reached an all-time high of Rs 15,171 crore, growing 34% YoY. EBITDA margins expanded sharply by 629 bps YoY to 41%. Our balance sheet continues to strengthen, with net debt to EBITDA improving to 1.23x from 1.40x YoY. The reaffirmation of our AA credit rating by CRISIL and ICRA following the NCLT demerger order, along with upgrades in VRL credit rating outlook from Stable to Positive by S&P, Moody’s & Fitch Ratings, underscore the market confidence in Vedanta’s growth trajectory. We are now entering an exciting phase of growth and value unlocking, creating long-term value for all our stakeholders.” Vedanta is a global producer of critical minerals, energy transition metals, power, and technology, with operations across India, South Africa, Namibia, Liberia, the UAE, Saudi Arabia, Korea, Taiwan, and Japan. It is the world’s largest integrated zinc producer, the fourth-largest silver producer, and among the top aluminium producers globally. Vedanta is also India’s only private oil and gas producer and one of the country’s largest private power generators. The counter rallied 3.93% to Rs 766.10 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vedanta_51452572110_502.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gillette India Q3 PAT climbs 37% YoY to Rs 172 cr; declares dividend of Rs 180/share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gillette-india-q3-pat-climbs-37-yoy-to-rs-172-cr-declares-dividend-of-rs-180share/1668707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668707</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[PAT growth was fueled by double-digit revenue expansion and a favorable product pricing mix, reflecting a strong quarterly performance.

PAT growth was fueled by double-digit revenue expansion and a favorable product pricing mix, reflecting a strong quarterly performance. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 232.14 crore in the December quarter, up 38.89% from Rs 167.14 crore reported in the corresponding quarter the previous year. During the quarter, the company's revenue from grooming was at Rs 647.06 crore (up 13.39% YoY), and revenue from oral care stood at Rs 142.94 crore (up 24.39% YoY). Kumar Venkatasubramanian, managing director of Gillette India, said, “We have delivered strong, balanced growth once again this quarter. This performance was enabled by our teams’ commitment to execute our integrated growth strategy. This includes a focused product portfolio of daily use categories, where performance drives brand choice; superiority (of product performance, packaging, brand communication, retail execution, and consumer and customer value); productivity; constructive disruption; and an agile and accountable organization. We remain committed to this strategy, which continues to drive our results, guiding us to deliver sustainable, balanced growth and value creation.” Meanwhile, the board of directors also declared an interim dividend of Rs 180 per equity share, including a one-time special dividend of Rs 60 per share, for FY26. The record date has been fixed as 4 February 2026, and the dividend will be paid on or before 26 February 2026. Gillette India is engaged in the manufacturing and sale of branded packaged fast-moving consumer goods in the grooming, portable power, and oral care businesses. Shares of Gillette India jumped 5.27% to close at Rs 8,275 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GilletteIndia_17228255119_288.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VST Inds Q3 PAT tumbles 56% YoY to Rs 60 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vst-inds-q3-pat-tumbles-56-yoy-to-rs-60-cr/1668693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668693</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) declined 1.71% YoY to Rs 373.45 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) declined 1.71% YoY to Rs 373.45 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Total expenses rose 1.57% YoY to Rs 419.82 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 413.30 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 212.07 crore (down 6.09% YoY), while employee benefits expense increased 2.41% YoY to Rs 36.43 crore during the period under review. Profit before tax tumbled 51.04% YoY to Rs 81.09 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 165.63 crore in the year-ago period. EBITDA jumped 26.47% to Rs 86 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 68 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 23% in Q3 FY26, compared with 18.7% in Q3 FY25. On a nine-month basis, the company’s standalone net profit fell 26.04% YoY to Rs 175.57 crore in 9M FY26, while revenue from operations slipped 3.91% YoY to Rs 1,007.47 crore. Meanwhile, based on the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee, the board approved the appointment of Piyush Srivastava as an additional director and as managing director & chief executive officer of the company, designated as a Key Managerial Personnel, for a period of five years with effect from 2 March 2026. The appointment is subject to shareholders’ approval through a postal ballot, notice of which will be issued in due course. VST Industries manufactures and distributes cigarettes and tobacco products. The counter rose 0.45% to Rs 235.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VSTInds_23522197115_598.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1668671</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668671</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,539, a premium of 120.1 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,418.90 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,539, a premium of 120.1 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,418.90 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index rose 76.15 points or 0.30% to 25,418.90. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was down 1.14% to 13.37. HDFC Bank, Hindustan Zinc and Bharat Electronics were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 222 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,400 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-222-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25400-level/1668669</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668669</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with moderate gains today, rising for the third consecutive session, as bargain hunting lifted sentiment, supported by encouraging economic data and the Economic Survey’s FY27 growth projection of 6.8%–7.2%.

The key equity benchmarks ended with moderate gains today, rising for the third consecutive session, as bargain hunting lifted sentiment, supported by encouraging economic data and the Economic Survey’s FY27 growth projection of 6.8%–7.2%. Going forward, investors will closely track movements in the rupee, the ongoing Q3 earnings season, and developments on the geopolitical front. The Nifty ended above the 25,400 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 221.69 points or 0.27% to 82,566.37. The Nifty 50 index added 76.15 points or 0.30% to 25,418.90. In three consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 1.26% while the Nifty rose 1.48%. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 0.10%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.19%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, fell 1.14% to 13.37. Among the sectoral indices, the Metal index (up 3.07%), the Nifty Private Bank index (up 1.03%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 0.78%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Healthcare index (down 0.96%), the Nifty FMCG index (down 0.91%) and the Nifty Pharma index (down 0.81%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economic Survey 2025-2026: The Economic Survey 2025–26, tabled in Parliament on January 29 ahead of the February 1 Union Budget, highlighted both improving macro fundamentals and a clear shift in India’s export strategy as exporters steadily reduce their reliance on the US amid tariff-related uncertainties. The survey noted that while the India–US trade agreement remains under discussion, export data for April to November FY26 show a pivot towards West Asia, Europe, Africa, and parts of Asia to sustain growth. Sectors such as gems and jewelry, marine products, auto components, and textiles saw weaker demand from the US, but this was offset by stronger shipments to alternative markets, while pharmaceuticals remained resilient with healthy growth led by Africa, Latin America and Europe. On the broader economy, the survey said the fiscal deficit has sharply improved from 9.2% of GDP in FY21 to 4.8% in FY25 and is budgeted at 4.4% in FY26, while real GDP growth for FY26 is estimated at a robust 7.4%, driven largely by domestic demand. Looking ahead, the Indian economy is expected to grow 6.8%–7.2% in FY27, supported by strong macro fundamentals and ongoing regulatory reforms, underscoring a combination of internal strength and strategic diversification on the global trade front. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signaling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.01% to 6.702 as compared with the previous close of 6.703. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9800 compared with its close of 91.9975 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 5.29% to Rs 174,650. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.02% to 96.37. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.09% to 4.255. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement rose 1.40 cents or 2.05% to $69.80 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares mostly traded higher, while Asian markets ended higher, as investors digested mixed mega-cap tech earnings on Wall Street and the Federal Reserve’s decision to keep rates unchanged. Investors will be keeping an eye on developments in Indonesia after the benchmark Jakarta Composite dropped over 1% on Wednesday after index provider MSCI had issued a statement warning of a potential downgrade of the country to frontier-market status. Meanwhile, Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 reached a milestone level, hitting 7,000 for the first time, before pulling back as the Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged and upped its economic growth assessment. The broad market index ended the day down 0.01% at 6,978.03. Earlier, the S&P 500 was up 0.3% on the day, hitting an all-time intraday high of 7,002.28. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.02% to close at 49,015.60. The Nasdaq Composite outperformed and gained 0.17%, settling at 23,857.45.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Coromandel Intl Q3 PAT drops 4% YoY to Rs 488 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/coromandel-intl-q3-pat-drops-4-yoy-to-rs-488-cr/1668668</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668668</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 26.58% to Rs 8,779.15 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 6,935.19 crore in Q3 FY25.

However, revenue from operations rose 26.58% to Rs 8,779.15 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 6,935.19 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 652.76 crore in Q3 FY26, down 4.44% compared with Rs 683.12 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses rose 29.14% to Rs 8,209.88 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 6,357.26 crore in Q3 FY25. Cost of material consumed stood at Rs 4,795.14 core (up 42.70%YoY), finance cost was at Rs 285.88 (up 39.73% YoY) during the period under the review. In Q3 FY26, revenue from the nutrient and other allied business rose 21.89% year on year to Rs 7,761.77 crore and revenue from crop protection segment jumped 72.77% year on year to Rs 1,098.27 crore in Q3 FY26. The company has declared an interim dividend of Rs 9 per equity share (900%) for FY26 on shares with a face value of Re 1 each. The dividend will be paid on or after February 18, 2026, and within 30 days of declaration. The record date for determining eligible shareholders has been fixed as February 4, 2026. Coromandel International is one of India's leading agri solutions provider. It offers a diverse range of products and services across the farming value chain. It specializes in fertilizers, crop protein, bio pesticide, specialty nutrients, organic fertilizers, etc. Shares of Coromandel International rose 0.38% to end at Rs 2,265.40 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CoromandelInter_32712622674_123.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty ends above 25,400 level; metal shares shine]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-ends-above-25400-level-metal-shares-shine/1668666</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668666</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices ended with moderate gains on Thursday, rising for the third consecutive session, as bargain hunting lifted sentiment, supported by encouraging economic data and the Economic Survey’s FY27 growth projection of 6.8%–7.2%.

The key equity indices ended with moderate gains on Thursday, rising for the third consecutive session, as bargain hunting lifted sentiment, supported by encouraging economic data and the Economic Survey’s FY27 growth projection of 6.8%–7.2%. Going forward, investors will closely track movements in the rupee, the ongoing Q3 earnings season, and developments on the geopolitical front. Investors are also awaiting quarterly results from ITC, Tata Motors, and Vedanta, due later today, while attention remains firmly on the Union Budget 2026 to be presented on February 1, 2026. Meanwhile, the Nifty managed to close above the 25,400 mark. Metal, private bank and oil& gas shares advanced while FMCG, pharma and PSU Bank shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 221.69 points or 0.27% to 82,566.37. The Nifty 50 index added 76.15 points or 0.30% to 25,418.90. In the three consecutive trading session, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.26% and 1.48%, respectively. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.10% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.19%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,706 shares rose and 2,531 shares fell. A total of 161 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, declined 1.14% to 13.37. Economic Survey 2025-2026: The Economic Survey 2025–26, tabled in Parliament on January 29 ahead of the February 1 Union Budget, highlighted both improving macro fundamentals and a clear shift in India’s export strategy as exporters steadily reduce their reliance on the US amid tariff-related uncertainties. The survey noted that while the India–US trade agreement remains under discussion, export data for April to November FY26 show a pivot towards West Asia, Europe, Africa and parts of Asia to sustain growth. Sectors such as gems and jewellery, marine products, auto components and textiles saw weaker demand from the US, but this was offset by stronger shipments to alternative markets, while pharmaceuticals remained resilient with healthy growth led by Africa, Latin America and Europe. On the broader economy, the survey said the fiscal deficit has sharply improved from 9.2% of GDP in FY21 to 4.8% in FY25 and is budgeted at 4.4% in FY26, while real GDP growth for FY26 is estimated at a robust 7.4%, driven largely by domestic demand. Looking ahead, the Indian economy is expected to grow 6.8%–7.2% in FY27, supported by strong macro fundamentals and ongoing regulatory reforms, underscoring a combination of internal strength and strategic diversification on the global trade front. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signalling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index jumped 2.96% to 12,465.40. The index gained 8.60% in three consecutive trading sessions. Hinudustan Copper(up 20%), National Aluminium (up 5.48%), Tata Steel (up 4.49%), Jindal Steel (up 4.34%), Vedanta (up 4.13%) and NMDC (up 3.79%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro added 3.58% after the company reported a 17.78% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 2,832.08 crore on 8.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 37,902.84 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Canara Bank declined 4.47%. The Bank eported standalone net profit jumped 25.61% to Rs 5,155.11 crore on a 10.43% increase in total income to Rs 39,880.96 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Net interest income (NII) rose 1.13% to Rs 9,252 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 9,149 crore in Q3 FY25. SBI Cards and Payment Services fell 1.82%. The company has reported 45% jump in net profit to Rs 557 crore on a 12% increase in total income to Rs 5,353 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Cards-in-force grew by 8% to 2.18 crore as of Q3 FY26 as against 2.02 crore as of Q3 FY25. New accounts volume stood at 864K in Q3 FY26 as compared to 1,175K in Q3 FY25. Heritage Foods tumbled 8.87% after the company reported 20% drop in consolidated net profit to Rs 346 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 431 crore in Q3 FY25. Gland Pharma surged 6.75% after the company reported 27.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 261.48 crore on a 22.5% rise in net sales to Rs 1695.36 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. ASK Automotive climbed 3.74% after the company reported an 21.29% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 79.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 18.48% YoY to Rs 1,084.22 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers gained 2.64% after the company reported 74% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 171 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 98 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased to Rs 1,896 crore during the period under review, up 49% YoY. Metro Brands rose 0.87%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 35.36% to Rs 128.02 crore on 15.39% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 811.27 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: European markets mostly traded higher, while Asian markets closed largely in the green, as investors digesting mixed mega-cap tech earnings on Wall Street and the Federal Reserve’s decision to keep rates unchanged. Investors will be keeping an eye on developments in Indonesia after the benchmark Jakarta Composite dropped over 1% on Wednesday after index provider MSCI had issued a statement warning of a potential downgrade of the country to frontier-market status. Meanwhile, Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday, while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 reached a milestone level, hitting 7,000 for the first time, before pulling back as the Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged and upped its economic growth assessment. The broad market index ended the day down 0.01% at 6,978.03. Earlier, the S&P 500 was up 0.3% on the day, hitting an all-time intraday high of 7,002.28. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.02% to close at 49,015.60. The Nasdaq Composite outperformed and gained 0.17%, settling at 23,857.45.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index gains 3.07%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-gains-307/1668662</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668662</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index ended up 3.07% at 12478.05 today.

Nifty Metal index ended up 3.07% at 12478.05 today. The index has gained 13.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Hindustan Copper Ltd rose 20.00%, National Aluminium Company Ltd added 5.59% and Tata Steel Ltd jumped 4.37%. The Nifty Metal index has soared 50.00% over last one year compared to the 9.74% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Energy index gained 1.87% and Nifty Commodities index gained 1.58% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 recorded a gain of 0.30% to close at 25418.9 while the SENSEX increased 0.27% to close at 82566.37 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/entrepreneur-1428452__340_stock_exchange.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IEX Q3 PAT rises 11% YoY to Rs 119 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/iex-q3-pat-rises-11-yoy-to-rs-119-crore/1668664</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668664</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 10.31% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 145.67 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 10.31% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 145.67 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 12.54% YoY to Rs 156.94 crore in Q3 FY26. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit rose 16.36% YoY to Rs 363.14 crore in 9M FY26, while revenue from operations increased 11.72% YoY to Rs 441.34 crore. Meanwhile, the company’s board of directors approved the payment of an interim dividend of Rs 1.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025–26. IEX is India's premier electricity exchange providing a nationwide, automated trading platform for physical delivery of electricity, renewable power, renewable energy certificates and energy-saving certificates. The counter shed 0.97% to Rs 127.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IndianEnergyExchangeLtd_3642743015_70961.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Arkade Developers slips after Q3 PAT slides 20% YoY to Rs 40 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/arkade-developers-slips-after-q3-pat-slides-20-yoy-to-rs-40-cr/1668639</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668639</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations fell 12.42% year-on-year to Rs 196.73 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations fell 12.42% year-on-year to Rs 196.73 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) stood at Rs 53.35 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025, down 19.96% as against Rs 66.65 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Total expenses declined 11.8% to Rs 145.82 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 165.32 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of construction stood at Rs 125.11 crore (down 47.79% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 7.63 crore (up 26.1% YoY) during the period under review. EBITDA stood at Rs 54 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a de-growth of 11.8% YoY. The company maintained a strong balance sheet with net debt of Rs 35 crore as of 31 December 2025, with a low net debt-to-equity ratio of 0.04x. It has a robust project pipeline with an estimated GDV of Rs 11,900 crore across around 4 million sq ft of saleable area. During the quarter, Arkade Developers acquired land parcels worth Rs 535 crore and launched two new verticals—Arkade Finroof and Arkade Assist 360. Amit Jain, chairman and managing director of Arkade Developers, said, “With exceptional pre-sales and collections in the last quarter, a robust project pipeline extending into 2026, and a supportive interest rate environment, we're poised to deliver premium residential developments and create sustained long-term value for all stakeholders. The year 2026 has begun on a positive note, and we remain optimistic about the upcoming budget, which is expected to further support sectoral growth. In the current quarter, we are targeting two additional Occupation Certificates in the Western Suburbs, reinforcing our consistent track record of ahead-of-schedule project completion. Looking ahead, the company has a robust project pipeline with an estimated GDV of Rs 11,900 crore across approximately 4 million sq ft of saleable carpet area. In the coming month, we plan to launch a new project at Bangur Nagar, Goregaon West, marking our eighth project in the Malad–Goregaon belt—a micro-market that continues to witness strong demand and buyer confidence.” Arkade Developers is a real estate development company concentrating on the development of premium aspirational lifestyle residential premises in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India’s commercial capital. The company is engaged in the development of new projects (development/construction of residential premises on land acquired by the company) and redevelopment of existing premises.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ArkadeDevelopersLtd_19074284_91895.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GBP/USD breaks above 1.3800 mark, FTSE100 near two-week high]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gbpusd-breaks-above-13800-mark-ftse100-near-two-week-high/1668627</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668627</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound has been witnessing excellent gains in last few sessions and broke above 1.3800 mark today, holding near four- and half-year highs against the US dollar.

British Pound has been witnessing excellent gains in last few sessions and broke above 1.3800 mark today, holding near four- and half-year highs against the US dollar. The US currency has turned very tepid recently and dollar index dipped near 96 mark after US Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said that the central bank would consider reducing the policy rate after prices declined. GBP/USD pair currently quotes at 1.3813, up marginally on the day. The pair has gained 2.66% this month. On NSE, GBP/INR futures are 127.22, up 0.33% on the day after nearing 127.50 mark earlier in the session. Meanwhile, UK equities are rising impressively with the FTSE100 index up half a percent today to approach two-week high.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pen-on-paper-1240899_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[A B Infrabuild hits the roof after bagging Rs 52-cr project ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/a-b-infrabuild-hits-the-roof-after-bagging-rs-52-cr-project/1668784</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668784</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said the order pertains to the construction of a road over bridge (ROB) featuring a 36.0-metre composite girder, two 24.0-metre composite girders and four 18.75-metre T-beam girders.

In an exchange filing, the company said the order pertains to the construction of a road over bridge (ROB) featuring a 36.0-metre composite girder, two 24.0-metre composite girders and four 18.75-metre T-beam girders. The project will be executed at railway kilometre 649/11–13, in lieu of LC No. 348 at km 649/13–15, between Sompeta and Baruva railway stations on the main line under the Khurda Road Division. The total contract value stands at Rs 51,79,91,303.99 and the project is scheduled to be completed within a period of 24 months. The company further clarified that none of its promoters or members of the promoter group have any interest in the entity awarding the contract. It also stated that the transaction does not qualify as a related-party transaction under applicable regulatory norms. A B Infrabuild is engaged in construction, alter, improve, maintain, enlarge, pull down, remove, replace and develop, work, manage, and roads, railways, branches and sidings, bridges; and other constructions related to civil works. The company’s standalone net profit tumbled 43.6% to Rs 2.11 crore, while revenue from operations declined 21% to Rs 37.30 crore in Q2 FY26 compared to Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ABInfrabuild_38628776_73120.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>