<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:42:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-copper-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1668486</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668486</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ABB India Ltd, Balu Forge Industries Ltd, Moschip Technologies Ltd and Gland Pharma Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 29 January 2026.

ABB India Ltd, Balu Forge Industries Ltd, Moschip Technologies Ltd and Gland Pharma Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 29 January 2026. Hindustan Copper Ltd spiked 16.90% to Rs 739.6 at 11:46 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 124.52 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 45.63 lakh shares in the past one month. ABB India Ltd surged 9.00% to Rs 5500.1. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 40601 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6513 shares in the past one month. Balu Forge Industries Ltd soared 8.55% to Rs 386.5. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 3.25 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.75 lakh shares in the past one month. Moschip Technologies Ltd advanced 8.10% to Rs 202.95. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 6.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.47 lakh shares in the past one month. Gland Pharma Ltd rose 7.18% to Rs 1810. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.68 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 34148 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindCopper_52829551966_3898.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gland Pharma rises after Q3 PAT jumps nearly 28% YoY to Rs 261 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gland-pharma-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-nearly-28-yoy-to-rs-261-crore/1668487</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668487</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from USA aggregated to Rs 868.5 crore (up 19% YoY), Europe revenue added up to Rs 4,071 crore (up 54% YoY) and that from Rest of the world was Rs 300 crore (up 4% YoY).

Revenue from USA aggregated to Rs 868.5 crore (up 19% YoY), Europe revenue added up to Rs 4,071 crore (up 54% YoY) and that from Rest of the world was Rs 300 crore (up 4% YoY). Sales in Canada, Australia and New Zealand were Rs 45.4 crore (down 1% YoY) and those in India were Rs 74.4 crore (up 32% YoY). PBIDT improved by 13.2% to Rs 473.70 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 418.45 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 362.13 crore in Q3 FY26, up by 21.0% from Rs 299.30 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Quarterly R&D investments increased to Rs 65 crore as against Rs 43.7 crore in the previous year. Srinivas Sadu, executive chairman of Gland Pharma, stated, “Our strong Q3 FY26 performance, driven by robust year-on-year revenue growth of 22% and healthy adj. EBITDA margin of 26%, reflects the disciplined execution across our businesses. We remain confident in sustaining this momentum as new product launches, CDMO contract ramp ups, and operational efficiencies continue to strengthen our trajectory.” Shyamakant Giri, chief executive officer of Gland Pharma, said: “Performance of Q3 FY26 was a clear reflection of consistent execution, with double-digit growth across key markets, of US and Europe, and steady improvement in margins. Cenexi’s breakeven and strong revenue traction in the base business were key contributors to our consolidated performance this quarter.” Gland Pharma was established in 1978 in Hyderabad and has grown over the years from a contract manufacturer of small-volume liquid parenteral products to become one of the largest and fastest growing injectable-focused companies, with a global footprint across 60 countries, including the United States, Europe, Canada, Australia, India, and other markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlandPharmaLtd._31222392_14546.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME KRM Ayurveda rings the opening bell like a healing conch]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-krm-ayurveda-rings-the-opening-bell-like-a-healing-conch/1668483</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668483</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 172.10, a premium of 27.48% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 172.10, a premium of 27.48% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently up 2.3% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 180.70 and a low of Rs 165.15. About 29.68 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. KRM Ayurveda's IPO was subscribed 46.98 times. The issue opened for bidding on 21 January 2026 and it closed on 23 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 128 to Rs 135 per equity share. The IPO comprised fresh issue of 57,40,000 equity shares. The promoter and promoter shareholding diluted to 67.28% from 92.16% pre-IPO. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds capital expenditure for construction and development of telemedicine operational facilities, purchase of CRM software & hardware infrastructure, human resources, repayment/prepayment of loan, to meet out the working capital requirements of the company and for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, KRM Ayurveda on 20 January 2026, raised Rs 20.81 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 15.42 lakh shares at Rs 135 per share to 5 anchor investors. KRM Ayurveda operates an expanding network of Ayurvedic hospitals and clinics across India, with six hospitals and five clinics offering integrated healthcare based on traditional Ayurvedic principles and modern quality standards. The company manufactures a wide range of Ayurvedic medicines, herbal remedies, dietary supplements, and wellness and skincare products, while also reaching patients internationally through telemedicine consultations and online sales. Its facilities provide in-patient and out-patient care for chronic conditions, lifestyle disorders, and rehabilitation, supported by Panchakarma therapy units, herbal pharmacies, Ayurvedic diet kitchens, yoga and meditation halls, and consultations with qualified Vaidyas. KRM Ayurveda also runs specialised clinics for orthopaedics, skin and hair care, women’s wellness and geriatric services, along with structured wellness programmes focused on stress management, weight control, preventive healthcare, and personalised diet and lifestyle guidance. As of 31 December 2025, the company had a total of 443 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 48.65 crore and net profit of Rs 8.14 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KRMAyurvedaLtd_25531329_95900.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jio BlackRock Mutual Fund hereby announces a change in Key Personnel. The details of the change are as under:]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jio-blackrock-mutual-fund-hereby-announces-a-change-in-key-personnel-the-details-of-the-change-are-as-under/1668482</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668482</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Jio BlackRock Mutual Fund has announced that Ms.

Jio BlackRock Mutual Fund has announced that Ms. Nomya Mahana and Mr. Vishwanath Raj have been appointed as Research Analysts of Jio BlackRock Asset Management Private Limited (“the AMC”) with effect from January 19, 2026 and January 22, 2026 Details of Ms. Nomya Mahana Age: 24 years Designation: Quantitative Research Analyst, Investments Qualification:• MSc Financial Mathematics from King’s College London • BSc Physics, Mumbai Details of Mr. Vishwanath Raj Age: 27 years Designation: Associate – Research Analyst, Investments Qualification:• B. Tech (Electrical and Electronics) from SRM Institute of Science and Technology

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade lower; consumer durables shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-lower-consumer-durables-shares-decline/1668481</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668481</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices trade with moderate losses amid profit booking and mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment overshadowed optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and positive economic data.

The key equity indices trade with moderate losses amid profit booking and mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment overshadowed optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and positive economic data. Participants are keeping a close watch on the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments. Investors are also awaiting quarterly results from ITC, Tata Motors, and Vedanta, due later today, along with the upcoming Union Budget 2026 scheduled for February 1, 2026. Meanwhile, the Nifty traded below the 25,300 level. Consumer durables shares declined after advancing in the past trading session. At 11:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 238.75 points or 0.29% to 82,108.31. The Nifty 50 index fell 74.70 points or 0.30% to 25,267.90. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.42% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.71%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,425 shares rose and 2,478 shares fell. A total of 185 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.09% to 13.67. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signalling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Consumer Durables index declined 1.74% to 33,575.45. The index advanced 0.64% in the past trading session. Titan Company (down 2.54%), Centruyply (down 2.28%), Amber Enterprises (down 2.15%), Voltas(down 2.03%), PG Electroplast (down 1.40%), Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals (down 1.55%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro added 3.54% after the company reported a 17.78% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 2,832.08 crore on 8.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 37,902.84 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sagility fell 2.79%. The company reported a 23.4% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 267.66 crore on a 35.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,971.15 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Global Markets: Asia market mostly traded lower on Thursday after the U.S. Federal Reserve overnight kept its benchmark rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%. Investors will be keeping an eye on developments in Indonesia after the benchmark Jakarta Composite plunged over 8% on Wednesday after index provider MSCI had issued a statement warning of a potential downgrade of the country to frontier-market status. Meanwhile, Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday, while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 reached a milestone level, hitting 7,000 for the first time, before pulling back as the Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged and upped its economic growth assessment. The broad market index ended the day down 0.01% at 6,978.03. Earlier, the S&P 500 was up 0.3% on the day, hitting an all-time intraday high of 7,002.28. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.02% to close at 49,015.60. The Nasdaq Composite outperformed and gained 0.17%, settling at 23,857.45.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Balu Forge jumps on induction into NATO defence supply chain]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/balu-forge-jumps-on-induction-into-nato-defence-supply-chain/1668480</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668480</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said it has been certified as a supplier of high-precision, mission-critical defence components for NATO member states.

The company said it has been certified as a supplier of high-precision, mission-critical defence components for NATO member states. The induction allows Balu Forge to manufacture and supply artillery shell bodies and complex forged components for global defence platforms. The development expands Balu Forge's defence portfolio into global artillery and advanced ammunition programmes. The company added that NATO onboarding provides long-term revenue visibility and access to high-margin international defence contracts. Balu Forge Industries is a precision engineering company delivering forged and machined components across multiple global industries. The company offers a comprehensive product portfolio, supporting diverse applications in automotive, industrial vehicles, earthmoving equipment, wind energy, aerospace, defence, oil and gas, railways, marine, and agriculture. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Balu Forge Industries rose 35.50% to Rs 65.04 crore while net sales rose 34.38% to Rs 299.51 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BaluForgeIndustriesLtd.._52578716_5893.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aeroflex Inds gains after Q3 PAT rises 8% YoY to Rs 16 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aeroflex-inds-gains-after-q3-pat-rises-8-yoy-to-rs-16-cr/1668475</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668475</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) grew 12.25% YoY to Rs 22.08 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Profit before tax (PBT) grew 12.25% YoY to Rs 22.08 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. EBITDA stood at Rs 28.58 crore, registering the growth 28.34% compared with Rs 22.27 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. EBITDA margin improved 141 bps to 23.59% in Q3 FY26 as against 22.18% in Q3 FY25. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit decreased 8.21% YoY to Rs 37.89 crore in 9M FY26, while revenue from operations rose 11.09% YoY to Rs 316.10 crore. Asad Daud, managing director, Aero Flex Industries, said, “Q3 FY26 was a strong quarter for the Company, with the delivery of its highest-ever quarterly revenue, driven by improved product mix and a growing contribution from value-added solutions. Export performance remained robust despite tariff pressures, with growth of 30% on a YoY basis, reflecting the strength of customer relationships, pricing discipline, and execution capabilities. During the quarter, the Company expanded into the high-growth data centre and AI infrastructure segment, including skid assemblies and advanced flow control components for high-performance liquidcooling applications. The first commercial dispatch during the quarter marks a meaningful step in diversifying the product portfolio and establishes a platform for repeat orders in mission-critical applications. To support demand and scale operations efficiently, the Company is expanding liquid cooling skid assembly capacity to 15,000 units per annum by June 2026 and investing in automation and advanced manufacturing, including robotic welding and a new annealing facility targeted for commissioning by December 2026. These initiatives are expected to enhance throughput, consistency, and margins across both new and existing product lines. With a strong and cash-generative business, deep engineering expertise, and growing exposure to global data centre and AI infrastructure markets, the Company is well positioned to deliver sustainable growth and continue compounding long-term shareholder value.” Aeroflex Industries is primarily engaged in the manufacturing of metallic flexible flow solutions, which are widely used across diverse industries including oil and gas, aerospace, petrochemicals, renewable energy, electric mobility and other critical engineering sectors.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AeroflexIndustries_75745062_34305.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[L&T gains as Q3 PAT climbs 18% YoY to Rs 2,832 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lt-gains-as-q3-pat-climbs-18-yoy-to-rs-2832-cr/1668471</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668471</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, the company’s net profit declined 4.27% year-on-year to Rs 3,215.11 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 10.48% to Rs 71,449.70 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 64,667.78 Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, the company’s net profit declined 4.27% year-on-year to Rs 3,215.11 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations rose 10.48% to Rs 71,449.70 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 64,667.78 Q3 FY25. The company’s consolidated PAT for the quarter includes a one-time Rs 1,191-crore provision (net of tax and non-controlling interest) for employee benefits under the new labour codes, classified as an exceptional item. The company’s revenue growth was driven by consistent execution across the company’s Projects & Manufacturing (P&M) businesses. Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 34.27% YoY to Rs 7,160.98 crore in Q3 December 2025. EBITDA stood at Rs 7,417 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 19% compared with Rs 6,255 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin stood at 10.4% in Q3 FY26 as against 9.7% in Q3 FY25. Larsen & Toubro (L&T) secured orders worth Rs 1,35,581 crore in Q3 FY26, up 17% year-on-year. The order inflow spanned multiple geographies and sectors, including Thermal Power, Hydrocarbons, Renewable Infrastructure, Transmission & Distribution, and Roads & Runways. International orders accounted for Rs 66,848 crore, contributing 49% of the total inflow. As of 31 December 2025, the Group’s consolidated order book reached Rs 7,33,161 crore, up 30% from December 2024, with international orders contributing 49% of the total. In Q3 FY26, Larsen & Toubro reported strong order inflows and mixed revenue performance across its businesses. The Infrastructure Projects segment recorded orders of Rs 61,876 crore (up 26% YoY) with an order book of Rs 4,24,937 crore, and revenues of Rs 33,700 crore (up 5%), supported by international project execution; EBITDA margin improved to 6.1%. Energy Projects secured Rs 46,049 crore in orders (Rs 19% YoY) with an order book of Rs 2,47,861 crore, revenues grew 15% to Rs 12,726 crore, while EBITDA margin declined to 5.9% due to early-stage execution and cost pressures. Hi-Tech Manufacturing posted Rs 2,168 crore in orders (down 74% YoY) and revenues of Rs 3,267 crore (Rs 34%), with EBITDA stable at 18.3%. IT & Technology Services delivered Rs 13,526 crore in revenues (up 12%) with EBITDA at 19.7%, largely driven by international billing. Financial Services reported revenues of Rs 4,477 crore (up 15%) and PBT of Rs 1,021 crore, while Development Projects saw revenues decline 19% to Rs 1,160 crore but EBIT rose to Rs 159 crore. The Others segment grew 55% YoY to Rs 2,594 crore, with EBITDA rising to 32.8%, led by Realty business handovers. On its outlook, the company stated that the Indian economy continues to show resilience, with Q2 GDP growth at 8.2% driven by manufacturing and services. With the RBI’s repo rate cut to 5.25% and easing inflation, FY26 GDP growth is expected around 7.4%. The Union Budget 2026–27 is likely to boost spending on technology, defence, and urban development, while private-sector capital expansion in 2025 provides a strong foundation for sustained growth. Globally, GDP is projected to grow around 3% in 2026. Key markets for the company, including the GCC region, are expected to see robust investments in AI, data centers, and urban infrastructure. The company said it is well-positioned to capitalize on opportunities through geographical expansion, efficient execution across Projects & Manufacturing, cost and cash flow management, and strengthened services businesses, aiming to enhance stakeholder returns. S. N. Subrahmanyan, chairman and managing director (MD), said, “the company posted its highest-ever quarterly order inflow, with the Projects & Manufacturing portfolio exceeding Rs 1 lakh crore for the first time, taking the overall order book past Rs 7 lakh crore. He attributed the growth to sustainable execution, cutting-edge technology, and integration of ESG principles. Looking ahead, he expressed optimism about continued pro-growth momentum, supported by capital expenditure, policy incentives for domestic manufacturing, and the expansion of India’s digital and AI ecosystem, while reaffirming the company’s focus on technology-led growth and long-term stakeholder value.” Larsen & Toubro is an Indian multinational engaged in EPC projects, hi-tech manufacturing, and services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LarsenToubro_5177126969_348.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sagility Q3 PAT rises 23% YoY to Rs 268 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sagility-q3-pat-rises-23-yoy-to-rs-268-cr/1668466</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668466</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company reported profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 371.34 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 289.81 crore a year ago.

The company reported profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 371.34 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 289.81 crore a year ago. The quarter included exceptional items of Rs 32.82 crore due to a one-time impact from India’s new labor codes, effective 21 November 2025, related to long-term employee benefits. In Q3 FY26, adjusted EBITDA stood at Rs 512.5 crore, up 24.2%, compared with Rs 412.7 crore posted in the same quarter last year. Adjusted EBITDA margin stood at 26% in Q3 FY26 as against 28.4% in Q3 FY25. In dollar terms, the company reported revenue of $222 million, while adjusted PAT stood at $36.4 million in Q3 FY26. In constant currency terms, revenue grew 29.1% YoY, while organic growth came in at 19.9% YoY (13.9% in constant currency). As of 31st December 2025, the company had 48,522 employees and operated 35 delivery centers across five countries. Attrition improved to 22.8% in Q3 FY26 as against 21.8% in Q3 FY25. Ramesh Gopalan, managing director and group CEO, said, “Building on the momentum from the first half of the year, our performance in this quarter has been exceptional. The open enrollment period was particularly successful, with strong outcomes across our large payer relationships. The addition of BroadPath expanded our exposure to open-enrollment-driven work and a broader payer client base. This was supported by disciplined and reliable execution. As clients navigate an evolving regulatory and profitability environment, engagements are increasingly shaped by outcome-oriented delivery models with a strong focus on cost reduction. This shift is clearly reflected in our deal pipeline with more complex constructs anchored in outcomes and efficiency commitments on the back of technology and transformation. Our execution excellence and our continued commitment to helping our clients navigate the immediate challenges place us in a strong position. We remain confident in sustaining this momentum through the final quarter.” Abhishek Kayan, deputy chief financial officer, added, “This quarter’s performance reflects our ability to scale rapidly while maintaining financial discipline. We delivered strong revenue growth without compromising margins, driven by operational excellence, robust cost management, and focused execution across the business. This has enabled us to maintain a healthy balance sheet, progressively reduce debt, and preserve financial flexibility. We will continue to allocate capital selectively, prioritizing investments in AI, domain capabilities, and the development of an AI-ready, healthcare-focused workforce, while maintaining a prudent approach to costs. This balance between financial discipline and strategic investment positions us well to sustain growth and margins and strengthen the long-term economics of the business.” Sagility is a global provider of technology-enabled business solutions and services to clients in the U.S. healthcare industry. Shares of Sagility fell 3.13% to Rs 50.07 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SagilityIndiaLtd_90478258_93271.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Max Financial Services Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-max-financial-services-ltd-counter/1668465</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668465</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Max Financial Services Ltd clocked volume of 2.56 lakh shares by 10:46 IST on BSE, a 59.63 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4292 shares

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MaxFinancial_51299011415_372.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HDFC Non-Cyclical Consumer Fund announces change in scheme name]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hdfc-non-cyclical-consumer-fund-announces-change-in-scheme-name/1668463</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668463</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[HDFC Mutual Fund has announced change in scheme name under the following scheme, with effect from 11 March 2026.

HDFC Mutual Fund has announced change in scheme name under the following scheme, with effect from 11 March 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Changes in Scheme Name: Existing Scheme Name Revised Scheme Name HDFC Non-Cyclical Consumer Fund HDFC Consumption Fund

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty slips below 25,250 mark; IT shares under pressure]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-slips-below-25250-mark-it-shares-under-pressure/1668401</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668401</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices trade with major losses amid mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment overshadowed optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and positive economic data.

The key equity indices trade with major losses amid mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment overshadowed optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and positive economic data. Participants are keeping a close watch on the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments. Investors are also awaiting quarterly results from ITC, Tata Motors, and Vedanta, due later today, along with the upcoming Union Budget 2026 scheduled for February 1, 2026. Meanwhile, the Nifty traded below the 25,250 mark. IT shares declined after U.S. Federal Reserve overnight kept its benchmark rate steady at a target range of 3.5% to 3.75%. The index ended its two-day winning streak. At 10:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex declined 492.32 points or 0.60% to 81,852.36. The Nifty 50 index fell 138.70 points or 0.54% to 25,205.40. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.61% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.88%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,296 shares rose and 2,445 shares fell. A total of 212 shares were unchanged. Result Today: ITC (down 0.58%), Tata Motors(down 1.16%), Swiggy(down 0.12%), One 97 Communications (Paytm)(down 0.45%), Canara Bank(up 0.41%), Colgate-Palmolive (India)(down 1.98%), Adani Power(down 0.41%), Dabur India(down 2.36%), Dixon Technologies(India)(down 1.91%), Indian Energy Exchange(IEX)(down 0.93%), Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research(down 1.50%), KPIT Technologies(down 1.83%), Manappuram Finance(up 1.06%), Nippon Life India Asset Management(up 1.19%), NTPC Green Energy(down 0.50%), Prestige Estates Projects(down 0.89%), Vedanta (up 1.49%) and Voltas(down 2.16%) will announce their quarterly earnings today. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signalling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index declined 1.45% to 38,165.25. The index jumped 1.27% in the past two consecutive trading sessions. Persistent Systems (down 1.53%), Oracle Financial Services Software (OFSS) (down 2.61%), Tata Consultancy Service (TCS) (down 2.08%), Mphasis (down 1.79%), Coforge(down 1.77%), LTIMindtree (down 1.55%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Cochin Shipyard rose 0.24%. The company reported an 18.3% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.67 crore on a 17.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,350.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers added 1.23% after the company reported 74% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 171 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 98 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased to Rs 1,896 crore during the period under review, up 49% YoY. Maharashtra Seamless rose 0.53%. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 242.65 crore in Q3 FY26, up 30.41% as against Rs 186.06 crore in Q3 FY25. However, total revenue declined 8.48% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,290.24 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/decreasing-graph-and-arrow-on-red-stock-board-vector-id6066_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IMF says innovation can boost the productivity growth rate by nearly 40%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/imf-says-innovation-can-boost-the-productivity-growth-rate-by-nearly-40/1668400</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668400</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[International Monetary Fund or IMF has stated in a latest update that India’s productivity growth over the past two decades has been impressive, reflecting rapid expansion in high-value services, gradual efficiency-enhancing reforms, and scale advantages from a large domestic market.

International Monetary Fund or IMF has stated in a latest update that India’s productivity growth over the past two decades has been impressive, reflecting rapid expansion in high-value services, gradual efficiency-enhancing reforms, and scale advantages from a large domestic market. That said, additional gains would support the country’s ambitions of becoming an advanced economy. Better supporting innovation, including by removing business barriers, can boost the productivity growth rate by nearly 40 percent, as the fund shows in its 2025 Article IV report. That significant productivity dividend would be like adding the output of the state of Karnataka, the fourth-largest state by output, to India’s economy each decade. IMF noted that domestic business dynamism remains low. The frequency of new business creation and when firms close or exit a market is far lower than in economies such as Korea, Chile, or the United States. Subdued dynamism discourages competition and slows the reallocation of resources toward more productive entities. It stated that Artificial intelligence could reinforce these gains. Nearly 60 percent of Indian firms already use some form of AI—well above global averages. AI can make businesses more efficient, speed up technology diffusion, and strengthen innovation. IMF staff simulations show that AI-driven productivity gains—scaled by AI preparedness and exposure—could raise total factor productivity in emerging Asia (including India) by roughly 0.3 to 3 percentage points over a decade—depending on sectors and scenarios.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-growth-1-1057028_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dollar index stays around 4-year low; Fed holds rates steady ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/dollar-index-stays-around-4-year-low-fed-holds-rates-steady/1668398</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668398</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The dollar index lingered around a four year low under 96 mark on Thursday amid ongoing geopolitical and trade tensions.

The dollar index lingered around a four year low under 96 mark on Thursday amid ongoing geopolitical and trade tensions. The Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged as expected, with Chair Powell signaling the central bank is likely to remain on hold for some time. The Fed noted that economic activity continues to expand at a solid pace, unemployment shows signs of stabilization, and inflation remains somewhat elevated. Th dollar index that measures the greenback against a basket of currencies is quoting at 95.92, down 0.34% on the day. Meanwhile, among basket currencies, EUR/USD surged above $1.20 mark, four and half year high amid dollar weakness. GBP/USD is also hovering around a 4-yer high near $1.38 mark. Meanwhile, USD/JPY continues to stay around three month high near 153 mark amid speculation that Japanese authorities would step in to stem further weakness in the domestic currency.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/dollar-exchange-rate-544949__340_commodities.jpg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Large Cap Fund announces Income Distribution cum capital withdrawal (IDCW)]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-large-cap-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw/1668397</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668397</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 02 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of distribution under the IDCW option of Mirae Asset Large Cap Fund.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 02 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of distribution under the IDCW option of Mirae Asset Large Cap Fund. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: 2.50 Direct Plan – IDCW Option: 5.75

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential MF announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under two schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mf-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-two-schemes/1668375</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668375</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 02 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced 02 February 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) option under the following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit will be: ICICI Prudential Equity - Arbitrage Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.0500 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.0500 ICICI Prudential Multi - Asset Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW: 0.1600 Direct Plan – IDCW: 0.1600

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[FM Nirmala Sitharaman to table Economic Survey 2025-26 in Parliament today]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/fm-nirmala-sitharaman-to-table-economic-survey-2025-26-in-parliament-today/1668373</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668373</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman will table the Economic Survey 2025–26 in Parliament today.

Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman will table the Economic Survey 2025–26 in Parliament today. The document has been prepared by the Finance Ministry’s Department of Economic Affairs under the guidance of the Chief Economic Advisor. The Economic Survey provides a comprehensive review of the country’s current economic situation and future outlook. The Union Budget 2026–27 will be presented on Sunday.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/budget-planning-and-allocating-money-concept-picture-id5081_debt-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Borosil Renewables reports turnaround Q3 numbers ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/borosil-renewables-reports-turnaround-q3-numbers/1668354</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668354</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 8.01% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 390.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 8.01% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 390.46 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Total expenses fell 28.38% YoY to Rs 292.59 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 85.35 crore (down 11.49% YoY), while employee benefit expenses fell 54.84% YoY to Rs 24.18 crore during the period under review. During Q3 FY26, the company reported a profit before exceptional items of Rs 105.59 crore, compared with a pre-tax loss of Rs 32.02 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 16.66 crore in Q3 FY26. On a nine-month basis, the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 40.06 crore in 9M FY26, compared with a net loss of Rs 49.47 crore in 9M FY25, while revenue rose 0.91% YoY to Rs 1,115.91 crore in 9M FY26. Borosil Renewables is engaged in the business of manufacturing of extra clear patterned glass and low iron solar glass for application in photovoltaic panels, flat plate collectors and green houses. The counter slipped 2.08% to Rs 516.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BorosilGlass_61703073247_92.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Garden Reach Shipbuilders rises after strong Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/garden-reach-shipbuilders-rises-after-strong-q3-performance/1668343</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668343</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations increased to Rs 1,896 crore during the period under review, up 49% YoY.

Revenue from operations increased to Rs 1,896 crore during the period under review, up 49% YoY. EBITDA improved by 59% to Rs 234 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 134 crore in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 218 crore in Q3 FY26, up by 63% from Rs 134 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Cmde PR Hari, IN (Retd.), chairman and managing director, Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers, said: "With a strong set of numbers recorded during Q3 FY26, we are well on track to register our best-ever financial performance during the current financial year." "We have delivered five warships so far during the year and are currently executing 10 major shipbuilding projects comprising of 42 platforms. Our other verticals, like Ship Repairs, Portable Steel Bridges and Naval Weapon Systems are also doing well. With the Next Generation Corvette contract on the anvil, we are confident of ending the current financial year with an orderbook of around Rs. 50,000 crore,” the chairman added. Separately, Garden Reach Shipbuilders and Engineers (GRSE) said that it has signed a memorandum of understanding with K2 Cranes & Components for the design, development, and manufacture of marine, defence and shipyard cranes and associated equipment. "While GRSE’s mainstay continues to remain warship building and construction of other marine platforms, it also manufactures engineering products. It holds the largest market share in the country in the modular, steel bridges sector, having delivered over 5,900 of them to both domestic and international clients,” the company said in a statement. It further stated that this collaborative initiative will enable GRSE and K2 Cranes to explore and implement profitable business in respect of cranes utilized for marine, defence and shipyard requirements, both in India and abroad. Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers (GRSE) is a defence public sector undertaking, under the administrative control of Ministry of Defence, and a Schedule ‘A’ Mini Ratna Category-I company. GRSE has built over 800 platforms, including 115 warships for Indian Navy, Indian Coast Guard, and friendly foreign countries. GRSE has also diversified into engineering business with a product profile of pre-fabricated steel bridges, various deck machinery items and assembly, testing & overhauling of marine diesel engines and the manufacture of 30mm naval surface guns.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GardenReachShipbuildersEngineersLtd_23484985591_13229.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Maharashtra Seamless Q3 PAT jumps 30% YoY to Rs 243 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/maharashtra-seamless-q3-pat-jumps-30-yoy-to-rs-243-cr/1668333</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668333</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, total revenue declined 8.48% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,290.24 crore in Q3 FY26.

However, total revenue declined 8.48% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,290.24 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 319.46 crore in Q3 FY26, up 26.89% as against Rs 251.75 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses decreased 16.18% YoY to Rs 967.55 crore. Employee benefits expense rose 8.26% to Rs 33.27 crore, while other expenses were lower by 10.28% at Rs 203.45 crore in Q3 FY26. The company said its board has approved the reappointment of S. P. Raj as Whole-time Director for a period of one year, effective 31 March 2026, subject to shareholders’ approval. It added that Raj is not debarred from holding the office of director under any order of SEBI or any other authority. Maharashtra Seamless manufactures carbon and alloy steel seamless pipes, ERW steel pipes, and casting pipes. The company also operates a windmill. Shares of Maharashtra Seamless rose 0.22% to Rs 515.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MahSeamless_64851063582_2191.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>