<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:39:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Finserv Q3 PAT inches up YoY to Rs 2,229 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-finserv-q3-pat-inches-up-yoy-to-rs-2229-cr/1671468</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671468</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[During the quarter, the company and its subsidiaries accounted for one-time charge of Rs 379 crore towards new labour codes released on 21 November 2025.

During the quarter, the company and its subsidiaries accounted for one-time charge of Rs 379 crore towards new labour codes released on 21 November 2025. Net impact on consolidated profit of BFS is Rs 540 crore for accelerated ECL provision and Rs 167 crore for new labour codes. Profit after tax, before accelerated ECL provision, one-time charge of New Labour Code and jumped 32% YoY to Rs 2,229 crore during the quarter. Bajaj Finserv is the holding company for the various financial services businesses under the Bajaj group. It participates in the financing business through its 51.32% holding in Bajaj Finance Limited (BFL) and in the life, general and health insurance businesses through its 74% holding in two unlisted subsidiaries, Bajaj General Insurance (Bajaj General) and Bajaj Life Insurance (Bajaj Life). BFL holds 86.70% stake in Bajaj Housing Finance (BHFL). Bajaj Finance profit after tax for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 3,978 crore, down 6% YoY. Loan losses and provisions in Q3 FY26 was Rs 3,625 crore during the quarter Loan losses and provisions before the accelerated ECL provision of Rs 1,406 crore was Rs 2,219 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2,043 crore in Q3 FY25, an increase of 9%. Assets Under Management (AUM) as on 31 December 2025 were Rs 484,477 crore compared with Rs 398,043 crore as on 31 December 2024, registering the growth of 22%. Gross non-performing assets (GNNPA) and Net NPA (NNPA) as on 31st December 2025 stood at 1.21% and 0.47% respectively as against 1.12% and 0.48% as on 31st December 2024. Provisioning coverage ratio on stage 3 assets was 61%. Capital adequacy ratio (CRAR) (including Tier-II capital) as on 31st December 2025 stood at 21.45%. The Tier-I capital was at 20.60%. Bajaj Finserv is the holding company for the various financial services businesses under the Bajaj group. It serves millions of customers by providing solutions for asset acquisition through financing, asset protection through general insurance, family and income protection in the form of life and health insurance, and retirement and savings solutions. The counter rose 0.44% to Rs 2021.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajFinservLtd_81833438_28075.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Emami edges higher after Q3 PAT grows 14.5% YoY to Rs 319 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/emami-edges-higher-after-q3-pat-grows-145-yoy-to-rs-319-crore/1671466</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671466</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total expenses for the period under review added up to Rs 767.61 crore, up 8% YoY.

Total expenses for the period under review added up to Rs 767.61 crore, up 8% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 345.05 crore, up by 14.5% from Rs 301.35 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company’s board has declared second interim dividend of Rs 6 per share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the same is 10 February 2026 and the dividend shall be paid on or before 06 March 2026. Emami is one of India’s leading FMCG Companies engaged in manufacturing & marketing of personal care & healthcare products. With over 550 diverse products, Emami’s portfolio includes trusted power brands like Navratna, BoroPlus, Fair & Handsome, Zandu Balm, Mentho Plus and Kesh King.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Emami_73966496059_6423.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[eClerx Services Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eclerx-services-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1671462</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671462</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cartrade Tech Ltd, Latent View Analytics Ltd, Sai Life Sciences Ltd and Triveni Turbine Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 04 February 2026.

Cartrade Tech Ltd, Latent View Analytics Ltd, Sai Life Sciences Ltd and Triveni Turbine Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 04 February 2026. eClerx Services Ltd tumbled 8.91% to Rs 4504.85 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 12371 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 19031 shares in the past one month. Cartrade Tech Ltd crashed 8.56% to Rs 2395.15. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 21950 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 25626 shares in the past one month. Latent View Analytics Ltd lost 7.73% to Rs 434.25. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 73770 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 75613 shares in the past one month. Sai Life Sciences Ltd fell 7.56% to Rs 812.3. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 25976 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 26372 shares in the past one month. Triveni Turbine Ltd plummeted 7.39% to Rs 507.6. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6.54 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.91 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/eClerxServices_24785005718_28293.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Carysil jumps after Q3 PAT spurts 68.6% YoY ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/carysil-jumps-after-q3-pat-spurts-686-yoy/1671463</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671463</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 68.6% YoY to Rs 21.08 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 12.50 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit rose 68.6% YoY to Rs 21.08 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 12.50 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit after tax declined 22.4% QoQ from Rs 27.19 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations stood at Rs 222.57 crore in Q3 FY26, up 9.6% YoY from Rs 203.12 crore in the year-ago quarter. On a quarter-on-quarter basis, revenue declined 7.5% from Rs 240.67 crore in Q2 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 29.40 crore in Q3 FY26, down 19.1% vs Q2 FY26 and up 62% vs Q3 FY25. Total expenses rose 2.84% YoY to Rs 194.65 crore in Q3 FY26. Employee benefits expense stood at Rs 22.18 crore in Q3 FY26, up 7% YoY from Rs 20.73 crore in Q3 FY25. Finance costs came in at Rs 4.74 crore in Q3 FY26, down 17.7% YoY from Rs 5.76 crore in the year-ago quarter. Carysil is engaged in the manufacturing of kitchen products. Its kitchen portfolio includes a wide range of items such as sinks, faucets, water dispensers, and kitchen appliances including hobs, cooktops, ovens, wine chillers, and dishwashers, among others.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Acrysil_97420867649_1200.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold regains momentum amid US–Iran tensions and Fed uncertainty]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-regains-momentum-amid-usiran-tensions-and-fed-uncertainty/1671441</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671441</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices rebounded above $5,100 per ounce in electronic trade on Wednesday, supported by bargain buying and renewed safe-haven demand as escalating US–Iran tensions restored a geopolitical risk premium to bullion markets.

Gold prices rebounded above $5,100 per ounce in electronic trade on Wednesday, supported by bargain buying and renewed safe-haven demand as escalating US–Iran tensions restored a geopolitical risk premium to bullion markets. The metal surged nearly 6% in the previous session, marking its strongest daily gain since 2008, after retreating from last week’s record high. While expectations for aggressive Federal Reserve rate cuts have moderated following President Trump’s nomination of Kevin Warsh as Fed chair, markets continue to price in two cuts later this year and into 2026. In India, MCX April gold futures rose nearly 4% to Rs 1,59,320 per 10 grams, while silver futures climbed close to 6% to Rs 2,83,200 per kg.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[RITES gains after PAT rises to Rs 115 crore in Q3; board OKs interim dividend of Rs 1.9/share]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rites-gains-after-pat-rises-to-rs-115-crore-in-q3-board-oks-interim-dividend-of-rs-19share/1671439</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671439</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total expenses for the period under review added up to Rs 484.07 crore, up 1.8% YoY.

Total expenses for the period under review added up to Rs 484.07 crore, up 1.8% YoY. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 154.05 crore, up by 7% from Rs 144.01 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. The company’s board has declared third interim dividend of Rs 1.90 per share for the financial year 2025-26. RITES is a Navratna Public Sector Enterprise and a leading player in the transport consultancy and engineering sector in India, having diversified services and geographical reach. The company has an experience spanning 50 years and undertaken projects in over 55 countries in Asia, Africa, Latin America, South America, and Middle East region. As on September, the Government of India held 72.20% in the company.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RitesLtd_46602882106_24268.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Timex Group India Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/timex-group-india-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1671438</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671438</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Naksh Precious Metals Ltd, Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, R O Jewels Ltd and Dishman Carbogen Amcis Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 04 February 2026.

Naksh Precious Metals Ltd, Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, R O Jewels Ltd and Dishman Carbogen Amcis Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 04 February 2026. Timex Group India Ltd crashed 9.99% to Rs 275.4 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 10.45 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 3.32 lakh shares in the past one month. Naksh Precious Metals Ltd lost 9.93% to Rs 6.08. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 10890 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 20306 shares in the past one month. Biofil Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals Ltd tumbled 9.89% to Rs 41.17. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 36867 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 17379 shares in the past one month. R O Jewels Ltd plummeted 9.66% to Rs 1.59. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6.44 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 73447 shares in the past one month. Dishman Carbogen Amcis Ltd dropped 8.17% to Rs 209.7. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 32895 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8749 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimexGroup_79144198960_3143.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,800 level; PSU Bank shares advance for 3rd day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25800-level-psu-bank-shares-advance-for-3rd-day/1671429</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671429</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in the mid- afternoon trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with minor gains in the mid- afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,800 level. PSU Bank shares extended gains for third consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 131.44 points or 0.15% to 83,869.86. The Nifty 50 index rose 80.75 points or 0.31% to 25,808.30. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index advanced 0.55% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.50%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,639 shares rose and 1,493 shares fell. A total of 173 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel will start its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday in the backdrop of the growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation, and more recently, the long-awaited India-US trade deal ending prolonged uncertainty on the external front. The decision of the RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Economy: The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Services PMI rose to 58.5 in January from 58.0 in December. The flash score was 59.3. A score above 50.0 indicates expansion. Both output and new orders grew at faster rates in January, and the upturn in the latter was driven by demand buoyancy, new business gains, and tech investment. The growth in sales was attributed to greater client interest in their services and a stronger online presence. New export orders grew at the fastest pace in three months, linked to new business gains from clients in Indonesia, Kenya, Malaysia, Oman, Qatar, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Vietnam. In line with rising new orders, Indian service providers resumed hiring activity in January, though the pace of job creation was only marginal. On the price front, input price inflation accelerated to a 4-month high in January, and selling price inflation was the strongest in three months. Looking ahead, business confidence strengthened amid optimistic forecasts for efficiency gains, marketing efforts, and new client wins. The composite output index rose to 58.4 in January from December's 11-month low of 57.8, indicating that the latest sharp rate of expansion in the Indian private sector was boosted by stronger growth at goods producers as well as service providers. Buzzing Index: The Nifty PSU Bank index added 1.18% to 8,923.40. The index jumped 4.76% in the three consecutive trading session. Bank of Maharashtra (up 2.06%), Bank of Baroda (up 2%), Indian Overseas Bank (up 1.61%), Central Bank of India (up 1.58%), Bank of India (up 1.51%), Union Bank of India (up 1.16%), UCO Bank (up 1.09%), Punjab & Sind Bank (up 0.96%), Indian Bank (up 0.87%) and State Bank of India (up 0.47%) added. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.30% to 6.701 compared with previous session close of 6.721. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.3100 compared with its close of 91.3200 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 3.72% to Rs 159,524. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.03% to 97.41. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.05% to 4.274. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 24 cents or 0.36% to $67.57 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Siyaram Recycling Industries rose 1.28% after the company announced securing two orders aggregating Rs 6.51 crore from The Supreme Industries and Dharma Metalex. Timex Group India hit the lower circuit of 10% after the company’s consolidated net profit tumbled 89.41% to Rs 3.20 crore on 38.12% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 150.78 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concepts-picture-id519261614_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-lloyds-metals-energy-ltd-counter/1671426</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671426</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[BLS International Services Ltd, Sundram Fasteners Ltd, Devyani International Ltd, JBM Auto Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 04 February 2026.

BLS International Services Ltd, Sundram Fasteners Ltd, Devyani International Ltd, JBM Auto Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 04 February 2026. Lloyds Metals & Energy Ltd notched up volume of 46.51 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 12.11 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.84 lakh shares. The stock rose 10.21% to Rs.1,288.00. Volumes stood at 4.18 lakh shares in the last session. BLS International Services Ltd witnessed volume of 197.98 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.44 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 18.97 lakh shares. The stock increased 12.38% to Rs.289.20. Volumes stood at 42.05 lakh shares in the last session. Sundram Fasteners Ltd notched up volume of 4.81 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.34 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 57727 shares. The stock slipped 3.79% to Rs.942.70. Volumes stood at 1.31 lakh shares in the last session. Devyani International Ltd witnessed volume of 196.16 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.39 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 26.55 lakh shares. The stock increased 7.64% to Rs.124.90. Volumes stood at 14.8 lakh shares in the last session. JBM Auto Ltd recorded volume of 38.53 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.05 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 5.47 lakh shares. The stock gained 6.35% to Rs.606.30. Volumes stood at 3.7 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LloydsMetals_76757705405_2629.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siyaram Recycling Ind rises after securing orders worth Rs 7 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siyaram-recycling-ind-rises-after-securing-orders-worth-rs-7-cr/1671374</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671374</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company received an order worth Rs 1.37 crore from The Supreme Industries for the supply of 1,610,560 units of female insert 1/2" CPVC/aqua thread toppers, to be executed within six months.

The company received an order worth Rs 1.37 crore from The Supreme Industries for the supply of 1,610,560 units of female insert 1/2" CPVC/aqua thread toppers, to be executed within six months. Additionally, Siyaram Recycling Industries secured an order valued at Rs 5.14 crore from Dharma Metalex for the supply of brass scrap honey, also scheduled for execution within six months. Siyaram Recycling Industries is primarily engaged in the recycling of brass scrap. On a full-year basis, the company's net profit jumped 93.8% to Rs 14.57 crore on a 23.9% rise in net sales to Rs 511.56 crore in FY25 over FY24.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiyaramRecyclingIndustriesLtd_80297349_92151.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India services sector PMI improves to 58.5 in January]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-services-sector-pmi-improves-to-585-in-january/1671347</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671347</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India's service sector growth rebounded at the start of the year amid quicker rises in new orders and output, final data compiled by S&P Global showed on Tuesday.

India's service sector growth rebounded at the start of the year amid quicker rises in new orders and output, final data compiled by S&P Global showed on Tuesday. The seasonally adjusted HSBC India Services PMI rose to 58.5 in January from 58.0 in December. The flash score was 59.3. A score above 50.0 indicates expansion. Both output and new orders grew at faster rates in January, and the upturn in the latter was driven by demand buoyancy, new business gains, and tech investment. The growth in sales was attributed to greater client interest in their services and a stronger online presence. New export orders grew at the fastest pace in three months, linked to new business gains from clients in Indonesia, Kenya, Malaysia, Oman, Qatar, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Vietnam. In line with rising new orders, Indian service providers resumed hiring activity in January, though the pace of job creation was only marginal. On the price front, input price inflation accelerated to a 4-month high in January, and selling price inflation was the strongest in three months. Looking ahead, business confidence strengthened amid optimistic forecasts for efficiency gains, marketing efforts, and new client wins. The composite output index rose to 58.4 in January from December's 11-month low of 57.8, indicating that the latest sharp rate of expansion in the Indian private sector was boosted by stronger growth at goods producers as well as service providers.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/female-manager-working-on-tablet-in-factory-picture-id52704_commodities.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades above 25,750; broader market outperforms]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-above-25750-broader-market-outperforms/1671326</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671326</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the afternoon trade.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded with minor gains in the afternoon trade. The Nifty traded above the 25,750 mark. Consumer durables, oil & gas, and metal shares advanced, while IT and pharma shares declined. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, added 48.73 points or 0.06% to 83,787.86. The Nifty 50 index rose 37.70 points or 0.15% to 25,764.70. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index advanced 0.26% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.23%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 2,528 shares rose and 1,536 shares fell. A total of 178 shares were unchanged. RBI MPC: The Reserve Bank's rate-setting panel will start its three-day meeting for the next bi-monthly monetary policy on Wednesday in the backdrop of the growth-focused Union Budget, low inflation, and more recently, the long-awaited India-US trade deal ending prolonged uncertainty on the external front. The decision of the RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra-headed six-member Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) will be announced on Friday. Gainers & Losers: Oil & Natural Gas Corporation (up 4.09%), Eternal (up 3.57%), Trent (up 3.31%), Power Grid Corporation of India (up 2.14%) and SBI Life Insurance Company (up 2.05%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Infosys (down 8.10%), Tata Consultancy Services (down 7.12%), Tech Mahindra (down 5.45%), HCL Technologies (down 4.95%) and Wipro (down 4.43%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: Rubicon Research rallied 3.12% after the company’s consolidated net profit climbed 91.2% to Rs 72.79 crore on 51.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 475.52 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Kansai Nerolac Paints tanked 2.52% after its standalone net profit tanked 75.08% to Rs 131.20 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 526.49 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 3.53% to Rs 1,907.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,842.16 crore posted in the same quarter last year. Sheela Foam surged 16.18% after the company’s consolidated net profit soared 211.97% to Rs 52.13 crore on 11.1% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 1,074.43 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ADF Foods surged 6.87% after the company reported 55.7% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 29.2 crore on a 29.5% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 191 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The Anup Engineering dropped 7.40% after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 15.5% year-on-year to Rs 25.53 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 30.21 crore posted in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from operations rose 20.5% YoY to Rs 206.92 crore during the quarter ended 31 December 2025, as against Rs 171.74 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Global Markets: European stocks opened flat to slightly higher on Wednesday amid anticipation of further corporate earnings announcements. Asian markets mostly rose, breaking ranks with Wall Street after a sell-off in U.S. technology stocks weighed on sentiment, while gold extended gains for a second day. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 pulled back as investors dumped technology stocks and moved into shares more broadly linked to improvements in the economy. The broad market index fell 0.84% and closed at 6,917.81. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 166.67 points, or 0.34%, to end at 49,240.99. Earlier, the 30-stock index rose as much as 0.5% to touch 49,653.13, a new record. The Nasdaq Composite shed 1.43%, settling at 23,255.19.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Timex Group hits the floor after Q3 PAT slumps 89% QoQ to Rs 3 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/timex-group-hits-the-floor-after-q3-pat-slumps-89-qoq-to-rs-3-cr/1671311</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671311</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 64.95% and 25.71%, respectively in Q3 FY26.

On year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 64.95% and 25.71%, respectively in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax surged 3.05 times to Rs 8.01 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2.63 crore in Q3 FY25. Exceptional items during the quarter amounted to Rs 3.21 crore and were related to the new labour codes. The company said that Timex emerged as the fastest-growing brand for the company, recording growth at 32%, Guess and Versace continued their upward trajectory with strong double-digit growth and other brands maintained steady growth during the quarter. The e-commerce channel reported high double-digit growth, aided by effective assortment planning, aligned with evolving consumer and category trends, along with strong merchandising. The trade channel also delivered solid growth, reflecting continued retailer confidence and steady consumer demand. Deepak Chhabra, managing director, Timex Group India, said, “This quarter’s performance reflects the consistency of our strategy and execution. The Indian watch industry is witnessing a clear shift towards premium, design-led and lifestyle-driven timepieces, with significant headroom for expansion in a large, underpenetrated market. Through key developments such as the launch of Aston Martin watches in India, continued expansion of our luxury and fashion portfolio, and higher-value collections within Timex, including the Atelier range, we saw positive consumer response during the quarter.” Timex Group India designs, manufactures, and markets innovative timepieces and is part of Timex Group, a privately held company headquartered in Middlebury, Connecticut, with multiple operating units and over 2,000 employees worldwide. In India, TGIL manages a portfolio of brands including Timex, Versace, Guess, Gc, Philipp Plein, Plein Sport, Ferragamo, Nautica, Ted Baker, adidas, and UCB. It retails via more than 5,000 offline trade stores and key online marketplaces, along with over 40 exclusive franchise stores under the Just Watches and Timex World banners.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TimexGroup_79144198960_3143.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bhel gains after receiving LoI from Hindalco]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bhel-gains-after-receiving-loi-from-hindalco/1671310</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671310</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The LOI, received on 3 February 2026, is for the design, engineering, manufacture, supply, installation, commissioning and performance acceptance testing of a 2 x 150 MW boiler-turbine-generator package.

The LOI, received on 3 February 2026, is for the design, engineering, manufacture, supply, installation, commissioning and performance acceptance testing of a 2 x 150 MW boiler-turbine-generator package. The project is part of Hindalco’s Aditya Expansion Project Phase II at its aluminium facility in Lapanga, Sambalpur district of Odisha. The order, awarded through a domestic tender, is valued at approximately Rs 1,200-1,500 crore. Commissioning of the BTG package is scheduled within 35 months for Unit 1 and 37 months for Unit 2 from the effective date of the contract. Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) is an integrated power plant equipment manufacturer, engaged in the design, engineering, manufacturing, erection, testing, commissioning, and servicing of a diverse range of products and systems. The company caters to key sectors of the Indian economy, including power, transmission, industry, transportation, renewable energy, oil & gas, and defence. BHEL is the flagship engineering and manufacturing enterprise of India and is owned and operated by the Government of India. The company's consolidated net profit surged 189.82% to Rs 390.40 crore while revenue from operations rose 16.43% to Rs 8,473.10 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BHEL_16865551712_2306.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yes Bank Ltd gains for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yes-bank-ltd-gains-for-third-consecutive-session/1671279</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671279</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Yes Bank Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

Yes Bank Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 21.59, up 1.31% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25723.35. The Sensex is at 83606.72, down 0.16%. Yes Bank Ltd has slipped around 5.43% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Yes Bank Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 0.15% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60041.3, up 0.16% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 618.26 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 1243.14 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 21.58, up 0.79% on the day. Yes Bank Ltd is up 11.17% in last one year as compared to a 8.55% spurt in NIFTY and a 19.45% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 21.32 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/YesBank_75840425465_25267.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-bank-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1671280</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671280</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

ICICI Bank Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1407.6, up 1.29% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25723.35. The Sensex is at 83606.72, down 0.16%. ICICI Bank Ltd has risen around 2.63% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which ICICI Bank Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 0.15% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60041.3, up 0.16% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 63.93 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 161.25 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1413.8, up 1.45% on the day. ICICI Bank Ltd is up 11.04% in last one year as compared to a 8.55% spurt in NIFTY and a 19.45% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 20.26 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIBank_93786457618_5418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/exide-industries-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1671281</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671281</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Exide Industries Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Exide Industries Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 339.35, up 3.46% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25723.35. The Sensex is at 83606.72, down 0.16%. Exide Industries Ltd has slipped around 7.61% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Exide Industries Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 3.85% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27500.3, up 1.02% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 72.51 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 17.29 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 340.2, up 3.55% on the day. Exide Industries Ltd is down 11.82% in last one year as compared to a 8.55% jump in NIFTY and a 18.13% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 26.3 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ExideInds_97756038201_111.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bharat-forge-ltd-rises-for-third-straight-session/1671282</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671282</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Bharat Forge Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Bharat Forge Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1574.1, up 2.28% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25723.35. The Sensex is at 83606.72, down 0.16%. Bharat Forge Ltd has gained around 6.19% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Bharat Forge Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 3.85% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27500.3, up 1.02% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 7.83 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 10.23 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1575.6, up 2.07% on the day. Bharat Forge Ltd is up 36.1% in last one year as compared to a 8.55% jump in NIFTY and a 18.13% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 54.04 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BharatForge_36016338711_69.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd soars 1.77%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-soars-177-up-for-third-straight-session/1671283</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671283</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 3590.3, up 1.77% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25723.35. The Sensex is at 83606.72, down 0.16%. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd has dropped around 5.28% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd is a constituent, has dropped around 3.85% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27500.3, up 1.02% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 15.02 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 25.99 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 3595.7, up 1.75% on the day. Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd is up 12.95% in last one year as compared to a 8.55% gain in NIFTY and a 18.13% gain in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 31.33 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MM_81551700988_365.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-ltd-up-for-third-straight-session/1671284</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1671284</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 5852.5, up 1.55% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.02% on the day, quoting at 25723.35. The Sensex is at 83606.72, down 0.16%. Hero MotoCorp Ltd has slipped around 2.22% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Auto index of which Hero MotoCorp Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 3.85% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27500.3, up 1.02% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.42 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.69 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 5813.5, up 1.01% on the day. Hero MotoCorp Ltd is up 37.05% in last one year as compared to a 8.55% jump in NIFTY and a 18.13% jump in the Nifty Auto index. The PE of the stock is 24.02 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>