<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:21:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Core industries index grows at 3.7% on year in Dec-25, cement sees excellent spurt]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/core-industries-index-grows-at-37-on-year-in-dec-25-cement-sees-excellent-spurt/1666064</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666064</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India’s eight core infrastructure sectors recorded 3.7% year-on-year growth in December, marking the fastest pace in four months.

India’s eight core infrastructure sectors recorded 3.7% year-on-year growth in December, marking the fastest pace in four months. The production of Cement, Steel, Electricity, Fertilizer and Coal recorded positive growth in December, 2025. The final growth rate of Index of Eight Core Industries for November 2025 was observed at 2.1 per cent. The cumulative growth rate during April to December, 2025-26 is 2.6 per cent (provisional) as compared to the corresponding period of last year. The summary of the Index of Eight Core Industries: Coal - Coal production (weight: 10.33 per cent) increased by 3.6 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index declined by 0.7 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year. Crude Oil - Crude Oil production (weight: 8.98 per cent) declined by 5.6 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index declined by 1.9 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year. Natural Gas - Natural Gas production (weight: 6.88 per cent) declined by 4.4 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index declined by 3.2 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year. Petroleum Refinery Products - Petroleum Refinery production (weight: 28.04 per cent) declined by 1.0 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index increased by 0.1 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year. Fertilizers - Fertilizer production (weight: 2.63 per cent) increased by 4.1 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index increased by 1.7 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year. Steel - Steel production (weight: 17.92 per cent) increased by 6.9 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index increased by 9.5 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year. Cement - Cement production (weight: 5.37 per cent) increased by 13.5 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index increased by 8.8 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year. Electricity - Electricity generation (weight: 19.85 per cent) increased by 5.3 per cent in December, 2025 over December, 2024. Its cumulative index increased by 0.3 per cent during April to December, 2025-26 over corresponding period of the previous year.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-concept-with-oil-rig-in-the-gulf-picture-id597_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SRF Q3 PAT climbs 60% YoY; declares dividend of Rs 5/sh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/srf-q3-pat-climbs-60-yoy-declares-dividend-of-rs-5sh/1666059</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666059</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total revenue from operations rose 6.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 3,712.53 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total revenue from operations rose 6.33% year on year (YoY) to Rs 3,712.53 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 524.91 crore in Q3 FY26, up 42.36% from Rs 368.70 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The company reported exceptional items amounting to Rs 73.24 crore during the quarter. Earnings before interest and tax (EBIT) increased 23% to Rs 653 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 529 crore in the corresponding period last year (CPLY). The Chemicals Business reported a 22% increase in segment revenue to Rs 1,825 crore from Rs 1,496 crore in Q3 FY26 over CPLY. Operating profit for the segment rose 36% YoY to Rs 496 crore in Q3 FY26. During the quarter, the Fluorochemicals Business delivered a record performance, driven by strong refrigerant gas demand, supported by firm global HFC prices, recovering domestic demand, and healthy overseas growth. The Specialty Chemicals Business posted a muted quarterly performance due to aggressive Chinese pricing and deferred offtake by key customers. However, the business continued to strengthen its long-term foundation through an improved product mix, operational efficiencies, robust R&D progress and a strong pipeline of agrochemical and pharmaceutical molecules. The Performance Films & Foil Business reported a 3% decline in segment revenue to Rs 1,342 crore from Rs 1,385 crore in Q3 FY26 over CPLY. However, operating profit increased 5% to Rs 95 crore from Rs 90 crore. The business experienced temporary disruption due to GST 2.0 implementation during the quarter. Domestic demand for BOPET films began recovering, with early signs of price improvement from China. Increased focus on aluminium foil exports and value-added products is expected to support future performance. The Technical Textiles Business reported an 11% decline in segment revenue to Rs 454 crore from Rs 510 crore in Q3 FY26 over CPLY. Operating profit declined 24% to Rs 45 crore from Rs 59 crore, impacted by continued pricing pressure from Chinese imports and lower conveyor belt exports to the United States. The Other Businesses segment recorded a 9% decline in revenue to Rs 92 crore from Rs 101 crore in Q3 FY26 over CPLY. Operating profit increased 8% to Rs 17 crore from Rs 16 crore. During the quarter, coated fabrics witnessed lower volumes due to cheaper Chinese imports, while laminated fabrics continued to face strong pricing pressure following the withdrawal of the Minimum Import Price (MIP). On the capital expenditure front, the board approved the establishment of a new pharma intermediates plant at Dahej, with an estimated investment of Rs 180 crore. As of 31 December 2025, SRF had filed a total of 506 patent applications globally, of which 153 patents have been granted. Meanwhile, the board declared an interim dividend of Rs 5 per equity share on the paid-up equity share capital of the company. The record date for the dividend is Tuesday, 27 January 2026, and the dividend will be paid on or before Tuesday, 17 February 2026. Further, the board approved the reappointment of Kartik Bharat Ram as Joint Managing Director for a further term from 1 June 2026 to 31 March 2031 (both days inclusive), subject to shareholder approval at the forthcoming Annual General Meeting. SRF is a chemical-based, multi-business entity engaged in the manufacturing of industrial and specialty intermediates. Its diversified portfolio includes fluorochemicals, specialty chemicals, packaging films, technical textiles, and coated and laminated fabrics. The counter slipped 2.88% to Rs 2,873.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SRF_56123073213_513.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee at record low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-at-record-low/1666058</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666058</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed lower at 91.0150 per Dollar on Tuesday (20 January 2026), versus its previous close of 90.9600 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[AU SFB Q3 PAT climbs 26% YoY to Rs 668 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/au-sfb-q3-pat-climbs-26-yoy-to-rs-668-crore/1666065</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666065</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25.

Total income increased 15.20% year on year (YoY) to Rs 5,451.26 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 4,731.89 crore in Q3 FY25. The bank’s operating profit before provisions and contingencies stood at Rs 1,215.31 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a marginal growth of 0.86% YoY. Net interest income (NII) rose 16% YoY to Rs 2,341 crore in Q3 FY26. Net interest margin (NIM) improved by 25 basis points quarter on quarter (QoQ) to 5.7%, compared with 5.5% in Q2 FY26. The banks pre-provisioning operating profit (PPoP) grew 3% YoY to Rs 1,235 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,205 crore in Q3 FY25. Total deposits grew 23.3% YoY and 4.5% QoQ to Rs 1,38,415 crore. The CASA ratio remained stable at around 29% as of December 2025, unchanged from September 2025. CASA deposits increased 16% YoY, driven by a 31% growth in current account deposits to Rs 7,404 crore and a 13% rise in savings account deposits to Rs 32,543 crore. On the asset quality front, gross non-performing assets (NPAs) stood at Rs 2,880.54 crore as on 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 2,335.51 crore as on 31 December 2024. Net NPAs were at Rs 1,091.46 crore, up from Rs 905.60 crore a year ago. The gross NPA ratio stood at 2.30% as of 31 December 2025, marginally lower than 2.31% a year earlier, while the net NPA ratio improved to 0.88% from 0.91%. The bank’s average liquidity coverage ratio (LCR) for the quarter stood at 118%, compared with 119% in Q2 FY26. Slippages declined 13% QoQ to Rs 791 crore from Rs 908 crore in the previous quarter. During the quarter, AU SFB added a net 100 touchpoints, including 27 new liability branches, taking the total network to 2,726 touchpoints across 21 states and four Union Territories. The bank caters to over 12.5 million customers and has a workforce of more than 59,000 employees. Sanjay Agarwal, Founder, MD & CEO, AU Small Finance Bank said, “Banking sector growth remained resilient this quarter, supported by GST rationalization and festive demand, even as the deposit environment stayed highly competitive. Against this backdrop, we delivered a strong and well rounded performance in Q3 across growth, margins, asset quality and profitability. We further strengthened our governance by inducting three independent directors to the Board. At the same time, we are accelerating the integration of AI across our core operations and reimagining processes to transition to an AI native architecture—built for scale, resilience and inclusion. With our core growth engines firmly in place, and a once in a generation opportunity to evolve into a universal banking platform, we are well positioned to scale with purpose, responsibility and long term sustainability”. Meanwhile, the board recommended the appointment of Phani Shankar as non-executive independent director (additional director) with effect from 20 January 2026 for a term of three years, subject to shareholder approval. Uttam Tibrewal, Whole-Time Director and Deputy CEO, will complete his current term on 18 April 2026, marking nine years as a Whole-Time Director. In line with RBI’s Small Finance Bank Governance Directions, 2025, he will conclude his term but continue as Deputy CEO and Senior Management Personnel, leading key business verticals including retail assets and liabilities. The board also approved the appointment of Vivek Tripathi, Chief Credit Officer, as Whole-Time Director (Executive Director) for a term of three years, subject to regulatory and shareholder approvals. Additionally, Divya Sehgal, Non-Executive Non-Independent Director, resigned with effect from the close of business hours on 20 January 2026 following the completion of the Fincare SFB integration. Further, Kannan Gopalaraghavan Vellur (V G Kannan), Independent Director, will complete his second term on 21 January 2026 and cease to be a director thereafter. The board placed on record its appreciation for his contributions. AU Small Finance Bank is engaged in providing a range of banking and financial services, including retail banking, wholesale banking, treasury operations, and other services. The counter slipped 1.95% to Rs 1,000.80 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AUSmallFinanceBankLtd_26708448592_34695.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Vikram Solar records five-fold jump in Q3 PAT to Rs 96-cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vikram-solar-records-five-fold-jump-in-q3-pat-to-rs-96-cr/1666057</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666057</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax soared 402.2% to Rs 148.45 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 29.56 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year.

Profit before exceptional items and tax soared 402.2% to Rs 148.45 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 29.56 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Exceptional items during the quarter included labour code charges amounting to Rs 5.61 crore. EBITDA rose sharply to Rs 205 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 142% increase from Rs 85 crore reported in the year-ago period. The EBITDA margin expanded significantly to 19% in Q3 FY26 from 8% in Q3 FY25. Order book stood at 10.6 GW as of 31st December 2025. Domestic operations accounted for 84% of total revenue, while exports contributed the remaining 16%. In Q3 FY26, module sales jumped 35% YoY to 796 MW. Capacity utilization stands at 90% in during the quarter. Gyanesh Chaudhary, chairman & managing director, Vikram Solar, said, “During this quarter, we delivered a resilient and disciplined performance, anchored by strong execution volumes and continued improvements in operating efficiency. Revenues grew 8% yearon-year, reflecting the steady scale-up of our manufacturing operations and our ability to execute consistently in a dynamic market environment. The broader solar industry continues to be firmly positioned for long-term growth, supported by robust demand fundamentals, enabling policy frameworks, and a growing shift toward high-efficiency and technologically advanced solutions. Our order book remains robust at 10.6 GW, providing strong medium-term revenue visibility across utility-scale, C&I, and other customer segments. During the quarter, we successfully commenced operations at our 5 GW Vallam manufacturing facility, which is ramping up as planned and meaningfully strengthens our ability to deliver high-quality, large-scale solutions to both domestic and global customers. In parallel, our Gangaikondan cell and module projects continue to progress in line with our roadmap, reinforcing our focus on backward integration, cost competitiveness, and long-term resilience of the value chain. During the quarter, we successfully transitioned our entire portfolio to high-efficiency N-Type modules, with our HYPERSOL series delivering power outputs of up to 640 Wp. This marks an important step in aligning Indian manufacturing with international standards on efficiency, form factor, and long-term bankability.” Vikram Solar is one of the leading Indian solar module manufacturers, specializing in efficient photovoltaic (PV) module manufacturing, with an international presence across 39 countries. The company is one of the largest PV module manufacturers in India with cumulative production capacity of 9.5 GW. The counter declined 9.71% to settle at Rs 214.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Vikram-Solar-Ltd_64374838_68162.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/INR and GBP/INR futures jump over half a percent ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurinr-and-gbpinr-futures-jump-over-half-a-percent/1666035</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666035</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures ended marginally lower at 90.97.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures ended marginally lower at 90.97. GBP/INR and EUR/INR rose over half a percent to close at 122.66 and 106.56 respectively. JPY/INR ended down 0.13% to end at 57.77.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR slides to record low amid rising geopolitical and tariff tensions]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-slides-to-record-low-amid-rising-geopolitical-and-tariff-tensions/1666034</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666034</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee depreciated 7 paise to close at a record low of 90.97 (provisional) against the US dollar on Tuesday, as strong dollar demand from metal importers and persistent foreign fund outflows dented investor sentiment.

The Indian rupee depreciated 7 paise to close at a record low of 90.97 (provisional) against the US dollar on Tuesday, as strong dollar demand from metal importers and persistent foreign fund outflows dented investor sentiment. The domestic unit slipped to a record low beyond Rs 91 per dollar mark briefly during the day before recovering back below the level. Rising geopolitical uncertainties, including renewed US expansionary signals, have increased risk aversion and kept emerging market currencies under pressure. Moreover, a sluggish domestic stock market triggered by sustained foreign capital outflow further weighed on the local unit. Local shares tumbled on Tuesday, with benchmark indexes Sensex and Nifty falling for a second straight session amid rising geopolitical and tariff tensions. The BSE Sensex slumped 1,065.71 points, or 1.28 percent, to 82,180.47 while the broader NSE Nifty index ended down 353 points, or 1.38 percent, at 25,232.50.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies IPO subscribed 47%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/shadowfax-technologies-ipo-subscribed-47/1666033</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666033</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>IPO Centre</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 4,18,39,800 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (20 January 2026).

Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 4,18,39,800 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 17:00 IST on Tuesday (20 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.47 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 January 2026 and it will close on 22 January 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. The Rs 1,907 crore IPO comprises a fresh issue of 80.6 million equity shares aggregating to Rs 1,000 crore and an offer for sale (OFS) of up to 73.2 million equity shares worth up to Rs 907.27 crore. Existing investors—Flipkart India, Eight Roads Investments Mauritius II, International Finance Corporation, Qualcomm Asia Pacific, Nokia Growth Partners, NewQuest Asia Fund, and Miare Asset—will offload part of their holdings through the OFS. Shadowfax plans to utilize Rs 423.43 crore from the net proceeds of the fresh issue to enhance network infrastructure capacity, Rs 138.64 crore towards lease payments for new first-mile, last-mile, and sort centers, and Rs 88.57 crore for branding, marketing, and communication initiatives. The balance will be used for unidentified inorganic acquisitions and general corporate purposes. Shadowfax Technologies is a leading Indian logistics and 3PL player providing e-commerce, D2C, quick commerce, and hyperlocal delivery services. It operates a nationwide network covering over 14,700 pin codes and serves major clients such as Flipkart, Meesho, Swiggy, Zomato, Blinkit, and Nykaa. The company is among the fastest-growing large-scale logistics providers, with rising market share and strong order growth. Ahead of the IPO of Shadowfax Technologies on 19 January 2026, the company raised Rs 856.02 crore from anchor investors by allotting 6.90 crore shares at Rs 124 each to 39 anchor investors. For the three months ended 30 September 2025, the firm recorded a consolidated net profit of Rs 21.04 crore and sales of Rs 1,805.64 crore.

<strong>Category:</strong> IPO Centre - IPO News<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Persistent Systems Q3 PAT slides 7% QoQ to Rs 439 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/persistent-systems-q3-pat-slides-7-qoq-to-rs-439-cr/1666029</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666029</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 17.82% and 23.38% respectively in Q3 FY26.

On a year on year basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations jumped 17.82% and 23.38% respectively in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items stood at Rs 654.01 crore, up 6.03% QoQ and 35.68% YoY. The exceptional item comprised the impact of new labour code charges amounting to Rs 89.02 crore during the quarter. Excluding the one-time impact of the new labour code charges, EBIT came in at Rs 631.78 crore, registering an 8.2% sequential growth and a 38.6% year-on-year increase. In dollar terms, the company has recorded revenue of $422.5 million (up 4% QoQ). In constant currency terms, the revenue is higher 4.1% sequentially. The order booking for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025, was $674.5 million in Total Contract Value (TCV) and $501.9 million in Annual Contract Value (ACV). Sandeep Kalra, chief executive officer and executive director, Persistent: “We delivered sustained performance, achieving our 23rd sequential quarter of revenue growth with 4.0% quarter-on-quarter and 17.3% year-on-year growth. This was accompanied by an EBIT margin of 16.7%, excluding a one-time impact of 2.3% arising from the New Labour Codes. In line with this performance, we are declaring an interim dividend of Rs 22 per share. Our performance reflects a deeper role in strategic client programs and sustained demand for data, cloud, and digital engineering across our core industries. This momentum is reinforced by our inclusion among India’s Most Valuable Brands by Kantar BrandZ. We are also applying Agentic AI within our own operations, as a ‘customer zero’ to improve productivity and speed adoption at scale, an approach further validated by our recognition as a Microsoft Frontier Firm.” Meanwhile, the company’s board declared an interim dividend of Rs 22 per equity share of face value Rs 5 each for FY26. In addition, to achieve entity rationalization and operational efficiency within the group, the Board of Directors approved the transfer of 100% shareholding in Persistent Systems Germany GmbH and Persistent Systems France S.A.S. from Persistent Systems, India, to Aepona Group, Ireland, subject to the execution of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) in due course. Persistent Systems is a global services and solutions company delivering AI-led, platform-driven digital engineering and enterprise modernization to businesses across industries. Persistent offers a comprehensive suite of services, including software engineering, product development, data and analytics, CX transformation, cloud computing, and intelligent automation. The counter fell 1.56% to settle at Rs 6,335.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PersistentSys_70071143_18286.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty January futures trade at a premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-january-futures-trade-at-a-premium/1666028</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666028</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,268, a premium of 35.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,585.50 in the cash market.

The Nifty January 2026 futures closed at 25,268, a premium of 35.5 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,585.50 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index dropped 353 points or 1.38% to 25,232.50. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 7.63% to 12.73. HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank and Reliance Industries were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The January 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 27 January 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex tanks 1066 pts, Nifty slips below 25,250 amid global trade jitters ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-tanks-1066-pts-nifty-slips-below-25250-amid-global-trade-jitters/1666027</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666027</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Benchmark equity indices closed sharply lower on Tuesday, with the Nifty slipping below the 25,250 level as selling pressure intensified across the board.

Benchmark equity indices closed sharply lower on Tuesday, with the Nifty slipping below the 25,250 level as selling pressure intensified across the board. All NSE sectoral indices ended in the red, with realty stocks leading the declines. Shares came under pressure amid renewed trade tensions between the US and Europe, rising geopolitical risks, and weaker-than-expected Q3 earnings from a few heavyweight companies. Persistent foreign institutional selling, a sharp sell-off in the broader market, and the weekly expiry of Nifty derivatives added to volatility. Investors also remained cautious ahead of a potential US Supreme Court ruling on Trump-era tariffs, as an adverse outcome could materially shift global trade dynamics, even though the timing and verdict remain uncertain. The S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,065.71 points or 1.28% to 82,180.47. The Nifty 50 index dropped 353 points or 1.38% to 25,232.50. Bajaj Finance (down 3.89%), Bajaj Finserv (down 2.85%) and Mahindra & Mahindra (down 2.73%) were major Nifty drags today. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 2.52% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 2.74%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 780 shares rose and 3,503 shares fell. A total of 129 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 7.63% to 12.73. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.04% to 6.681 as compared with the previous close of 6.684. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9675 compared with its close of 90.9000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement jumped 2.25% to Rs 1,48,922. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.88% to 98.33. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 1.37% to 4.291. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement lost 12 cents or 0.19% to $64.01 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 749 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European market declined on Tuesday as the specter of fresh trade tariffs lingers, hurting market sentiment. Asian indices ended lower as a resurgence of trade-war concerns hit risk sentiment and sparked selling in U.S. assets. U.S. President Donald Trump's push to take control of Greenland by threatening additional tariffs—a move that risks fueling trade tensions with Europe—has led to uncertainty in the markets, with investors scurrying for safe-haven assets, including the Swiss franc and gold. The tensions have revived talk of the 'Sell America' trade that emerged in the aftermath of his sweeping "Liberation Day" levies last April, where investors sell U.S. stocks, dollars, and Treasuries. That trade appeared to be gathering momentum in Asian hours on Tuesday. Trump's threats triggered a sharp pushback in Europe, and his remarks have raised questions on the outlook of trade deals struck since then with Europe. All eyes will now be on Davos, where Trump is expected to meet global business leaders on Wednesday, as the U.S. president's presence looms large over the annual gathering of the global elite in Switzerland. Meanwhile, Japan's Nikkei saw some selling as investors looked ahead to next month's election. Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi is seeking voter backing for increased spending, tax cuts, and a new security strategy that is expected to accelerate a defence buildup. U.S. equity markets were closed on Monday for Martin Luther King Jr. Day. Stocks in Spotlight: LTIMindtree dropped 6.67% after the company reported a 30.73% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 970.6 crore despite a 3.72% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q2 September 2025. CEAT declined 4.35%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 60.40% to Rs 155.77 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 97.11 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 25.97% to Rs 4,157.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atishay dropped 9.70% after its standalone net profit slipped 10.90% to Rs 1.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2.11 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 1.51% to Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Oberoi Realty dropped 7.37% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 18.10% to Rs 622.64 crore, despite a 5.77% rise in net sales to Rs 1,492.64 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Tips Music surged 3.10% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 32.63% to Rs 58.65 crore on 21.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 94.28 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Deepak Nitrite gained 4.40%, following a capacity expansion update. The company said its wholly owned subsidiary, Deepak Chem Tech, commissioned a nitration and second hydrogenation plant on 19 January 2026. The facility is located at Dahej in Bharuch district, Gujarat. Total capital expenditure incurred so far is around Rs 85 crore. Ola Electric Mobility fell 8.9% after the electric vehicle maker announced a change in its top finance leadership. In a regulatory filing, the company said Deepak Rastogi has been appointed chief financial officer with effect from 20 January 2026. He succeeds Harish Abichandani, who resigned from the post citing personal reasons, effective at the close of business on 19 January 2026. Hindustan Zinc rose 2.92% after the company’s consolidated net profit after tax rose 46% YoY and 48% QoQ to Rs 3,916 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,678 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 2,649 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue climbed 27% YoY and 28% QoQ to a record Rs 10,980 crore in Q3 FY26, led by higher commodity prices, increased production, and a stronger dollar. Jindal Saw surged 3.74% after the company reported a 69.85% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 257.99 crore on 16.77% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 4,943.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a Year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations declined 49.06% and 6.22% respectively in Q3 FY26. Tata Capital shed 0.46%. The company’s consolidated net profit (attributable to owners) jumped 16.85% to Rs 1,256.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,075.57 crore in Q3 FY26. The company's consolidated interest income increased 10% to Rs 7,242 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 6,585 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations rallied 12.27% year on year (YoY) to Rs 7,975.44 crore in Q3 FY26. Rajoo Engineers advanced 1.48% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 79.04% to Rs 16.83 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 9.40 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 56.21% YoY to Rs 87.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Senores Pharmaceuticals shed 2.90%. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 2.22% to Rs 31.66 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 32.38 crore in Q2 FY26. However, total revenue from operations rallied 7.91% to Rs 174.56 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Bansal Wire Industries declined 5.10%. The company reported 3.81% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 43.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 41.68 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 11.29% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,029.02 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 4,13,35,800 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 16:27 IST on Tuesday (20 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.46 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers ends with significant losses; Nifty settles below 25,250 marks]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-ends-with-significant-losses-nifty-settles-below-25250-marks/1666026</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666026</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today amid the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

The domestic equity benchmarks ended with major losses today amid the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. The Nifty settled below the 25,250 mark after hitting an intraday high of 25,585 in early trade. Investors tracked the ongoing Q3 earnings season and developments from the World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex tumbled 1,065.71 points or 1.28% to 82,180.47. The Nifty 50 index dropped 353 points or 1.38% to 25,232.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 2.52% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 2.74%. The market breadth was weak. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 7.63% to 12.73. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Bank index (down 0.81%), the Nifty Private Bank index (down 0.96%) and the Nifty Financial Services (down 1.16%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Realty index (down 5.04%), Nifty Chemicals index (down 2.85%) and the Nifty Consumer Durables index (down 2.80%) and the underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was down 0.04% to 6.681 as compared with the previous close of 6.684. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.9675 compared with its close of 90.9000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement jumped 2.25% to Rs 1,48,922. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.88% to 98.33. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 1.37% to 4.291. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement lost 12 cents or 0.19% to $64.01 a barrel. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 729 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European markets traded lower on Tuesday as the specter of fresh trade tariffs lingers, hurting market sentiment. Asian markets ended lower as a resurgence of trade-war concerns hit risk sentiment and sparked selling in U.S. assets. U.S. President Donald Trump's push to take control of Greenland by threatening additional tariffs, a move that risks fueling trade tensions with Europe—has led to uncertainty in the markets, with investors scurrying for safe-haven assets, including the Swiss franc and gold. The tensions have revived talk of the 'Sell America' trade that emerged in the aftermath of his sweeping "Liberation Day" levies last April, where investors sell U.S. stocks, dollars, and Treasuries. That trade appeared to be gathering momentum in Asian hours on Tuesday. Trump's threats triggered a sharp pushback in Europe, and his remarks have raised questions on the outlook of trade deals struck since then with Europe. All eyes will now be on Davos, where Trump is expected to meet global business leaders on Wednesday, as the U.S. president's presence looms large over the annual gathering of the global elite in Switzerland. Meanwhile, Japan's Nikkei saw some selling as investors looked ahead to next month's election. Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi is seeking voter backing for increased spending, tax cuts, and a new security strategy that is expected to accelerate a defence buildup. U.S. cash equity markets were closed on Monday for Martin Luther King Jr. Day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index falls 5.04%, NIFTY Tumbles 1.38% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-falls-504-nifty-tumbles-138/1666020</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666020</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index ended down 5.04% at 793.9 today.

Nifty Realty index ended down 5.04% at 793.9 today. The index has slipped 10.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Sobha Ltd shed 8.61%, Oberoi Realty Ltd dropped 7.92% and Lodha Developers Ltd fell 6.20%. The Nifty Realty index has fallen 16.00% over last one year compared to the 8.09% increase in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Auto index has dropped 2.48% and Nifty Energy index has dropped 2.22% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 has slid 1.38% to close at 25232.5 while the SENSEX has dropped 1.28% to close at 82180.47 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 1,066 pts lower; Nifty ends below 25,250 ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-1066-pts-lower-nifty-ends-below-25250/1666019</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666019</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers ended with sharp losses today amid the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE.

The key equity barometers ended with sharp losses today amid the expiry of F&O contracts on the NSE. The Nifty settled below the 25,250 mark after hitting an intraday high of 25,585 in early trade. Investors tracked the ongoing Q3 earnings season and developments from the World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos. All the sectoral indices in the NSE traded in the red, with realty, consumer durables, and auto shares losing the most. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 1,065.71 points or 1.28% to 82,180.47. The Nifty 50 index lost 353 points or 1.38% to 25,232.50. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 2.52% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 2.74%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 782 shares rose and 3,498 shares fell. A total of 122 shares were unchanged. World Economic Forum: UAE Minister of Economy and Tourism Abdulla bin Touq Al Marri on Tuesday (January 20) agreed during a meeting with Andhra Pradesh Chief Minister N Chandrababu Naidu to set up a food cluster in the state. Despite concerns over India’s lack of an “AI trade,” Investcorp Chief Executive Rishi Kapoor dismissed fears that the country risks falling behind in the global artificial intelligence race, instead describing the technological shift as a massive opportunity for India to emerge as a global business conduit. Amid developments related to Greenland-linked tariffs and his Gaza Peace Board proposal, US President Donald Trump is scheduled to address the World Economic Forum (WEF) 2026 on January 21. IPO Update: The initial public offer (IPO) of Shadowfax Technologies received bids for 3,78,59,040 shares as against 8,90,88,807 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:30 IST on Tuesday (20 January 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.42 times. The issue opened for bidding on Tuesday (20 January 2026) and it will close on Thursday (22 January 2026). The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 118 and 124 per share. An investor can bid for a minimum of 120 equity shares and in multiples thereof. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index fell 5.04% to 793.90. The index dropped 4.1% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Sobha (down 10.59%), Oberoi Realty (down 7.68%), Lodha Developers (down 6.32%), Godrej Properties (down 5.95%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 5.83%), DLF (down 4.96%), Anant Raj (down 4.6%), Phoenix Mills (down 3.39%), Brigade Enterprises (down 2.6%) and SignatureGlobal India (down 0.68%) tumbled. Stocks in Spotlight: LTIMindtree dropped 6.67% after the company reported a 30.73% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 970.6 crore despite a 3.72% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 10,781 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q2 September 2025. Ceat declined 4.35%. The company’s consolidated net profit jumped 60.40% to Rs 155.77 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 97.11 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 25.97% to Rs 4,157.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Atishay dropped 9.70% after its standalone net profit slipped 10.90% to Rs 1.88 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 2.11 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 1.51% to Rs 15.45 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 15.22 crore in Q3 FY25. Oberoi Realty dropped 7.37% after the company’s consolidated net profit fell 18.10% to Rs 622.64 crore, despite a 5.77% rise in net sales to Rs 1,492.64 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Tips Music surged 3.10% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 32.63% to Rs 58.65 crore on 21.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 94.28 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Jindal Saw surged 3.74% after the company reported a 69.85% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 257.99 crore on 16.77% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 4,943.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a Year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit and revenue from operations declined 49.06% and 6.22% respectively in Q3 FY26. Tata Capital shed 0.51%. The company’s consolidated net profit (attributable to owners) jumped 16.85% to Rs 1,256.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,075.57 crore in Q3 FY26. The company's consolidated interest income increased 10% to Rs 7,242 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 6,585 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations rallied 12.27% year on year (YoY) to Rs 7,975.44 crore in Q3 FY26. Rajoo Engineers advanced 1.48% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 79.04% to Rs 16.83 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 9.40 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 56.21% YoY to Rs 87.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Senores Pharmaceuticals shed 0.81%. The company’s consolidated net profit fell 2.22% to Rs 31.66 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 32.38 crore in Q2 FY26. However, total revenue from operations rallied 7.91% to Rs 174.56 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Bansal Wire Industries declined 5.10%. The company reported 3.81% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 43.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 41.68 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 11.29% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 1,029.02 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025. Hindustan Zinc rose 2.92% after the company’s consolidated Net profit after tax rose 46% YoY and 48% QoQ to Rs 3,916 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,678 crore in Q3 FY25 and Rs 2,649 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue climbed 27% YoY and 28% QoQ to a record Rs 10,980 crore in Q3 FY26, led by higher commodity prices, increased production, and a stronger dollar. Global Markets: The US Dow Jones index futures is currently down by 810 points, signaling a weak opening for US stocks today. European markets traded lower on Tuesday as the specter of fresh trade tariffs lingers, hurting market sentiment. Asian stocks ended lower as a resurgence of trade-war concerns hit risk sentiment and sparked selling in U.S. assets. U.S. President Donald Trump's push to take control of Greenland by threatening additional tariffs—a move that risks fueling trade tensions with Europe—has led to uncertainty in the markets, with investors scurrying for safe-haven assets, including the Swiss franc and gold. The tensions have revived talk of the 'Sell America' trade that emerged in the aftermath of his sweeping "Liberation Day" levies last April, where investors sell U.S. stocks, dollars, and Treasuries. That trade appeared to be gathering momentum in Asian hours on Tuesday. Trump's threats triggered a sharp pushback in Europe, and his remarks have raised questions on the outlook of trade deals struck since then with Europe. All eyes will now be on Davos, where Trump is expected to meet global business leaders on Wednesday, as the U.S. president's presence looms large over the annual gathering of the global elite in Switzerland. Meanwhile, Japan's Nikkei saw some selling as investors looked ahead to next month's election. Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi is seeking voter backing for increased spending, tax cuts, and a new security strategy that is expected to accelerate a defence buildup. U.S. cash equity markets were closed on Monday for Martin Luther King Jr. Day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gujarat Gas slumps as Q3 PAT slides 5% QoQ to Rs 266 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gujarat-gas-slumps-as-q3-pat-slides-5-qoq-to-rs-266-cr/1666012</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666012</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a standalone basis, Gujarat Gas’ net profit fell 5.49% to Rs 265.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 281.01 crore in Q2 FY26.

On a standalone basis, Gujarat Gas’ net profit fell 5.49% to Rs 265.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 281.01 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations declined 2.86% to Rs 3,865.11 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. PBT tanked 5.27% to Rs 357.98 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the company's consolidated net profit jumped 19.83% while revenue from operations tanked 10.78% in Q3 FY26. PBT rallied 19.23% YoY. EBITDA stood at Rs 502 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 439 crore in Q3 FY25, reflecting a 14% increase. CNG volumes hit a record high of 3.45 mmscmd in Q3 FY26, up 11% from 3.12 mmscmd in Q3 FY25. PNG (domestic) volumes stood at 0.83 mmscmd in Q3 FY26, while PNG (commercial) volumes were at 0.17 mmscmd, compared with 0.74 mmscmd and 0.15 mmscmd, respectively, in Q3 FY25, reflecting growth of 11% and 8%. On the infrastructure front, GGL is aggressively expanding under the FDODO model and has signed 78 FDODO agreements with various dealers to accelerate growth. During Q2 FY26, one FDODO CNG station became operational in Jamnagar, with several more stations expected to commence operations in the near term. The CNG segment continued to see strong momentum, with volumes rising 11% quarter-on-quarter, supported by a network of 833 CNG stations. During Q3 FY26, the company added over 38,600 new domestic customers and now supplies natural gas to more than 23.83 lakh households. GGL’s cumulative pipeline network stood at 44,540 inch-km. Gujarat Gas is the largest City Gas Distribution Company in India. The company has a successful track record of providing uninterrupted services to households for over 3 decades through a network of 44,540+ kms of gas pipeline, distributing approx. 8.37 mmscmd of natural k gas in Q3 FY 26. The company operates 833 CNG stations and provides natura l gas to more than 23.83 lakh households in six states and one union territory.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GujaratGas_6190462003_43934.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ITC Hotels Q3 PAT rise 9% YoY to Rs 235 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/itc-hotels-q3-pat-rise-9-yoy-to-rs-235-cr/1666001</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1666001</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 411.13 crore in Q3 FY26, up 39.84% from Rs 293.98 crore reported in Q3 FY25.

Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 411.13 crore in Q3 FY26, up 39.84% from Rs 293.98 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The company reported exceptional loss amounting to Rs 84 crore during the quarter. Total expenses for the period under review aggregated to Rs 870.02 crore, up 17.50% year on year (YoY). On the segmental front, revenue from Hotels division was Rs 1,132.51 crore (up 13.76% YoY) and Other revenue was Rs 12.88 crore (up 13.98% YoY) in the Dec’25 quarter. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 32.65% YoY to Rs 501 crore, while revenue increased 15.46% YoY to Rs 2,885.70 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. ITC Hotels is an Indian hospitality company that operates and manages hotels. It has over 100 hotels and is India's third largest hotel chain. It has a franchise agreement to operate most of its hotels as part of The Luxury Collection of Marriott International. It was a subsidiary of ITC Limited until its demerger in 2025. ITC Hotels Limited, formerly a subsidiary of ITC Limited, is a leading Indian hospitality company known for its luxury accommodations and commitment to sustainable practices, operating over 140 hotels across 90+ destinations under brands like ITC Hotels, Mementos, Storii, Welcomhotel, Fortune, and WelcomHeritage. The counter slipped 2.86% to Rs 179.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ITCHotelsLtd_20685940_91836.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Newgen Software skid after Q3 PAT drops 23% QoQ to Rs 63-cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/newgen-software-skid-after-q3-pat-drops-23-qoq-to-rs-63-cr/1665990</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665990</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 29.43% while revenue from operations jumped 5.03% in Q3 FY26.

On a year on year (YoY) basis, the company’s consolidated net profit declined 29.43% while revenue from operations jumped 5.03% in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 115.15 crore in Q3 FY26, up 9.32% QoQ and 7.99% YoY. Exceptional item included labour code charges amounting to Rs 35.09 crore in Q3 FY26. Excluding the impact of labour code charges, profit stood at Rs 90 crore, with PAT margin of 22.5% during the quarter. Annuity revenue streams, comprising ATS/AMC, support services, and cloud/SaaS and subscription licenses, stood at Rs 250 crore. Subscription revenue amounted to Rs 134 crore, recording a 29% year-on-year growth in Q3, while the SaaS component grew 48% year-on-year during the quarter. Diwakar Nigam, chairman & managing director, Newgen Software Technologies, said, ““Our nine months performance showcases our strong business momentum. Subscription-led growth remains robust with strong contributions from the US, UK, and Australia, validating our geographic expansion strategy. We onboarded 34 new logos during the nine - month period, reinforcing the trust and preference global enterprises place in our platform. We also maintained margin strength through targeted productivity initiatives during this period.” Virender Jeet, CEO, Newgen Software, said, “Our leadership in Insurance is deepening steadily, with our Policy Administration System (PAS) offering helping us secure a strong foothold in this high-value vertical. Meanwhile, our AI-driven solutions are gaining global traction—most notably through early deployments, establishing us as a credible player in applied AI for mission-critical use cases. We are particularly excited about our next-generation, AI-led products, which are expected to significantly enhance productivity, design intelligence, and automation." Newgen Software Technologies is a global software company and is engaged in the business of software product development, including designing and delivering end-to-end software solutions covering the entire spectrum of software services from workflow automation to document management to imaging

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewgenSoftwareTechnologiesLtd_46602882106_13722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rajoo Engineers gains as Q3 PAT climbs 79% YoY to Rs 17 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rajoo-engineers-gains-as-q3-pat-climbs-79-yoy-to-rs-17-cr/1665988</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665988</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 56.21% YoY to Rs 87.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 56.21% YoY to Rs 87.59 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company’s total expenses spiked 47.97% YoY to Rs 68.72 crore during the quarter. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 59.78 crore (up 423% YoY) and employee benefit expenses stood at Rs 8.77 crore (up 51.99% YoY) during the period under review. Profit before tax stood at Rs 21.31 crore in Q3 FY26, up 84.66% as against Rs 11.54 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Rajoo Engineers is engaged in manufacturing and selling a reputed brand of plastic processing machinery and post-extrusion equipment. The company caters to both international and domestic markets.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RajooEngineers_6307734512_4163.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India Launches Responsible Nations Index, ranks 16th in the list of 154 nations]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-launches-responsible-nations-index-ranks-16th-in-the-list-of-154-nations/1665989</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665989</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India today launched the Responsible Nations Index (RNI) at the Dr.

India today launched the Responsible Nations Index (RNI) at the Dr. Ambedkar International Centre, New Delhi, under the aegis of the World Intellectual Foundation (WIF). The Index introduces a comprehensive global framework for assessing nations on parameters such as ethical governance, social well-being, environmental stewardship, and global responsibility, going beyond conventional indicators of power and economic prosperity. India ranked 16 in the list of 154 nations. Singapore topped the ranking.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-background-design-picture-id511195524_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold surges past $4,750; Eyes on US inflation data]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-surges-past-4750-eyes-on-us-inflation-data/1665987</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1665987</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices staged a powerful rally in early European trade on Tuesday, with futures vaulting more than 3% to trade near 4,750 dollars per ounce, carving out a new all-time high as investors sought refuge amid intensifying US–EU trade frictions.

Gold prices staged a powerful rally in early European trade on Tuesday, with futures vaulting more than 3% to trade near 4,750 dollars per ounce, carving out a new all-time high as investors sought refuge amid intensifying US–EU trade frictions. Sentiment was unsettled by President Donald Trump’s renewed bid to acquire Greenland and the threat of additional tariffs on multiple European nations, prompting markets to brace for potential retaliatory measures. The strength in international markets was mirrored domestically, with MCX February gold futures racing to a fresh lifetime high of 152,500 rupees per 10 grams, registering gains of nearly 2.5%. A softer US dollar added further momentum, as the dollar index slipped below 99 on fading confidence in US assets, while attention now turns to the delayed US PCE inflation data later this week for signals on the Federal Reserve’s future policy trajectory.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>