<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:51:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[WTI Crude oil hovers around $62 per barrel]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/wti-crude-oil-hovers-around-62-per-barrel/1670957</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670957</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures dipped below $62 per barrel in Asia electronic trading on Tuesday, extending the sharpest decline in months as easing geopolitical concerns eased the risk premium in energy markets.

WTI crude oil futures dipped below $62 per barrel in Asia electronic trading on Tuesday, extending the sharpest decline in months as easing geopolitical concerns eased the risk premium in energy markets. Prices were pressured after the US and Iran agreed to resume talks this Friday to restore diplomacy and reduce regional conflict risks, helping calm supply-disruption fears. Further weighing on sentiment, OPEC+ confirmed plans to keep production steady in March, reinforcing ample supply conditions even as seasonal demand remains soft. Meanwhile, a US-India trade announcement — including lower tariffs and shifts in oil buying patterns — added to market uncertainty. Prices edge up a bit on supportive equities and the counter currently trades at $62.27 per barrel, up marginally on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-at-sunset-picture-id515924876_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee makes a gaint leap]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-makes-a-gaint-leap/1670956</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670956</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 90.3675 per Dollar on Tuesday (03 February 2026), versus its previous close of 91.6500 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[COMEX Copper bounces from one-month low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/comex-copper-bounces-from-one-month-low/1670939</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670939</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures saw an excellent recovery from one-month low as supportive equities boosted the metal.

COMEX Copper futures saw an excellent recovery from one-month low as supportive equities boosted the metal. The commodity currently trades at $6.01 per pound, up 3.10% on the day. A steep drop was seen in the last session but gains in US equities had curbed losses in intraday moves. Meanwhile, risk appetite was stable today. In Asia, Shanghai Composite index added 1.29% after heavy collapse in last session. Hong Kong's Hang Seng index edged up 0.22%. Japanese Nikkei 225 index spiked around 4% to record high. European stocks spiked as German DAX surged more than 1%, The US stocks gained on Monday. The major averages all moved to the upside on the day following mixed outing in last week as supportive economic cues boosted sentiments. The Dow soared 1.1%.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-chart-picture-id497754124_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/INR futures slide nearly 2% under 107 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurinr-futures-slide-nearly-2-under-107-mark/1670913</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670913</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USDINR futures fell 1.43% to end at 90.34.

On the NSE, USDINR futures fell 1.43% to end at 90.34. GBP/INR also slipped by 1.6% to close for the day at 123.58. Meanwhile, EUR/INR and JPY/INR fell by close to 2% to settle at 106.73 and 58.15 respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Ent sizzles after Q3 profit spikes 97x to Rs 5,627 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-ent-sizzles-after-q3-profit-spikes-97x-to-rs-5627-cr/1670915</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670915</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax surged 125.84% YoY to Rs 1,299.84 crore during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional items and tax surged 125.84% YoY to Rs 1,299.84 crore during the quarter. Exceptional items amounting to Rs 5,632.09 crore were recognised in the quarter ended December 31, 2025, primarily due to Adani Commodities LLP (ACLLP) divesting its entire 20% stake in Adani Wilmar (AWL)—selling 13% to Lenee Pte Ltd under a share purchase agreement with the parent company and the remaining 7% through open market transactions. Consequently, the Group recorded an exceptional gain of Rs 5,632.09 crore (post-tax gain of Rs 4,661.11 crore), and AWL ceased to be an associate of the parent company. EBITDA climbed 15% to Rs 4297 crore during the quarter, compared with Rs 3723 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from ANIL Ecosystem increased 7% YoY to Rs 3,161 crore during the quarter. Module sales jumped 12% to 997 MW in Q3 FY26 compared with 893 MW in Q3 FY25. Wind turbine generator (WTG) deliveries increased 38% to 66 units in Q3 FY26. compared with 48 units in Q3 FY25. Total income from airports jumped 28% YoY to Rs 3,770 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 2,939 crore in Q3 FY25. Cargo volumes also grew 12% to 3.1 lakh metric tonnes in Q3 FY26 compared with 2.7 lakh metric tonnes a year earlier. In the mining services segment, dispatches rose to 10.7 MMT in Q3 FY26, up 9% from 11.8 MMT in Q3 FY2 while In the IRM segment, volumes declined to 11.2 MMT in Q3 FY26, down 7% from 2.1 MMT in Q3 FY25. Gautam Adani, Chairman of the Adani Group, said, “With resilient execution and a clear strategic focus, Adani Enterprises has delivered a robust operating performance in the first nine months of FY26, reflecting the strength of our incubator model and the depth of our diversified infrastructure portfolio. The commencement of operations at the Navi Mumbai International Airport represents a landmark achievement, reinforcing our commitment to building nationally critical assets at scale and speed. Our continued progress across airports, renewable manufacturing, data centres and transport infrastructure, alongside strong capital market support through our successful rights issue and NCD offerings, positions us well to accelerate the next phase of growth. As India advances towards becoming a $5 trillion economy, AEL remains steadfast in its mission to incubate globally competitive businesses that combine economic value creation with sustainability, technological leadership and longterm national impact.” Adani Enterprises (AEL) is the flagship company of Adani Group, one of India's largest business conglomerates. The company's business investments are centered on the fields of airport management, technology parks, roads, data centers, and water infrastructure.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniEnterp_85164503493_4244.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bulls take charge as India-US pact unlocks a market sprint, Nifty ends above 25,700]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bulls-take-charge-as-india-us-pact-unlocks-a-market-sprint-nifty-ends-above-25700/1670912</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670912</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended sharply higher on Tuesday, rising for a second straight session on strong buying interest.

The key equity benchmarks ended sharply higher on Tuesday, rising for a second straight session on strong buying interest. Sentiment improved after India and the United States announced a long-awaited trade deal, easing tariff worries that had clouded markets for months. Supportive global cues and softer crude oil prices added to the momentum. The Nifty closed above the 25,700 mark. All NSE sectoral indices finished in positive territory, led by realty, pharma and consumer durables stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 2,072.67 points or 2.54% to 83,739.13. The Nifty 50 index added 639.15 points or 2.55% to 25,727.55. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.74% while the Nifty gained 3.63%. Adani Ports & SEZ (up 9.19%), Bajaj Finance (up 6.67%) and Reliance Industries (up 3.42%) boosted the indices today. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 2.79% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.91%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,304 shares rose and 981 shares fell. A total of 151 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 6.99% to 12.90. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.69% to 6.722 compared with previous session close of 6.769. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2500 compared with its close of 91.4950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 5.73% to Rs 152,235. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 97.58. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.21% to 4.287. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell 19 cents or 0.29% to $66.11 a barrel. Global Markets: European stocks advanced on Tuesday as global markets settled following a short-lived sell-off in cryptocurrencies and precious metals. Asian indices ended higher after the U.S. and India trade deal, sparking a sharp risk-on move across the region. Japan's Nikkei 225 jumped nearly 4%, and the Topix rose over 3.3%. South Korea’s Kospi surged about 6.84%, triggering a buy-side trading curb. U.S. stocks climbed overnight as Wall Street kicked off the new month on a positive note, with investors looking past recent volatility in silver and bitcoin and turning their focus to the upcoming earnings slate. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.05%, the S&P 500 gained 0.54%, and the Nasdaq Composite added 0.56%. Markets are also tracking key economic signals and cues from the Federal Reserve on interest rates, even as efforts continue in Washington to avert a partial government shutdown. Data releases have been disrupted, with the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics postponing the January jobs report and other labour data until federal operations resume. Stocks in Spotlight: One Mobikwik Systems surged 20% after the company reported a profitable December quarter, driven by strong execution across its payments and financial services businesses and sharp operating discipline. On a consolidated basis, Mobikwik posted a net profit of Rs 4.05 crore in Q3 December 2025, reversing a loss of Rs 55.28 crore in Q3 December 2024 and a loss of Rs 28.62 crore in Q2 September 2025. Total income rose 8.29% YoY and 6.40% QoQ to Rs 297.22 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Ather Energy surged 11.47% after the company delivered its strongest-ever quarter performance, with robust growth in market share and revenue alongside a sharp narrowing of EBITDA losses. On a standalone basis, the company reported a net loss of Rs 84.60 crore in Q3 December 2025, narrowing sharply from a loss of Rs 197.80 crore in Q3 December 2024 and lower than the Rs 154.10 crore loss in Q2 September 2025. For the quarter ended December 2025, Ather Energy reported total income of Rs 995.7 crore, up 53% YoY, driven by robust volume growth and a rising contribution of non-vehicle revenue, including software subscriptions, charging, accessories, spares, and service, which rose to 14% of revenue. Adjusted Gross Margin (AGM) reached Rs 251.3 crore in Q3 FY26, up 111% YoY, while AGM excluding incentives improved to 23%, up 1,100 bps YoY. This was driven by Ather’s value engineering capabilities and the ability to command strong premiums, reflecting a continued focus on healthier unit economics and structurally stronger margins. Aditya Birla Capital rose 3.71% after the company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Aditya Birla Housing Finance, has secured Rs 2,750 crore in growth capital from an affiliate of Advent International. Following completion, Aditya Birla Capital will hold about 85.7% stake in the housing finance arm, while Advent will own around 14.3%. Adani Ports & Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) surged 9.12% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 21.16% to Rs 3,053.61 crore on 21.86% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 9,704.59 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Bajaj Auto advanced 1.07% after the company reported 25% increase in total auto sales for January 2026, selling 4.77 lakh units as against 3.81 lakh units sold in January 2025. Bajaj Housing Finance rose 1.62% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 21.32% to Rs 664.89 crore on a 17.8% increase in total income to Rs 2,886.04 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Maruti Suzuki India added 2.73% after the company’s total production increased 9.33% to 226,146 units in January 2026, compared with 206,851 units produced in January 2025. Bharat Wire Ropes rallied 5.71% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 22.58% to Rs 18.24 crore despite an 11.75% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 142.81 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. SMC Global Securities rose 2.94% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 47.82% to Rs 30.54 crore on a 12.06% rise in total income to Rs 495.53 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. City Union Bank surged 5.59% after reporting a standalone net profit of Rs 332.16 crore, up 16.14% YoY, on the back of a 17.22% rise in total income to Rs 2,001.03 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. Transrail Lighting rallied 10.10% after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 17.7% to Rs 109.74 crore on a 32.6% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,777.19 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Seats jumped 6.07% after the company’s standalone net profit spiked 30.43% to Rs 9.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 7.59 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rallied 60.25% to Rs 491 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 306.39 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Zydus Wellness slipped 2.76% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 39.9 crore in Q3 FY26 as against a net profit of Rs 6.4 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Net sales more than doubled to Rs 963.3 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 450.8 crore in the same period last year. HFCL added 2.85% after the company reported 41.04% jump in consolidated to Rs 102.37 crore on a 19.65% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,210.79 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Thermax jumped 4.19% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 76.16% to Rs 204.18 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 115.90 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations grew 4.19% to Rs 2,634.68 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR surges to 3-week high on US-India trade deal]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-surges-to-3-week-high-on-us-india-trade-deal/1670911</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670911</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee surged to a three-week high and climbed over 1% on Tuesday, emerging as the best-performing Asian currency.

The Indian rupee surged to a three-week high and climbed over 1% on Tuesday, emerging as the best-performing Asian currency. INR registering a gain of 122 paise or 1.33 per cent in a single trading session to settle at 90.27 (provisional) against the US dollar, after India and the US agreed to a trade deal. India and the US agreed to a trade deal under which Washington will bring down reciprocal tariff on Indian goods to 18 per cent from current 25 per cent, US President Donald Trump said on Monday after a phone conversation with Prime Minister Narendra Modi. Domestic indices also surged by over 2.5 per cent, boosting domestic market sentiments. Further, weakness in crude oil prices and expected foreign inflows also favoured investor sentiment. The benchmark BSE Sensex surged 2,072.67 points, or 2.54 percent, to 83,739.13, while the broader NSE Nifty index soared 639.15 points, or 2.55 percent, to 25,727.55.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1670897</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670897</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,823.10, a premium of 95.55 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,727.55 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,823.10, a premium of 95.55 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,727.55 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index added 639.15 points or 2.55% to 25,727.55. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 6.99% to 12.90. HDFC Bank, Reliance Industries and ICICI Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Solar Industries India Q3 PAT rises 38% YoY to Rs 467 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/solar-industries-india-q3-pat-rises-38-yoy-to-rs-467-cr/1670895</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670895</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations increased 29.15% YoY to Rs 2548.32 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations increased 29.15% YoY to Rs 2548.32 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 635.91 crore in Q3 FY26, up 38.51% from the Rs 459.11 crore reported in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 733 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of 37% as compared with Rs 536 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 28.77% in Q3 FY26 from 27.17% in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 27.08% to Rs 1,937.35 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 1,524.47 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of raw material consumed stood at Rs 1,116.34 crore (up 22.39% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 213.90 crore (up 41.95% YoY) during the period under review. Solar Industries India (SIIL) is the flagship company of the Solar Group. SIIL, along with its subsidiaries, manufactures bulk explosives, packaged explosives, and initiating systems, which find application in the mining, infrastructure, and construction industries. Shares of Solar Industries India jumped 5.09% to close at Rs 13,868.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SolarInds_52858264363_25386.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty extend gains for 2nd day; realty index climbs ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-extend-gains-for-2nd-day-realty-index-climbs/1670893</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670893</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with robust gains today, extending gains for a second consecutive session, after India and the United States announced a long-awaited trade deal that eased tariff-related concerns which had weighed on domestic markets for months.

The key equity benchmarks ended with robust gains today, extending gains for a second consecutive session, after India and the United States announced a long-awaited trade deal that eased tariff-related concerns which had weighed on domestic markets for months. The Nifty settled above the 25,700 level. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 2,072.67 points or 2.54% to 83,739.13. The Nifty 50 index added 639.15 points or 2.55% to 25,727.55. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.74% while the Nifty gained 3.63%. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 2.79% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.91%. The market breadth was strong. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 6.99% to 12.90. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty Realty index (up 4.79%), the Nifty Pharma index (up 3.02%) and the Nifty Consumer Durables index (up 3.05%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Private Bank index (up 2.50%), the Nifty Oil & Gas index (up 1.91%) and the Nifty Media index (up 1.49%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.69% to 6.722 compared with previous session close of 6.769. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2500 compared with its close of 91.4950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 5.73% to Rs 152,235. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 97.58. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.21% to 4.287. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement fell 19 cents or 0.29% to $66.11 a barrel. Global Markets: European stocks advanced on Tuesday as global markets settled following a short-lived sell-off in cryptocurrencies and precious metals. Asian markets ended higher after the U.S. and India trade deal, sparking a sharp risk-on move across the region. Japan's Nikkei 225 jumped nearly 4%, and the Topix rose over 3.3%. South Korea’s Kospi surged about 6.84%, triggering a buy-side trading curb. U.S. stocks climbed overnight as Wall Street kicked off the new month on a positive note, with investors looking past recent volatility in silver and bitcoin and turning their focus to the upcoming earnings slate. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.05%, the S&P 500 gained 0.54%, and the Nasdaq Composite added 0.56%. Markets are also tracking key economic signals and cues from the Federal Reserve on interest rates, even as efforts continue in Washington to avert a partial government shutdown. Data releases have been disrupted, with the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics postponing the January jobs report and other labour data until federal operations resume.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Realty Index records a surge of 4.79%, NIFTY climbs 2.55% ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-realty-index-records-a-surge-of-479-nifty-climbs-255/1670891</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670891</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Realty index ended up 4.79% at 815.3 today.

Nifty Realty index ended up 4.79% at 815.3 today. The index has lost 9.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Godrej Properties Ltd jumped 8.93%, Lodha Developers Ltd added 7.33% and Sobha Ltd rose 5.94%. The Nifty Realty index has decreased 14.00% over last one year compared to the 10.13% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Financial Services index increased 3.27% and Nifty Infrastructure index gained 3.03% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 recorded a gain of 2.55% to close at 25727.55 while the SENSEX witnessed a rise of 2.54% to close at 83739.13 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background-picture-i_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 2,073 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,700 level; VIX slumps 6.99%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-2073-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25700-level-vix-slumps-699/1670889</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670889</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with robust gains today, extending gains for a second consecutive session, after India and the United States announced a long-awaited trade deal that eased tariff-related concerns which had weighed on domestic markets for months.

The key equity benchmarks ended with robust gains today, extending gains for a second consecutive session, after India and the United States announced a long-awaited trade deal that eased tariff-related concerns which had weighed on domestic markets for months. The Nifty settled above the 25,700 level. All NSE indices closed in the green, with realty, financial services and consumer durables stocks leading the gains. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex zoomed 2,072.67 points or 2.54% to 83,739.13. The Nifty 50 index added 639.15 points or 2.55% to 25,727.55. In two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex added 3.73% while the Nifty gained 3.63%. In the broader market, the S&P BSE 150 MidCap Index rallied 2.79% and the S&P BSE 250 SmallCap Index jumped 2.91%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 3,300 shares rose and 991 shares fell. A total of 145 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, tanked 6.99% to 12.90. India-US Trade Deal: India and the United States on Monday announced a landmark trade deal following a phone call between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and U.S. President Donald Trump, marking a clear thaw in bilateral ties after months of tariff-related tensions. Under the agreement, Washington will cut tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and scrap the additional 25% penalty imposed earlier over India’s purchases of Russian crude oil. Trump said New Delhi had agreed to stop buying Russian oil and would move to reduce tariffs and non-tariff barriers on U.S. goods to zero. The deal is seen as a major boost to trade relations between the two countries, which are targeting bilateral trade of $500 billion by 2030. Market participants expect the agreement to lift sentiment for Indian equities and the rupee, while export-oriented sectors such as textiles, apparel and seafood are likely to be key beneficiaries. Modi welcomed the announcement, saying reduced tariffs on Made in India products would unlock immense opportunities for mutually beneficial cooperation between the world’s two largest democracies. Commerce and Industry Minister Piyush Goyal called the pact a historic turning point, saying it would open new opportunities for farmers, MSMEs, entrepreneurs and skilled workers, while accelerating India’s progress towards Viksit Bharat 2047. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index added 4.79% to 815.30. The index rallied 6.26% in the two consecutive trading session. Godrej Properties (up 8.82%), Lodha Developers (up 7.37%), Sobha (up 6.34%), Brigade Enterprises (up 5.98%), Prestige Estates Projects (up 4%), DLF (up 3.84%), Oberoi Realty (up 3.72%), Phoenix Mills (up 2.94%), Anant Raj (up 0.99%) added. Stocks in Spotlight: Bajaj Auto advanced 1.07% after the company reported 25% increase in total auto sales for January 2026, selling 4.77 lakh units as against 3.81 lakh units sold in January 2025. Bajaj Housing Finance rose 1.58% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 21.32% to Rs 664.89 crore on a 17.8% increase in total income to Rs 2,886.04 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Maruti Suzuki India added 2.67% after the company’s total production increased 9.33% to 226,146 units in January 2026, compared with 206,851 units produced in January 2025. Bharat Wire Ropes rallied 7.30% after the company’s standalone net profit jumped 22.58% to Rs 18.24 crore despite an 11.75% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 142.81 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. SMC Global Securities rose 4.95% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 47.82% to Rs 30.54 crore on a 12.06% rise in total income to Rs 495.53 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Dhampur Sugar Mills rose 0.84%. The company’s consolidated net profit climbed 75.2% to Rs 26.49 crore on 9.54% increase in revenue from operations (excluding net excise duty) to Rs 451.18 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December. City Union Bank surged 4.08% after reporting a standalone net profit of Rs 332.16 crore, up 16.14% YoY, on the back of a 17.22% rise in total income to Rs 2,001.03 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Q3 FY25. Transrail Lighting rallied 9.23% after the company’s consolidated net profit increased 17.7% to Rs 109.74 crore on a 32.6% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,777.19 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Dev Information Technology (Dev IT) rallied 1.02% after the company secured an order worth around Rs 29 lakh from Gujarat International Finance Tec-City (GIFT), an undertaking of the Government of Gujarat. Bharat Seats jumped 7.08% after the company’s standalone net profit spiked 30.43% to Rs 9.90 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 7.59 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rallied 60.25% to Rs 491 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 306.39 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Adani Ports & Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) surged 9.19% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 21.16% to Rs 3,053.61 crore on 21.86% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 9,704.59 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Zydus Wellness slipped 3.24% after the company reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 39.9 crore in Q3 FY26 as against a net profit of Rs 6.4 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Net sales more than doubled to Rs 963.3 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 450.8 crore in the same period last year. HFCL added 3.43% after the company reported 41.04% jump in consolidated to Rs 102.37 crore on a 19.65% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1,210.79 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Thermax jumped 3.65% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 76.16% to Rs 204.18 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 115.90 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations grew 4.19% to Rs 2,634.68 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Global Markets: European stocks advanced on Tuesday as global markets settled following a short-lived sell-off in cryptocurrencies and precious metals. Asian indices ended higher after the U.S. and India trade deal, sparking a sharp risk-on move across the region. Japan's Nikkei 225 jumped nearly 4%, and the Topix rose over 3.3%. South Korea’s Kospi surged about 6.84%, triggering a buy-side trading curb. U.S. stocks climbed overnight as Wall Street kicked off the new month on a positive note, with investors looking past recent volatility in silver and bitcoin and turning their focus to the upcoming earnings slate. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.05%, the S&P 500 gained 0.54%, and the Nasdaq Composite added 0.56%. Markets are also tracking key economic signals and cues from the Federal Reserve on interest rates, even as efforts continue in Washington to avert a partial government shutdown. Data releases have been disrupted, with the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics postponing the January jobs report and other labour data until federal operations resume.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kamat Hotels (India) tanks after Q3 PAT drops 33% YoY to Rs 17 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kamat-hotels-india-tanks-after-q3-pat-drops-33-yoy-to-rs-17-cr/1670896</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670896</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations rose 11.64% to Rs 117.74 crore in Q3 FY26 over Rs 105.46 crore in Q3 FY25.

However, revenue from operations rose 11.64% to Rs 117.74 crore in Q3 FY26 over Rs 105.46 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 26.63 crore in Q3 FY26, down 25.09% from Rs 35.55 crore in the same quarter last year. During the quarter, an exceptional item of Rs 3.68 crore was recorded. Total expenses increased 29.19% YoY to Rs 92.88 crore during the quarter. Employee benefits expense rose 25.76% to Rs 22.94 crore, finance cost fell 19.52% to Rs 6.79 crore. On a nine-month basis, the company reported an 49.43% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 18 crore in 9M FY26, compared with Rs 35.60 crore in 9M FY25. Revenue from operations rose 4.12% YoY to Rs 275.51 crore in 9M FY26. Kamat Hotels (India) operates a diverse portfolio of luxury and mid-premium hotels across India. Their brands include the "Orchid" chain, along with Fort JadhavGadh, Mahodadhi Palace, Lotus Resorts, and IRA by Orchid. The company focuses on continuous property improvement and expansion, primarily utilizing lease agreements, revenue sharing, and management contracts for growth.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KamatHotels_86174243622_4354.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Euro attempts recovery near $1.18 levels against dollar; EUR/INR futures slide 2% under 107 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/euro-attempts-recovery-near-118-levels-against-dollar-eurinr-futures-slide-2-under-107-mark/1670887</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670887</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro is attempting recovery from a one and half week low on Tuesday as dollar took a breather following a streak of gains.

Euro is attempting recovery from a one and half week low on Tuesday as dollar took a breather following a streak of gains. Dollar index is holding above 97 mark owing to strong US economic data and shifting Federal Reserve (Fed) policy expectations toward hawkish. Data on Monday showed an unexpected rebound in US factory activity, underscoring economic resilience, as the Institute for Supply Management's (ISM) Manufacturing Purchasing Managers' Index (PMI) rose to 52.6 from 47.9 in December. Meanwhile, US President Donald Trump nominated Kevin Warsh as the next Federal Reserve (Fed) Chair who is perceived to have a more disciplined and cautious approach to monetary easing. On the domestic docket, upcoming European Central Bank (ECB) monetary policy decision will be keenly watched for further cues. EUR/USD is currently quoting at $1.1824, up 0.11% on the day and rebounding from its lowest level in one and half weeks. On the NSE, EUR/INR futures are down almost 2% under 107 mark.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/european-union-1328255__340_economy.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Thermax jumps after Q3 PAT soars 76% YoY to Rs 204 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/thermax-jumps-after-q3-pat-soars-76-yoy-to-rs-204-cr/1670867</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670867</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations grew 4.19% to Rs 2,634.68 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations grew 4.19% to Rs 2,634.68 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax of Rs 229.92 crore in Q3 FY26, up 47.12% from Rs 156.27 crore in the same quarter last year. During the quarter, an exceptional item of Rs 58.75 crore was recorded. On the segmental front, revenue from industrial products stood at Rs 1,580 crore (up 14% YoY), revenue from industrial infrastructure was Rs 1,120 crore (up 68% YoY), revenue from green solutions rose to Rs 173 crore (up 268% YoY) and revenue from the chemical segment stood at Rs 207 crore (up 8% YoY) during the quarter. As of 31 December 2025, the order book stood at Rs 12,641 crore, reflecting an 11.05% increase from Rs 11,383 crore in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. Order booking for the quarter was Rs 3,080 crore, representing a 34.14% decline compared with Rs 2,296 crore in the same quarter of the previous fiscal year. On a nine-month basis, the company reported an 11.07% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 476.22 crore in 9M FY26, compared with Rs 428.74 crore in 9M FY25. Revenue from operations declined 0.77% YoY to Rs 7,266.11 crore in 9M FY26. Meanwhile, the company’s board has approved the incorporation of a wholly owned step-down subsidiary in Dubai through Thermax Engineering Singapore Pte Ltd, a wholly owned subsidiary of the company. Thermax, a leading energy and environment solutions provider, is one of the few companies in the world that offers integrated innovative solutions in the areas of heating, cooling, power, water and waste management, air pollution control and chemicals. Thermax has manufacturing facilities in India, Europe and Southeast Asia.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Thermax_89686957655_4767.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[HFCL rises after strong Q3 performance; order book rises to Rs 11,125 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hfcl-rises-after-strong-q3-performance-order-book-rises-to-rs-11125-crore/1670846</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670846</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While EBITDA improved by 41.67% YoY to Rs 243.52 crore, EBITDA margin expanded by 312 basis points YoY to 20.11% in Q3 FY26.

While EBITDA improved by 41.67% YoY to Rs 243.52 crore, EBITDA margin expanded by 312 basis points YoY to 20.11% in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 138.11 crore, up by 37.75% from Rs 100.26 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. HFCL stated that during the quarter, the company made steady progress across its core strategic priorities, supported by a sharp recovery in global optical fibre demand, strengthening export momentum, and continued execution across its telecom product and defence portfolios. The company’s order book stood at Rs 11,125 crore as on 31 December 2025, providing healthy revenue visibility across products and services. Revenue mix continued to improve, with products contributing 60% and exports 27% of revenues, reflecting the company’s ongoing transition towards a product-led and internationally diversified business model. Capacity expansion in optical fibre and optical fibre cables progressed as planned, positioning HFCL well to address rising demand from data centres, next generation networks and global customers. HFCL is a diversified telecom infrastructure enabler with businesses spanning telecom infrastructure development, system integration, and the manufacture and supply of high-end telecom equipment, optical fiber, and optical fiber cables (OFC).

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HFCL_23392864533_1189.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Ports spurts after Q3 PAT climbs 21% YoY to Rs 3,053 cr ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-ports-spurts-after-q3-pat-climbs-21-yoy-to-rs-3053-cr/1670844</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670844</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional item and tax jumped 23.27% to Rs 3,756.80 crore during the quarter compared with Rs 3,047.72 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year.

Profit before exceptional item and tax jumped 23.27% to Rs 3,756.80 crore during the quarter compared with Rs 3,047.72 crore posted in corresponding quarter last year. Exceptional items amounted to Rs 146.08 crore, primarily related to labour code provisions. EBITDA stood at Rs 5,786 crore in Q3 FY26, registering the growth of 20%, compared with Rs 4,802 crore posted in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, the company’s Cargo volume was 123 MMT (up 9% YoY), Rail volume was 170,466 TEUs (up 4% YoY) and GPWIS volume was 5.2 MMT (down 6% YoY). On the segmental front, revenue from Domestic Ports was Rs 6,701 crore (up 15.02% YoY), International Ports revenue was Rs 1,067 crore (up 20.56% YoY), revenue from Logistics was Rs 1,121 crore (up 61.76% YoY), Marine revenue was Rs 773 crore (up 90.39% YoY) and Other revenue was Rs 43 crore (down 72.08% YoY). The All-India market share of Adani Ports for December 2025 quarter was 26.4% (down 60 basis points YoY). The all-India container market share stood at 45.8%, up 40 basis points YoY. On the guidance front, the company revised its FY26 revenue guidance to Rs 38,000 crore, up from earlier range of Rs 36,000-38,000 crore. The EBITDA guidance was also raised to Rs 22,800 crore from the earlier range of Rs 21,000 -22,000 crore. Additionally, the company now expects revenue from its marine business to grow by 2.3 times in FY26, up from the earlier estimate of 2 times. Ashwani Gupta, whole-time director & CEO, said, “As India’s largest and the world’s fastest-growing Integrated Transport Utility, APSEZ has once again delivered a strong and resilient performance. Sustained momentum across our four business pillars, combined with the consolidation of NQXT, has enabled us to raise the upper end of our FY26 EBITDA guidance by a robust Rs 800 crore. Our financial and operational stability has been further reinforced by multiple credit rating upgrades, including an exceptional ‘A-/Stable’ rating from Japan Credit Rating Agency, which is a notch above India’s sovereign rating - a strong validation of our governance standards and financial prudence. Towards the end of FY24, we articulated a clear ambition to double our revenue and EBITDA by FY29 to Rs 65,500 crore and Rs 36,500 crore respectively.” Meanwhile, the company’s board approved the resignation of chief financial officer (CFO), D. Muthukumaran with effect from 28 February 2026. Following his cessation, Sreedhar Krishna Menon will assume the role of CFO with effect from March 1, 2026. Menon is a Cost Accountant and a Management Graduate. He has also completed the Advanced Management Program at Harvard Business School. Menon is an experienced professional with more than 30 years of experience in various disciplines of finance and accounts. Throughout his career, he has held various leadership positions at Pennar Group, AFL Private Limited, Bharti Airtel Limited and AdaniConnex. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) is the largest private port operator in India. APSEZ operates a portfolio of 15 domestic ports/terminals with an international presence at 4 global ports/terminals. Along with its port operations, it has its wide logistics network and offers various port-based marine services to its owned ports/terminals as well as other ports.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniPorts_15044199473_21281.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[One Mobikwik Systems jumps as Q3 turns profitable]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/one-mobikwik-systems-jumps-as-q3-turns-profitable/1670845</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670845</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The turnaround was driven by strong execution across its payments and financial services businesses and sharp operating discipline.

The turnaround was driven by strong execution across its payments and financial services businesses and sharp operating discipline. On a consolidated basis, Mobikwik posted a net profit of Rs 4.05 crore in Q3 December 2025, reversing a loss of Rs 55.28 crore in Q3 December 2024 and a loss of Rs 28.62 crore in Q2 September 2025. Total income rose 8.29% YoY and 6.40% QoQ to Rs 297.22 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Contribution profit climbed 76% YoY and 34% QoQ to Rs 128.8 crore, reflecting continued focus on cost efficiency. Fixed costs as a percentage of total income declined to 38% in Q3 FY26 from 42% a year ago. EBITDA stood at Rs 15 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a return to profitability and a sharp improvement of Rs 57.6 crore YoY and Rs 21.4 crore QoQ. The company said disciplined cost control and healthier margins led to a YoY EBITDA swing, translating into PAT profitability. Operationally, payments GMV rose 63% YoY and 11% QoQ to Rs 48,064 crore, while gross margin in the payments business touched an all-time high of 37%, reflecting a 125% YoY and 36% QoQ expansion. ZIP EMI GMV increases 126% YoY and 12% QoQ to Rs 900 crore. Financial services gross profit surged 405% YoY and 45% QoQ to Rs 37.2 crore, with net financial services margin improving to 4.13% in Q3 FY26 from 1.05% a year earlier and 3.17% in Q2FY26, aided by better credit quality. Commenting on the performance, Upasana Taku, executive director, co-founder and CFO, said the profitable quarter reflects disciplined execution and sustained cost optimisation, adding that the company remains focused on scaling responsibly while creating long-term shareholder value. Founded in 2009, Mobikwik is India’s largest digital wallet and a leading fintech platform, serving over 186.6 million registered users and 4.79 million merchants. As of December 2025, it held an 18% share of PPI wallet GTV and ranked fourth by registered users in India, according to RedSeer.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OneMobikwikSystemsLtd_63812553_68099.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pound off one-week low in global markets but tumbles against INR]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pound-off-one-week-low-in-global-markets-but-tumbles-against-inr/1670843</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670843</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[British Pound has gained after recent losses and GBP/USD pair is currently trading up 0.23% at 1.3689.

British Pound has gained after recent losses and GBP/USD pair is currently trading up 0.23% at 1.3689. The counter had toppled to one-week low in last session but cut losses amid supportive risk appetite today. Economic cues also remain positive for the pair as the UK manufacturing sector strengthened in January with growth in both output and new orders accelerating, final data from S&P Global showed Monday. The final manufacturing Purchasing Managers' Index rose to a 17-month high of 51.8 in January from 50.6 in December. Market is now waiting for the monetary policy announcement from the Bank of England. However, Pound has eased in local markets as INR is soaring following the announcement of India-US trade deal. GBP/INR futures are currently trading at 123.45, down 1.70% on the day.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-growing-on-grass-picture-id157606379_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[PB Fintech Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/pb-fintech-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1670842</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1670842</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Zydus Wellness Ltd, Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd and Varun Beverages Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 03 February 2026.

AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd, Zydus Wellness Ltd, Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd and Varun Beverages Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 03 February 2026. PB Fintech Ltd lost 5.76% to Rs 1472.3 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 35.99 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.01 lakh shares in the past one month. AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd crashed 3.69% to Rs 374.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 21305 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5464 shares in the past one month. Zydus Wellness Ltd tumbled 3.49% to Rs 419.8. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 40703 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 13148 shares in the past one month. Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd dropped 3.36% to Rs 66.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.41 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6.48 lakh shares in the past one month. Varun Beverages Ltd corrected 3.12% to Rs 451.95. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 16.84 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.76 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PB-Fintech-Ltd_61882656_41343.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>