<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:21:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee closes up]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-closes-up/1667746</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667746</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher 91.6625 per Dollar on Tuesday (27 January 2026), versus its previous close of 91.8650 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JPY/INR futures surge over 3% to settle near 60 mark]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jpyinr-futures-surge-over-3-to-settle-near-60-mark/1667745</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667745</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On the NSE, USD/INR futures lost 0.2% to end at 91.66.

On the NSE, USD/INR futures lost 0.2% to end at 91.66. EUR/INR and GBP/INR futures added nearly 1% to settle for the day at 108.90 and 125.61 respectively. JPY/INR futures surged more than 3% to end at 59.55.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/colored-pencil-bar-graph-lined-paper-gives-successful-resul_personal-finance.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jyoti Structures Q3 PAT jumps 45% YoY to Rs 17 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jyoti-structures-q3-pat-jumps-45-yoy-to-rs-17-cr/1667727</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667727</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rallied 52.13% year on year (YoY) to Rs 208.96 crore in Q3 FY26.

Revenue from operations rallied 52.13% year on year (YoY) to Rs 208.96 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before tax stood at Rs 15.46 crore in the December 2025 quarter, registering a growth of 34.78% on a YoY basis. EBITDA added 45.3% to Rs 19.73 crore in Q3 FY26, as against Rs 13.58 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total expenses jumped 56.17% to Rs 198.61 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 127.17 crore in Q3 FY25. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 119.74 crore (up 150.86% YoY), while employee benefits expenses were Rs 19.84 crore (up 33.42% YoY) during the period under review. The company delivered a strong operational and financial performance during the quarter, supported by disciplined execution, effective cost management, and steady progress across its order book. The results reflect sustained momentum across its core businesses. A company spokesperson said, “the company has demonstrated an accelerated pace of growth in Q3 and over the first nine months of FY 2025–26. This performance reflects a stronger order book, improved on-ground execution, and the operationalisation of the second tower manufacturing unit at Nashik. The company continues to see a healthy pipeline with expanding opportunities in the transmission and distribution space.” Jyoti Structures is engaged in Electricity, transmission, distribution and substations. The registered office of the company is in Mumbai. Shares of Jyoti Structures rose 1.88% to end at Rs 9.21 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JyotiStructures_63966842065_1196.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR rebounds after India-EU confirm historic FTA  ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-rebounds-after-india-eu-confirm-historic-fta/1667728</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667728</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee rebounded from its all-time low levels and gained 19 paise to close at 91.71 (provisional) against the US dollar on Tuesday, amid weakness in US dollar index and India-EU FTA announcement.

The Indian rupee rebounded from its all-time low levels and gained 19 paise to close at 91.71 (provisional) against the US dollar on Tuesday, amid weakness in US dollar index and India-EU FTA announcement. The deal over India-EU FTA boosted domestic market sentiments. However, rising commodity and crude oil prices capped sharp gains. Local equities also ended modestly higher after India and the European Union confirmed that they had signed a historic trade pact. The giant free trade deal will cut or eliminate tariffs on almost 97 percent of European exports, saving up to 4 billion euros ($4.75 billion) annually in duties, the 27-nation bloc said. For India, the tariff cuts with the EU will lead to more exports in labor intensive sectors that will help partly offset the impact of U.S. tariffs. The benchmark BSE Sensex ended the session up 319.78 points, or 0.39 percent, at 81,857.48 after a choppy ride on worries over U.S. President Donald Trump's additional tariffs announcement on South Korea and escalating U.S.-Iran tensions. The broader NSE Nifty index closed up 126.75 points, or 0.51 percent, at 25,175.40.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-woman-are-checking-stock-market-picture-id51119792_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Marico Q3 PAT rises 12% YoY to Rs 447 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/marico-q3-pat-rises-12-yoy-to-rs-447-crore/1667726</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667726</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 26.59% YoY to Rs 3,537 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 26.59% YoY to Rs 3,537 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax (PBT) declined 9.45% YoY to Rs 567 crore, while EBITDA increased 11% YoY to Rs 592 crore, compared with Rs 533 crore in Q3 FY25. However, EBITDA margin contracted by 234 basis points to 16.7%, from 19.1% a year ago. The India business revenues stood at Rs 2,681 crores, up 28% YoY, on the back of a sequential improvement in underlying volume growth supplemented by pricing interventions across core portfolios over the last 12 months, in response to inflation in key input costs. . E-commerce and quick commerce continued to lead growth, while traditional trade showed improved traction. More than 95% of the portfolio gained or maintained market share, and around 80% gained or sustained penetration on a MAT basis. Parachute Rigids demonstrated resilience during the quarter. While reported volumes declined 1%, underlying volumes—adjusted for ml-age reductions grew 2%. The brand recorded 50% revenue growth, underscoring strong pricing inelasticity and consumer loyalty. Value-Added Hair Oils delivered a stellar quarter, recording 29% value growth. The portfolio gained 170 bps in value market share on a MAT basis to reach an all-time high of 30%. The company remains confident of sustaining this double-digit growth trajectory in the near and medium term. Saffola Edible Oils had a soft quarter, amidst a relatively elevated pricing environment. Revenue growth was flattish, while prior pricing actions anniversarized in this quarter. The company said brand will continue to pivot towards premium offerings within the portfolio, including the recently introduced Cold Pressed Oils. Foods grew 5% YoY, in line with the company’s ongoing strategic focus on calibrating franchise profitability in view of the growing scale of the business. Saffola Oats continued to gain market share on a MAT basis, retaining its position as the No. 1 oats brand. The company expects the portfolio to revert to an accelerated growth trajectory in the coming quarters. Premium Personal Care, including the digital-first portfolio, sustained strong momentum. The Premium Personal Care portfolio is expected to exit FY26 at Rs 350+ crore ARR, while the digital-first portfolio is projected to cross Rs 1,000 crore ARR. The international business recorded 21% constant currency growth, with broad-based double-digit growth across markets. Bangladesh posted 29% CCG, Vietnam rebounded with 22% CCG, MENA delivered 17% CCG, and South Africa reported 16% CCG. NCD and Exports grew 27%. On the outlook front, the company said the sector has witnessed steady demand trends throughout the year so far. It remains optimistic about a gradual uptick in consumption across categories in the coming quarters, supported by favourable macroeconomic indicators and the potential for further stimulus in the upcoming Union Budget. Amidst this backdrop, the company expects a steady growth trajectory in its core categories, despite near-term input cost headwinds. Growth will be supported by ongoing initiatives to strengthen select General Trade (GT) channel partners and the continued expansion of its direct reach footprint under Project SETU. The company also cited healthy offtake trends, penetration gains and market share expansion across key portfolios. Marico said it will continue to aggressively diversify its portfolio in line with its medium-term strategic priorities. It aims to grow the Foods portfolio at a CAGR of over 25%, reaching nearly eight times FY20 revenues by FY27. The digital-first portfolio is expected to scale to around 2.5x of FY24 ARR by FY27, up from the earlier target of 2x. The India revenue share of the Foods and Premium Personal Care portfolios stood at around 22% in 9MFY26, and the company expects this to increase to approximately 25% by FY27. Among digital-first brands, Beardo is expected to post double-digit EBITDA margins in FY26, while Plix is likely to deliver single-digit EBITDA margins, with the overall portfolio targeted to achieve double-digit EBITDA margins by FY27. The international business has shown broad-based strength, and the company aims to maintain double-digit constant currency growth over the medium term. Marico added that it remains on track to deliver over 25% consolidated revenue growth in FY26. While pricing-led growth is expected to moderate gradually, the company expects strong volume momentum in the India business to continue. With input costs easing and margin pressures beginning to subside, it anticipates a progressive improvement in operating profit growth in the coming quarters. Saugata Gupta, MD & CEO, commented, “Our performance in the quarter and year so far reflects the strength of our operating model and the effectiveness of agile execution in driving consistent outcomes. The India business has delivered strong volume and revenue growth, supported by improving trends in core categories and the profitable scaling up of foods and digital-first businesses in line with our strategic priorities. The international business remains a consistent growth engine, delivering broad-based performance across markets. Looking ahead, we expect to sustain the healthy volume growth momentum, with profitability strengthening progressively as input cost pressures moderate.” Marico is one of India's leading consumer products companies in the global beauty and wellness space. It sells products under brands such as Parachute, Saffola, Hair & Care, Parachute Advansed, Nihar Naturals, Mediker, Pure Sense, Coco Soul, Revive, Set Wet, Livon, Beardo, Just Herbs etc. Shares of Marico rose 0.85% to close at Rs 747.20 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Marico_77423580094_12585.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices edge up on India-EU trade optimism, RBI liquidity support]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-edge-up-on-india-eu-trade-optimism-rbi-liquidity-support/1667735</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667735</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended modestly higher in a volatile session, supported by improving risk appetite.

The key equity benchmarks ended modestly higher in a volatile session, supported by improving risk appetite. Sentiment was lifted by optimism around the India-European Union free trade agreement and expectations of a potential easing of US tariff measures related to India’s imports of Russian oil. The rupee rebounded from record lows, providing additional support to domestic equities, while firm global market cues aided sentiment. Investors also took note of remarks at Davos by US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent, who indicated that the additional 25% tariffs on India could be withdrawn amid reduced Indian purchases of Russian oil. Separately, liquidity support from the Reserve Bank of India boosted confidence after the central bank announced measures to inject funds into the banking system. The Nifty closed above the 25,150 level, led by gains in metal and banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 319.78 points or 0.39% to 81,857.48. The Nifty 50 index added 126.75 points or 0.51% to 25,175.40. Mahindra & Mahindra (down 4.25%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (down 2.58%) and Bajaj Finance (down 1.07%) were major Nifty drags today. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.44%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.03%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1803 shares rose and 2510 shares fell. A total of 171 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 1.83% to 14.45. RBI Liquidity Measures: The Reserve Bank of India on Friday announced a set of liquidity-enhancing measures to ease conditions in the banking system. These include a Rs 25,000 crore 90-day variable rate repo operation on January 30, a $10 billion USD/INR buy-sell swap auction with a three-year tenor on February 4, and open market purchases of government securities worth Rs 1 lakh crore in two equal tranches on February 5 and February 12. The RBI said it will continue to closely monitor liquidity and market conditions and act as needed to ensure orderly system liquidity. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union on January 27, 2026, concluded a landmark Free Trade Agreement at the 16th India-EU Summit, marking a major milestone in bilateral economic ties between the world's 4th and 2nd largest economies, together accounting for about 25% of global GDP. The pact grants preferential market access to over 99% of Indian exports to the EU, with labour-intensive sectors such as textiles, leather, gems and jewellery, marine products and engineering goods set to benefit, while safeguarding sensitive areas like dairy and key agricultural products. The agreement delivers calibrated auto liberalisation, ambitious access in services, and a structured mobility framework to support skilled and semi-skilled Indian professionals. It also addresses non-tariff barriers, CBAM-related cooperation, digital trade, MSMEs, and future technologies including AI and clean energy. With India-EU goods trade at Rs 11.5 lakh crore and services trade at Rs 7.2 lakh crore in 2024-25, the FTA is expected to significantly boost exports, jobs, investment, and India’s integration into global value chains, laying the foundation for inclusive, resilient and future-ready growth. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.63% to 6.706 as compared with the previous close of 6.664. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.7100 compared with its close of 91.9050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 1.80% to Rs 158,860. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 97.02. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.21% to 4.223. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 04 cents or 0.06% to $65.55 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares traded higher on Tuesday, helped by a trade deal between the European Union and India, as investors await more quarterly earnings and a Federal Reserve rate decision. Asian indices ended higher despite concerns regarding tariffs resurfacing post-US President Donald Trump threatening to increase levies on South Korean goods. Trump said on Truth Social that South Korea's legislature has not approved Seoul’s trade deal with Washington and that tariffs on the country will climb to 25%, from 15%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 advanced 0.50% to settle at 6,950.23, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 0.64% to close at 49,412.40. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.43% to end at 23,601.36, supported by jumps of about 3%, 2% and 1% in Apple, Meta Platforms and Microsoft, respectively, ahead of their earnings reports later in the week. Stocks in Spotlight: Asian Paints fell 2.81% after the company's consolidated net profit declined 4.55% to Rs 1,059.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,110.48 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26. Axis Bank jumped 4.31% after the bank reported a 2.94% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 6,489.57 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 6,303.77 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26. IndusInd Bank slipped 0.18%. The bank reported 88.5% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 161.16 crore on 13.67% fall in total income to Rs 13,079.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. DCB Bank surged 9.50% after the bank reported 22% jump in net profit to Rs 185 crore on a 16% increase in total income to Rs 846 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Shriram Finance lost 0.39%. The NBFC’s standalone net profit declined 29.36% to Rs 2,521.67 crore on a 13.88% increase in total income to Rs 12,191.58 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sona BLW Precision Forgings rose 6.52% after the auto components maker posted strong quarterly performance in Q3 FY26. Consolidated net profit on an adjusted basis increased 20% YoY to Rs 180.9 crore in Q3 FY26. The company disclosed that reported PAT was impacted by a one-time charge of Rs 30.1 crore linked to the new labour code. Revenue rose 39% YoY to Rs 1,208.5 crore in Q3 FY26, primarily driven by the expansion of electric vehicle traction motor and railway business in India. Kirloskar Pneumatic Company rose 4.12% after the company was provisionally selected by the Government of India in the latest round of the Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for white goods. Kirloskar Pneumatic has committed an investment of Rs 320 crore to manufacture key components such as compressors, motors, heat exchangers and sheet metal parts. Separately, Kirloskar Pneumatic Company reported a solid performance for the quarter ended December 2025. On a consolidated basis, net profit came in at Rs 42.2 crore, up 15.9% YoY from Rs 36.4 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Net sales rose 18.8% YoY to Rs 406.9 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 342.6 crore in the year-ago period. Tata Consumer Products gained 2.86% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 37.91% to Rs 384.61 crore on a 15.04% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5,112 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Godrej Consumer Products tumbled 5.34% after the company's consolidated net profit remained flat at Rs 497.91 crore in Q3 FY26, even as net sales increased 8.8% year-on-year to Rs 4,079.47 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Ultratech Cement advanced 1.97% after the company reported a 26.92% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,725.40 crore on 22.78% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 21,829.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) added 2.30% after the company reported a 62.29% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 7,545.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 4,649.20 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-premium/1667711</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667711</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,427.20, a premium of 251.80 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,175.40 in the cash market.

The Nifty 24 February 2026 futures closed at 25,427.20, a premium of 251.80 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,175.40 in the cash market. In the cash market, The Nifty 50 index rose 126.75 points or 0.51% to 25,175.40. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, was up 1.83% to 14.45. HDFC Bank, Reliance Industries and Axis Bank were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2025 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-data-picture-id181151058_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 320 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,150]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-320-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25150/1667710</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667710</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks ended with modest gains in a volatile session today after India and the European Union clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA), ending 18 years of prolonged negotiations.

The key equity benchmarks ended with modest gains in a volatile session today after India and the European Union clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA), ending 18 years of prolonged negotiations. Investor sentiment is also buoyed by expectations ahead of the Union Budget 2026. The Nifty settled above the 25,150 mark. The barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 319.78 points or 0.39% to 81,857.48. The Nifty 50 index added 126.75 points or 0.51% to 25,175.40. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.44%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.03%. The market breadth was negative. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 1.83% to 14.45. Among the sectoral indices, the Metal index (up 3.07%), the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 1.76%) and the Nifty Bank index (up 1.25%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Media index (down 1.44%), the Nifty Auto index (down 0.93%) and the Nifty FMCG index (down 0.60%) underperformed the Nifty 50 index. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union have signed the “mother of all deals,” PM Modi said on Tuesday. Prime Minister Narendra Modi lauded the signing of the free trade agreement between India and the European Union and said that the deal represented “25 percent of the global GDP and 1/3 of global trade.” The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Automobile tariffs will fall sharply, with duties on cars gradually reduced from 110% to as low as 10%, and car parts tariffs fully eliminated within five to ten years. Agri-food tariffs will drop significantly, including wine tariffs cut from 150% to 75% initially and as low as 20% later, and olive oil tariffs reduced from 45% to zero over five years. The pact includes strong sustainability and climate commitments, alongside plans for an EU–India climate cooperation platform and up to €500 million in EU support for India’s green transition. On tariffs overall, Sefcovic said the aim is 97–99% partial or full tariff liberalisation, which could generate savings of around €4 billion a year and help double bilateral trade within five years. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.63% to 6.706 as compared with the previous close of 6.664. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.7100 compared with its close of 91.9050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement advanced 1.80% to Rs 158,860. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.03% to 97.02. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.21% to 4.223. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 04 cents or 0.06% to $65.55 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares traded higher on Tuesday, helped by a trade deal between the European Union and India, as investors await more quarterly earnings and a Federal Reserve rate decision. Asian markets ended higher despite concerns regarding tariffs resurfacing post-US President Donald Trump threatening to increase levies on South Korean goods. Trump said on Truth Social that South Korea's legislature has not approved Seoul’s trade deal with Washington and that tariffs on the country will climb to 25%, from 15%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 advanced 0.50% to settle at 6,950.23, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 0.64% to close at 49,412.40. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.43% to end at 23,601.36, supported by jumps of about 3%, 2% and 1% in Apple, Meta Platforms and Microsoft, respectively, ahead of their earnings reports later in the week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty Metal Index rises 3.07%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-metal-index-rises-307/1667709</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667709</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty Metal index closed up 3.07% at 11829.65 today.

Nifty Metal index closed up 3.07% at 11829.65 today. The index is up 9.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Jindal Stainless Ltd added 8.59%, Adani Enterprises Ltd gained 5.11% and Hindustan Copper Ltd rose 4.90%. The Nifty Metal index is up 44.00% over last one year compared to the 10.28% surge in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty PSU Bank index added 1.76% and Nifty Commodities index added 1.70% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 added 0.51% to close at 25175.4 while the SENSEX recorded a gain of 0.39% to close at 81857.48 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks end with modest gains; metal shares surge]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-end-with-modest-gains-metal-shares-surge/1667708</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667708</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The equity benchmarks registered modest gains in a volatile trading session after India and the European Union reached a landmark free trade agreement (FTA), ending 18 years of prolonged negotiations.

The equity benchmarks registered modest gains in a volatile trading session after India and the European Union reached a landmark free trade agreement (FTA), ending 18 years of prolonged negotiations. Investor sentiment was also shaped by anticipation ahead of the Union Budget 2026. The Nifty settled above the 25,150 mark. Gains were led by metal, PSU bank, and private bank stocks, while media, auto, and FMCG shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 319.78 points or 0.39% to 81,857.48. The Nifty 50 index added 126.75 points or 0.51% to 25,175.40. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.44%, while the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.03%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,803 shares rose and 2,510 shares fell. A total of 171 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, jumped 1.83% to 14.45. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union have signed the “mother of all deals”, PM Modi said on Tuesday. Prime Minister Narendra Modi hailed the landmark free trade agreement, noting that it represents nearly 25% of global GDP and about one-third of global trade. The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Automobile tariffs will fall sharply, with duties on cars gradually reduced from 110% to as low as 10%, and car parts tariffs fully eliminated within five to ten years. Agri-food tariffs will drop significantly, including wine tariffs cut from 150% to 75% initially and as low as 20% later, and olive oil tariffs reduced from 45% to zero over five years. The pact includes strong sustainability and climate commitments, alongside plans for an EU–India climate cooperation platform and up to €500 million in EU support for India’s green transition. On tariffs overall, Sefcovic said the aim is 97–99% partial or full tariff liberalisation, which could generate savings of around €4 billion a year and help double bilateral trade within five years. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Metal index surged 3.25% to 11,851.10. the index declined 0.83% in the past trading session. Jindal Stainless (up 8.84%), Adani Enterprises (up 5.03%), Steel Authority of India (up 4.91%), JSW Steel (up 4.74%) and Hindustan Copper (up 4.7%), Hindustan Zinc (up 4.32%), National Aluminium Company (up 3.95%), NMDC (up 3.22%), Vedanta (up 3.22%) and APL Apollo Tubes (up 3.07%) surged. Stocks in Spotlight: Axis Bank jumped 4.31% after the bank reported a 2.94% increase in standalone net profit to Rs 6,489.57 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 6,303.77 crore in Q3 FY25. Total income increased 4.26% year on year (YoY) to Rs 38,500.06 crore in Q3 FY26. Indusind Bank slipped 0.11%. The bank reported 88.5% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 161.16 crore on 13.67% fall in total income to Rs 13,079.39 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shriram Finance lost 0.39%. The NBFC’s standalone net profit declined 29.36% to Rs 2,521.67 crore on a 13.88% increase in total income to Rs 12,191.58 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Ultratech Cement advanced 1.97% after the company reported a 26.92% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,725.40 crore on 22.78% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 21,829.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) added 2.30% after the company reported a 62.29% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 7,545.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 4,649.20 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter. DCB Bank surged 9.50% after the bank reported 22% jump in net profit to Rs 185 crore on a 16% increase in total income to Rs 846 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Godrej Consumer Products tumbled 5.34% after the company's consolidated net profit remained flat at Rs 497.91 crore in Q3 FY26, even as net sales increased 8.8% year-on-year to Rs 4,079.47 crore compared with Q3 FY25. Tata Consumer Products gained 2.86% after the company’s consolidated net profit jumped 37.91% to Rs 384.61 crore on a 15.04% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5,112 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Asian Paints fell 2.81% after the company’s consolidated net profit declined 4.55% to Rs 1,059.87 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,110.48 crore in Q3 FY25. However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26. Global Markets: European markets traded higher on Tuesday, helped by a trade deal between the European Union and India, as investors await more quarterly earnings and a Federal Reserve rate decision. Asian markets ended higher despite concerns regarding tariffs resurfaced post US President Donald Trump threatening to increase levies on South Korean goods. Trump said on Truth Social that South Korea's legislature has not approved Seoul’s trade deal with Washington, and that tariffs on the country will climb to 25%, from 15%. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 advanced 0.50% to settle at 6,950.23, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 0.64% to close at 49,412.40. The Nasdaq Composite climbed 0.43% to end at 23,601.36, supported by jumps of about 3%, 2% and 1% in Apple, Meta Platforms and Microsoft, respectively, ahead of their earnings reports later in the week.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NBCC gains after bagging Rs 63-cr construction orders]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nbcc-gains-after-bagging-rs-63-cr-construction-orders/1667744</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667744</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In an exchange filing, the company said it has secured an order from NHPC for the construction of residential rooms above Blocks II and III at NHPC’s Regional Office in Narwal, Jammu, along with the partial dismantling of the existing ground floor as required for the project.

In an exchange filing, the company said it has secured an order from NHPC for the construction of residential rooms above Blocks II and III at NHPC’s Regional Office in Narwal, Jammu, along with the partial dismantling of the existing ground floor as required for the project. The project value stands at Rs 6.39 crore and NBCC has been appointed as the project management consultant (PMC). The company also received another order from the Higher Education Department, Government of Odisha, for construction and renovation works across five state public universities under the GSU of PM-USHA scheme. The total value of this order is Rs 56.23 crore, with NBCC designated as the project management consultant. NBCC (India) is in business and operates in three major segments, namely project management consultancy, real estate, and engineering procurement & construction. The company's consolidated net profit advanced 25.21% to Rs 156.68 crore on an 18.99% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,910.19 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NBCC_1807915630_13166.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[JSW Energy Q3 PAT climbs 150% YoY to Rs 420 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jsw-energy-q3-pat-climbs-150-yoy-to-rs-420-cr/1667707</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667707</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations jumped 67.36% YoY to Rs 4,081.76 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations jumped 67.36% YoY to Rs 4,081.76 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company posted a pre-tax loss exceptional items of Rs 107.69 crore in Q3 FY26, as against a profit before tax of Rs 150.04 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported an exceptional loss of Rs 65.19 crore during the quarter. EBITDA increased 97.48% YoY to Rs 2,202 crore in Q3 FY26, primarily driven by contributions from acquired assets, including the Mahanadi thermal plant and the O2 Power portfolio. Strategic acquisitions boosted EBITDA growth, with the Mahanadi plant contributing approximately Rs 726 crore and O2 Power contributing Rs 278 crore of EBITDA during the quarter. During the quarter, total power sale volumes rose 65% YoY to 11,118 MUs, while power sales under long-term PPAs increased 63% YoY to 9,151 MUs. Growth was driven by organic renewable energy capacity additions, contributions from the Mahanadi plant and O2 Power, and higher generation at the Utkal and Vijayanagar thermal plants. Short-term thermal sales increased 80% YoY to 1,968 MUs, supported by a shift towards domestic coal-based capacity at Utkal and Mahanadi. Cash and cash equivalents stood at Rs 6,181 crore as of 30 September 2025. Liquidity remained ample, with total cash balances of Rs 7,159 crore as of 31 December 2025. The company’s consolidated net worth and net debt as of 31 December 2025 stood at Rs 29,634 crore and Rs 63,771 crore, respectively, resulting in a net debt-to-equity ratio of 2.2x. Net debt to pro-forma steady-state EBITDA (excluding CWIP debt) stood at 4.9x. Receivables, measured in DSO terms, improved to 73 days, compared with 96 days a year ago. Sharad Mahendra, joint managing director and CEO of JSW Energy, said, "We delivered a strong quarterly performance, driven by sizeable capacity additions leading to record-high power sales and robust EB/TOA growth. The quarter was a milestone for us with the commissioning of India's largest green hydrogen plant at Vijayanagar, with a capacity of 3,800 TPA. Our acquisitions of 02 Power and KSK have been fully integrated and are now contributing meaningfully to earnings. We remain firmly committed to our 2030 goals of 30 GW of generation capacity and 40 GWh of storage" JSW Energy is a private sector power producer in India and part of JSW group. It has established its presence across the value chains of power sector with diversified assets in power generation and transmission. The counter fell 7.35% to Rs 442.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JSWEnergy_53555504993_27323.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tata Consumer rises after Q3 PAT climbs 38% YoY to Rs 385 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tata-consumer-rises-after-q3-pat-climbs-38-yoy-to-rs-385-cr/1667698</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667698</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax stood at Rs 539.91 crore in the third quarter of FY26, registering a growth of 34.33% on a year-on-year basis.

Profit before tax stood at Rs 539.91 crore in the third quarter of FY26, registering a growth of 34.33% on a year-on-year basis. EBITDA jumped to Rs 728 crore in Q3 FY26, registering growth of 26% YoY from Rs 578 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 14.2% in Q3 FY26 as compared to 13% recorded in the corresponding quarter of the previous year. For the quarter, India’s packaged beverages business recorded a 3% revenue growth during the quarter. Coffee continued its strong momentum with a 40% revenue growth. The ready-to-drink (RTD) business delivered its second consecutive quarter of double-digit growth, reporting a 26% revenue increase. Tetley entered the RTD tea segment with the launches of Tetley Green Tea Slimcare and Tetley Fruit Tea. India Foods' business revenue grew 19% YoY. Salt revenue rose 14%, supported by strong volume growth, marking the fourth consecutive quarter of double-digit growth. Tata Sampann continued its strong performance, registering 45% growth during the quarter, aided by new launches and innovations. Capital Foods accelerated innovation with launches such as Ching’s Premium Soy Sauces and Premium Stir-fry Sauces. International business revenue grew 11% in constant currency terms, led by strong coffee performance in the US. Eight O’Clock Coffee continued to gain market share in the US, while Tetley emerged as the fastest-growing specialty tea brand in Canada. In line with its store expansion plans, Tata Starbucks added 12 net new stores during the quarter, bringing the total to 504 stores across 81 cities. The key growth drivers for the quarter were beverage collaborations with Baileys, continued innovation in the food program, and the enhanced Diwali gifting portfolio. Sunil D’Souza, MD & CEO of Tata Consumer Products, said, “Q3 FY26 marked another quarter of strong, broad-based performance for Tata Consumer Products, led by healthy volume-led growth and sustained momentum across our core as well as growth businesses. Our India-branded business delivered double-digit underlying volume growth, with foods and beverages continuing on a strong trajectory driven by strong execution, portfolio expansion, and premiumization. We are encouraged by the consistent performance in our foods business, the accelerating momentum in Tata Sampann and Ready-to-Drink, and the steady gains in our international business, particularly in coffee. Innovation remains a key growth engine, with 15 new launches during the quarter across the Health & Wellness, Convenience, and Premium segments. With improving margins, disciplined execution, and a sharper focus on high-growth categories, we remain confident in our strategy to build a more agile, innovation-led, and profitable consumer business for the long term.” Tata Consumer Products is a focused consumer products company uniting the principal food and beverage interests of the Tata Group under one umbrella. The company’s portfolio of products includes tea, coffee, water, RTD, salt, pulses, spices, ready-to-cook and ready-to-eat offerings, breakfast cereals, snacks, and mini meals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TataGlobal_86798028265_557.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/onesource-specialty-pharma-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1667697</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667697</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[SBFC Finance Ltd, Syngene International Ltd, JSW Energy Ltd and Avantel Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 January 2026.

SBFC Finance Ltd, Syngene International Ltd, JSW Energy Ltd and Avantel Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 January 2026. OneSource Specialty Pharma Ltd tumbled 18.35% to Rs 1169.8 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6142 shares in the past one month. SBFC Finance Ltd lost 11.37% to Rs 90.05. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 26.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.51 lakh shares in the past one month. Syngene International Ltd crashed 10.03% to Rs 488.15. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 6.61 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 36060 shares in the past one month. JSW Energy Ltd dropped 8.49% to Rs 437.9. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 9.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 91637 shares in the past one month. Avantel Ltd pared 7.26% to Rs 126.45. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 4.58 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.07 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/OneSourceSpecialtyPharmaLtd_27536112_89433.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sona BLW Precision jumps after Q3 results]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sona-blw-precision-jumps-after-q3-results/1667696</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667696</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Consolidated net profit on an adjusted basis increased 20% YoY to Rs 180.9 crore in Q3 FY26.

Consolidated net profit on an adjusted basis increased 20% YoY to Rs 180.9 crore in Q3 FY26. The company disclosed that reported PAT was impacted by a one-time charge of Rs 30.1 crore linked to the new labour code. Revenue rose 39% YoY to Rs 1,208.5 crore in Q3 FY26, primarily driven by the expansion of electric vehicle traction motor and railway business in India. EBITDA increased 30% YoY to Rs 304.6 crore in Q3 FY26. EBITDA margin stood at 25.2% in Q3 FY26, down from 27.0% in Q3 FY25, reflecting a change in product mix. Business and operational updates showed BEV revenue declined 3% YoY to Rs 320.2 crore but still accounted for a higher 38% share of automotive product revenue, up from 32% in Q2 FY26. The company said its net order book stood at Rs 23,500 crore as of 31 December 2025, providing strong revenue visibility over the medium term. The company commercialised a new hydraulic motor controller during the quarter and commenced sample production of in-cabin radar sensors at its Chennai SMT facility, strengthening its localisation capabilities. Management highlighted continued addition of new EV customers and fresh programme wins from existing clients. Gurugram-based Sona BLW Precision Forgings is one of the world’s leading mobility technology companies. It is a global supplier with manufacturing and assembly facilities, R&D centres, and engineering capability centres across India, the USA, Serbia, Mexico, and China. The company designs, manufactures, and supplies highly engineered, mission-critical systems and components to mobility OEMs. It is a leading supplier of driveline and traction motor solutions to the fast-growing global electric vehicle (EV) market.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SonaBLWPrecisionForgingsLtd_30715559_18341.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[British Pound net speculative shorts fall further]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/british-pound-net-speculative-shorts-fall-further/1667694</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667694</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).

Large currency speculators further reduced net short position in the Pound futures market from a near six year high, according to the latest Commitment of Traders (COT) data released by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The non-commercial futures contracts of Pound futures, traded by large speculators and hedge funds, totaled a net short position of 21980 contracts in the data reported through January 20, 2026. This was a weekly drop of 3290 net short contracts.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold and silver pause near $5,108 and $117.7 after historic rally]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-and-silver-pause-near-5108-and-1177-after-historic-rally/1667693</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667693</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices traded marginally lower in early Tuesday electronic trade after surging to an all-time high above $5,107.9 in the previous session, as the market paused following an intense safe-haven rally driven by escalating geopolitical tensions.

Gold prices traded marginally lower in early Tuesday electronic trade after surging to an all-time high above $5,107.9 in the previous session, as the market paused following an intense safe-haven rally driven by escalating geopolitical tensions. Silver futures witnessed a sharper pullback, sliding nearly 4% after scaling fresh lifetime highs of $117.7 per ounce, reflecting profit-taking after a rapid advance fueled by trade uncertainties, investor flight from sovereign bonds and currencies, and heightened demand for defensive assets. Sentiment was further influenced by renewed trade frictions after US President Donald Trump threatened higher tariffs on autos, lumber, and pharmaceutical imports from South Korea, while lifting duties on other goods to 25% amid stalled negotiations. Investor focus has now shifted to the US Federal Reserve’s two-day policy meeting beginning today, where interest rates are expected to remain unchanged but Chair Jerome Powell’s guidance will be closely scrutinized amid mounting pressure from the White House to ease monetary policy. In domestic markets, MCX March silver futures surged nearly 10% to a record Rs 364,821 per kg, while MCX February gold futures climbed almost 2% to a fresh all-time high of Rs 159,820 per 10 grams.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Asian Paints slides as Q3 PAT decline 5% YoY to Rs 1,060 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/asian-paints-slides-as-q3-pat-decline-5-yoy-to-rs-1060-cr/1667689</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667689</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26.

However, revenue from sales rose 3.85% year on year (YoY) to Rs 8,849.72 crore in Q3 FY26. Profit before exceptional items and tax increased by 8.5% to Rs 1,646.7 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,518.2 Crore in Q3 FY25. PBDIT (Profit before depreciation, interest, tax, other income, and exceptional items) (before share in profit of associates) increased 8.8% to Rs 1,781.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,636.7 crore in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, PBDIT margin as % to Net Sales increased to 20.1%, up from 19.2% posted in the same quarter last year. The company recognised exceptional items totalling Rs 157.61 crore in its consolidated financial results for Q3 FY26. This included a one-time labour code impact of Rs 63.74 crore, arising from an increase in gratuity liability of Rs 52.88 crore and a rise in compensated absences liability of Rs 10.86 crore, along with an impairment loss of Rs 93.87 crore on intangible assets related to the acquisition of Obgenix Software (White Teak). The Decorative Business in India delivered strong volume growth of 7.9% despite a shorter festive period and an extended monsoon, while value growth stood at 2.8%. Although demand remained subdued, a series of internal initiatives helped drive resilient performance. Net sales from the International Business rose 6.3% year-on-year to Rs 869.6 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by strong performance in Sri Lanka, the UAE, and Ethiopia. Within the industrial business segment, revenue from APPPG increased 16.5% year-on-year to Rs 334.7 crore in Q3 FY26, while PPGAP sales rose 16.9% year-on-year to Rs 713.3 crore in Q3 FY26. Within the Home Décor segment, net sales from the Bath Fittings business declined 4.1% year-on-year to Rs 84 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 87.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Kitchen business net sales increased 2.6% year-on-year to Rs 105.4 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 102.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Meanwhile, net sales at White Teak rose 12.4% year-on-year to Rs 29.2 crore, while Weatherseal posted a sharp 58.6% year-on-year increase to Rs 18.7 crore in Q3 FY26. Amit Syngle, managing director & CEO of Asian Paints, said, “We had a third consecutive quarter of good volume growth with our India Decorative Business delivering a robust 7.9% volume growth in the quarter. The overall coatings business registered a 4.4% revenue growth for the quarter with Decorative business revenue growth of 2.8%. This performance for the quarter reflects the sustained momentum delivered through persistent actions across our identified growth initiatives even as the broader market faced persistent competitive intensity and subdued demand conditions. We have intensified our brand building efforts, launched a robust wave of retailing initiatives and introduced a wide range of innovative product and service propositions. Our disciplined cost management, backward integration efforts and enhanced operational efficiencies enabled us to fuel these brand investments while simultaneously improving our operating margins. Our industrial coatings segment registered good double-digit growth, boosting our overall coatings performance. In the same league, our international business achieved a 6.3% revenue increase led by steady performance in key markets of UAE, Sri Lanka and Ethiopia. As the external environment remains dynamic, we continue to drive differentiated strategies, harness our structural strengths, and embrace technology to sustain momentum, respond with agility, creating long term value for all stakeholders.” Asian Paints, established in 1942, is the largest listed company in India's decorative paints segment. It ranked among the top eight decorative coatings companies in the world. It is engaged in the business of manufacturing, selling, and distributing paints, coatings, and products related to home décor and bath fittings and providing related services.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AsianPaints_3886867460_34.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex Nifty trade with minor cuts; auto shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-nifty-trade-with-minor-cuts-auto-shares-decline/1667688</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667688</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity barometers traded near flat line in mid-afternoon trade.

The key equity barometers traded near flat line in mid-afternoon trade. The movement came after India and the European Union clinched a landmark free trade agreement (FTA) following 18 years of stalled negotiations. The Nifty traded below the 25,100 level. Auto shares declined for three consecutive trading sessions. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 118.09 points or 0.14% to 81,419.61. The Nifty 50 index fell 3.90 points or 0.02% to 25,043.15. The broader market underperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index declined 0.41% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.54%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,556 shares rose and 2,673 shares fell. A total of 188 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, surged 6.29% to 14.19. India-EU Trade Deal: India and the European Union have signed the “mother of all deals”, PM Modi said on Tuesday. Prime Minister Narendra Modi lauded the signing of the free trade agreement between India and the European Union and said that the deal represented “25 per cent of the global GDP and 1/3rd of global trade”. The Narendra Modi government is said to have agreed to immediately lower duties on up to 200,000 European cars a year priced above €15,000, or about Rs 16.5 lakh. Electric vehicles are excluded. Automobile tariffs will fall sharply, with duties on cars gradually reduced from 110% to as low as 10%, and car parts tariffs fully eliminated within five to ten years. Agri-food tariffs will drop significantly, including wine tariffs cut from 150% to 75% initially and as low as 20% later, and olive oil tariffs reduced from 45% to zero over five years. The pact includes strong sustainability and climate commitments, alongside plans for an EU–India climate cooperation platform and up to €500 million in EU support for India’s green transition. On tariffs overall, Sefcovic said the aim is 97–99% partial or full tariff liberalisation, which could generate savings of around €4 billion a year and help double bilateral trade within five years. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index fell 2.05% to 26,255.65. The index dropped 3.15% in the past three consecutive trading sessions. Mahindra & Mahindra (down 4.32%), Tube Investments of India (down 2%), Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (down 1.87%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 1.85%), Exide Industries (down 1.65%), Ashok Leyland (down 1.41%), Uno Minda (down 1.29%), Hero MotoCorp (down 1.12%), Bosch (down 0.47%) and TVS Motor Company (down 0.34%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was advanced 0.47% to 6.695 as compared with the previous close of 6.664. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.6875 compared with its close of 91.9050 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement advanced 1.71% to Rs 1,58,710. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.22% to 97.25. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.26% to 4.240. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 34 cents or 0.52% to $65.25 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Marine Electricals (India) surged 6.38% after the company announced that it has received orders worth Rs 284.39 crore from multiple clients. The company has secured an order from Digital Edge DC (India) for the supply of power distribution systems for the BOM-2 Data Center Project. The order is to be executed over a period of 6–8 months. Marine Electricals has also received an order from Crescon Projects & Services for the supply of power distribution systems for the LBOM-12 Data Center Project, with deliveries expected to be completed within 1–2 months. In addition, the company bagged an order from SHM Shipcare for the supply of power distribution systems, which is to be executed over a period of 4–5 months. Kirloskar Pneumatic Company rallied 3.19% after the company was provisionally selected by the Government of India in the latest round of the Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for white goods. According to an official release dated January 23, the PLI scheme for white goods, covering air conditioners and LED lights, is expected to attract investments of Rs 11,198 crore from 85 companies over the scheme period. In the fourth round, five applicants were provisionally selected with a combined committed investment of Rs 863 crore, while eight other applications were referred to a committee of experts for further evalu

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-down-picture-id463115585_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[IFB Industries Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ifb-industries-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1667687</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667687</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shiva Texyarn Ltd, Digicontent Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 January 2026.

Shiva Texyarn Ltd, Digicontent Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 January 2026. IFB Industries Ltd lost 16.54% to Rs 1128.5 at 14:31 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 43924 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1332 shares in the past one month. Shiva Texyarn Ltd crashed 12.98% to Rs 164.85. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1057 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 221 shares in the past one month. Digicontent Ltd tumbled 12.81% to Rs 27.03. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 13018 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1442 shares in the past one month. Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd fell 11.64% to Rs 48.11. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 184 shares in the past one month. Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd dropped 11.35% to Rs 109. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 1925 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2043 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IFBInds_5044625029_281.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>