<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:58:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Auto gains as Q3 PAT rises 19% YoY to Rs 2,503 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-auto-gains-as-q3-pat-rises-19-yoy-to-rs-2503-cr/1669933</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669933</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s PAT was reported after adjusting for a one-time exceptional impact arising from the reassessment of employee benefit obligations, following the revised definition of wages under the new Labour Codes notified in November 2025.

The company’s PAT was reported after adjusting for a one-time exceptional impact arising from the reassessment of employee benefit obligations, following the revised definition of wages under the new Labour Codes notified in November 2025. The company’s revenue growth was driven by record quarterly volumes and a richer product mix, underpinned by double-digit growth across all businesses—domestic motorcycles, electric two-wheelers, three-wheelers and exports. This performance was supported by buoyant festive demand and GST-led momentum in the domestic market, alongside a sustained resurgence in exports. Profit before tax was at Rs 3,326.64 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of 18.74% from Rs 2,801.45 crore posted in Q3 FY25. In Q3 FY26, EBITDA rose to Rs 3,161 crore, up 22% year-on-year, scaling a new peak as margins expanded to 20.8%, reflecting dynamic P&L management. Margins improved by 30 bps sequentially, with currency tailwinds and PU benefits more than offsetting the decision to absorb cost inflation during a strong festive season, as well as the margin drag from the highest-ever quarterly sales of electric two-wheelers. The firm added that domestic motorcycles turned in its biggest quarter on 125cc+ with double-digit revenue growth YoY, buoyed by sports segment. "Improved traction on the Pulsar portfolio, led by product refreshes/upgrades and amplified by impactful activation which drove quarterly retail volumes to a historic high and the competitive performance of the strategically important 125cc+ segment," it added. Domestic volumes rose 3% to 7,31,037 units in Q3 FY26 as compared with 7,07,105 units sold in the corresponding quarter last year. Export volumes jumped 18% to 6,10,215 units in Q3 FY26 as compared with 5,17,367 units sold in the corresponding quarter last year. Commercial vehicles posted record retails, crossing 100,000 units for the tenth straight quarter, while electric three-wheelers achieved peak billings and retails, exiting the quarter in a leadership position. Chetak delivered a strong rebound, with volumes up 70% QoQ, aided by resolution of sourcing constraints, rapid production ramp-up and a 500 bps QoQ market-share gain. The company approved an additional investment of up to Rs 12 crore in the equity share capital of Clean Max Godavari for an open-access group captive power purchase arrangement for its Akurdi and Chakan (Plant 2) manufacturing facilities in Pune.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajAuto_20897586_28074.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[The New India Assurance gains as Q3 PAT rises 9% YoY to Rs 380 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/the-new-india-assurance-gains-as-q3-pat-rises-9-yoy-to-rs-380-cr/1669932</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669932</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total income increased 14.2% YoY to Rs 12,234.97 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Total income increased 14.2% YoY to Rs 12,234.97 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Consolidated profit before tax (PBT) surged 247% YoY to Rs 372.22 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 107.26 crore a year ago. For the quarter ended 31 December 2025, gross written premium stood at Rs 11,762.83 crore, up 8.32% YoY. Net written premium was at Rs 9,716.72 crore in the third quarter of FY25, registering a growth of 8.38% compared to the same period a year ago. On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit rose 5.1% to Rs 371.59 crore on a 14.1% rise in total income to Rs 12,178.85 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Profit before tax (PBT) jumped 214.8% YoY to Rs 366.54 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 116.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Commenting on the Q3 result, Girija Subramanian, CMD, said, “Our Global Gross Written Premium for the nine-month period grew by 10.5%. Notably, our Domestic Gross Direct Premium growth significantly outpaced the industry average, resulting in our market share improving to 13.4%, compared to 12.8% in the corresponding previous year. The Q3FY26 incurred claim ratio stood at 90.77%, a significant improvement over the 94.49% reported in Q3FY25. The company recognized provisions of approximately Rs 2,500 Cr toward wage arrears and retirement benefits following government-approved wage revisions, partly offset by robust investment income from its equity portfolio. Despite these one-time costs, the company reported Profit Before Tax (PBT) growth of 62% for the nine-month period and 215% for the quarter. The company maintains a strong balance sheet, with improvements in net worth and general reserves, and a solvency ratio of 1.81 times, well above the regulatory requirement of 1.50 times.” The New India Assurance Company is India's largest non-life insurance company.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewIndiaAssuranceCompanyLtd_27148328361_12214.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Escorts Kubota gains after January 2025 sales rise 47% YoY to 9,799 units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/escorts-kubota-gains-after-january-2025-sales-rise-47-yoy-to-9799-units/1669930</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669930</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic tractor sales rose 50.8% to 9,137 units in January 2026, compared with 6,058 units sold in January 2025.

Domestic tractor sales rose 50.8% to 9,137 units in January 2026, compared with 6,058 units sold in January 2025. Exports jumped 8.3% to 662 units in January 2026, as against 611 units in January 2025. Meanwhile, the company’s construction equipment business division sold 524 machines in January 2026, registering a decline of 3.7% from 544 machines sold in January 2025. Escorts Kubota is primarily engaged in the business of manufacturing agricultural tractors, engines for agricultural tractors, construction, earthmoving, and material handling equipment; round and flat tubes; heating elements; and double-acting hydraulics. Escorts Kubota’s consolidated net profit declined 1.87% to Rs 318.16 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 324.23 crore posted in Q2 FY25. However, revenue from operations jumped 22.58% year on year (YoY) to Rs 2,791.56 crore in the quarter ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Escorts_12276934110_161.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashoka Buildcon gaiins as Q3 PAT skyrockets 223% YoY to Rs 2,111 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashoka-buildcon-gaiins-as-q3-pat-skyrockets-223-yoy-to-rs-2111-cr/1669929</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669929</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[However, revenue from operations fell 23.47% YoY to Rs 1,827.33 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

However, revenue from operations fell 23.47% YoY to Rs 1,827.33 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax were at Rs 2,609 crore in Q3 FY26, up 750.80% as against Rs 306.65 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses declined 22.92% YoY to Rs 1,633.86 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 470.37 crore (down 33.56% YoY), while employee benefit expenses were at Rs 98.78 crore (down 13.58% YoY), and finance cost stood at Rs 200.22 crore (down 35.97% YoY). On a standalone basis, the company’s net profit surged 68% year-on-year to Rs 101.8 crore in Q3 FY26, even as revenue from operations declined 18.35% to Rs 1,463.04 crore compared with Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 157.4 crore in Q3 FY26, down 16% compared with Rs 187.1 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin improved to 10.6% in Q3 FY26 from 10.3% posted in the same quarter last year. On a standalone basis, the company’s debt stands at Rs 1,046 crore, comprising Rs 79 crore in equipment loans, Rs 667 crore in working capital loans, and Rs 300 crore in non-convertible debentures (NCDs). As of 31 December 2025, the company’s total order book stood at Rs 15,927 crore, before exceptional gains. Road EPC projects accounted for Rs 7,025 crore, or 44.1% of the total, while Road HAM contributed Rs 1,705 crore (10.7%). Building EPC orders were Rs 528 crore (3.3%), railways Rs 1,562 crore (9.8%), and Power T&D projects Rs 5,108 crore (32.1%). Ashoka Buildcon is engaged in the construction & maintenance of roads and supporting services to land support and operation of toll roads.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokaBuildcon_9945804621_25513.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Grid rises after Q3 PAT jumps 8% YoY to Rs 4,185 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/power-grid-rises-after-q3-pat-jumps-8-yoy-to-rs-4185-cr/1669913</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669913</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 12,395.09 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 12,395.09 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax and regulatory deferral account balances rose 6.7% YoY to Rs 5,238.79 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,909.32 crore in Q3 FY25. Total expenses rose 7.11% YoY to Rs 7,314.07 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Employee expenses stood at Rs 659.28 crore (up 10.48% YoY), and finance cost was at Rs 2,190.50 crore (up 14.24% YoY) during the period under review. On the segmental front, revenue from transmission business stood at Rs 11,801.23 crore (up 5.93% YoY), revenue from consultancy business stood at Rs 496.51 crore (up 106.27% YoY), and revenue from telecom business stood at Rs 298.79 crore (up 8.91% YoY) during the quarter. Meanwhile, the company’s board has recommended a second interim dividend of Rs 3.25 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the purpose of dividend payment has been fixed as Monday, 9 February 2026, and the second interim dividend will be paid to the members on Friday, 27 February 2026. Further, the Board cleared a proposal to borrow up to Rs 32,000 crore in FY26 through instruments including domestic bonds, term loans, external commercial borrowings, foreign currency bonds, multilateral funding, or supplier credit. Separately, Power Grid Corporation of India has approved an investment of Rs 173.14 crore for a power transmission project in Kerala, as per a regulatory filing on January 31. The project involves the augmentation of a third 500 MVA interconnecting transformer at the Thrissur 400/220 kV VSC HVDC station and is scheduled for commissioning by 21 August 2027. The Power Grid Corporation of India is a Maharatna CPSU and India’s largest electric power transmission company.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PowerGridCorpn_89479008350_5455.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sun Pharma gains as Q3 PAT jumps 16% YoY to Rs 3,369 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sun-pharma-gains-as-q3-pat-jumps-16-yoy-to-rs-3369-cr/1669914</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669914</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax were at Rs 4,227.16 crore in Q3 FY26, up 21.59% as against Rs 3,476.4 crore in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax were at Rs 4,227.16 crore in Q3 FY26, up 21.59% as against Rs 3,476.4 crore in Q3 FY25. Formulation sales in India were Rs 49,98.59 crore, registering a growth of 16.2%. India Formulation sales accounted for 32.3% of total consolidated sales. Formulation sales in the US were $477 million, marginally up by 0.6%. Innovative Medicines continued to grow offsetting the decline in generics business. US sales accounted for approximately 27.5% of total consolidated sales. Emerging Markets formulations sales were $337 million, up by 21.6% and accounted for 19.4% of total consolidated sales. Formulation sales in Rest of World (RoW) markets were $296 million, up by 14.5% and accounted for 17.1% of total consolidated sales. Global Innovative Medicines sales were $423 million for Q3 FY26. This included a milestone income of $55 million. Ex-milestone, Global Innovative Medicines sales were up 13.2% and accounted for 21.2% of sales. For Q3 FY26, external sales of API were Rs 541.2 crore, down by 4.7%. Sun Pharma’s R&D efforts span both innovative and generic businesses, and the company continues to invest in building a robust pipeline for various markets. Sun’s innovative R&D pipeline includes five novel entities in the clinical stage. The company has a comprehensive product offering in the US market, consisting of 550 approved ANDAs, while 116 ANDA filings await US FDA approval, including 28 tentative approvals. During the quarter, two ANDAs were filed, and two ANDAs received approval. Sun’s portfolio includes 57 approved NDAs, while 14 NDAs are currently pending approval from the US FDA. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs 11 per equity share of Re 1 each for the financial year 2025–26. As intimated on 20 January 2026, the record date for determining entitlement to the interim dividend is 05 February 2026. The interim dividend shall be paid on or before 16 February 2026. Sun Pharmaceutical Industries is engaged in the business of manufacturing, developing and marketing a wide range of branded and generic formulations and Active Pharma Ingredients (APIs). The company and its subsidiaries has various manufacturing facilities spread across the world with trading and other incidental and related activities extending to global market. It is the largest pharmaceutical company in India.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SunPharmaInds_69091260890_4325.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hyundai Motor sells 0.73 lakh auto units in Jan'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hyundai-motor-sells-073-lakh-auto-units-in-jan26/1669896</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669896</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While domestic sales rose by 9.5% to 59,107 units, total exports increased by 20.9% to 14,030 units in January 2026 as compared with January 2025.

While domestic sales rose by 9.5% to 59,107 units, total exports increased by 20.9% to 14,030 units in January 2026 as compared with January 2025. Tarun Garg, MD & CEO, HMIL, said: "January 2026 marks a defining chapter in Hyundai Motor India’s journey. As we look ahead in the year, we will continue to lead with purpose - creating enduring value for our customers, empowering our stakeholders and shaping the future of mobility in India." Hyundai Motor India manufactures and sells passenger cars, along with vehicle parts and accessories. The company's consolidated net profit rose 14.31% to Rs 1,572.26 crore on a 1.15% increase in revenue to Rs 17,155.83 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. The company's board will consider its earning for Q3 FY26 on 02 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HyundaiMotorIndiaLtd_73449848_16486.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indices trade sideways; breadth positive]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indices-trade-sideways-breadth-positive/1669861</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669861</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The benchmark equity indices began Sunday’s session on a mixed footing in early trade, with the Sensex edging higher and the Nifty slipping marginally, as markets turned cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026.

The benchmark equity indices began Sunday’s session on a mixed footing in early trade, with the Sensex edging higher and the Nifty slipping marginally, as markets turned cautious ahead of the Union Budget 2026. The Nifty hovered around the 25,300 mark in early trade. Investors are gearing up for the release of the Union Budget 2026-27 today. Apart from sectoral announcements, all eyes would be on the growth projections and the fiscal deficit numbers that would be laid out by the Central Government today. Meanwhile, traders are also closely monitoring movements in the rupee, the flow of Q3 corporate earnings, and shifting geopolitical developments, all of which could influence near-term market sentiment. Metal, PSU bank and IT shares leading the fall while auto, private bank and pharma stocks advanced. At 09:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 28.66 points or 0.03% to 82,298.44. The Nifty 50 index fell 18.25 points or 0.07% to 25,306. In the broader market, the BSE 150 Mid-Cap index fell 0.77% and the BSE 250 Small-Cap index declined 0.72%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 1,566 shares rose and 1,442 shares fell. A total of 164 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) had bought shares worth Rs 2,251.37 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 601.03 crore in the Indian equity market on 29 January 2026, provisional data showed. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper remain unchanged at 6.695 In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.9350 compared with its close of 91.9950 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement tumbled 9% to Rs 1,36,185. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.74% to 96.99. The United States 10-year bond yield advanced 0.33% to 4.241. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement advanced 23 cents or 0.33% to $69.82 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Sun Pharmaceutical Industries rallied 3.13% after the company has reported a 16.03% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,368.81 crore on a 13.49% increase in revenue to Rs 15,520.54 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Auto added 1.65% after the company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on an 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. AstraZeneca Pharma India shed 0.08%. The company said it has received approval from the CDSCO to import, sell, and distribute Durvalumab (Imfinzi) solution for infusion in 120 mg/2.4 mL and 500 mg/10 mL strengths. Global Markets: On Friday, stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Spot gold and silver dropped around 9% and 28%, respectively. Over the past year, gold and silver futures have soared about 67% and 142%, respectively. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc extends downfall for second day]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-extends-downfall-for-second-day/1669862</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669862</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[In two sessions, the stock has declined 21.90% to currently trade at Rs 558.90, from its recent closing high of Rs 715.60 recorded on 29 January 2026.

In two sessions, the stock has declined 21.90% to currently trade at Rs 558.90, from its recent closing high of Rs 715.60 recorded on 29 January 2026. The recent selling in this counter was trigger after the company’s promoter announced an offer for sale (OFS) to pare its stake in Hindustan Zinc. Promoter Vedanta Limited had offered a base lot of 3,35,00,000 shares, representing 0.79% of the company’s equity. The offer included an oversubscription option for an additional 1,40,77,066 shares or 0.33% stake, taking the total divestment to 4,75,77,066 shares, or 1.13% stake. As of September 2025, Vedanta Limited held a 61.84% stake in Hindustan Zinc. The floor price had been set at Rs 685 per share, a discount of 5.73% to the stock’s previous close of Rs 726.60 on January 27, 2026. The OFS opened on January 28 for non-retail investors. Retail investors were allowed to participate on January 29, along with non-retail bidders carrying forward unallotted bids. The offer was conducted through a special window on the BSE and NSE during market hours. On Day 1 (T-day), the OFS had received subscription for 4,28,19,359 shares. It was subscribed 100.00% on the total non-retail offer size of 4,28,19,359 shares. On Day 2 (T+1 day), the OFS received subscription for 1,12,61,549 shares. It was subscribed 236.70% on the total offer size of 47,57,707 shares. Hindustan Zinc, a Vedanta Group company, is the world's largest integrated zinc producer and is amongst the top 5 silver producers globally. The company supplies to more than 40 countries and holds a market share of about 77% of the primary zinc market in India. The company had reported 46.23% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,916 crore on a 27.81% increase in revenue to Rs 10,627 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd Slips 9.99%, BSE Metal index Shed 3.13%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hindustan-zinc-ltd-slips-999-bse-metal-index-shed-313/1669834</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669834</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Zinc Ltd fell 9.99% today to trade at Rs 566.

Hindustan Zinc Ltd fell 9.99% today to trade at Rs 566. The BSE Metal index is down 3.13% to quote at 37628.6. The index is up 2.22 % over last one month. Among the other constituents of the index, Vedanta Ltd decreased 8.26% and National Aluminium Company Ltd lost 7.84% on the day. The BSE Metal index went up 33.43 % over last one year compared to the 7.33% surge in benchmark SENSEX. Hindustan Zinc Ltd has lost 7.56% over last one month compared to 2.22% gain in BSE Metal index and 3.32% drop in the SENSEX. On the BSE, 4.29 lakh shares were traded in the counter so far compared with average daily volumes of 12.23 lakh shares in the past one month. The stock hit a record high of Rs 732.6 on 28 Jan 2026. The stock hit a 52-week low of Rs 378.65 on 03 Mar 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HindZinc_20940848350_2307.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty suggests green start for equities; focus to remain on growth and fiscal deficit numbers]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-suggests-green-start-for-equities-focus-to-remain-on-growth-and-fiscal-deficit-numbers/1669802</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669802</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 16.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty February 2026 futures were up 16.00 points, suggesting a positive start for the Nifty 50 today. Investors are gearing up for the release of the Union Budget 2026-27 today. Apart from sectoral announcements, all eyes would be on the growth projections and the fiscal deficit numbers that would be laid out by the Central Government today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) had bought shares worth Rs 2,251.37 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net sellers to the tune of Rs 601.03 crore in the Indian equity market on 29 January 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs had sold shares worth Rs 41,435.22 in January. This follows their cash sales of Rs 34,349.62 crore in December and Rs 17,500.31 crore in November. Global Markets: On Friday, stocks witnessed some profit taking, with technology shares remaining in a funk, even as investors largely approved of President Donald Trump’s pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve. The S&P 500 fell 0.43% to finish at 6,939.03, its third straight down day. The Dow Jones Industrial Average pulled back 179 points, or 0.36%, to settle at 48,892.47. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite underperformed, dropping 0.94%, to end the day at 23,461.82. All three indexes fell more than 1% at session lows. Spot gold and silver dropped around around 9% and 28%, respectively. Over the past year, gold and silver futures have soared about 67% and 142%, respectively. Warsh’s selection was likely to ease concern about Fed independence because of his experience as a Fed governor and strong stance at times against inflation. While he is likely to push for lower rates in short term as Trump wants, the financial markets view him as someone who wouldn’t always follow the president’s direction and maintain credibility for monetary policy. Domestic Market: The benchmark equity indices Sensex and Nifty slipped on Friday, snapping a three-day rally, as weak global cues and caution ahead of the Union Budget on February 1 weighed on sentiment. Fresh foreign fund outflows added to the pressure. Investors also remained watchful of rupee movements, ongoing Q3 earnings and geopolitical developments. Reflecting the cautious mood, the Nifty closed below the 25,350 level, dragged down by losses in metal, IT and private banking stocks. The S&P BSE Sensex declined 296.59 points or 0.36% to 82,269.78. The Nifty 50 index lost 98.25 points or 0.39% to 25,320.65. In the past three consecutive trading session, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1.26% and 1.48%, respectively.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Economic Survey sets out a clear medium-term reform and growth agenda aligned with the Viksit Bharat vision: CII]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/economic-survey-sets-out-a-clear-medium-term-reform-and-growth-agenda-aligned-with-the-viksit-bharat-vision-cii/1669801</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669801</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Welcoming the Economic Survey 2025–26 presented in Parliament today, Mr Chandrajit Banerjee, Director General, CII, stated “the Survey offers a pragmatic, professional, and well-articulated assessment of India’s macroeconomic conditions at a critical juncture.

Welcoming the Economic Survey 2025–26 presented in Parliament today, Mr Chandrajit Banerjee, Director General, CII, stated “the Survey offers a pragmatic, professional, and well-articulated assessment of India’s macroeconomic conditions at a critical juncture. Drawing on extensive data, it sets out a clear medium-term reform and growth agenda aligned with the Viksit Bharat vision.” “CII concurs with the Survey’s assessment of India’s growth outlook, with the projected growth rate of 6.8–7.2 per cent in FY27 appearing realistic amid global uncertainties and external headwinds. It is our sense that with moderate level inflation, we can be looking at double digit nominal growth, which should help augment revenues and therefore, have a moderating effect on borrowings. That would further ease pressures on real interest rate thus triggering a virtuous cycle.” “It is heartening that the Survey underscores the unifying role of state capacity, society, and deregulation in advancing India’s development and strengthening its global influence. Reflecting this, the medium-term potential growth of Indian economy has been upgraded to 7%, up from 6.5% three years ago. This is also very welcome in a fractured world where such kind of sustained growth would be a stand out feature.” “We find the Survey’s thrust on the requirement of the state machinery to evolve into an ‘entrepreneurial state’ by building deeper system-level institutional capacity and adopting entrepreneurial policymaking to support growth with job creation, as an imperative, which needed emphasis.” “CII fully supports the Survey’s articulation that a competitive India must emerge as a global manufacturing hub. Anchored in the Industry’s Next Leap framework, the Survey highlights innovation, skill development, world-class infrastructure and logistics, and MSME scaling as key drivers of a high-productivity manufacturing economy, closely aligned with CII’s vision of a competitive India.”

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Genesys Int bags Rs 13-cr WAPCOS contract to develop urban digital twin platform for Guwahati]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/genesys-int-bags-rs-13-cr-wapcos-contract-to-develop-urban-digital-twin-platform-for-guwahati/1669799</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669799</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves creation of a 3D digital twin and will be executed over a period of four years, from February 5, 2026 to February 5, 2030, the company said in a regulatory filing.

The project involves creation of a 3D digital twin and will be executed over a period of four years, from February 5, 2026 to February 5, 2030, the company said in a regulatory filing. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity and does not fall under related party transactions. The company clarified that its promoters, promoter group, or group companies do not have any interest in WAPCOS. Genesys International further stated that the contract has been awarded on an arm’s length basis and forms part of its growing portfolio in urban mapping and digital twin solutions. Genesys International Corporation is engaged in providing Geographical Information Services comprising of photogrammetry, remote sensing, cartography, data conversion, state of the art terrestrial and 3D geocontent including location navigation mapping andother computer based related services. The company’s consolidated net profit rose 6.9% to Rs 12 crore on 6.8% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 76.95 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Genesys International rallied 5.49% to end at Rs 312.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GenesysIntl_54329690550_2371.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Bajaj Auto, Godfrey Phillips India, Power Grid]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-sun-pharmaceutical-industries-bajaj-auto-godfrey-phillips-india-power-grid/1669798</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1669798</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 1 February 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&O trading on 1 February 2026. Key Events to Watch: Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman is set to table and present the Union Budget in Parliament today, while January auto sales data will be keenly watched. Result Today: Latent View Analytics will announce its quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Sun Pharmaceutical Industries has reported a 16.03% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,368.81 crore on a 13.49% increase in revenue to Rs 15,520.54 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Auto’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on an 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Godfrey Phillips India reported a steady performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit after tax rising 8.7% year-on-year to Rs 343 crore, compared with Rs 316 crore in Q3 FY25. Net revenue rose 15.1% YoY to Rs 1,829 crore, compared with Rs 1,589 crore a year ago. On a consolidated basis, Meesho's net loss widened to Rs 490.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 37.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter Garware Hi-Tech Films (GHFL) reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 55.77 crore in Q3 FY26, down 8.3% year-on-year, on a 1.6% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 458.74 crore compared with Q3 FY25. NTPC reported an 8.27% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 5,597.05 crore on a 1.72% rise in net sales to Rs 45,845.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Power Grid Corporation of India reported an 8.4% YoY rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 4,184.96 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,861.63 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 12,395.09 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Steel Authority of India reported a 163.6% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 374 crore on an 11.8% rise in net sales to Rs 27,371.4 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. AstraZeneca Pharma India said it has received approval from the CDSCO to import, sell, and distribute Durvalumab (Imfinzi) solution for infusion in 120 mg/2.4 mL and 500 mg/10 mL strengths. Durvalumab, in combination with FLOT chemotherapy as neoadjuvant and adjuvant therapy, followed by single-agent durvalumab, is indicated for adult patients with resectable gastric or gastroesophageal junction adenocarcinoma (GC/GEJC).

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>