<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:51:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gains in INR backed by positive domestic equity markets]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gains-in-inr-backed-by-positive-domestic-equity-markets/1678302</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678302</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee gained 5 paise to settle at 90.69 (provisional) against the US dollar on Tuesday, backed by positive domestic equity markets and lower crude prices overseas.

The Indian rupee gained 5 paise to settle at 90.69 (provisional) against the US dollar on Tuesday, backed by positive domestic equity markets and lower crude prices overseas. Indian shares eked out modest gains on Tuesday amid easing tensions surrounding Iran and Russia. The benchmark BSE Sensex recovered from an early slide to end the session up 173.81 points, or 0.21 percent, at 83,450.96. The broader NSE Nifty index inched up by 42.65 points, or 0.17 percent, to 25,725.40 while the BSE mid-cap and small-cap indexes rose 0.3 percent and 0.9 percent, respectively. IT stocks bounced back after recent string of losses, with Infosys climbing nearly 2 percent after saying that artificial intelligence services accounted for 5.5 percent of its revenue in the December quarter. Sustained outflow of foreign funds and a firm American currency, however, weighed on the Indian currency and capped its gains. In the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 90.72 against the US dollar and moved in a tight range, touching a high of 90.64 and a low of 90.78 in intraday deals.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rupee closes up]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/rupee-closes-up/1678301</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678301</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Rupee closed higher at 90.7100 per Dollar on Tuesday (17 February 2026), versus its previous close of 90.7225 per Dollar.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/pexels-photo-68912_foreign-markets.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Copper near two-week low]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/copper-near-two-week-low/1678300</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678300</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[COMEX Copper futures fell sharply today, turning lower amid a bearish activity in metals.

COMEX Copper futures fell sharply today, turning lower amid a bearish activity in metals. The red metal currently trades down 1.74% at $5.70 per pound, testing near two-week low. Equities offered minimal cues. Trading volumes were thin as markets in mainland China, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan and South Korea were closed for the Lunar New Year holidays. Japanese NIKKEI 225 index eased 0.42%. European stocks gained marginally. The US markets were also shut on Monday in observance of Presidents' Day. Meanwhile, German economic confidence weakened in February after a strong rebound at the start of the year, the financial market survey conducted by the think tank ZEW showed Tuesday. The ZEW indicator of economic sentiment dropped to 58.3 in February from 59.6 in January, which was the highest since July 2021.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Base Metals<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/closeup-of-blue-chart-growth-progress-picture-id177428264_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex rises 174 pts, Nifty climbs past 25,700; IT, FMCG lead advance ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-rises-174-pts-nifty-climbs-past-25700-it-fmcg-lead-advance/1678292</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678292</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Frontline equity indices closed with moderate gains on Tuesday, extending their winning streak to a second straight session, as buying in index heavyweights lent support to the market.

Frontline equity indices closed with moderate gains on Tuesday, extending their winning streak to a second straight session, as buying in index heavyweights lent support to the market. The Nifty settled above the 25,700 mark, aided by strength in PSU banks, IT and FMCG stocks. After opening on a weak note, benchmarks rebounded sharply within the first hour and moved in a narrow range through the first half. Fresh buying interest during mid-session trade lifted sentiment further, pushing the Nifty higher into the close. The S&P BSE Sensex jumped 173.81 points or 0.21% to 83,450.96. The Nifty 50 index rallied 42.65 points or 0.17% to 25,725.40. Over the past two sessions, both the Sensex and the Nifty have advanced about 1% each. ITC (up 2.34%), Infosys (up 1.88%) and Larsen & Toubro (up 1.77%) boosted the Nifty higher today. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.31% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.86%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,447 shares rose and 1,756 shares fell. A total of 163 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 4.93% to 12.67. Economy: India’s trade engine gathered pace in January 2026, but imports ran faster than exports. Total exports, including merchandise and services, were estimated at $80.45 billion in January, up 13.17% from a year earlier. Imports stood at $90.83 billion, rising a sharper 18.76% YoY. For the April to January period of FY26, cumulative exports touched $720.76 billion, marking a 6.15% increase, while imports rose 6.54% to $823.41 billion. Breaking it down, merchandise exports in January edged up to $36.56 billion from $36.34 billion last year. Merchandise imports, however, jumped to $71.24 billion from $59.77 billion, widening the goods trade gap. Services continued to be the bright spot. Services exports surged to $43.90 billion from $34.75 billion, while services imports rose to $19.60 billion from $16.71 billion. On the merchandise side, growth was driven by engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy and poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports rose 10.37% to $10.40 billion, while petroleum product exports climbed 8.55% to $3.77 billion. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.22% to 6.653 compared with the previous session close of 6.668. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6950 compared with its close of 90.7400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.23% to Rs 152,850. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.22% to 97.03. The United States 10-year bond yield slipped 0.69% to 4.024. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 62 cents or 0.92% to $68.37 a barrel. Global Markets: Most European shares declined on Tuesday as UK's unemployment rate rose to a five-year high while wage growth slowed. The jobless rate climbed to 5.2% in the final quarter of last year, the Office for National Statistics said Tuesday, the highest since early 2021 and above the 5.1% economists were forecasting. Regular private sector wage growth, the BOE’s preferred pay indicator, fell to 3.4%, the lowest level in over five years. Separate tax figures showed the the number of employees on payroll fell 11,000 in January, taking the drop over the last year to 134,000. Together, the data are likely to reassure BOE policymakers that inflationary pressures in the labor market are easing fast enough to cut interest rates again. German inflation came in at 2.1% in January, up from 1.8% the previous month, the German Federal Statistical Office reported on Tuesday. Asian indices ended lower amid holiday-thinned volumes, while oil prices edged higher ahead of U.S.-Iran nuclear negotiations set to begin later today in Geneva. The Mainland Chinese, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan, and South Korean markets were closed on Tuesday for Lunar New Year holidays. U.S. markets were shut on Monday for Presidents’ Day. Stocks in Spotlight: Adani Energy Solutions gained 2.59%, Adani Enterprises rose 2.64%, Adani Green Energy advanced 2.55%, and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone climbed 1.62%. Adani Total Gas added 1.06%, while Adani Power rose 1.09%. The Adani Group will invest $100 billion to develop green energy-backed, hyperscale AI-ready data centres, in what it described as one of the world’s largest integrated energy-compute commitments. The initiative is expected to catalyse an additional $150 billion across manufacturing, servers and sovereign cloud services over the next decade, creating a projected $250 billion AI infrastructure ecosystem. Infosys advanced 1.83% after the company announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic, an AI safety and research company, to develop and deliver advanced enterprise AI solutions to companies across industries. Texmaco Rail & Engineering surged 4.49% after the company secured an order worth Rs 219.18 crore from Mumbai Railway Vikas Corporation (MRVC). Lupin added 0.93%. The company announced that it has signed a licence and supply agreement with Spektus Pharma to commercialize the novel antidepressant DeslaFlex in Canada. Highway Infrastructure soared 7.39% after the company said it has secured a contract from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for toll operations on key stretches of the Vadodara-Mumbai Expressway in Gujarat. Delhivery jumped 4.05% after the company announced a strategic partnership with electric mobility startup RIDEV (ANV Web Ventures) to deploy 150 high performance electric vehicles (EVs) across India over the next three months. KNR Constructions surged 5.75% after it has secured a Rs 2,163-crore contract for the construction of a four-lane elevated corridor along the East Coast Road (ECR). HFCL advanced 4.36% after the company, along with its material subsidiary HTL, secured purchase orders worth Rs 60.95 crore from a domestic telecom service provider. Cochin Shipyard advanced 3.95% after the state-run shipbuilder said it was declared the lowest bidder at a meeting held at the Ministry of Defence in New Delhi. TVS Supply Chain Solutions (TVS SCS) added 1.11% after the firm signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with ALA Group, to explore opportunities in India’s aerospace and defence supply chain.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at a premium]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-february-futures-trade-at-a-premium/1678290</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678290</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,736, a premium of 10.6 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,725.40 in the cash market.

The Nifty February 2026 futures closed at 25,736, a premium of 10.6 points compared with the Nifty's closing at 25,725.40 in the cash market. In the cash market, the Nifty 50 index rallied 42.65 points or 0.17% to 25,725.40. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 4.93% to 12.67. Infosys, HDFC Bank and ITC were the top-traded individual stock futures contracts in the F&O segment of the NSE. The February 2026 F&O contracts will expire on 24 February 2026.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Futures Market<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Market ends with decent gains; Nifty settles above 25,700 level; VIX drops 4.93%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/market-ends-with-decent-gains-nifty-settles-above-25700-level-vix-drops-493/1678289</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678289</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The frontline equity indices ended with moderate gains on Tuesday, extending rally for the second consecutive session, supported by buying in index heavyweights and strength in the broader market.

The frontline equity indices ended with moderate gains on Tuesday, extending rally for the second consecutive session, supported by buying in index heavyweights and strength in the broader market. The Nifty ended above the 25,700 level. In the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex jumped 173.81 points or 0.21% to 83,450.96. The Nifty 50 index rallied 42.65 points or 0.17% to 25,725.40. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1% each. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.31% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.86%. The market breadth was positive. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 4.93% to 12.67. Among the sectoral indices, the Nifty PSU Bank index (up 2.11%), the Nifty IT index (up 1.03%) and the Nifty FMCG index (up 0.90%) outperformed the Nifty 50 index. Meanwhile, the Nifty Media index (down 1.06%), Nifty Realty index (down 0.30%) and the Nifty Oil & Gas index (down 0.11%) and the underperformed the Nifty 50 index. Economy: India’s total exports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $80.45 billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17% vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $90.83 billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76% vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $720.76 billion, registering a positive growth of 6.15%. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $823.41 billion, registering a growth of 6.54%. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were $36.56 billion as compared to $36.34 billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were $71.24 billion as compared to $59.77 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is $43.90 billion as compared to $34.75 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is $19.60 billion as compared to $16.71 billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy & poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports increased by 10.37% from $9.42 billion in January 2025 to $10.40 billion in January 2026, while petroleum products exports increased by 8.55% from $3.48 billion in January 2025 to $3.77 billion in January 2026. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.22% to 6.653 compared with the previous session close of 6.668. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.6950 compared with its close of 90.7400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement declined 1.23% to Rs 152,850. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.22% to 97.03. The United States 10-year bond yield slipped 0.69% to 4.024. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement gained 62 cents or 0.92% to $68.37 a barrel. Global Markets: European shares advanced on Tuesday despite UK’s unemployment rate rose to a five-year high while wage growth slowed. UK unemployment reached its highest since the pandemic and wage growth eased as the labor market continued to weaken, prompting traders to increase bets on further interest-rate cuts from the Bank of England. The jobless rate climbed to 5.2% in the final quarter of last year, the Office for National Statistics said Tuesday, the highest since early 2021 and above the 5.1% economists were forecasting. Regular private sector wage growth, the BOE’s preferred pay indicator, fell to 3.4%, the lowest level in over five years. Separate tax figures showed the the number of employees on payroll fell 11,000 in January, taking the drop over the last year to 134,000. Together, the data are likely to reassure BOE policymakers that inflationary pressures in the labor market are easing fast enough to cut interest rates again. The pound weakened against the dollar, dropping 0.5% to $1.3564. Markets moved to fully price two rate cuts this year to 3.25% after the soft jobs data. German inflation came in at 2.1% in January, up from 1.8% the previous month, the German Federal Statistical Office reported on Tuesday. Asian markets ended lower amid holiday-thinned volumes, while oil prices edged higher ahead of U.S.–Iran nuclear negotiations set to begin later today in Geneva. The Mainland Chinese, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan, and South Korean markets were closed on Tuesday for Lunar New Year holidays. U.S. markets were shut on Monday for Presidents’ Day. Japan’s weakening economy remained in focus on Tuesday, one day after much softer than expected GDP numbers. The country on Monday reported its economy grew an annualized 0.2% in the fourth quarter, far below the widely reported gain forecast of 1.6% as government spending dragged on activity. In today's session, the Japanese yen strengthened 0.15% against the greenback to 153.28 per dollar. The weak figures highlight the challenges ahead for Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and should support her push for more aggressive fiscal stimulus, media reports said. The Bank of Japan next meets on rates in March, with traders forecasting only a slim chance for a hike. Widely reported polls in the media suggest that investors expect the central bank to wait until July before tightening policy again. Meanwhile, oil saw some price gains as investors looked ahead to the U.S. and Iran nuclear negotiations that are scheduled to begin in Geneva later in the day. The higher volatility in crude was triggered by the latest drill that was reportedly held by Iran’s Revolutionary Guards in the Hormuz Strait on Monday. The passage accounts for about 20% of global oil shipments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review Indices<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jio Financial Services CRO S. Anantharaman resigns; Sandeep Khetan appointed successor]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/jio-financial-services-cro-s-anantharaman-resigns-sandeep-khetan-appointed-successor/1678288</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678288</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said Anantharaman has resigned as Group Chief Risk Officer, with his last working day being 20 March 2026.

The company said Anantharaman has resigned as Group Chief Risk Officer, with his last working day being 20 March 2026. Subsequently, the board approved the appointment of Sandeep Khetan as Group Chief Risk Officer for a five-year term, effective 23 March 2026. Khetan is a Chartered Accountant with more than 24 years of experience in banking, with expertise spanning credit appraisal, credit risk, market risk and operational risk. He joined the company on 30 July 2025 as Head of Integrated Risk Management. In that role, he played a key part in establishing a unified risk governance framework across the group’s lending, insurance and payments businesses, strengthening internal controls and building a technology-led second line of defence. Before joining Jio Financial Services, Khetan spent over 23 years at ICICI Bank, where he led multiple functions and built high-performing teams. His experience includes overseeing credit and policy functions across SME, MSME and supply chain financing segments, as well as retail and business banking distribution. Jio Financial Services is a Core Investment Company (CIC), registered with the Reserve Bank of India. JFSL is a new-age institution, which operates a full-stack financial services business through customer-facing entities, including Jio Credit, Jio Insurance Broking, Jio Payment Solutions, Jio Leasing Services, Jio Finance Platform and Service, and Jio Payments Bank. The company reported 8.8% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 268.98 crore despite a 105.5% surge in total revenue from operations to Rs 900.90 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The scrip shed 0.08% to end at Rs 262.35 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/JioFinancialServicesLtd_17889422_20712.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quick Wrap: Nifty PSU Bank Index records a surge of 2.11%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quick-wrap-nifty-psu-bank-index-records-a-surge-of-211/1678283</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678283</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Nifty PSU Bank index ended up 2.11% at 9500.8 today.

Nifty PSU Bank index ended up 2.11% at 9500.8 today. The index has added 5.00% over last one month. Among the constituents, Bank of Baroda rose 3.66%, Punjab National Bank gained 3.52% and Indian Bank added 3.51%. The Nifty PSU Bank index has increased 61.00% over last one year compared to the 12.05% spike in benchmark Nifty 50 index. In other indices, Nifty Metal index has slid 1.06% and Nifty IT index added 1.03% on the day. In broad markets, the Nifty 50 added 0.17% to close at 25725.4 while the SENSEX increased 0.21% to close at 83450.96 today.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - End-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/business-city-stock-market-data-and-charts-on-skyscrapers-b_stock-trading.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajel Projects gains after signing Saudi Arabia JV pact]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajel-projects-gains-after-signing-saudi-arabia-jv-pact/1678284</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678284</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to an exchange filing, the proposed joint venture company (JVCo) will undertake engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) projects in high voltage (HV), extra high voltage (EHV) overhead transmission lines, substations and underground cabling in Saudi Arabia.

According to an exchange filing, the proposed joint venture company (JVCo) will undertake engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) projects in high voltage (HV), extra high voltage (EHV) overhead transmission lines, substations and underground cabling in Saudi Arabia. The JVCo will execute projects based on successful bids. Bajel Projects will hold 50% of the equity share capital of the JVCo, while the remaining 50% will be held by Al-Sharif Contracting & Commercial Development Co. Ltd. The board of the JVCo will comprise an equal number of nominees from both partners. Post incorporation, the JVCo will be classified as an associate of Bajel Projects. Each partner will initially invest up to SAR 1 million (approximately $270,000) in cash towards equity capital. The proposed entity is yet to be incorporated, with formation expected within three to six months from the signing of the agreement. The name of the JVCo is currently under discussion. The company clarified that the investment does not fall under the purview of related party transactions. Apart from the proposed equity participation in the JVCo, the promoters and promoter group have no interest in the entity. The joint venture aims to capture emerging EPC opportunities in Saudi Arabia. This association will bolster the company’s engineering capabilities, project management expertise and superior execution strength in the EPC segment. The partnership will further enhance the company’s international presence in the EPC business ecosystem and support its strategic growth objectives, while enabling it to capture emerging business opportunities in the region of KSA. This is in line with the main business of the company. Rajesh Ganesh, MD & CEO, Bajel Projects, said, "The signing of this joint venture agreement with Al Sharif Contracting and Commercial Development Company is a defining moment for Bajel Projects as we strategically expand our presence outside India. Saudi Arabia is currently witnessing an unprecedented infrastructure surge. This partnership enables us to bid for complex, extra-high-voltage inter-regional corridors and substations that are vital to Saudi Vision 2030 and beyond. BAJEL is excited and looking forward to contributing to the grand vision of the Kingdom ”. Al Sharif Contracting CEO, Engineer Hussain N. Gardezi, said, “We are happy to conclude the agreement. The resources of two big players will be pooled together for development of infrastructure of Kingdom of Saudi Arabia. This is the need of the hour in line with vision 2030 and beyond of Kingdom of Saudi Arabia. Kingdom of Saudi Arabia plans to build one of the most sustainable transmission networks to connect abundance renewable energy to the load centres." Bajel Projects (BPL) is a leading company in the business of power infrastructure, with a strong presence in the power transmission and power distribution sectors. BPL was formerly part of Bajaj Electricals under the EPC segment. Bajel Projects reported a consolidated net loss of Rs 0.42 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a net profit of Rs 1.46 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 9.64% year-on-year to Rs 562.34 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajelProjectsLtd_49283474_76479.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex settles 174 pts higher; Nifty ends above 25,700 level]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-settles-174-pts-higher-nifty-ends-above-25700-level/1678282</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678282</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key domestic indices ended with modest gains on Tuesday, extending rally for the second consecutive session, supported by buying in index heavyweights and strength in the broader market.

The key domestic indices ended with modest gains on Tuesday, extending rally for the second consecutive session, supported by buying in index heavyweights and strength in the broader market. The Nifty ended above the 25,700 level. PSU bank, IT, and FMCG shares advanced, while metal, realty, and oil & gas shares declined. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 173.81 points or 0.21% to 83,450.96. The Nifty 50 index rallied 42.65 points or 0.17% to 25,725.40. In the two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex and Nifty jumped 1% each. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The BSE 150 MidCap Index climbed 0.31% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.86%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,445 shares rose and 1,757 shares fell. A total of 150 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, dropped 4.93% to 12.67. Economy: India’s total exports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $80.45 billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17% vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $90.83 billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76% vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $720.76 billion, registering a positive growth of 6.15%. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $823.41 billion, registering a growth of 6.54%. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were $36.56 billion as compared to $36.34 billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were $71.24 billion as compared to $59.77 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is $43.90 billion as compared to $34.75 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is $19.60 billion as compared to $16.71 billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy & poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports increased by 10.37% from $9.42 billion in January 2025 to $10.40 billion in January 2026, while petroleum products exports increased by 8.55% from $3.48 billion in January 2025 to $3.77 billion in January 2026. Buzzing Index: The Nifty IT index rose 1.03% to 33,075.05. The index added 1.2% in the two consecutive trading sessions. Oracle Financial Services Software (up 2.13%), Infosys (up 1.74%), HCL Technologies (up 1.44%), Wipro (up 1.15%), Persistent Systems (up 0.88%), Tech Mahindra (up 0.79%), LTIMindtree (up 0.72%), Tata Consultancy Services (up 0.35%), and Mphasis (up 0.08%) surged. On the other hand, Coforge (down 1.06%) lower. Stocks in Spotlight: Adani Energy Solutions gained 2.79%, Adani Enterprises rose 2.72%, Adani Green Energy advanced 2.32%, and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone climbed 1.32%. Adani Total Gas added 1.06%, while Adani Power rose 0.91%. The Adani Group will invest $100 billion to develop green energy-backed, hyperscale AI-ready data centres, in what it described as one of the world’s largest integrated energy-compute commitments. The initiative is expected to catalyse an additional $150 billion across manufacturing, servers and sovereign cloud services over the next decade, creating a projected $250 billion AI infrastructure ecosystem. The group said the investment will expand its existing 2 GW national data centre platform under AdaniConnex toward a 5 GW capacity target. The infrastructure will integrate renewable power generation, transmission networks and high-density AI compute facilities within a unified architecture. The announcement also builds on partnerships with global technology players, including Google and Microsoft, and an expanded collaboration with Flipkart to develop additional AI-focused data centre capacity. A portion of GPU capacity will be reserved for Indian AI startups and research institutions to support domestic innovation. The proposed rollout is aligned with India’s push for technological self-reliance and data sovereignty, with the group positioning the initiative as a long-term energy and compute backbone for the country’s AI ecosystem. Infosys advanced 2.83% after the company announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic, an AI safety and research company, to develop and deliver advanced enterprise AI solutions to companies across industries. Texmaco Rail & Engineering surged 4% after the company secured an order worth Rs 219.18 crore from Mumbai Railway Vikas Corporation (MRVC). Lupin added 0.93%. The company announced that it has signed a licence and supply agreement with Spektus Pharma to commercialize the novel antidepressant DeslaFlex in Canada. Delhivery jumped 4.05% after the company announced a strategic partnership with electric mobility startup RIDEV (ANV Web Ventures) to deploy 150 high performance electric vehicles (EVs) across India over the next three months. BLS E-Services shed 0.39%. The company’s board approved to acquire 100% stake in Atyati Technologies (ATPL) from existing shareholders, to deliver financial and banking services to rural areas in India. TVS Supply Chain Solutions (TVS SCS) added 1.11% after the firm signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with ALA Group, to explore opportunities in India’s aerospace and defence supply chain. KNR Constructions surged 5.75% after it has secured a Rs 2,163-crore contract for the construction of a four-lane elevated corridor along the East Coast Road (ECR). HFCL advanced 4.36% after the company, along with its material subsidiary HTL, secured purchase orders worth Rs 60.95 crore from a domestic telecom service provider. Highway Infrastructure soared 7.39% after the company said it has secured a contract from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for toll operations on key stretches of the Vadodara–Mumbai Expressway in Gujarat. Cochin Shipyard advanced 3.95% after the state-run shipbuilder said it was declared the lowest bidder at a meeting held at the Ministry of Defence in New Delhi. Global Markets: European shares advanced on Tuesday despite UK’s unemployment rate rose to a five-year high while wage growth slowed. UK unemployment reached its highest since the pandemic and wage growth eased as the labor market continued to weaken, prompting traders to increase bets on further interest-rate cuts from the Bank of England. The jobless rate climbed to 5.2% in the final quarter of last year, the Office for National Statistics said Tuesday, the highest since early 2021 and above the 5.1% economists were forecasting. Regular private sector wage growth, the BOE’s preferred pay indicator, fell to 3.4%, the lowest level in over five years. Separate tax figures showed the the number of employees on payroll fell 11,000 in January, taking the drop over the last year to 134,000. Together, the data are likely to reassure BOE policymakers that inflationary pressures in the labor market are easing fast enough to cut interest rates again. The pound weakened against the dollar, dropping 0.5% to $1.3564. Markets moved to fully price two rate cuts this year to 3.25% after the soft jobs data. German inflation came in at 2.1% in January, up from 1.8% the previous month, the German Federal Statistical Office reported on Tuesday. Asian markets ended lower amid holiday-thinned volumes, while oil prices edged higher ahead of U.S.–Iran nuclear negotiations set to begin later today in Geneva. The Mainland Chinese, Hong Kong, Singapore, Taiwan, and South Korean markets were closed on Tuesday for Lunar New Year holidays. U.S. markets were shut on Monday for Presidents’ Day. Japan’s weakening economy remained in focus on Tuesday, one day after much softer than expected GDP numbers. The country on Monday reported its economy grew an annualized 0.2% in the fourth quarter, far below the widely reported gain forecast of 1.6% as government spending dragged on activity. In today's session, the Japanese yen strengthened 0.15% against the greenback to 153.28 per dollar. The weak figures highlight the challenges ahead for Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi and should support her push for more aggressive fiscal stimulus, media reports said. The Bank of Japan next meets on rates in March, with traders forecasting only a slim chance for a hike. Widely reported polls in the media suggest that investors expect the central bank to wait until July before tightening policy again. Meanwhile, oil saw some price gains as investors looked ahead to the U.S. and Iran nuclear negotiations that are scheduled to begin in Geneva later in the day. The higher volatility in crude was triggered by the latest drill that was reportedly held by Iran’s Revolutionary Guards in the Hormuz Strait on Monday. The passage accounts for about 20% of global oil shipments.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Quick Review<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aequs climbs after infusing funds in ASMIPL via rights issue]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aequs-climbs-after-infusing-funds-in-asmipl-via-rights-issue/1678281</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678281</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ASMIPL is engaged in the business of manufacturing of aerostructure parts.

ASMIPL is engaged in the business of manufacturing of aerostructure parts. As on 31st March 2025, the company reported a turnover of Rs 508.2 crore. This investment is a part of utilization of the IPO proceeds as specified in Aequs’ prospectus dated December 5, 2025. These funds will be utilised to repay the bank loan and to meet CAPEX requirements. Aequs has subscribed 79,89,750 shares at a price of Rs 288.76 per equity share, aggregating to a total consideration of Rs 230,71,20,210 Meanwhile, the company has entered into a nonbinding memorandum of understanding (MoU) with the Guidance, the nodal agency of the Government of Tamil Nadu (GoTN) for setting up a manufacturing unit in the Tamil Nadu. The company has proposed to set up unit for manufacturing components for aircraft engines, landing gear and systems and has proposed to invest up to Rs 1900 crore over a period of ten years. Aequs is a vertically integrated precision manufacturer operating within a single SEZ in India, with operations across the aerospace and consumer segments. The company operates a unique ecosystem with co-located capabilities spanning forging, precision machining, surface treatment, and assembly, enabling end -to-end manufacturing of complex, high-precision components. The company reported consolidated net loss of Rs 42.68 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 39.81 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 50.8% YoY to Rs 326.17 crore in Q3 FY26.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AequsLtd_41158355_34784.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[G R Infraprojects bags Rs 1,898-cr railway EPC contract in Madhya Pradesh]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/g-r-infraprojects-bags-rs-1898-cr-railway-epc-contract-in-madhya-pradesh/1678280</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678280</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project involves execution of earthwork, minor and major bridges, important bridges, viaducts, road overbridges (RCC box type), RUB/LHS, station buildings, tunnels, track work and other associated works.

The project involves execution of earthwork, minor and major bridges, important bridges, viaducts, road overbridges (RCC box type), RUB/LHS, station buildings, tunnels, track work and other associated works. The contract has been awarded under the engineering, procurement and construction (EPC) mode and is scheduled to be completed within 900 days from the appointed date. GR Infraprojects is engaged in the construction of infrastructure facilities on an engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) and build, operate, and transfer (BOT) basis. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 37.70% to Rs 232.15 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 168.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 35.91% YoY to Rs 2,039.49 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Shares of GR Infraprojects shed 0.39% to Rs 975.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GRInfraprojectsLtd_18239026_35408.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Anand Rathi Wealth incorporates subsidiary in GIFT City ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/anand-rathi-wealth-incorporates-subsidiary-in-gift-city/1678278</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678278</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The subsidiary will set up a fund management entity to undertake fund management activities through alternate investment fund (AIF).

The subsidiary will set up a fund management entity to undertake fund management activities through alternate investment fund (AIF). It will apply for fund management license under International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA) (Fund Management) Regulations, 2025. The company has subscribed to 100% of the share capital of Anand Rathi FME (IFSC), acquiring 10,000 equity shares of Rs 10 each for a total cash consideration of Rs 1,00,000. Anand Rathi Wealth is among India’s leading wealth management firms, catering to high and ultra-high-net-worth individuals with a unique and differentiated client strategy. The company reported 29.6% rise in net profit to Rs 100.1 crore on a 22.2% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 289.6 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The counter rose 0.09% to Rs 3001.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Anand-Rathi-Wealth_80898926_67729.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[The Anup Engineering Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/the-anup-engineering-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1678276</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678276</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Hindustan Copper Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd, Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd and Engineers India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 17 February 2026.

Hindustan Copper Ltd, Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd, Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd and Engineers India Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 17 February 2026. The Anup Engineering Ltd crashed 4.67% to Rs 1793 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 14028 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 14024 shares in the past one month. Hindustan Copper Ltd tumbled 4.66% to Rs 547.7. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 20.53 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 51.65 lakh shares in the past one month. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd lost 4.29% to Rs 259.7. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.65 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 93838 shares in the past one month. Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd shed 4.15% to Rs 540.4. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 3.06 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.04 lakh shares in the past one month. Engineers India Ltd slipped 3.97% to Rs 217.75. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 47.17 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7.43 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TheAnupEngg_12732804_73498.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Naksh Precious Metals Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/naksh-precious-metals-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1678273</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678273</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shiva Mills Ltd, Semac Construction Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd and Indowind Energy Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 17 February 2026.

Shiva Mills Ltd, Semac Construction Ltd, Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd and Indowind Energy Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 17 February 2026. Naksh Precious Metals Ltd lost 9.85% to Rs 5.49 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 11799 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 7771 shares in the past one month. Shiva Mills Ltd crashed 9.32% to Rs 54.77. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 180 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 789 shares in the past one month. Semac Construction Ltd tumbled 8.42% to Rs 244.05. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 8 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 750 shares in the past one month. Lypsa Gems & Jewellery Ltd corrected 7.97% to Rs 5.43. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 6399 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 11334 shares in the past one month. Indowind Energy Ltd plummeted 7.85% to Rs 11.03. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 68547 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 67238 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VaksonsAutomob_57424103445_66072.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[KNR Constructions jumps after winning Rs 2,163-cr ECR elevated corridor project]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/knr-constructions-jumps-after-winning-rs-2163-cr-ecr-elevated-corridor-project/1678274</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678274</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The project spans from Km 11+480 to Km 11+800 (West Avenue Road) and up to Km 24+780 (Thiruvanmiyur to Uthandi) on SH-49, strengthening the company’s presence in the road infrastructure segment.

The project spans from Km 11+480 to Km 11+800 (West Avenue Road) and up to Km 24+780 (Thiruvanmiyur to Uthandi) on SH-49, strengthening the company’s presence in the road infrastructure segment. The project will be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM) with a construction period of 1,095 days and an operation period of five years from the commercial operation date (COD). The signing of the concession agreement is subject to the outcome of W.A. No. 284 of 2026 pending before the Madras High Court. Once completed, the corridor is expected to improve traffic flow and connectivity along the ECR, reinforcing KNR Constructions’ position in large-scale infrastructure projects. KNR Constructions is engaged in the business of infrastructure sector, primarily in the construction of roads, bridges, flyovers and irrigation projects. The company’s consolidated net profit tanked 58.6% to Rs 102.80 crore on 12.4% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 743.20 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KNRConstruct_79641670773_28334.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Adani Group stocks gain after $100 billion AI infrastructure push]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/adani-group-stocks-gain-after-100-billion-ai-infrastructure-push/1678272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678272</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Adani Energy Solutions gained 2.59%, Adani Enterprises rose 2.44%, Adani Green Energy advanced 2.14%, and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone climbed 1.57%.

Adani Energy Solutions gained 2.59%, Adani Enterprises rose 2.44%, Adani Green Energy advanced 2.14%, and Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone climbed 1.57%. Adani Total Gas added 0.80%, while Adani Power rose 0.67%. The Adani Group will invest $100 billion to develop green energy-backed, hyperscale AI-ready data centres, in what it described as one of the world’s largest integrated energy-compute commitments. The initiative is expected to catalyse an additional $150 billion across manufacturing, servers and sovereign cloud services over the next decade, creating a projected $250 billion AI infrastructure ecosystem. The group said the investment will expand its existing 2 GW national data centre platform under AdaniConnex toward a 5 GW capacity target. The infrastructure will integrate renewable power generation, transmission networks and high-density AI compute facilities within a unified architecture. The announcement also builds on partnerships with global technology players, including Google and Microsoft, and an expanded collaboration with Flipkart to develop additional AI-focused data centre capacity. A portion of GPU capacity will be reserved for Indian AI startups and research institutions to support domestic innovation. The proposed rollout is aligned with India’s push for technological self-reliance and data sovereignty, with the group positioning the initiative as a long-term energy and compute backbone for the country’s AI ecosystem.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AdaniEnterp_85164503493_4244.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex jumps 124 pts; FMCG shares advance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-jumps-124-pts-fmcg-shares-advance/1678269</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678269</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade.

The key equity benchmarks traded with modest gains in mid-afternoon trade. Nifty traded a tad above the 25,700 level after hitting the day's low of 25,570.30 in early trade. FMCG shares extended gains for the second consecutive trading session. At 14:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, jumped 123.77 points or 0.15% to 83,400.92. The Nifty 50 index rose 3.50 points or 0.03% to 25,702.20. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index added 0.11% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index rose 0.74%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,391 shares rose and 1,680 shares fell. A total of 194 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s total exports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $80.45 billion, registering a positive growth of 13.17% vis-à-vis January 2025. Total imports (merchandise and services combined) for January 2026 are estimated at $90.83 billion, registering a positive growth of 18.76% vis-à-vis January 2025. India’s total exports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $720.76 billion registering a positive growth of 6.15%. Total imports during April-January 2025-26 are estimated at $823.41 billion registering a growth of 6.54%. Merchandise exports during January 2026 were $36.56 billion as compared to $36.34 billion in January 2025. Merchandise imports during January 2026 were $71.24 billion as compared to $59.77 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services export for January 2026 is $43.90 billion as compared to $34.75 billion in January 2025. The estimated value of services imports for January 2026 is $19.60 billion as compared to $16.71 billion in January 2025. Major drivers of merchandise exports growth in January 2026 include engineering goods, petroleum products, meat, dairy & poultry products, marine products, and iron ore. Engineering goods exports increased by 10.37% from $9.42 billion in January 2025 to $10.40 billion in January 2026, while petroleum products exports increased by 8.55% from $3.48 billion in January 2025 to $3.77 billion in January 2026. Buzzing Index: The Nifty FMCG index rose 0.72% to 51,690.90. The index rose 1.55% in the two consecutive trading sessions. United Spirits (up 1.36%), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (up 1.24%), Tata Consumer Products (up 0.93%), Emami (up 0.77%), Godrej Consumer Products (up 0.75%), Varun Beverages (up 0.68%), Patanjali Foods (up 0.64%), Dabur India (up 0.49%) and Radico Khaitan (up 0.42%) rose. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper shed 0.40% to 6.641 compared with the previous session close of 6.668. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.7150 compared with its close of 90.7400 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement fell 1.28% to Rs 152,780. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.04% to 97.13. The United States 10-year bond yield shed 0.81% to 4.019. In the commodities market, Brent crude for April 2026 settlement rose 32 cents or 0.47% to $68.07 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Delhivery jumped 3.05% after the company announced a strategic partnership with electric mobility startup RIDEV (ANV Web Ventures) to deploy 150 high-performance electric vehicles (EVs) across India over the next three months. Refex Industries rose 0.24%. The company said that it has secured an order worth Rs 49.22 crore from a Mini Ratna public sector undertaking (PSU).

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-indicator-and-financial-data-view-from-led-dou_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Crude stays in rangebound mode]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/crude-stays-in-rangebound-mode/1678267</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678267</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[WTI crude oil futures are holding around $63 per barrel in tight moves.

WTI crude oil futures are holding around $63 per barrel in tight moves. Markets continue to eye tensions escalate between the United States (US) and Iran ahead of renewed nuclear talks in Geneva. Chinese markets are shut due to New Year holiday and US stocks were closed yesterday as well due to a public holiday, making it an overall lacklustre session for oil. Focus will now shift to the US weekly supplies data. MCX Crude oil futures are trading at Rs 5719 per barrel, down 1.24% on the day, struggling after a weak open. WTI Crude oil soared around 13% in last month but shed around 3% this month so far.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Crude Oil<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/silhouette-of-drilling-rig-on-the-north-sea-picture-id48328_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Newgen Software Technologies Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-newgen-software-technologies-ltd-counter/1678263</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1678263</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Cochin Shipyard Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Ola Electric Mobility Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 17 February 2026.

Cochin Shipyard Ltd, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd, Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd, Ola Electric Mobility Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 17 February 2026. Newgen Software Technologies Ltd recorded volume of 394.09 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 36.82 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 10.70 lakh shares. The stock gained 13.59% to Rs.526.00. Volumes stood at 13.16 lakh shares in the last session. Cochin Shipyard Ltd witnessed volume of 37.06 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.54 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4.92 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.60% to Rs.1,522.30. Volumes stood at 3.51 lakh shares in the last session. Go Digit General Insurance Ltd notched up volume of 20.79 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.89 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.53 lakh shares. The stock slipped 0.50% to Rs.330.55. Volumes stood at 6.38 lakh shares in the last session. Akums Drugs & Pharmaceuticals Ltd registered volume of 11.75 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 3.17 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3.71 lakh shares. The stock rose 2.64% to Rs.489.80. Volumes stood at 25.55 lakh shares in the last session. Ola Electric Mobility Ltd registered volume of 1205.51 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 2.93 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 411.46 lakh shares. The stock slipped 3.05% to Rs.27.95. Volumes stood at 853.59 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/NewgenSoftwareTechnologiesLtd_46602882106_13722.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>