<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gandhar Oil Refinery Q3 PAT jumps 68% YoY to Rs 32 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gandhar-oil-refinery-q3-pat-jumps-68-yoy-to-rs-32-cr/1667406</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667406</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax climbed 67.93% to Rs 45.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 26.88 crore posted in Q3 FY25.

Profit before tax climbed 67.93% to Rs 45.14 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 26.88 crore posted in Q3 FY25. EBITDA stood at Rs 59.1 crore, registering growth of 42.06% as compared with Rs 41.6 crore recorded in previous quarter same fiscal. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit soared 38.53% YoY to Rs 94.70 crore, while revenue increased 6.63% YoY to Rs 3,129.93 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Aslesh Parekh, joint managing director said, “We delivered a strong performance in Q3 FY26, supported by sustained domestic demand and our strategic focus on high-margin PHPO products. Despite global macroeconomic headwinds and logistical disruptions, we recorded sequential growth across all major financial indicators. Looking ahead, we remain optimistic about domestic demand and expect steady improvement in international logistics, further strengthening our confidence. Gandhar Oil Refinery India is a leading manufacturer of white oils by revenue with a growing focus on the consumer and healthcare end-industries. It is engaged in producing pharmaceutical, health care, and performance oil (PHPO), process insulating oil (PIO) and lubricants. The firm’s products are sold under flagship brand “Divyol”. The counter advanced 2.98% to Rs 163.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GandharOilRefineryIndiaLtd_37404581_38912.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund announces IDCW Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mirae-asset-mutual-fund-announces-idcw-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1667405</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667405</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes: Mirae Asset Equity Savings Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.07 per unit.

Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has announced 28 January 2025 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the following schemes: Mirae Asset Equity Savings Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.07 per unit. Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.165 per unit. Mirae Asset Healthcare Fund: Regular Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 1.92 per unit. Direct Plan – IDCW Option: Rs 2.21 per unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172204552_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quantum Nifty 50 ETF announces change in Face Value of Units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quantum-nifty-50-etf-announces-change-in-face-value-of-units/1667402</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667402</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Quantum Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Quantum Nifty 50 ETF from Rs.

Quantum Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Quantum Nifty 50 ETF from Rs. 10/- to Rs. 1/- of units, effective February 13, 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Face Value of Units of Quantum Nifty 50 ETF. Name of the Scheme Existing Face Value (Rs.) Proposed Face Value (Rs.) Quantum Nifty 50 ETF 10 1

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF announces change in Face Value of Units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/groww-gold-etf-and-groww-silver-etf-announces-change-in-face-value-of-units/1667400</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667400</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Groww Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF from Rs.

Groww Mutual Fund has decided the change in the face value per unit of Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF from Rs. 10/- to Rs. 1/- of units, effective February 06, 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Face Value of Units of Groww Gold ETF and Groww Silver ETF. Name of the Schemes Existing Face Value (Rs.) Proposed Face Value (Rs.) Groww Gold ETF 10 1 Groww Silver ETF 10 1

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BPCL Q3 PAT jumps 62% YoY to Rs 7,545 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bpcl-q3-pat-jumps-62-yoy-to-rs-7545-cr/1667336</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667336</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter.

Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Profit before tax (PBT) surged 63.43% YoY to Rs 10,093.99 crore during the quarter. Total expenses increased 4.17% YoY to Rs 1,27,279.21 crore in Q3 FY26. The cost of materials consumed stood at Rs 53,680.89 crore (up 5.62% YoY), while employee benefits expenses declined 28.37% YoY to Rs 860.52 crore during the period under review. In Q3 FY26, refinery throughput stood at 10.51 million metric tonnes (MMT), up 10.16% from 9.54 MMT in Q3 FY25. Domestic sales increased 4.76% YoY to 14.07 MMT in Q3 FY26 compared with 13.43 MMT in Q3 FY25. Domestic market sales growth stood at 4.76% in Q3 FY26, compared with 3.95% in Q3 FY25. Export sales improved to 0.38 MMT in Q3 FY26 from 0.26 MMT in Q3 FY25. The average gross refining margin (GRM) of the corporation for the nine months ended 31 December 2025 stood at $9.68 per barrel, compared with $5.95 per barrel in the corresponding period last year. On the margins front, the company’s operating margin improved to 6.77% in Q3 FY26 from 3.75% in Q3 FY25, while the net profit margin rose to 5.26% from 2.98% during the same period. The board of directors, at its meeting held on 23 January 2026, declared a second interim dividend of Rs 10 per equity share of face value Rs 10 each (100%) for the financial year 2025–26. The dividend will be paid through electronic mode on or before 21 February 2026. The Board has fixed Monday, 2 February 2026, as the record date to determine shareholder eligibility for the dividend. Bharat Petroleum Corporation is a public sector company which is engaged in the business of refining crude oil and marketing petroleum products. The counter slipped 1.37% to Rs 349.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BPCL_78782939994_2290.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MCX Q3 PAT jumps 151% YoY to Rs 401 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/mcx-q3-pat-jumps-151-yoy-to-rs-401-crore/1667272</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1667272</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Income from operations jumped 120.85% YoY to Rs 665.62 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Income from operations jumped 120.85% YoY to Rs 665.62 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Profit before tax stood at Rs 503.25 crore, registering a growth of 149.29% on a YoY basis. EBITDA increased 144% YoY to Rs 527 crore during the quarter. Average daily turnover (ADT) in the futures and options (F&O) segment rose to Rs 7,50,136 crore. Total expenses rose 56.38% YoY to Rs 192.40 crore in the December 2025 quarter. Employee benefits expense stood at Rs 44.42 crore (up 33.63% YoY), while finance costs declined 82.35% YoY to Rs 0.03 crore during the period under review. On a nine-month basis, the company’s consolidated net profit soared 88.84% YoY to Rs 801.78 crore, while revenue increased 72.04% YoY to Rs 1,413.06 crore in 9M FY26 compared with 9M FY25. Praveena Rai, Managing Director & CEO, MCX said, “It gives me great pleasure to share our results for Q3 of FY 2026. This quarter’s results underscore our continued momentum and deepening participation across segments. Guided by the highest level of governance and compliance, we are enhancing product breadth and operational readiness for growth, delivering value to hedgers, investors and members while shaping the future of commodity derivatives.” MCX is India's largest commodity derivatives exchange with around 98% market share in commodity futures. It offers trading in a diverse range of commodities, spanning multiple segments including bullion, energy, metals and agri commodities, as well as sectoral commodity indices. The counter slipped 1.40% to Rs 2,282.65 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MultiCommExc_54258329132_25746.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>