<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:45:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Rupee: Under pressure amid soaring international oil prices ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-rupee-under-pressure-amid-soaring-international-oil-prices/1680053</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680053</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Indian rupee came under renewed pressure in opening trades on Monday tracking surging oil prices and strength in greenback amid escalating tensions in the Middle East.

The Indian rupee came under renewed pressure in opening trades on Monday tracking surging oil prices and strength in greenback amid escalating tensions in the Middle East. INR opened at Rs 91.23 per dollar and fell to a low of 91.40 so far during the day. On Friday the counter ended at 91.08. Indian shares were sharply lower in early trade on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump signaled the U.S.-Israeli military assault on Iranian targets could continue for weeks. Israel launched new air strikes targeting Tehran and expanded its military campaign to include attacks on Iran-backed Hezbollah militants in Lebanon, suggesting the conflict may spread across the Middle East. The benchmark BSE Sensex was down 682 points, or 0.8 percent, at 80,605 while the broader NSE Nifty index fell by 233 points, or 0.9 percent, to 24,945. International oil prices are soaring amid disruptions in the Strait of Hormuz, which handles roughly one-fifth of global oil shipments. This does not bode well for the Indian unit.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id50_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ashok Leyland’s total sales climb 24% YoY to 22,157 units in Feb’26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ashok-leylands-total-sales-climb-24-yoy-to-22157-units-in-feb26/1680052</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680052</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Total Medium & Heavy Commercial Vehicles (M&HCV) sales jumped 28% YoY to 14,755 units in February 26, while light commercial vehicle (LCV) sales climbed 15% YoY to 7,402 units in February 2026.

Total Medium & Heavy Commercial Vehicles (M&HCV) sales jumped 28% YoY to 14,755 units in February 26, while light commercial vehicle (LCV) sales climbed 15% YoY to 7,402 units in February 2026. In the domestic market, total vehicle sales increased 28% to 20,314 units in February 2026 compared with 15,879 units in February 2025. Total Medium & Heavy commercial vehicles sales jumped 31% YoY to 13,264 units in February 2026. Ashok Leyland is involved in the manufacture and sale of a broad range of commercial vehicles and also makes engines for industrial and marine applications, as well as forgings and castings. The company’s consolidated net profit increased 6.8% YoY to Rs 813.49 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 761.92 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales jumped 23.6% to Rs 14,761.95 crore in the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The scrip shed 0.17% to Rs 210.75 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AshokLeyland_6904859924_31.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Bajaj Auto registers 27% YoY growth in Feb’26 auto sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bajaj-auto-registers-27-yoy-growth-in-feb26-auto-sales/1680051</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680051</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Domestic sales stood at 2.32 lakh units, up 27% YoY, while exports totalled 2.15 lakh units, marking a 28% YoY growth.

Domestic sales stood at 2.32 lakh units, up 27% YoY, while exports totalled 2.15 lakh units, marking a 28% YoY growth. Two-wheeler sales rose 27% to 3.79 lakh units, while commercial vehicle sales jumped 30% to 68,338 units in February 2026 over February 2025. On a year-to-date basis, Bajaj Auto registered a 9% growth in total auto sales, with 46.72 lakh units sold compared to 42.81 lakh units in the corresponding period last year. Bajaj Auto is engaged in the business of development, manufacturing, and distribution of automobiles such as motorcycles, commercial vehicles, electric two-wheelers, etc., and parts thereof. The company’s standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on an 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BajajAuto_20897586_28074.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Escorts Kubota's February 2026 sales rise 20% YoY to 10,339 units]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/escorts-kubotas-february-2026-sales-rise-20-yoy-to-10339-units/1680049</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680049</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While domestic sales also rose 22.1% to 9,725 units in February 2026 compared with 7,968 units sold in February 2025, aided by positive rural sentiment, higher farm activity, supportive government policies, GST reduction, and a favorable Rabi outlook.

While domestic sales also rose 22.1% to 9,725 units in February 2026 compared with 7,968 units sold in February 2025, aided by positive rural sentiment, higher farm activity, supportive government policies, GST reduction, and a favorable Rabi outlook. The company’s exports fell 1.3% to 614 units in February 2026 as against 622 units posted in February 2025. Further, the company’s construction equipment business division sold 588 machines in February 2026, registering a growth of 4.8% from 561 machines sold in February 2025. Escorts Kubota is primarily engaged in the business of manufacturing agricultural tractors, engines for agricultural tractors, construction, earthmoving, and material handling equipment; round and flat tubes; heating elements; and double-acting hydraulics. The company’s consolidated net profit increased 11.8% to Rs 358.32 crore on an 11.3% jump in net sales to Rs 3,280.49 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Shares of Escorts Kubota shed 0.76% to Rs 3,490 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Escorts_12276934110_161.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Benchmarks drop in early trade on Iran conflict with US, Israel; VIX zooms 17.17%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/benchmarks-drop-in-early-trade-on-iran-conflict-with-us-israel-vix-zooms-1717/1680035</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680035</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in early trade as rising tensions in the Middle East dampened global risk appetite.

The domestic equity indices traded with major losses in early trade as rising tensions in the Middle East dampened global risk appetite. Iran has moved to the centre of an intensifying conflict involving the United States and Israel, heightening geopolitical uncertainty. Fresh strikes over the weekend triggered a sharp rise in crude oil prices and prompted investors to shift towards safer assets. The risk-off sentiment weighed heavily on equities, resulting in significant early losses for the benchmark indices. The Nifty slipped below the 24,950 mark. Except for the metal index, all other sectoral indices on the NSE traded in the red. At 09:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, slumped 828.39 points or 1.03% to 80,448.56. The Nifty 50 index tanked 246.20 points or 0.99% to 24,938.65. The broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index declined 1.06% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 1.64%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 530 shares rose and 2,997 shares fell. A total of 181 shares were unchanged. Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 7,536.36 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 12,292.81 crore in the Indian equity market on 27 February 2026, provisional data showed. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, zoomed 17.71% to 16.13. Stocks in Spotlight: VST Tillers Tractors fell 0.83%. The company reported a 36.04% jump in total sales to 4,435 units in February 2026, up from 3,260 units sold in February 2025. Artefact Projects fell 2.20%. The company has secured a consultancy services contract worth Rs 3.53 crore from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI). The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and will be executed over a period of 36 months. Economy: India’s foreign exchange reserves declined by $2.11 billion to $723.608 billion for the week ended February 20, according to data released on Friday by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI). During the reporting week, foreign currency assets (FCAs)—the largest component of the reserves—fell by $1.039 billion to $572.564 billion, the central bank said. Gold reserves decreased by $977 million to $127.489 billion, the RBI added. Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) declined by $84 million to $18.84 billion. India’s reserve position with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) also dropped by $18 million to $4.716 billion during the week, according to the RBI data. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper rose 0.41% to 6.688 compared with the previous session close of 6.661. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged lower against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.2750 compared with its close of 91.0800 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 2 April 2026 settlement jumped 3.17% to Rs 167,221. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was up 0.22% to 97.82. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.43% to 3.975. In the commodities market, Brent crude for May 2026 settlement jumped $4 or 5.31% to $76.74 a barrel. Global Markets: Asian markets traded lower on Monday after the United States and Israel launch their most ambitious attacks on Iran in decades, killing Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei. U.S. and Israeli strikes, and the Iranian retaliation, have sent shockwaves across the Middle East and through sectors from shipping to air travel to oil on warnings of rising energy costs and disruption to business in the Gulf, a strategic waterway and global trade hub. Most Gulf equities fell on Sunday, though Boursa Kuwait suspended trading and the UAE ordered its stock markets closed on Monday, a sign of the growing economic disruption sweeping the Gulf. Oil futures initially jumped 8% before trimming gains to about 4%. West Texas Intermediate futures last traded at $69.68, while Brent crude was at $76.13 per barrel. Gold futures jumped 2.3% as investors piled into the global safe haven. Stock futures tumbled in overnight trading after the weekend strikes in Iran. Futures on the Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 517 points, or 1%. S&P 500 futures lost 1%, and Nasdaq 100 futures declined a little more than 1%. On Friday, stocks saw a sharp sell-off after the latest producer price index data came in much hotter than expected, adding sticky inflation to a list of concerns that has caused market turbulence this month. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 521.28 points, or 1.05%, to close at 48,977.92. The S&P 500 closed down 0.43% at 6,878.88, while the Nasdaq Composite lost 0.92% to settle at 22,668.21. The S&P 500 and Nasdaq finished in the red for February amid growing fears about the impact of artificial intelligence on specific industries and the overall economy. Fueling the downbeat sentiment, January’s producer price index, a measure of wholesale inflation, showed a 0.5% increase for the month. Media reports had suggested that the headline reading could come in at 0.3%. The core PPI reading, which excludes food and energy prices, recorded a 0.8% gain, much more than the 0.3% rise that was widely reported in the media.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stocking-around-1315269_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SML Mahindra reports 17% YoY rise in Feb’26 sales ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sml-mahindra-reports-17-yoy-rise-in-feb26-sales/1680034</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680034</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s cargo vehicle sales rose 4% to 486 units in February 2026 from 468 units in February 2025, while passenger vehicle sales soared 24% YoY to 1,017 units.

The company’s cargo vehicle sales rose 4% to 486 units in February 2026 from 468 units in February 2025, while passenger vehicle sales soared 24% YoY to 1,017 units. For the period April to February 2026, the company's total sales aggregated to 14,175 units, registering a growth of 19% from 11,906 units sold in the same period a year ago. SML Mahindra (formerly known as SML Isuzu) is primarily engaged in the business of the manufacture and sale of commercial vehicles and their parts. The company’s standalone net profit surged 3,209.43%, while revenue from operations increased 62.53% in Q3 FY26. Shares of SML Mahindra rose 0.03% to Rs 4,784.90 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SMLISUZU_60285231401_544.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TVS Motor total monthly sales climb 31% YoY in February'26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tvs-motor-total-monthly-sales-climb-31-yoy-in-february26/1680032</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680032</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Two-wheeler sales surged 30% year-on-year in February 2026, rising to 507,862 units from 391,889 units in February 2025.

Two-wheeler sales surged 30% year-on-year in February 2026, rising to 507,862 units from 391,889 units in February 2025. Domestic two-wheeler sales grew 32%, increasing from 276,072 units in February 2025 to 365,471 units in February 2026. Motorcycle sales grew 25%, rising from 192,960 units in February 2025 to 241,282 units in February 2026. Scooter sales increased 34%, from 164,415 units in February 2025 to 219,895 units in February 2026. Electric vehicle (EV) sales rose 60%, increasing from 24,017 units in February 2025 to 38,386 units in February 2026. Three-wheeler sales surged 77%, rising from 12,087 units in February 2025 to 21,446 units in February 2026. The company’s total exports grew 27%, increasing from 124,993 units in February 2025 to 158,268 units in February 2026. Two-wheeler exports rose 23%, from 115,817 units in February 2025 to 142,391 units in February 2026. TVS Motor Company is a reputed global manufacturer of two-wheelers and three-wheelers, with four manufacturing facilities located in India and Indonesia. The company’s standalone net profit jumped 52.04% to Rs 940.37 crore on 37.14% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 12,476.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. The stock added 0.20% to Rs 3,877.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TVSMotorCo_68147319859_8029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hero MotoCorp posts 44% YoY jump in February two-wheeler sales]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/hero-motocorp-posts-44-yoy-jump-in-february-two-wheeler-sales/1680027</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680027</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company also reported 18% YoY growth in VAHAN registrations, with 458,346 units registered during February 2026.

The company also reported 18% YoY growth in VAHAN registrations, with 458,346 units registered during February 2026. Motorcycle dispatches increased by 42% to 499,756 units in February 2026 from 352,312 units in the corresponding month last year. Scooter volumes rose 56% YoY to 58,460 units as against 35,756 units in February 2025, supported by sustained demand in the 100cc–125cc segment. Domestic sales grew 37% YoY to 516,968 units during the period under review. Exports rose 34% to 41,248 units in February 2026 from 30,772 units in the year-ago period, reflecting improved traction in key international markets. VIDA, the company’s electric mobility business, continued its expansion momentum, recording 12,514 VAHAN registrations in February 2026, reflecting rising adoption of electric two-wheelers across key urban markets. On a year-to-date (YTD) basis, the company has dispatched 58,70,636 units, up 7% YoY, as against 53,49,583 units in the corresponding period of the previous financial year. Hero MotoCorp is the world's largest manufacturer of motorcycles and scooters, with a global footprint spanning 48 countries across Asia, Africa, and Latin America. It has collaborations with Harley-Davidson and Zero Motorcycles and strategic investments in Ather Energy and Euler Motors. The company has reported 12% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 1,349 crore on a 21% increase in revenue from operations from Rs 12,328 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. The scrip fell 1.08% to currently trade at Rs 5647.70 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeroMotocorp_63306901672_237.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty indicates gap down opening for equities as US-Iran tensions escalate]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gift-nifty-indicates-gap-down-opening-for-equities-as-us-iran-tensions-escalate/1680019</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680019</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty March 2026 futures were down 216.50 points, suggesting a gap down opening for the Nifty 50 today.

GIFT Nifty: GIFT Nifty March 2026 futures were down 216.50 points, suggesting a gap down opening for the Nifty 50 today. Institutional Flows: Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) sold shares worth Rs 7,536.36 crore, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) were net buyers to the tune of Rs 12,292.81 crore in the Indian equity market on 27 February 2026, provisional data showed. The FIIs have sold shares worth Rs 11,002.35 crore in the cash market in February. This follows their cash sales of Rs 41,435.22 crore in January 2026 and Rs 34,349.62 crore in December. Global Markets: Asian markets traded lower on Monday after the United States and Israel launch their most ambitious attacks on Iran in decades, killing Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei. U.S. and Israeli strikes, and the Iranian retaliation, have sent shockwaves across the Middle East, and through sectors from shipping to air travel to oil on warnings of rising energy costs and disruption to business in the Gulf, a strategic waterway and global trade hub. Most Gulf equities fell on Sunday though Boursa Kuwait suspended trading and the UAE ordered its stock markets closed on Monday, a sign of the growing economic disruption sweeping the Gulf. Oil futures initially jumped 8% before trimming gains to about 4%. West Texas Intermediate futures last traded at $69.68, while Brent crude was at $76.13 per barrel. Gold futures jumped 2.3% as investors piled into the global safe haven. Stock futures tumbled in overnight trading after the weekend strikes in Iran. Futures on the Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 517 points, or 1%. S&P 500 futures lost 1% and Nasdaq 100 futures declined a little more than 1%. On Friday, stocks saw sharp sell off after the latest producer price index data came in much hotter than expected, adding sticky inflation to a list of concerns that has caused market turbulence this month. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 521.28 points, or 1.05%, to close at 48,977.92. The S&P 500 closed down 0.43% at 6,878.88, while the Nasdaq Composite lost 0.92% to settle at 22,668.21. The S&P 500 and Nasdaq finished in the red for February amid growing fears about the impact of artificial intelligence on specific industries and the overall economy. Fueling the downbeat sentiment, January’s producer price index, a measure of wholesale inflation, showed a 0.5% increase for the month. Media reports had suggested that the headline reading could come in at 0.3%. The core PPI reading, which excludes food and energy prices, recorded a 0.8% gain, much more than the 0.3% rise that was widely reported in the media. Domestic Market: Domestic equity benchmarks ended sharply lower on Friday, pressured by continued foreign institutional investor outflows and escalating geopolitical tensions. Investor sentiment remained fragile amid rising hostilities between Pakistan and Afghanistan and lingering uncertainty over US-Iran talks. The Nifty slipped below the 25,200 mark, weighed down by losses in auto and FMCG stocks. The index opened on a weak note and stayed under sustained selling pressure through most of the session. A fresh wave of selling in the final hours intensified the decline, pulling the benchmark closer to the day’s low by the closing bell. The S&P BSE Sensex tanked 961.42 points or 1.17% to 81,287.19. The Nifty 50 index dropped 317.90 points or 1.25% to 25,178.65.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Pre-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-_002_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stock Alert: Aurobindo Pharma, Oriental Rail, ITCONS E-Solution, SWPE, Artefact Projects]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/stock-alert-aurobindo-pharma-oriental-rail-itcons-e-solution-swpe-artefact-projects/1680016</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680016</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital will be banned from F&O trading on Monday 02 March 2026.

Securities in F&O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital will be banned from F&O trading on Monday 02 March 2026. IPO Listing: Shree Ram Twistex will make its debut on the stock exchanges on Monday. The issue was subscribed 43.66 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026, and it closed on 25 February 2026. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions will make its debut on the stock exchanges on Monday. The issue was subscribed 0.94 times. The issue opened for bidding on 23 February 2026 and it closed on 25 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Auto stocks likely to remain focus as they will declare monthly auto sales data. Oriental Rail Infrastructure has secured an order worth Rs 1.73 crore from the Integral Coach Factory (ICF), Chennai, a unit of Indian Railways. The contract involves the manufacturing, supply and installation of 13 sets of “one coach set of seats and berths with hardware.” The order is to be executed by March 29, 2026. Artefact Projects has secured a consultancy services contract worth Rs 3.53 crore from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI). The contract has been awarded by a domestic entity and will be executed over a period of 36 months. ITCONS E-Solution has secured an order worth Rs 2.62 crore from Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL), under the Department of Defence Production, Ministry of Defence. The contract involves deployment of 43 resources for a period of two years. It will commence on 3 March 2026 and remain valid till 2 March 2028, unless extended by mutual agreement between the parties. Aurobindo Pharma has informed that the USFDA inspection concluded with four observations at a formulation manufacturing facility of its wholly owned subsidiary, Eugia Pharma Specialities, in Telangana. Kabra Extrusiontechnik has secured an order worth approximately Rs 133 crore from a domestic customer for energy storage solutions. The contract pertains to contract manufacturing and is scheduled to be executed during FY 2026–27. Due to confidentiality obligations and commercial sensitivity, the name of the customer has not been disclosed. South West Pinnacle Exploration (SWPE) has secured a work order worth Rs 307 crore from Hind Metal Exploration Services (HMESPL), a wholly-owned subsidiary of Hindustan Zinc, for mineral exploration services in Rajasthan.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Stock Alert<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/businessman-checking-stock-market-data-picture-id826058232_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VST Tillers reports 36% YoY sales growth in February 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vst-tillers-reports-36-yoy-sales-growth-in-february-2026/1680005</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1680005</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company’s power tiller sales grew by 34.24% to 3,963 units in February 2026, compared to 2,952 units in the same month last year.

The company’s power tiller sales grew by 34.24% to 3,963 units in February 2026, compared to 2,952 units in the same month last year. Tractor sales also grew 53.24% to 472 units in February 2026, up from 308 units sold in February 2025. VST Tillers Tractors is engaged in the manufacturing of power tillers and diesel engines. The company’s consolidated net profit soared to Rs 30.43 crore in Q3 FY26, compared to Rs 1.28 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 43.5% year-on-year to Rs 314.30 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The counter rose 0.14% to Rs 5,779.50 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VSTTillTract_79364939960_2531.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>