<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Reliance denies reports of Russian crude shipments to Jamnagar refinery]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/reliance-denies-reports-of-russian-crude-shipments-to-jamnagar-refinery/1663400</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663400</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company was responding to reports suggesting that shipments of Russian oil were approaching the Jamnagar complex.

The company was responding to reports suggesting that shipments of Russian oil were approaching the Jamnagar complex. Reliance said its refinery has not received any Russian crude cargo for nearly three weeks and is not expecting any deliveries in January. Reliance clarified that it had already committed in November 2025 to halting the use of Russian crude at its export-oriented unit, citing rising geopolitical and regulatory risks. These include the threat of higher US tariffs linked to purchases of Russian oil. The company also pointed to inaccuracies in satellite-based vessel tracking data, stating that automated signals and intermediary-linked trades do not reflect its actual procurement plans. It said it is distancing itself from potential secondary sanctions and moving towards a more diversified crude sourcing strategy. The issue remains sensitive as Russian oil imports have drawn scrutiny from the US. In August 2025, US President Donald Trump imposed 25% penalty tariffs on Indian imports over New Delhi’s purchases of Russian oil. Reliance, once India’s largest buyer of Russian crude, said it is now sourcing non-Russian oil for exports to ensure sanctions compliance and continued access to key global markets. Reliance Industries is India's largest private sector company. Its activities span hydrocarbon exploration and production, petroleum refining and marketing, petrochemicals, advanced materials and composites, renewables (solar and hydrogen), retail and digital services. The company‘s consolidated net profit jumped 9.54% to Rs 18,165 crore on 9.94% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2,58,898 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. Shares of Reliance Industries are currently down 4.49% at Rs 1506.60 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RelianceInds_29114129325_476.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Systematix Corporate Services Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/systematix-corporate-services-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1663399</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663399</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vivimed Labs Ltd, Indian Metals & Ferro Alloys Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 January 2026.

Vivimed Labs Ltd, Indian Metals & Ferro Alloys Ltd, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd and California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 06 January 2026. Systematix Corporate Services Ltd lost 19.33% to Rs 110 at 14:30 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 3.09 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.94 lakh shares in the past one month. Vivimed Labs Ltd tumbled 9.94% to Rs 12.23. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 7.8 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10049 shares in the past one month. Indian Metals & Ferro Alloys Ltd crashed 9.55% to Rs 1317. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 81090 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 9187 shares in the past one month. Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd corrected 9.15% to Rs 48.15. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 110 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 544 shares in the past one month. California Software Company Ltd Partly Paidup pared 8.97% to Rs 4.77. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 143 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2097 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SystematixCorp_19909031607_3845.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold storms higher on Venezuela upheaval and flight to safety]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-storms-higher-on-venezuela-upheaval-and-flight-to-safety/1663395</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663395</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold prices surged toward $4490 per ounce in Asia electronic trading on Tuesday, marking a third consecutive session of gains as investors flocked to safe-haven assets amid escalating political turmoil in Venezuela.

Gold prices surged toward $4490 per ounce in Asia electronic trading on Tuesday, marking a third consecutive session of gains as investors flocked to safe-haven assets amid escalating political turmoil in Venezuela. Bullion jumped more than $100 on Monday following a US military operation over the weekend that resulted in the capture of President Nicolas Maduro, sharply lifting geopolitical risk sentiment. President Donald Trump further intensified concerns after stating that the US would temporarily run Venezuela and warning of a second strike if the interim government failed to meet Washington’s demands. Attention has now shifted to key US labor market indicators, with the December jobs report due on Friday expected to offer fresh insight into the Federal Reserve’s policy trajectory. In the domestic market, MCX February gold futures rose 0.4% to ₹138625 per 10 grams, mirroring the strong momentum in international prices.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/IDBIGoldETF_23794422_41429.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex slumps 460 pts; realty shares decline]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-slumps-460-pts-realty-shares-decline/1663393</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663393</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity indices traded with significant losses in the mid- afternoon trade.

The domestic equity indices traded with significant losses in the mid- afternoon trade. The Nifty traded below the 26,150 mark. Realty shares declined after advancing for previous four consecutive trading session. At 14:28 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 459.91 points or 0.54% to 84,980.50. The Nifty 50 index dropped 117.15 points or 0.45% to 26,133.15. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.57% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.59%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,497 shares rose and 2,595 shares fell. A total of 185 shares were unchanged. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index declined 0.44% to 913.40. The index added 5.01% in the previous four consecutive trading session. Sobha (down 1.66%), Brigade Enterprises (down 1.01%), Lodha Developers (down 0.94%), Oberoi Realty (down 0.89%) and SignatureGlobal India (down 0.64%), DLF (down 0.56%), Anant Raj (down 0.43%), Godrej Properties (down 0.03%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 0.01%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper added 0.02% to 6.634 compared with previous session close of 6.633. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 90.2050 compared with its close of 90.3000 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2025 settlement added 0.33% to Rs 138,576. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.04% to 98.28. The United States 10-year bond yield added 0.29% to 4.180. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2025 settlement shed 38 cents or 0.62% to $61.38 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Ddev Plastiks Industries shed 0.53%. The company announced that its board has approved the proposal to venture into the Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) business, marking its expansion into the renewable energy sector. Desco Infratech fell 1.74%. The company said it has secured orders worth Rs 5.37 crore from Adani Total Gas (ATGL), Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL), and Maharashtra Natural Gas (MNGL).

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/stock-market-graph-and-bar-chart-price-display-picture-id62_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[LG Electronics India gains after inking APA with CBDT]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/lg-electronics-india-gains-after-inking-apa-with-cbdt/1663392</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663392</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Following the signing of APA, contingent liabilities of Rs 172.43 crore related to direct taxes will become Nil.

Following the signing of APA, contingent liabilities of Rs 172.43 crore related to direct taxes will become Nil. In Addition, contingency amount of Rs 315.30 crore related to royalty payments to LG Electronics Inc., Korea (Promoter) will also become Nil. The company will incur net tax expense of Rs 17.71 crore (excluding applicable interest, which will be computed as per payment date). Further, LG Electronics India will be required to make net payment of Rs 3.85 crore to LG Electronics Inc. under the secondary adjustment provisions in compliance with India’s transfer pricing regulations. Earlier, the company had filed advance pricing agreement application dated March 29, 2018, with the Tax Authorities of India for the period of 9 Years i.e. April 1, 2014 to March 31, 2023. LG Electronics India (LEIL), a subsidiary of South Korea–based LG Electronics, is one of India’s leading consumer durables companies. It manufactures and sells a wide range of products, including TVs, refrigerators, washing machines, and air conditioners, serving both retail and institutional customers. The company’s standalone net profit declined 27.3% to Rs 389.43 crore despite 1% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 6,174.03 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/LGElectronicsIndiaLtd_35129397_18787.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes jump at Poly Medicure Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-jump-at-poly-medicure-ltd-counter/1663391</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663391</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Dr Agarwals Health Care Ltd, Nava Ltd, Trent Ltd, Redington Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 06 January 2026.

Dr Agarwals Health Care Ltd, Nava Ltd, Trent Ltd, Redington Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 06 January 2026. Poly Medicure Ltd saw volume of 14.7 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 11.86 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 1.24 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.14% to Rs.1,778.40. Volumes stood at 96746 shares in the last session. Dr Agarwals Health Care Ltd notched up volume of 8.65 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 10.13 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 85357 shares. The stock rose 2.53% to Rs.512.75. Volumes stood at 59639 shares in the last session. Nava Ltd saw volume of 22.69 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.66 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.62 lakh shares. The stock increased 5.67% to Rs.616.30. Volumes stood at 4.22 lakh shares in the last session. Trent Ltd witnessed volume of 43.96 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.65 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 6.61 lakh shares. The stock dropped 8.40% to Rs.4,057.70. Volumes stood at 5.1 lakh shares in the last session. Redington Ltd witnessed volume of 84.04 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 5.11 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 16.46 lakh shares. The stock increased 3.25% to Rs.287.50. Volumes stood at 13.72 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PolyMedicure_79821669903_13973.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal MF launches Diversified Flexicap Passive Fund Of Funds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/motilal-oswal-mf-launches-diversified-flexicap-passive-fund-of-funds/1663390</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663390</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has launched a new scheme, the Motilal Oswal Diversified Equity Flexicap Passive Fund of Funds.

Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund has launched a new scheme, the Motilal Oswal Diversified Equity Flexicap Passive Fund of Funds. The new fund offer opened on 2 January 2026, and will close on 15 January 2026. The open-ended fund of funds will invest in passive equity funds and ETFs to provide diversified exposure across large-cap, mid-cap and small-cap segments through a structured allocation model. The scheme will begin with an equal allocation of one-third each to large, mid and small caps. Allocations will be reviewed quarterly and rebalanced only if any segment deviates by more than 5% from its target weight. According to the fund house, this approach is intended to systematically rebalance portfolios by trimming outperforming segments and increasing exposure to underweighted segments, without relying on market timing. The scheme aims to address challenges faced by investors in predicting market-cap leadership cycles, as leadership has historically rotated between large, mid and small caps across market cycles. By investing through passive instruments, the fund seeks to avoid structural large-cap bias seen in several flexicap strategies. The benchmark for the scheme is the Nifty 500 Total Return Index. The minimum investment during the NFO period is Rs 500, with additional investments in multiples of Re 1. On an ongoing basis, the minimum lump sum investment remains Rs 500. An exit load of 1% will be applicable if units are redeemed within 15 days from the date of allotment, with no exit load thereafter. The fund will be managed by Swapnil Mayekar for the equity component and Rakesh Shetty for the debt component. Motilal Oswal Asset Management Company said the scheme is suitable for investors seeking long-term capital growth through diversified exposure to equity market segments using a passive investment approach.

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/yellow-warning-mutual-funds-highway-road-sign-picture-id512_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's auto retails grew 7.71% in CY'25; reports FADA]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-auto-retails-grew-771-in-cy25-reports-fada/1663389</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663389</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to the data released by the Federation of Automobile Dealers Associations (FADA), India's auto retails delivered a confident close, with total retails at 2,81,61,228 units, registering a 7.71% Y-o-Y growth.

According to the data released by the Federation of Automobile Dealers Associations (FADA), India's auto retails delivered a confident close, with total retails at 2,81,61,228 units, registering a 7.71% Y-o-Y growth. The year, however, was a tale of two halves—Jan to Aug remained subdued despite supportive macro cues such as direct tax relief in the Union Budget and RBI’s cumulative rate easing through 2025 . The turning point came from September onwards, when the landmark GST 2.0 rate rationalization—including meaningful reductions for mass segments like small cars, two-wheelers (up to 350cc), three-wheelers and key commercial categories—improved affordability and lifted sentiment, leading to a clear upshift through Sept–Dec. Category-wise, 2W grew 7.24%, PV rose 9.70%, CV expanded 6.71%, and Tractors posted 11.52%. Importantly, the year saw broad-based participation—urban retail grew 8.20% and rural 7.31%—and within PVs, rural demand was a standout, growing 12.31% versus 8.08% in urban markets, underlining the strengthening spread of personal mobility beyond metros. CY’25 also reinforced the transition underway—EV share moved up in 2W, PV, CV and remained dominant in 3W, while CNG strengthened its presence in PV and CV, signalling a more diversified mobility mix. December’25 proved to be a strong finish to the calendar year for auto retail. The industry retailed 20,28,821 vehicles, posting a healthy 14.63% Y-o-Y growth. In Two-Wheelers, retail was up 9.50% Y-o-Y. Commercial Vehicles witnessed a robust month, registering 24.60% Y-o-Y growth. Passenger Vehicles continued their positive run, up 26.64% Y-o-Y, with rural PV growth at 32.40% outpacing urban growth.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/smart-fortwo-3438102__340_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GM Breweries Q3 PAT soars 91% YoY to Rs 42 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gm-breweries-q3-pat-soars-91-yoy-to-rs-42-cr/1663388</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663388</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased 21.89% YoY to Rs 202.14 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.

Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) increased 21.89% YoY to Rs 202.14 crore for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Sequentially, the company’s standalone net profit rose 20.41%, while revenue increased 11.98%. Profit before tax (PBT) for the quarter stood at Rs 56.13 crore in Q3 FY26, up 91.24% from the Rs 29.35 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Total expenses increased 22.96% to Rs 757.24 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Rs 615.86 crore in Q3 FY25. Raw material consumed stood at Rs 135.88 crore (up 7.64% YoY), and employee benefit expenses were at Rs 3.51 crore (up 1.15% YoY) during the period under review. GM Breweries is engaged in the manufacturing and marketing of alcoholic beverages, including country liquor (CL) and Indian-made foreign liquor (IMFL). The company is the largest producer of country liquor in Maharashtra and commands a significant share of the state’s market. Shares of GM Breweries fell 3.44% to Rs 1,205 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GMBreweries_92584802133_3240.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aether Industries extends rally, jumps 22% in six days]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aether-industries-extends-rally-jumps-22-in-six-days/1663386</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663386</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock has gained 21.81% over the past six consecutive trading sessions.

The stock has gained 21.81% over the past six consecutive trading sessions. It is up 18.77% over the last one month and has risen 24% over the past three months, reflecting sustained buying interest in the counter. Aether Industries is a Surat-based specialty chemicals manufacturer focused on advanced intermediates used in pharmaceuticals, agrochemicals, material sciences, coatings and oil & gas. On a consolidated basis, net profit of Aether Industries rose 55.06% to Rs 53.96 crore while net sales rose 38.38% to Rs 275.10 crore in Q2 September 2025 over Q2 September 2024.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AetherIndustriesLtd_40383479_76355.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank’s average total deposits climb 15% YoY in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kotak-mahindra-banks-average-total-deposits-climb-15-yoy-in-q3/1663385</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663385</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a sequential basis, the bank’s average total deposits rose 3.1%.

On a sequential basis, the bank’s average total deposits rose 3.1%. The bank’s average CASA deposits stood at Rs 2,07,955 crore as of 31 December 2025, registering a 4.9% quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) growth and a 9% YoY increase. During the quarter, net advances (end-of-period basis) jumped 16% YoY to Rs 4,80,229 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 4,13,839 crore in Q3 FY25. On a QoQ basis, net advances rose 3.8%. Total deposits (end-of-period basis) increased 14.6% YoY to Rs 5,42,638 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,73,497 crore in Q3 FY25, while rising 2.6% on a QoQ basis. Kotak Mahindra Bank is the flagship company of the Kotak Group and has diversified operations covering commercial vehicle financing, consumer loans, corporate finance, and asset reconstruction. Through its subsidiaries, the bank is engaged in investment banking, equity broking, securities-based lending, and car finance. Kotak Mahindra Bank’s standalone net profit slipped 2.70% to Rs 3,253.33 crore in Q2 FY26 as against Rs 3,343.72 crore posted in Q2 FY25. However, total income rose 2.12% year on year (YoY) to Rs 16,238.59 crore in Q2 FY26. The counter slipped 1.87% to Rs 2,149.95 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KotakMahBank_47062626511_2330.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nifty trades below 26,200 level; European mrkt advance ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nifty-trades-below-26200-level-european-mrkt-advance/1663382</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663382</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S.

The key equity benchmarks continued to trade with modest cuts in early-afternoon trade as investors weighed the risks of fresh U.S. tariffs against a steady stream of quarterly earnings reports that have kept hopes of an earnings recovery alive. The Nifty traded below the 26,200 level. Oil & gas and media shares declined, while pharma, PSU bank and metal shares advanced. At 1:30 ST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, declined 466.30 points or 0.55% to 84,973.32. The Nifty 50 index dropped 91.05 points or 0.35% to 26,157.90. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index fell 0.21% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index shed 0.33%. The market breadth was negative. On the BSE, 1,620 shares rose and 2,398 shares fell. A total of 191 shares were unchanged. Economy: India’s services sector continued to expand in December 2025, but at the slowest pace in 11 months. The HSBC India Services PMI fell to 58.0 in December from 59.8 in November, indicating a moderation in activity while remaining well above the 50-point expansion threshold. Slower growth was driven by easing new business inflows and stalled hiring, while business confidence slipped to its lowest level in over three years. On the positive side, new export orders rose, supporting international demand, and inflationary pressures remained subdued, allowing firms to maintain competitive pricing. The composite PMI, which combines both services and manufacturing activity, also eased to 57.8, reflecting continued overall expansion of the economy but at a moderated pace. Gainers & Losers: Apollo Hospitals Enterprise (up 3.44%), ICICI Bank (up 2.78%), Bajaj Auto (up 2.48%), HDFC Life Insurance Company (up 2.20%) and Hindalco Industries (up 2.18%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. Trent (down 7.66%), Reliance Industries (down 4.45%), Kotak Mahindra Bank (down 2.39%), ITC (down 1.93%) and Jio Financial Services (down 1.61%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Stocks in Spotlight: KSH International rallied 3.69% after the company’s consolidated net profit surged 129.02% to Rs 29.59 crore on a 50.73% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 712.14 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. MOIL added 3.14% after the company said that it has achieved a record manganese ore production of 4.77 lakh tonnes in Q3 FY26, registering a growth of about 3.7% over the corresponding period last year (CPLY). Dev Information Technology rose 1.41% after the company announced that it had secured an order worth about Rs 26 lakh from Core Technologies. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (PV) declined 1.54% after Jaguar Land Rover (JLR)’s Q3 volumes were impacted by a cyber incident and US tariffs, leading to sharp year-on-year and sequential declines in both wholesale and retail sales. IndusInd Bank rose 2.16%. The bank reported a 3.8% decline in deposits to Rs 3,94,022 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 4,09,438 crore as of 31st December 2024. Global Markets: European shares opened higher on Tuesday as investors track geopolitical developments following the U.S.′ ouster of Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Asia-Pacific markets traded mixed, building on a record-breaking rally in global stocks as investors continued to assess ongoing geopolitical tensions following the U.S. attack on Venezuela and capture of ousted leader Nicolas Maduro. U.S. big oil got a boost from the country's military raid at the weekend that captured Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Crude oil eased back after rising $1 a barrel overnight as traders assessed the possible impact on crude flows from Venezuela, home to the world's largest oil reserves. Overall, however, the events had a limited effect on risk sentiment, with equities driven more by momentum and currencies focused on macroeconomic data. U.S. President Donald Trump said he would put Venezuela under temporary American control and that he could order another strike if the South American nation does not cooperate with U.S. efforts to open up its oil industry and stop drug trafficking. He also threatened military action in Colombia and Mexico. Trump plans to meet with executives from U.S. oil companies later this week to discuss boosting Venezuelan oil production, media reports stated. Overnight in the U.S., stocks rose even after the U.S. attack on Venezuela, as crude oil prices advanced and investors bet the action would not lead to broader geopolitical conflict. The Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 594.79 points, or 1.23%, to close at 48,977.18. The 30-stock index also hit a new all-time high in the session. The S&P 500 advanced 0.64% and ended at 6,902.05. The Nasdaq Composite added 0.69%, settling at 23,395.82.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-data-on-a-monitorstock-market-data-on-led-picture_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ddev Plastiks Inds board OKs to enter BESS Segment]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ddev-plastiks-inds-board-oks-to-enter-bess-segment/1663383</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663383</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company proposes to launch a multi-phase BESS manufacturing program aimed at catering to utilities, commercial & industrial, and residential segments.

The company proposes to launch a multi-phase BESS manufacturing program aimed at catering to utilities, commercial & industrial, and residential segments. As part of Phase 1, the company will establish a 5 GWh BESS manufacturing facility by FY 2026-27, with an initial capital outlay of approximately Rs 150-200 crore. The new segment is expected to contribute to the company’s revenues starting from the second half of FY 2026-27. A key feature of this initiative will be the development of a state-of-the-art research & development (R&D) centre, focused on advanced battery technologies and innovative energy storage solutions to strengthen the company’s technological capabilities and market positioning. According to Globe Newswire, the global BESS market is estimated to grow from $56.29 billion in 2024 to $ 68.70 billion in 2025 and is projected to reach $186.90 billion by 2030, registering a CAGR of 22.13%. In India, BESS capacity could reach 208 GWh with an estimated market value of $32 billion by 2030. Ddev Plastiks Industries houses the polymer compounding business of the Kkalpana group. The company is engaged in the manufacture of Polyvinyl Chloride (PVC) and Polyethylene (PE) compounds, along with other engineered plastic products such as polycarbonate and polypropylene compounds. The company’s standalone net profit increased 5.3% to Rs 47.11 crore in Q2 FY26, compared with Rs 44.72 crore in Q2 FY24. Net sales jumped 17.2% YoY to Rs 680.15 crore in Q2 FY26. The counter shed 0.13% to end at Rs 302.45 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DDevPlastiksIndustriesLtd_14757513_75251.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Desco Infratech bags Rs 5-cr orders from Adani Total Gas, BPCL, MNGL]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/desco-infratech-bags-rs-5-cr-orders-from-adani-total-gas-bpcl-mngl/1663381</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663381</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders cover PNG (Piped Natural Gas) infrastructure and operational services across multiple states.

The orders cover PNG (Piped Natural Gas) infrastructure and operational services across multiple states. The scope includes PE PNG works in Faridabad and Palwal for ATGL, operations and maintenance services for BPCL’s PNG network in the Hanumangarh district of Rajasthan, and support services for PNG operations and maintenance of connections in PCMC areas, including Wakad and Talegaon, for MNGL’s CGD network in Pune. Desco Infratech is an infrastructure company focused on engineering, planning, & construction, particularly in city gas distribution, renewable energy, water, and power sectors. On a full-year basis, the company's net profit surged 172.9% to Rs 9.06 crore on a 102.3% rise in revenue to Rs 59.45 crore in FY25 over FY24. Shares of Desco Infratech fell 2.50% to Rs 185.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/DescoInfratechLtd_59821997_94075.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd rises for third consecutive session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-bank-ltd-rises-for-third-consecutive-session/1663374</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663374</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Bank Ltd gained for a third straight session today.

ICICI Bank Ltd gained for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 1408.5, up 2.7% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 26158.5. The Sensex is at 85002, down 0.51%. ICICI Bank Ltd has risen around 1.36% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which ICICI Bank Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.5% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60044.2, up 0.14% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 121.35 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 83.42 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1414.2, up 2.84% on the day. ICICI Bank Ltd is up 10.1% in last one year as compared to a 10.34% spurt in NIFTY and a 19.77% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 19.79 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICIBank_93786457618_5418.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Union Bank of India spurts 2.52%, up for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/union-bank-of-india-spurts-252-up-for-third-straight-session/1663375</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663375</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Union Bank of India rose for a third straight session today.

Union Bank of India rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 166.45, up 2.52% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 26158.5. The Sensex is at 85002, down 0.51%. Union Bank of India has added around 12.19% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Union Bank of India is a constituent, has added around 1.5% in last one month and is currently quoting at 60044.2, up 0.14% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 202.06 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 105.86 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 167, up 2.33% on the day. Union Bank of India is up 47.55% in last one year as compared to a 10.34% gain in NIFTY and a 19.77% gain in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 6.9 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/UnionBankI_88937846814_5493.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd spurts 1.87%]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/aegis-logistics-ltd-spurts-187/1663376</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663376</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Aegis Logistics Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Aegis Logistics Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 745.75, up 1.87% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 26158.5. The Sensex is at 85002, down 0.51%. Aegis Logistics Ltd has risen around 2.17% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Aegis Logistics Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 3.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36050.05, down 0.77% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 3.14 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 2.5 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 48.73 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AegisLogistics_61348536029_9.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/siemens-energy-india-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1663377</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663377</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Siemens Energy India Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

Siemens Energy India Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2612.1, up 1.86% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 26158.5. The Sensex is at 85002, down 0.51%. Siemens Energy India Ltd has slipped around 11.57% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Energy index of which Siemens Energy India Ltd is a constituent, has slipped around 3.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 36050.05, down 0.77% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 2.23 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 9.13 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 83.04 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SiemensEnergyIndiaLtd_11731431_93274.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-lombard-general-insurance-company-ltd-gains-for-third-straight-session/1663378</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663378</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd is up for a third straight session today.

ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd is up for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 2002.2, up 1.13% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 26158.5. The Sensex is at 85002, down 0.51%. ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd has gained around 2.1% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Financial Services index of which ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd is a constituent, has gained around 0.84% in last one month and is currently quoting at 27851.45, up 0.25% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 1.87 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 4.31 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark January futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 2016, up 1.42% on the day. ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd is up 6.29% in last one year as compared to a 10.34% jump in NIFTY and a 19.16% jump in the Nifty Financial Services index. The PE of the stock is 35.21 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ICICILombardGeneralInsuranceCompanyLtd_66159376115_22664.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Prime Focus Ltd spurts 2.11%, rises for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/prime-focus-ltd-spurts-211-rises-for-third-straight-session/1663379</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1663379</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime Focus Ltd rose for a third straight session today.

Prime Focus Ltd rose for a third straight session today. The stock is quoting at Rs 244.04, up 2.11% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.35% on the day, quoting at 26158.5. The Sensex is at 85002, down 0.51%. Prime Focus Ltd has added around 29.06% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Media index of which Prime Focus Ltd is a constituent, has added around 4.48% in last one month and is currently quoting at 1472, down 0.96% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 26.78 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 93.65 lakh shares in last one month. The PE of the stock is 0 based on TTM earnings ending September 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/PrimeFocus_61388003233_27264.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>