<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:46:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd leads gainers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/vl-e-governance-it-solutions-ltd-leads-gainers-in-b-group/1679825</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679825</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd Partly Paidup, XT Global Infotech Ltd, Avadh Sugar & Energy Ltd and Foseco India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 February 2026.

Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd Partly Paidup, XT Global Infotech Ltd, Avadh Sugar & Energy Ltd and Foseco India Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 27 February 2026. VL E-Governance & IT Solutions Ltd surged 19.94% to Rs 15.64 at 27-Feb-2026 EOD IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'B' group. On the BSE, 3.32 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2.45 lakh shares in the past one month. Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd Partly Paidup soared 18.93% to Rs 348. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 1 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1139 shares in the past one month. XT Global Infotech Ltd spiked 17.24% to Rs 38.9. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 82735 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2666 shares in the past one month. Avadh Sugar & Energy Ltd spurt 11.13% to Rs 370.5. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 12015 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2938 shares in the past one month. Foseco India Ltd advanced 11.00% to Rs 5245. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'B' group. On the BSE, 788 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 64 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/VLEGovernanceITSolutionsLtd_93531239_76164.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Kirloskar Brothers bags Rs 214-cr orders from Adani Power group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/kirloskar-brothers-bags-rs-214-cr-orders-from-adani-power-group/1679823</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679823</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The orders have been awarded by domestic entities, including Anuppur Thermal Energy (MP) and Korba Power.

The orders have been awarded by domestic entities, including Anuppur Thermal Energy (MP) and Korba Power. The scope of work includes supply and erection, testing and commissioning of Circulating Water Pumps (Concrete Volute pump technology) and Auxiliary Cooling Water Pumps, along with associated electrical and control systems. The projects are located in Madhya Pradesh, Assam, Chhattisgarh and Bihar. Payments will be made in phases, with a portion payable within 30 days of receipt of goods at the delivery point and the balance upon erection, commissioning and testing. The contract carries a defect liability period of 12 months from the date of commissioning. The orders are to be executed within 18 to 24 months from the date of purchase order. KBL clarified that neither its promoter nor promoter group companies have any interest in the awarding entities, and the transactions do not fall under related party transactions. Kirloskar Brothers is a part of the Kirloskar Group engaged in the business of engineering and manufacturing of systems for fluid management. The core businesses include large infrastructure projects (Water Supply, Power Plants, and Irrigation), Pumps, Valves, Motors and Hydro turbines. The scrip fell 1.04% to Rs 1,570.40 on the BSE. Adani Power (APL), a part of the Adani portfolio, is the largest private thermal power producer in India. The scrip fell 0.28% to Rs 140.94 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/KirlBrothers_10364475530_336.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund announces Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) under its scheme]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/invesco-mutual-fund-announces-income-distribution-cum-capital-withdrawal-idcw-under-its-scheme/1679821</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679821</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Invesco Mutual Fund has announced 04 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the IDCW option of following schemes.

Invesco Mutual Fund has announced 04 March 2026 as the record date for declaration of Income Distribution cum Capital Withdrawal (IDCW) on the face value of Rs 10 per unit under the IDCW option of following schemes. The amount of IDCW (Rs per unit) will be: Invesco India Large Cap Fund – Regular IDCW Option & Direct IDCW Option: 3.00

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/accounting-picture-id172184798_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tejas Networks Ltd leads gainers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/tejas-networks-ltd-leads-gainers-in-a-group/1679816</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679816</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Redington Ltd, Sarda Energy & Minerals Ltd, SpiceJet Ltd and Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 February 2026.

Redington Ltd, Sarda Energy & Minerals Ltd, SpiceJet Ltd and Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd are among the other gainers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 27 February 2026. Tejas Networks Ltd spiked 14.33% to Rs 425.7 at 11:45 IST. The stock was the biggest gainer in the BSE's 'A' group. On the BSE, 78.11 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 4.5 lakh shares in the past one month. Redington Ltd soared 13.04% to Rs 276.5. The stock was the second biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 45.13 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 67266 shares in the past one month. Sarda Energy & Minerals Ltd surged 7.13% to Rs 555.4. The stock was the third biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 1.37 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 26881 shares in the past one month. SpiceJet Ltd advanced 6.60% to Rs 16.95. The stock was the fourth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 393.46 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 319.86 lakh shares in the past one month. Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd jumped 6.05% to Rs 15.43. The stock was the fifth biggest gainer in 'A' group. On the BSE, 68.66 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 39.7 lakh shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/TejasNetworksLtd_74416007001_35619.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian Oil Corp to consider second interim dividend on 6 Mar'26   ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-oil-corp-to-consider-second-interim-dividend-on-6-mar26/1679817</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679817</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The official announcement was made on 26 February 2026, after market hours.

The official announcement was made on 26 February 2026, after market hours. Indian Oil Corporation is a Maharatna PSU under the Government of India, with operations spanning the entire hydrocarbon value chain, including refining, pipeline transportation, and marketing of petroleum products, as well as exploration and production, natural gas, and petrochemicals. The company’s standalone net profit surged 321.98% to Rs 12,125.86 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 2,873.53 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations (excluding excise duty) rose 5.43% YoY to Rs 2,04,424.39 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 1,93,899.5 crore reported in Q3 FY25. The counter rose 0.72% to Rs 187.85 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/IOCL_64283819279_12002.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels declines for second day; trades below key moving averages]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/apeejay-surrendra-park-hotels-declines-for-second-day-trades-below-key-moving-averages/1679820</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679820</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The stock has added 3.84% in two sessions, from its recent closing high of Rs 126.25 recorded on 25 February 2026.

The stock has added 3.84% in two sessions, from its recent closing high of Rs 126.25 recorded on 25 February 2026. In the last six months, the stock has risen by 13.86% while the S&P BSE MidCap Index has lost 2.60% in the same period. On the technical front, the stock’s RSI (14) was currently at 40.643. An RSI reading of 70 or above indicates an overbought condition. A reading of 30 or below indicates an oversold condition. On the daily chart, the scrip is trading below its 10-day, 20-day and 100-day simple moving averages placed at 126.31, 126.99 and 135.44, respectively. In a regulatory filing made after market hours on Thursday, Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels said that it has entered into a hotel management and licensing agreement with West Bengal-based Luxmi Tea Co. for operation and management of a proposed 100-room premium hotel project under “The Park” brand. The aforesaid premium hotel would be developed on approximately 3.25 acres land that is lies within the Chandmani Tea Estate, Siliguri, West Bengal. The 100-room hotel will comprise of associated facilities including food & beverage outlets, banquet hall, bar and wellness facilities. The construction of the hotel is proposed to be completed by March 2031. The agreement is for a period of twenty years from the opening date. Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels is primarily engaged in the business of owning, operating and managing hotels in India under the names The Park Hotels, The Park collection and Zone by the Park. The company's consolidated net profit declined 24.75% to Rs 24.20 crore despite a 12.72% rise in revenue to Rs 200.06 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/ApeejaySurrendraParkHotelsLtd_33471002_24029.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Yen steadies near 155.8 as policy caution prevails]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/yen-steadies-near-1558-as-policy-caution-prevails/1679814</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679814</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Japanese yen edged up to around 155.8 per dollar on Friday but remained set for a second straight weekly loss, as uncertainty over Bank of Japan policy continued to cap gains.

The Japanese yen edged up to around 155.8 per dollar on Friday but remained set for a second straight weekly loss, as uncertainty over Bank of Japan policy continued to cap gains. Recent government nominations to the BOJ board and comments from Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi have reinforced expectations of a cautious approach to further rate hikes. Tokyo inflation slowed to its weakest pace in over a year, helped by utility subsidies that lowered energy costs, strengthening the case for the BOJ to delay near-term tightening. Meanwhile, the dollar index slipped below 97.6 and traded sideways through the week as investors awaited US inflation data. The Federal Reserve is expected to keep rates on hold at least until June, balancing elevated inflation against labor market risks.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/young-woman-taking-money-from-atm-picture-id519363550_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icici-prudential-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1679815</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679815</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 02 March 2026.

ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 02 March 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name List of Existing Fund Manager(s) List of Revised Fund Manager(s) ICICI Prudential Banking & Financial Services Fund • Roshan Chutkey • Antariksha Banerjee ICICI Prudential Manufacturing Fund • Antariksha Banerjee • Roshan Chutkey ICICI Prudential FMCG Fund • Priyanka Khandelwal • Nitya Mishra ICICI Prudential ELSS Tax Saver Fund • Mittul Kalawadia • Mittul Kalawadia • Priyanka Khandelwal ICICI Prudential Large Cap Fund • Sankaran Naren Vaibhav Dusad • Sankaran Naren • Vaibhav Dusad • Sharmila D’Silva** Ms. Sharmila D’Silva would manage derivative segment of ICICI Prudential Large Cap Fund

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[EUR/USD extends tight moves amid lax economic sentiment index data]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eurusd-extends-tight-moves-amid-lax-economic-sentiment-index-data/1679812</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679812</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Euro is witnessing tepid action in month end trades.

Euro is witnessing tepid action in month end trades. EUR/USD pair is currently quoting at 1.1817, up marginally on the day as it attempts to hold above 1.1800 mark. Economic cues are lax for the single currency. Eurozone economic confidence weakened in February largely due to the significant drop in sentiment among services providers, survey data from the European Commission showed Thursday. The economic sentiment index slipped to 98.3 in February from 99.3 in the prior month. Steady gains were seen in major European equity indices yesterday, offering some support to the EUR/USD pair. On NSE, EUR/INR futures are currently quoting at 107.75, up marginally on the day in very thin movement so far in the session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/money-trading-2-1444149_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[BPCL incorporates subsidiary in Singapore to trade crude, gas and petrochemicals]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/bpcl-incorporates-subsidiary-in-singapore-to-trade-crude-gas-and-petrochemicals/1679811</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679811</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The new entity will focus on trading crude oil, natural gas, petroleum, petrochemical products, and related commodities, along with associated commercial and operational activities.

The new entity will focus on trading crude oil, natural gas, petroleum, petrochemical products, and related commodities, along with associated commercial and operational activities. Bharat Petroleum Global Energy Services (Singapore) has issued share capital of $2 million, comprising 2 million shares at $1 per share. The entire shareholding of the incorporated entity will be held by BPCL. Bharat Petroleum Corporation is a public sector company which is engaged in the business of refining of crude oil and marketing petroleum products. The company reported a 62.29% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 7,545.27 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 4,649.20 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Net sales (excluding excise duty) rose 5.18% YoY to Rs 1,18,999.37 crore in the December 2025 quarter. The counter declined 0.35% to Rs 384.55 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/BPCL_78782939994_2290.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[NSE SME Manilam Industries begins its market journey in the red zone]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nse-sme-manilam-industries-begins-its-market-journey-in-the-red-zone/1679809</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679809</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The scrip was listed at Rs 55.20, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price.

The scrip was listed at Rs 55.20, a discount of 20% compared with the initial public offer (IPO) price. The stock is currently frozen at its upper limit of 5% over its listing price. The counter hit a high of Rs 55.20 and a low of Rs 52.45. About 7.68 lakh shares of the company changed hands at the counter. Manilam Industries India's IPO was subscribed 4.22 times. The issue opened for bidding on 20 February 2026 and it closed on 24 February 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 65 to Rs 69 per share. The IPO comprised 57,90,000 equity shares, including a fresh issue of 46,98,000 equity shares and offer for sale (OFS) of 10,92,000 equity shares. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds for capital expenditure - purchase of equipment/machineries, capital expenditure - purchase and installation of solar panel at its manufacturing plant, repayment in full or in part, of certain loans availed by the company, working capital requirements of the company and expenses for general corporate purposes. Ahead of the IPO, Manilam Industries India on 19 February 2026, raised Rs 11.30 crore from anchor investors. The board allotted 16.38 lakh shares at Rs 69 per share to 3 anchor investors. Manilam Industries India is engaged in the manufacturing and sale of decorative laminates, offering products in various thicknesses ranging from 0.7 mm to 1 mm. The products cater to both residential and commercial applications. In addition, the company is also involved in the trading of plywood, available in different grades and sizes, primarily serving the industrial and commercial sectors. The company had a total workforce of 152 employees. The company recorded revenue from operations of Rs 60.14 crore and net profit of Rs 3.16 crore for the period ended 30 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/MANILAMINDUSTRIESINDIALIMITED_21274017_96150.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sensex drops 514 pts; FMCG shares tumble ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sensex-drops-514-pts-fmcg-shares-tumble/1679808</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679808</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The frontline indices traded with substantial losses in the morning session, weighed down by weak global cues and rising geopolitical tensions surrounding Iran.

The frontline indices traded with substantial losses in the morning session, weighed down by weak global cues and rising geopolitical tensions surrounding Iran. The Nifty slipped below the 25,350 mark. FMCG shares extended their losses for the third consecutive trading session. At 11:30 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex, dropped 514.14 points or 0.63% to 81,734.10. The Nifty 50 index slumped 191.30 points or 0.75% to 25,305.25. In the broader market, the BSE 150 MidCap Index slumped 0.78% and the BSE 250 SmallCap Index fell 0.77%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,487 shares rose and 2,308 shares fell. A total of 212 shares were unchanged. IPO Update: Omnitech Engineering received bids for 30,99,954 shares as against 1,89,09,890 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 11:15 IST on Friday (27 Februray 2026). The issue was subscribed 0.16 times. The issue opened for bidding on 25 February 2026 and it will close on 27 February 2026. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 216 and 227 per share. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Realty index dropped 1.39% to 787.55. The index rose 0.23% in the past trading session. Brigade Enterprises (down 2.46%), Prestige Estates Projects (down 2.13%), Godrej Properties (down 2.09%), Anant Raj (down 2.02%), SignatureGlobal India (down 1.89%), Lodha Developers (down 1.51%), Oberoi Realty (down 1.45%), DLF (down 1.39%), Phoenix Mills (down 1.26%) and Sobha (down 0.81%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Steel Exchange India jumped 4.44% after the company announced that its board will meet on Wednesday (04 March 2026) to consider a proposal to raise funds amounting to Rs 350 crore. Jio Financial Services rose 0.51%. The company said that it has subscribed to 3,35,71,923 equity shares of Rs 10 each of Jio Credit (JCL), a wholly owned subsidiary, for cash at a premium of Rs 585.70 per equity share, aggregating to Rs 1,999.88 crore. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services shed 0.26%. The company has entered into multiple agreements to provide its corporate expense management solutions to leading domestic entities. Global Markets: Asia market traded mixed on Friday, after U.S. stocks declined overnight as Nvidia shares tumbled despite a quarterly earnings beat. In Asian tech stocks, SK Hynix, which is a key supplier of high-bandwidth memory to Nvidia, dipped over 2%. Samsung Electronics, which has been a decades-old partner of Nvidia, was down 0.69%. Gold prices held broadly steady on Friday, with investors digesting the previous day's U.S.-Iran nuclear talks, while the dollar, hovering near three-week highs, pressured the yellow metal. An Omani mediator of U.S. and Iran nuclear talks has reportedly given an optimistic readout over the latest round of negotiations, but uncertainty still hung over energy markets with no sign of a breakthrough that would avert potential U.S. strikes. Following these developments, Brent crude futures settled down 10 cents, or 0.14%, to $70.75 a barrel. Overnight on Wall Street, the S&P 500 pulled back after the latest results from tech titan Nvidia and software giant Salesforce failed to boost the broader market. The broad market index fell 0.54% to end at 6,908.86, while the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.18% and closed at 22,878.38. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 17.05 points, or 0.03%, to settle at 49,499.20. Nvidia shares fell more than 5%, even after the chip giant posted fourth-quarter earnings and revenue that were higher than widely reported forescasts. On the other end, Salesforce, which has been one of the biggest victims of recent artificial intelligence disruption fears, rose 4% after the software company’s latest quarterly results were higher than widely reported forecasts on the top and bottom lines. However, the company issued a disappointing fiscal 2027 revenue forecast. Sentiment has been fragile in software and cybersecurity stocks this year as worries remain about the rapidly developing capabilities of AI products that could interfere with incumbent software vendors’ businesses.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/bank-exchange-rate-display-picture-id546782886_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GMDC inks MoU with NTPC to explore coal, lignite gasification opportunities]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gmdc-inks-mou-with-ntpc-to-explore-coal-lignite-gasification-opportunities/1679806</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679806</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The MoU sets out a collaborative framework to assess the feasibility of gasifying coal from GMDC’s coal blocks in Odisha and lignite from its mining operations in Gujarat.

The MoU sets out a collaborative framework to assess the feasibility of gasifying coal from GMDC’s coal blocks in Odisha and lignite from its mining operations in Gujarat. As part of the agreement, GMDC will undertake pilot initiatives, including surface and underground coal and lignite gasification, to evaluate technical feasibility, operational parameters and scalability. NTPC, on the other hand, will assess potential end-use applications of syngas produced, including techno-commercial viability and market opportunities across relevant industrial sectors. Subject to successful pilot outcomes, the two companies plan to evolve mutually agreed frameworks for joint production, marketing and commercialisation of syngas. They will also formulate a clearly defined, time-bound action plan to ensure systematic progress of the initiative. GMDC said it has already initiated preliminary assessments for commercialisation of downstream products and is in the process of engaging technical partners for detailed feasibility studies. The MoU is expected to strengthen these efforts by leveraging NTPC’s expertise in large-scale energy systems and project execution. Commenting on the development, Roopwant Singh, managing director (MD), GMDC, said the collaboration underscores the company’s commitment to innovation-led growth and optimal utilisation of mineral resources, while supporting national goals of energy security and industrial development. GMDC, India’s second-largest lignite producer and the leading merchant seller of lignite, is a state-owned enterprise with the Gujarat government holding a 74% stake. The company mines lignite from deposit-rich regions across the state and supplies it to high-growth industries such as textiles, chemicals, ceramics, bricks, and captive power. The scrip fell 0.47% to Rs 573.50 on the BSE. NTPC, along with its subsidiaries/associates & JVs, is primarily involved in the generation and sale of bulk power to state power utilities. Other business of the group includes providing consultancy, project management & supervision, energy trading, oil & gas exploration, and coal mining. The scrip rose 0.58% to Rs 384.05 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GMDC_68292060483_13868.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's total power installed capacity has crossed 520 GW, more than half is coming from non-fossil sources]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-total-power-installed-capacity-has-crossed-520-gw-more-than-half-is-coming-from-non-fossil-sources/1679804</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679804</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Shripad Yesso Naik, Minister of State for Power and New & Renewable Energy, Govt of India has stated that India’s energy transition is not just an aspiration but is an ongoing transformation, anchored with clear targets with decisive decisions.

Shripad Yesso Naik, Minister of State for Power and New & Renewable Energy, Govt of India has stated that India’s energy transition is not just an aspiration but is an ongoing transformation, anchored with clear targets with decisive decisions. Under the Prime Minister Modi’s vision, India has set ambitious goal of 500 GW of non-fossil fuel capacity by 2030 and progressing towards Net Zero by 2070, he added. Addressing the two-day ‘India Energy Transition Summit’, organized by FICCI, Naik stated that today, the total power installed capacity has crossed 520 GW with more than half coming from non-fossil sources. Solar capacity has more than tripled in recent years and renewable energy is now mainstream and not marginal. This progress reflects the policy clarity, transparent competitive bidding, expansion of green energy corridors, promotion of ultra mega renewable energy parks, roof top solar through PM Surya Ghar Yojna, agricultural solarization through PM KUSUM Yojna along with strong push for domestic manufacturing, he noted.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/chart-with-data-on-screen-picture-id488603736_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICRA reaffirms AU Small Finance Bank's long-term rating at 'AA']]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/icra-reaffirms-au-small-finance-banks-long-term-rating-at-aa/1679805</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679805</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[ICRA stated that the rating factors in AU Small Finance Bank’s (AUSFB) established retail asset franchise with a track record of maintaining comfortable asset quality, adequate capitalisation and healthy earnings.

ICRA stated that the rating factors in AU Small Finance Bank’s (AUSFB) established retail asset franchise with a track record of maintaining comfortable asset quality, adequate capitalisation and healthy earnings. The bank registered a compound annual growth rate of around 30% in its gross loan portfolio (GLP) during March 2020 to March 2025 while deposits increased by 37% during this period. It has more than two decades of experience in the vehicle finance segment and more than a decade of experience in the micro, small and medium enterprise (MSME) segment; the share of secured retail loans stood at 68% of the GLP as on 31 December 2025. AUSFB has received in-principle approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to transition into a Universal Bank, which augurs well for its competitive positioning – the transition is expected to be completed in FY2027. ICRA expects AUSFB to maintain its growth momentum and keep scaling up its GLP at 20-25% per annum over the medium term with continued focus on the current target borrower segments. The bank vide a stock exchange disclosure dated 22 February 2026 intimated of its de-empanelment for Government business in the State of Haryana. The de-empanelment follows suspected unauthorised transactions between an account of a particular department of Government of Haryana and another customer account of the bank. The bank has initiated an internal review on the matter. The bank maintains that based on available facts and preliminary review, there has not been any indication of any fraudulent activity towards the bank. ICRA notes that the de-empanelment shall result in deposits outflow amounting to Rs 735 crore (Rs 538 crore as on 21 February 2026 or 0.4% of bank’s overall deposits as on 31 December 2025). While this is not material in relation to the bank’s overall deposits, the impact of the above on its deposit profile and its ability to improve its franchise shall remain a monitorable. AU Small Finance Bank (AUSFB) is a scheduled commercial bank, which transitioned to a small finance bank (SFB) from an asset financing non-banking financial company (NBFC). The bank had reported a PAT of Rs 1,809 crore in 9M FY2026 on a total asset base of Rs 1,74,052 crore compared to Rs 1,602 crore and Rs 1,43,044 crore, respectively, in 9M FY2025. The scrip shed 0.80% to currently trade at Rs 965.30 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AUSmallFinanceBankLtd_26708448592_34695.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes soar at Redington Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-soar-at-redington-ltd-counter/1679802</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679802</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, Action Construction Equipment Ltd, Bikaji Foods International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 27 February 2026.

Vishal Mega Mart Ltd, Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd, Action Construction Equipment Ltd, Bikaji Foods International Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on BSE today, 27 February 2026. Redington Ltd recorded volume of 30.43 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 51.37 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 59237 shares. The stock gained 12.02% to Rs.274.00. Volumes stood at 88584 shares in the last session. Vishal Mega Mart Ltd registered volume of 118.27 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 23.14 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 5.11 lakh shares. The stock slipped 6.43% to Rs.119.40. Volumes stood at 8.93 lakh shares in the last session. Cholamandalam Investment & Finance Company Ltd clocked volume of 14.73 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 9.49 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 1.55 lakh shares. The stock lost 0.81% to Rs.1,734.10. Volumes stood at 9.64 lakh shares in the last session. Action Construction Equipment Ltd recorded volume of 1.02 lakh shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 8.03 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 12648 shares. The stock lost 1.30% to Rs.882.00. Volumes stood at 16262 shares in the last session. Bikaji Foods International Ltd registered volume of 25661 shares by 10:45 IST on BSE, a 7.24 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 3547 shares. The stock rose 0.82% to Rs.636.10. Volumes stood at 2973 shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/RedingtonIndia_88236728935_12586.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[INR under stress, market eyes release of India's Q3 GDP data ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/inr-under-stress-market-eyes-release-of-indias-q3-gdp-data/1679801</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679801</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Indian Rupee continued to witness narrow movement today amid sustained weakness in local equities.

Indian Rupee continued to witness narrow movement today amid sustained weakness in local equities. INR trades down 5 paise at 90.96 per US dollar. The US dollar index is consolidating near four-week high and currently trades down marginally at 97.60. Overall mood is cautious for local markets as India’s economic growth data for the third quarter of FY26 will be released today, alongside a new GDP series that shifts the base year from 2011-12 to 2022-23. Domestic equity indices ended sideways on Thursday after a volatile trading session and fell in morning moves today. The benchmark NIFTY50 index has dipped under 25300 mark, testing around four-week low.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Foreign Exchange<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/calculator-v3-1463124_currency.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund announces change in fund manager under its schemes]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/uti-mutual-fund-announces-change-in-fund-manager-under-its-schemes/1679810</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679810</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Mutual Funds</category>
    <description><![CDATA[UTI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 27 February 2026.

UTI Mutual Fund has announced change in fund manager under the following schemes, With effect from 27 February 2026. Table, th, td {border: 1px Solid black; Border-collapse: collapse;} Change in Fund Manager: Scheme Name Existing Fund Manager New Fund Manager UTI Equity Savings Fund Mr. Sunil Patil - (Debt Portion) Mr. V Srivatsa - (Equity Portion) Mr. Anurag Mittal - (Debt Portion) Mr. V Srivatsa - (Equity Portion) UTI Medium to Long Duration Fund Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Amit Sharma Mr. Amit Sharma UTI Annual Interval Fund – I Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Amit Sharma Mr. Amit Sharma UTI - Unit Linked Insurance Plan Mr. Sunil Patil - (Debt Portion) Mr. Anurag Mittal - (Debt Portion) Mr. Ajay Tyagi - (Equity Portion) Mr. Kamal Gada - Assistant Fund Manager (Equity Portion) Mr. Akash Shah - Assistant Fund Manager (Equity Portion) Mr. Anurag Mittal - (Debt Portion) Mr. Ajay Tyagi - (Equity Portion) Mr. Kamal Gada - Assistant Fund Manager (Equity Portion) Mr. Akash Shah - Assistant Fund Manager (Equity Portion) UTI Children's Hybrid Fund Mr. Sunil Patil - (Debt Portion) Mr. Anurag Mittal - (Debt Portion) Mr. Sachin Trivedi -(Equity Portion) Mr. Anurag Mittal - (Debt Portion) Mr. Sachin Trivedi - (Equity Portion) UTI Retirement Fund Mr. Sunil Patil - (Debt Portion) Mr. Anurag Mittal - (Debt Portion) Mr. Sachin Trivedi -(Equity Portion) Mr. Anurag Mittal - (Debt Portion) Mr. Sachin Trivedi - (Equity Portion) UTI Aggressive Hybrid Fund Mr. V Srivatsa - (Equity Portion) Mr. Sunil Patil - (Debt Portion) Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal -(Debt Portion) Mr. V Srivatsa - (Equity Portion) Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal - (Debt Portion) UTI Nifty SDL Plus AAA PSU Bond Apr 2026 75:25 Index Fund Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI Nifty SDL Plus AAA PSU Bond Apr 2028 75:25 Index Fund Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI CRISIL SDL Maturity April 2033 Index Fund Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI CRISIL SDL Maturity June 2027 Index Fund Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI Fixed Term Income Fund - Series XXXV-III (1176 days) Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI Fixed Term Income Fund - Series XXXV-I (1260 Days) Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI Fixed Term Income Fund - Series XXXV-II (1223 Days) Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI Fixed Term Income Fund Series XXXVI - I (1574 Days) Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal Mr. Jaydeep Bhowal UTI Long Duration Fund Mr. Sunil Patil Mr. Pankaj Pathak Mr. Pankaj Pathak

<strong>Category:</strong> Mutual Funds - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/finanzen-und-mrkte-picture-id700709972_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nearly 95% of India’s trade by volume and around 70% by value is handled through ports]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/nearly-95-of-indias-trade-by-volume-and-around-70-by-value-is-handled-through-ports/1679800</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679800</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Minister of State for Ports, Shipping and Waterways, S Shantanu Thakur, has highlighted in a speech the central role of the maritime sector in India’s global trade expansion and the vision to position India as a leading shipping hub by 2047.

Minister of State for Ports, Shipping and Waterways, S Shantanu Thakur, has highlighted in a speech the central role of the maritime sector in India’s global trade expansion and the vision to position India as a leading shipping hub by 2047. Thakur noted that nearly 95% of India’s trade by volume and around 70% by value is handled through our ports. This clearly shows that the maritime sector is not merely a transport channel — it is a strategic enabler of India’s global trade ambitions. Emphasising the progress achieved in the maritime sector over the past decade, the Minister noted that India’s port capacity has more than doubled, cargo handling efficiency has improved significantly, and turnaround time at major ports has reduced substantially, supported by mechanisation and digitalisation initiatives. He added that as India moves towards becoming a USD 5 trillion economy and realising the vision of Viksit Bharat 2047, export competitiveness will be one of the strongest pillars of our economic transformation. Thakur also highlighted the Government’s renewed focus on strengthening India’s shipbuilding ecosystem, noting that recent policy measures and budgetary support will help position India as a major global shipbuilding nation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/coworker-carrying-cardboard-box-in-warehouse-picture-id5207_commodities.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SEBI broadens MF categories, introduces life cycle funds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sebi-broadens-mf-categories-introduces-life-cycle-funds/1679799</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1679799</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Market regulator Securities Exchange Board of India or SEBI has introduced another new category of mutual funds called the life cycle fund.

Market regulator Securities Exchange Board of India or SEBI has introduced another new category of mutual funds called the life cycle fund. SEBI said that life cycle funds will have a minimum duration of five years and a maximum duration of 30 years. Asset management companies can now introduce mutual fund schemes investing in debt instruments of companies in specific sectors. A sectoral fund would have a minimum investment of 80% in debt and debt related instruments of a particular sector across duration. The investment would be listed only in corporate bonds with a credit rating of more than AA+. SEBI has scrapped the solution-oriented schemes category and tightened disclosure and portfolio-overlap norms as part of a revamped classification framework. SEBI also mentioned the Sectoral Debt Funds may be launched in Financial Services, Energy, Infrastructure, Housing, Real Estate. In addition to the introduction of the new category, SEBI also said that the residual investment in long duration funds can be invested in InvITS. This is on the condition that the stocks that are not more than 50% of the stocks in a sectoral debt fund can overlap with any other equity fund, the circular read. SEBI now allowed mutual funds to invest the residual portion of an equity scheme to in equity, money market instruments and other liquid instruments, gold and silver instruments as permitted by SEBI and in InvITs. In equity schemes, the overall between sectoral and thematic funds were fixed at 50% except for large caps. The market regulator gave three years for AMCs to comply to the overlap condition for the new fund.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/notebook-with-mutual-funds-sign-on-a-table-business-concept_mutual-funds.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>