<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Market - Live News</title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news</link>
    <description>Latest market news and updates from Capital Market</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:38:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gold rewrites highs as haven demand intensifies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/gold-rewrites-highs-as-haven-demand-intensifies/1668623</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668623</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Other Markets</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Gold extended its record-breaking rally beyond $5,600 per ounce in electronic trade on Thursday, carving out fresh highs as persistent US dollar weakness and elevated economic and geopolitical risks reinforced haven demand.

Gold extended its record-breaking rally beyond $5,600 per ounce in electronic trade on Thursday, carving out fresh highs as persistent US dollar weakness and elevated economic and geopolitical risks reinforced haven demand. The metal has already advanced more than 30% in the opening month of the year, building on last year’s explosive gains of over 60%, underpinned by fiscal concerns, aggressive central-bank buying, and steady ETF inflows. Momentum accelerated as the dollar index slipped below 96 and hovered near four-year lows, with markets parsing mixed signals from US policymakers over currency policy and the Federal Reserve’s independence. Heightened geopolitical tensions, particularly fresh US warnings over Iran, further strengthened gold’s appeal. Reflecting global strength, MCX April bullion futures vaulted past Rs 193,000 per 10 grams, marking an intraday jump of over Rs 15,000.

<strong>Category:</strong> Other Markets - Bullion Markets<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/xmas-decoration-1517637_gold.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[eClerx Services climbs on strong Q3 FY26 earnings, bonus issue boost]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/eclerx-services-climbs-on-strong-q3-fy26-earnings-bonus-issue-boost/1668624</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668624</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[On a consolidated basis, net profit increased 40.1% YoY to Rs 191.8 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 137.2 crore in Q3 FY25.

On a consolidated basis, net profit increased 40.1% YoY to Rs 191.8 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 137.2 crore in Q3 FY25. On a sequential basis, profit after tax rose 4.8% from Rs 183.19 crore in Q2 FY26. Revenue from operations grew 25.4% YoY to Rs 1,070.3 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 853.8 crore a year ago. Sequentially, revenue rose about 6.5% QoQ from Rs 1,004.85 crore in Q2 FY26. In dollar terms, operating revenue rose 20.9% YoY to $121.7 million from $100.7 million a year ago and increased 5.4% sequentially. Profit before tax stood at Rs 250.1 crore in Q3 FY26, up 35.9% YoY from Rs 184 crore in Q3 FY25 and higher by 2.1% compared with Rs 245 crore in the previous quarter. EBIT for the quarter came in at Rs 261.2 crore, registering a 35.9% YoY increase and a 2.1% sequential rise. On the cost front, total expenses rose 22.86% YoY to Rs 794.07 crore in Q3 FY26. Employee benefit expenses increased 25% YoY to Rs 654 crore, while depreciation and amortisation expense climbed 29.4% YoY to Rs 46.3 crore. Finance costs rose to Rs 9.9 crore from Rs 8.3 crore in the year-ago quarter. Operationally, total delivery headcount stood at 21,847 as of December 2025, reflecting an 18% YoY increase. The company's board has recommended the issue of bonus equity shares in the ratio of 1:1, subject to shareholder approval via postal ballot, a move that further buoyed investor sentiment. eClerx provides business process management, automation and analytics services to Fortune 2000 enterprises across financial services, communications, retail, fashion, media, manufacturing, travel and technology. Incorporated in 2000, the company operates across multiple geographies including India, the US, Europe and Asia-Pacific.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/eClerxServices_24785005718_28293.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Five-Star Business Finance Ltd leads losers in 'A' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/five-star-business-finance-ltd-leads-losers-in-a-group/1668620</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668620</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Heritage Foods Ltd, Sterlite Technologies Ltd, Azad Engineering Ltd and Craftsman Automation Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 29 January 2026.

Heritage Foods Ltd, Sterlite Technologies Ltd, Azad Engineering Ltd and Craftsman Automation Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'A' group today, 29 January 2026. Five-Star Business Finance Ltd crashed 11.70% to Rs 442.5 at 14:46 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'A' group.On the BSE, 6.23 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 29623 shares in the past one month. Heritage Foods Ltd tumbled 8.09% to Rs 364.9. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 1.56 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 21866 shares in the past one month. Sterlite Technologies Ltd lost 6.81% to Rs 96.55. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 8.69 lakh shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 1.41 lakh shares in the past one month. Azad Engineering Ltd fell 6.51% to Rs 1402.75. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 17969 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 8706 shares in the past one month. Craftsman Automation Ltd slipped 6.25% to Rs 7283.8. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'A' group.On the BSE, 2528 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 10874 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Five-StarBusinessFinanceLtd_16909642_6468.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India records one of the sharpest declines in headline inflation among major emerging economies]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-records-one-of-the-sharpest-declines-in-headline-inflation-among-major-emerging-economies/1668617</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668617</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Economic Survey has noted that India recorded the lowest inflation rate since the beginning of the CPI series, with April-Dec ‘25 average headline inflation coming in at 1.7%.

Economic Survey has noted that India recorded the lowest inflation rate since the beginning of the CPI series, with April-Dec ‘25 average headline inflation coming in at 1.7%. The moderation in retail inflation can primarily be attributed to the general disinflationary trend in food and fuel prices, which together account for 52.7 per cent of India’s Consumer Price Index (CPI) basket. Notably, among major Emerging Markets & Developing Economies (EMDEs), India has recorded one of the sharpest declines in headline inflation in 2025 over 2024, amounting to about 1.8 percentage points.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/financial-chart-at-digital-display-picture-id638855738_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SRG Housing Finance Ltd leads losers in 'B' group]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/srg-housing-finance-ltd-leads-losers-in-b-group/1668608</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668608</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Digicontent Ltd, N K Industries Ltd, Jindal Drilling & Industries Ltd and Damodar Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 29 January 2026.

Digicontent Ltd, N K Industries Ltd, Jindal Drilling & Industries Ltd and Damodar Industries Ltd are among the other losers in the BSE's 'B' group today, 29 January 2026. SRG Housing Finance Ltd lost 12.49% to Rs 262.5 at 14:12 IST.The stock was the biggest loser in the BSE's 'B' group.On the BSE, 8 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 327 shares in the past one month. Digicontent Ltd tumbled 10.63% to Rs 26.24. The stock was the second biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 11303 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 2690 shares in the past one month. N K Industries Ltd crashed 10.00% to Rs 63. The stock was the third biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 533 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 52 shares in the past one month. Jindal Drilling & Industries Ltd corrected 9.90% to Rs 475.5. The stock was the fourth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 32923 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 6522 shares in the past one month. Damodar Industries Ltd slipped 9.13% to Rs 25.07. The stock was the fifth biggest loser in 'B' group.On the BSE, 617 shares were traded on the counter so far as against the average daily volumes of 5127 shares in the past one month.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SRGHousing_13569090817_42562.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trade in positive terrain; Nifty tops 25,400 level ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trade-in-positive-terrain-nifty-tops-25400-level/1668605</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668605</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The key equity indices trade with moderate gains in Mid-afternoon trade as value buying emerged, supported by positive economic data and the Economic Survey’s growth forecast of 6.8%–7.2% for FY27.

The key equity indices trade with moderate gains in Mid-afternoon trade as value buying emerged, supported by positive economic data and the Economic Survey’s growth forecast of 6.8%–7.2% for FY27. Participants are keeping a close watch on the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments. Investors are also awaiting quarterly results from ITC, Tata Motors, and Vedanta, due later today, along with the upcoming Union Budget 2026 scheduled for February 1, 2026. Meanwhile, the Nifty traded above the 25,400 level. Auto shares declined after registering gains in the previous trading session. At 11:25 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex advanced 185.55 points or 0.23% to 82,530.23. The Nifty 50 index added 68.60 points or 0.27% to 25,411.35. In the broader market, the S&P BSE Mid-Cap index remained flat and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index fell 0.41%. The market breadth was strong. On the BSE, 1,578 shares rose and 2,563 shares fell. A total of 160 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.09% to 13.67. Economic Survey 2025-2026: The Economic Survey 2025–26, tabled in Parliament on January 29 ahead of the February 1 Union Budget, highlighted both improving macro fundamentals and a clear shift in India’s export strategy as exporters steadily reduce their reliance on the US amid tariff-related uncertainties. The survey noted that while the India–US trade agreement remains under discussion, export data for April to November FY26 show a pivot towards West Asia, Europe, Africa and parts of Asia to sustain growth. Sectors such as gems and jewellery, marine products, auto components and textiles saw weaker demand from the US, but this was offset by stronger shipments to alternative markets, while pharmaceuticals remained resilient with healthy growth led by Africa, Latin America and Europe. On the broader economy, the survey said the fiscal deficit has sharply improved from 9.2% of GDP in FY21 to 4.8% in FY25 and is budgeted at 4.4% in FY26, while real GDP growth for FY26 is estimated at a robust 7.4%, driven largely by domestic demand. Looking ahead, the Indian economy is expected to grow 6.8%–7.2% in FY27, supported by strong macro fundamentals and ongoing regulatory reforms, underscoring a combination of internal strength and strategic diversification on the global trade front. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signalling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index fell 0.96% to 26,481.60. The index gained 0.69% in the past trading session. Maruti Suzuki India (down 2.57%, Mahindra & Mahindra (M&M) (down 2.55%), TVS Motor Company(down 2.07%), Bharat Forge (down 1.51%), Uno MInda Corporation(down 0.90%) declined. Numbers to Track: The yield on India's 10-year benchmark federal paper was added 0.18% to 6.715 as compared with the previous close of 6.703. In the foreign exchange market, the rupee edged higher against the dollar. The partially convertible rupee was hovering at 91.8950 compared with its close of 91.9975 during the previous trading session. MCX Gold futures for 5 February 2026 settlement rallied 5.75% to Rs 1,75,450. The US Dollar Index (DXY), which tracks the greenback's value against a basket of currencies, was down 0.09% to 96.26. The United States 10-year bond yield rose 0.31% to 4.264. In the commodities market, Brent crude for March 2026 settlement advanced $1.15 or 1.68% to $69.55 a barrel. Stocks in Spotlight: Quadrant Future Tek rose 3.28% after the company received a major domestic order from the Integral Coach Factory, Chennai. The company said it has received and accepted an offer from ICF for the supply, retrofitting, testing and commissioning of 192 onboard KAVACH equipment Version 4.0. The contract includes warranty and long-term annual maintenance. The total contract value stands at Rs 230.42 crore. The order is to be executed within 12 months and is entirely domestic in nature. GE Vernova T&D India rallied 7.86% after the company’s standalone net profit surged 103.81% to Rs 290.8 crore on 58.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 1700.64 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/graph-chart-of-stock-market-investment-trading-picture-id58_forex.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Heritage Foods slumps after weak Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/heritage-foods-slumps-after-weak-q3-performance/1668601</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668601</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations increased to Rs 11,192 crore during the period under review, up 8% YoY.

Revenue from operations increased to Rs 11,192 crore during the period under review, up 8% YoY. EBITDA declined by 15% to Rs 629 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 741 crore in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margin for Q3 FY26 was 5.6% as against 7.2% in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax stood at Rs 464 crore in Q3 FY26, down by 21% from Rs 588 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Brahmani Nara – Executive Director, said: “Q3 FY26 was characterised by an exceptionally tight industry supply environment, marked by milk shortages, elevated procurement costs, and heightened competitive intensity. Despite these challenges, Heritage Foods delivered 8% topline growth, supported by strong execution, disciplined cost management, and sustained momentum in our value-added portfolio. While procurement volumes were impacted by supply-side constraints during the flush season, sequential stabilisation and improved mix underscore our focus on disciplined procurement in a volatile input cost environment. We remain focused on strengthening our core markets through sharper route-to-market execution, targeted brand investments, and new product interventions. Looking ahead, the commissioning of our ice cream and flavoured milk capacities in Q4 FY26 positions us well to capture incremental demand and support VAP-led growth.” Heritage Foods is one of India’s leading dairy companies. With operations spanning 14 states, the company offers a wide range of milk, curd, butter, paneer, and other value- added dairy products.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/HeritageFoods_5113459552_4439.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Canara Bank Q3 PAT climbs 26% YoY to Rs 5,155 cr]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/canara-bank-q3-pat-climbs-26-yoy-to-rs-5155-cr/1668611</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668611</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before tax (PBT) rose 23.29% YoY to Rs 6,705.11 crore in Q3 FY26.

Profit before tax (PBT) rose 23.29% YoY to Rs 6,705.11 crore in Q3 FY26. Net interest income (NII) rose 1.13% to Rs 9,252 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 9,149 crore in Q3 FY25. Domestic deposits stood at Rs 13,97,045 crore as of 31 December 2025, registering a growth of 11.10% compared with Rs 12,57,426 crore as of 31 December 2024. Domestic advances rose 13.34% to Rs 11,19,289 crore as of 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 9,87,591 crore as of 31 December 2024. The Gross Non-Performing Assets (GNPA) ratio improved to 2.08% as of 31 December 2025, reduced from 2.35% as of September 2025 and 3.34% as of December 2024. The Net Non-Performing Assets (NNPA) ratio improved to 0.45% as of 31 December 2025, down from 0.54% as of 30 September 2025 and 0.89% as of 31 December 2024. Provision Coverage Ratio (PCR) stood at 94.19% as of December 2025 against 93.59% as of September 2025 and 91.26% as of December 2024. CRAR stood at 16.50% as of 31 December 2025. Out of which CET1 stood at 12.37%, Tier-I was at 14.60%, and Tier-II stood at 1.90%. Canara Bank is a public sector bank in India. As of 31 December 2025, the bank has 10,066 branches, out of which 3,195 are rural, 3,007 semi-urban, 1,980 urban, and 1,884 metro, along with 7,048 ATMs. Bank is also having 4 Overseas Branches in London, New York, Dubai & IBU Gift City Gujrat. Shares of Canara Bank fell 4.85% to Rs 150.15 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/CanaraBank_17338928867_5471.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volumes spurt at Gland Pharma Ltd counter]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/volumes-spurt-at-gland-pharma-ltd-counter/1668593</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668593</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Five-Star Business Finance Ltd, ABB India Ltd, Gillette India Ltd, Star Health & Allied Insurance Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 29 January 2026.

Five-Star Business Finance Ltd, ABB India Ltd, Gillette India Ltd, Star Health & Allied Insurance Company Ltd are among the other stocks to see a surge in volumes on NSE today, 29 January 2026. Gland Pharma Ltd registered volume of 27.34 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 28.57 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 95695 shares. The stock rose 7.13% to Rs.1,810.10. Volumes stood at 2.33 lakh shares in the last session. Five-Star Business Finance Ltd registered volume of 90.56 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 13.19 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 6.87 lakh shares. The stock slipped 11.38% to Rs.444.25. Volumes stood at 8.98 lakh shares in the last session. ABB India Ltd notched up volume of 21.89 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 8.56 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 2.56 lakh shares. The stock rose 9.37% to Rs.5,516.00. Volumes stood at 4.19 lakh shares in the last session. Gillette India Ltd saw volume of 1.54 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 7.39 fold spurt over two-week average daily volume of 20794 shares. The stock increased 4.51% to Rs.8,223.00. Volumes stood at 16644 shares in the last session. Star Health & Allied Insurance Company Ltd witnessed volume of 27.23 lakh shares by 14:14 IST on NSE, a 6.59 times surge over two-week average daily volume of 4.13 lakh shares. The stock increased 2.28% to Rs.450.60. Volumes stood at 7.53 lakh shares in the last session.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GlandPharmaLtd._31222392_14546.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India notifies coking coal as critical and strategic mineral]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/india-notifies-coking-coal-as-critical-and-strategic-mineral/1668590</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668590</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[India has notified coking coal as a “Critical and Strategic Mineral” under the Mines and Minerals (Development and Regulation) Act, 1957, a move likely aimed at reducing import dependence and strengthening the domestic steel supply chain.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/mineral-oil-297487__340_crude_oil.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[SBI Cards registers 45% YoY rise in Q3 PAT; balance sheet size rises to Rs 67,365 crore]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/sbi-cards-registers-45-yoy-rise-in-q3-pat-balance-sheet-size-rises-to-rs-67365-crore/1668575</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668575</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[While total spends grew by 33% at Rs 1,14,702 crore, receivables grew by 4% to Rs 57,213 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.

While total spends grew by 33% at Rs 1,14,702 crore, receivables grew by 4% to Rs 57,213 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Cards-in-force grew by 8% to 2.18 crore as of Q3 FY26 as against 2.02 crore as of Q3 FY25. New accounts volume stood at 864K in Q3 FY26 as compared to 1,175K in Q3 FY25. Operating expenses rose by 23% to Rs 2,597 crore in the December 2025 quarter from Rs 2,107 crore in the December 2024 quarter. Accordingly, the company registered an operating profit of Rs 1,971 crore in Q3 FY26, up 8% YoY. Impairment charge on financial instruments was Rs 1,222 crore in Q3 FY26, lower by declined by 7% as compared with the charge of Rs 1,313 crore recorded in Q3 FY25. Profit before tax in Q3 FY26 stood at Rs 749 crore, up by 45% from Rs 518 crore in Q3 FY25. The gross non-performing assets were at 2.86% of gross advances as of 31 December 2025, as against 3.24% as of 31 December 2024. Net non-performing assets were at 1.28% as of 31 December 2025, as against 1.18% as of 31 December 2024. The company’s total balance sheet size as of 31 December 2025 was at Rs 67,365 crore as against Rs 65,546 crore as of 31 March 2025. Total advances (net of provisions) as of 31 December 2025, at Rs 55,224 crore, up _ % YoY. As per the capital adequacy norms issued by the RBI, Company's capital to risk ratio consisting of Tier I and Tier II capital should not be less than 15% of its aggregate risk weighted assets on balance sheet and of risk adjusted value of off-balance sheet items. As of 31 December 2025, the company's CRAR was 24.4% compared to 22.9% as of 31 December 2024. The Tier I capital in respect of an NBFC-ND-SI, at any point of time, can't be less than 10%. The company's Tier I capital was 19.1% as of 31 December 2025, compared to 17.0% as of 31 December 2024. SBI Cards and Payment Services is a non-banking financial company that offers extensive credit card portfolio to individual cardholders and corporate clients which includes lifestyle, rewards, travel & fuel, and banking partnerships cards along with corporate cards covering all major cardholders' segments in terms of income profile and lifestyle. The company has a wide base of over 21 MM+ cards in force as of 31 December 2025. The scrip fell 1.79% to currently trade at Rs 768.25 on the BSE.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/SBICardsPaymentServicesLtd_48121040_20149.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Quadrant Future Tek jumps on Rs 230 crore KAVACH order ]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/quadrant-future-tek-jumps-on-rs-230-crore-kavach-order/1668562</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668562</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The company said it has received and accepted an offer from ICF for the supply, retrofitting, testing and commissioning of 192 onboard KAVACH equipment Version 4.0.

The company said it has received and accepted an offer from ICF for the supply, retrofitting, testing and commissioning of 192 onboard KAVACH equipment Version 4.0. The contract includes warranty and long-term annual maintenance. The total contract value stands at Rs 230.42 crore. The order is to be executed within 12 months and is entirely domestic in nature. KAVACH is India’s indigenous automatic train protection system developed under the Railways’ safety modernisation programme and specified by the Research Designs and Standards Organisation. Quadrant Future Tek clarified that the contract is awarded on an arm’s length basis and that neither the promoters nor group entities have any interest in ICF. Quadrant Future Tek is engaged in the development of next-generation train control and signalling systems that enhance safety and reliability for rail passengers. The company also operates a specialty cable manufacturing facility equipped with an in-house Electron Beam Irradiation Centre. Its specialty cables are supplied for railway rolling stock and the naval defence sector. The facility also has end-to-end infrastructure for the production of solar and electric vehicle cables. On a standalone basis, Quadrant Future Tek reported net loss of Rs 15.89 crore in Q2 September 2025, higher than net loss of Rs 3.56 crore in Q2 September 2024. Net sales declined 13.20% YoY to Rs 34.40 crore in Q2 September 2025.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Quadrant-Future-Tek-Ltd_73067085_93245.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's industrial activity strengthened despite global headwinds]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-industrial-activity-strengthened-despite-global-headwinds/1668552</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668552</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Industrial activity strengthened in FY26, with Industry GVA growing 7.0% (real terms) in H1, despite subdued and persistent global headwinds.

Industrial activity strengthened in FY26, with Industry GVA growing 7.0% (real terms) in H1, despite subdued and persistent global headwinds. Manufacturing growth accelerated, with GVA expanding 7.72% in Q1 and 9.13% in Q2 FY26, reflecting structural recovery. Production Linked Incentive (PLI) Schemes across 14 sectors have attracted over ₹2.0 lakh crore of actual investment, generating incremental production/sales exceeding ₹18.7 lakh crore and over 12.6 lakh jobs as of September 2025. India’s innovation performance has strengthened steadily, with its Global Innovation Index rank improving to 38th in 2025 from 66th in 2019. The India Semiconductor Mission has advanced domestic capabilities, with 10 semiconductor manufacturing and packaging projects approved across 6 States, involving about ₹1.60 lakh crore of investment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/factory-picture-id485339173_crude-oil.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Barometers trades sideways; European markets edge higher]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/barometers-trades-sideways-european-markets-edge-higher/1668548</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668548</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Market Commentary</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the afternoon trade amid profit booking and mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment overshadowed optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and positive economic data.

The domestic equity benchmarks traded sideways in the afternoon trade amid profit booking and mixed cues from global markets as cautious investor sentiment overshadowed optimism over the conclusion of the India–EU free trade agreement (FTA) and positive economic data. Participants are keeping a close watch on the rupee’s movement, ongoing Q3 corporate earnings, and evolving geopolitical developments. Investors are also awaiting quarterly results from ITC, Tata Motors, and Vedanta, due later today, along with the upcoming Union Budget 2026 scheduled for February 1, 2026. Meanwhile, the Nifty traded below the 25,350 mark. Metal, private bank and oil & gas shares advanced, while auto, FMCG and healthcare shares corrected. At 13:26 IST, the barometer index, the S&P BSE Sensex added 31.52 points or 0.04% to 82,376.20. The Nifty 50 index shed 10.15 points or 0.06% to 25,332.60. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. The S&P BSE Mid-Cap index jumped 1.56% and the S&P BSE Small-Cap index surged 2.06%. The market breadth was weak. On the BSE, 1,494 shares rose and 2,593 shares fell. A total of 165 shares were unchanged. Gainers & Losers: Larsen & Toubro (up 3.84%), NTPC (up 2.64%), Tata Steel (up 2.43%), Hindalco Industries (up 2.37%) and Axis Bank (up 2.33%) were the major Nifty50 gainers. SBI Life Insurance Company (down 4.08%), Asian Paints (down 3.53%), Mahindra & Mahindra (down 2.87%), InterGlobe Aviation (down 2.82%) and Maruti Suzuki India (down 2.79%) were the major Nifty50 losers. Economy: India’s industrial production rose to a 26-month high of 7.8% in December, up from 7.2% in November, according to data released by the government on January 28. The sharp pickup was driven by a broad-based acceleration across manufacturing, capital goods and infrastructure-linked segments, signalling resilient momentum at the end of the calendar year. Stocks in Spotlight: Larsen & Toubro added 3.91% after the company reported a 17.78% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 2,832.08 crore on 8.34% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 37,902.84 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sagility fell 3.79%. The company reported a 23.4% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 267.66 crore on a 35.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,971.15 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. ASK Automotive advanced 2.06% after the company reported an 21.29% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 79.92 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 65.89 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased 18.48% YoY to Rs 1,084.22 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Gland Pharma surged 7.40% after the company reported 27.7% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 261.48 crore on a 22.5% rise in net sales to Rs 1695.36 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Cochin Shipyard rose 0.39%. The company reported an 18.3% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 144.67 crore on a 17.7% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,350.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers gained 2.16% after the company reported 74% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 171 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 98 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations increased to Rs 1,896 crore during the period under review, up 49% YoY. Maharashtra Seamless added 0.71%. The company reported consolidated net profit of Rs 242.65 crore in Q3 FY26, up 30.41% as against Rs 186.06 crore in Q3 FY25. However, total revenue declined 8.48% year on year (YoY) to Rs 1,290.24 crore in Q3 FY26. Global Markets: Most European markets traded higher on Thursday as traders focused on a raft of earnings reports from some of Europe’s biggest companies. Asian market advanced as technology shares eased after recent gains, with investors digesting mixed mega-cap tech earnings on Wall Street and the Federal Reserve’s decision to keep rates unchanged. Investors will be keeping an eye on developments in Indonesia after the benchmark Jakarta Composite plunged over 8% on Wednesday after index provider MSCI had issued a statement warning of a potential downgrade of the country to frontier-market status. Meanwhile, Singapore’s central bank left its monetary policy unchanged Thursday, while warning of upside risks to inflation and demand as the city-state’s economic outlook stays resilient. The country’s benchmark Straits Times Index inched 0.19% higher. Overnight in the U.S., the S&P 500 reached a milestone level, hitting 7,000 for the first time, before pulling back as the Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged and upped its economic growth assessment. The broad market index ended the day down 0.01% at 6,978.03. Earlier, the S&P 500 was up 0.3% on the day, hitting an all-time intraday high of 7,002.28. The Dow Jones Industrial Average added 0.02% to close at 49,015.60. The Nasdaq Composite outperformed and gained 0.17%, settling at 23,857.45.

<strong>Category:</strong> Market Commentary - Mid-Session<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/display-stock-market-quotes-city-260nw-564998512_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[GE Vernova T&D surges on strong Q3 performance]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/ge-vernova-td-surges-on-strong-q3-performance/1668549</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668549</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 459.01 crore, up 141.72% YoY during the quarter.

Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at Rs 459.01 crore, up 141.72% YoY during the quarter. Exceptional items included an additional provision of Rs 69.30 crore related to the implementation of the labour code. EBITDA stood at Rs 454.6 crore during the quarter, registering the growth of 152.98% compared with Rs 179.7 crore posted in same period last year. EBITDA margin improved 26.7% in Q3 FY26 as against 16.7% in Q3 FY25. Order bookings for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 stood at Rs 2,940 crore, registering a 41% increase compared with Rs 2,080 crore recorded in the quarter ended December 31, 2024. Sandeep Zanzaria, managing director & CEO of GE Vernova T&D India, said, “Our strong Q3 performance reflects India's fast paced energy transformation, driven by record renewable capacity additions that are reshaping the nation's power landscape. As renewables increase in India's energy mix, the demand for robust transmission and distribution infrastructure has never been greater to ensure grid stability and reliability. We remain committed to our disciplined approach of pursuing margin-accretive orders that deliver sustainable value, positioning us to capitalize on India's long-term energy transition while maintaining operational excellence." GE Vernova T&D India is a engaged in the power transmission and distribution business. The company offers a comprehensive and robust range of solutions for connecting and evacuating power from generation sources to the grid, and a wide range of products including power transformers, circuit breakers, gas-insulated switchgear, instrument transformers, substation automation, digital software solutions, turnkey substation solutions, FACTS, HVDC, and maintenance support.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/GETDIndia_25039636117_159.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[India's capex rose 4.2x from FY18 to FY26]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indias-capex-rose-42x-from-fy18-to-fy26/1668538</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668538</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[The Government of India’s capital expenditure has increased nearly 4.2 times, from ₹2.63 lakhcrore in FY18 to ₹11.21 lakh crore in FY26 (BE), while effective capital expenditure in FY26 (BE) is ₹15.48 lakh crore, positioning infrastructure as a key growth driver.

The Government of India’s capital expenditure has increased nearly 4.2 times, from ₹2.63 lakhcrore in FY18 to ₹11.21 lakh crore in FY26 (BE), while effective capital expenditure in FY26 (BE) is ₹15.48 lakh crore, positioning infrastructure as a key growth driver. National highway infrastructure expanded substantially, with the NH network growing by about 60 per cent from 91,287 km (FY14) to 1,46,572 km (FY26, up to December), and operational High-Speed Corridors increasing nearly ten-fold—from 550 km (FY14) to 5,364 km (FY26, up to December). Railway infrastructure continued to expand, with the rail network reaching 69,439 route km as of March 2025, a targeted addition of 3,500 km in FY26, and 99.1 per cent electrification achieved by October 2025. India has emerged as the world’s third-largest domestic aviation market, with the number of airports increasing from 74 in 2014 to 164 in 2025. The power sector recorded sustained capacity expansion, with installed capacity rising 11.6 per cent (y-o-y) to 509.74 GW as of November 2025, and the demand–supply gap declined from 4.2 per cent in FY14 to nil by November 2025. Power sector reforms delivered a historic turnaround, with DISCOMs recording a positive Profit after Tax (PAT) of ₹2,701 crore in FY25 for the first time, alongside a reduction in AT&C losses from 22.62 per cent (FY14) to 15.04 per cent (FY25). Renewable energy constitutes around 49.83 per cent of total power generation capacity as of November 2025, with India ranking third globally in overall RE and installed solar capacity. Tele-density reached 86.76 per cent, and 5G services are now available in 99.9 per cent of districts in the country. Over 81 per cent of rural households have access to clean tap water under the Jal Jeevan Mission, as of October 2025. Space infrastructure strengthened, with India becoming the fourth nation to achieve autonomous satellite docking (SpaDeX), alongside expanded indigenous missions and increased private-sector participation.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/global-business-growth-picture-id518037359_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Global environment remains fragile and risks elevated; Ongoing trade negotiations with the US expected to conclude this year: Economic Survey]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/global-environment-remains-fragile-and-risks-elevated-ongoing-trade-negotiations-with-the-us-expected-to-conclude-this-year-economic-survey/1668537</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668537</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Global environment remains fragile, with growth holding up better than expected but risks elevated amid intensifying geopolitical tensions, trade fragmentation and financial vulnerabilities, the economic survey noted.

Global environment remains fragile, with growth holding up better than expected but risks elevated amid intensifying geopolitical tensions, trade fragmentation and financial vulnerabilities, the economic survey noted. The impact of these shocks may still surface with a lag. For India, the global conditions translate into external uncertainties rather than immediate macroeconomic stress. Slower growth in key trading partners, tariff induced disruptions to trade and volatility in capital flows could intermittently weigh on exports and investor sentiment. At the same time, ongoing trade negotiations with the United States are expected to conclude during the year, which could help reduce uncertainty on the external front. Meanwhile, India’s external sector is placed comfortably in the short run, the survey noted saying that forex reserves cover over 11 months of imports as of 16 January 2026 and approximately 94.0 per cent of the external debt outstanding as of the end of September 2025, offering a comfortable liquidity cushion.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/technical-financial-graph-on-technology-abstract-background_stock-exchange.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Indian economy achieved stability through credible fiscal consolidation; says Economic Survey]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/indian-economy-achieved-stability-through-credible-fiscal-consolidation-says-economic-survey/1668536</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668536</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Economy</category>
    <description><![CDATA[According to the Economic Survey 2026, the government’s prudent fiscal management has strengthened credibility and reinforced confidence in India’s macroeconomic and fiscal framework.

According to the Economic Survey 2026, the government’s prudent fiscal management has strengthened credibility and reinforced confidence in India’s macroeconomic and fiscal framework. This led to three sovereign credit rating upgrades in 2025 - by Morningstar DBRS, S&P Global Ratings, and Rating and Investment Information (R&I), Inc. Centre’s revenue receipts strengthened from an average of about 8.5 per cent of GDP in FY16–FY20 to 9.2% of GDP in FY25 (PA). This improvement was driven by buoyant non-corporate tax collections, which rose from about 2.4 per cent of GDP pre-pandemic to around 3.3 per cent post-pandemic. The direct tax base expanded steadily, with income tax returns filed increasing from 6.9 crore in FY22 to 9.2 crore in FY25. Higher return filings reflect improved compliance, greater use of technology in tax administration, and a growing number of individuals entering the tax net as their incomes rise. Gross GST collections during April–December 2025 stood at ₹17.4 lakh crore, registering a year-on-year growth of 6.7 per cent. GST revenue growth is broadly aligned with prevailing nominal GDP growth conditions. In parallel, high-frequency indicators suggest robust transaction volumes, with cumulative e-way bill volumes during April-December 2025 growing by 21 per cent YoY. The effective capital expenditure of the Central government rose from an average of 2.7 per cent of GDP in the pre-pandemic period to about 3.9 per cent post-pandemic, and to a higher 4 per cent of GDP in FY25. Through Special Assistance to States for Capital Expenditure (SASCI), the Centre has incentivized States to maintain capital spending at around 2.4 per cent of GDP in FY25. The combined fiscal deficit of State Governments stayed broadly stable at around 2.8 per cent of GDP in the post-pandemic period, similar to pre-pandemic levels, but has edged up in recent years to 3.2 per cent in FY25, reflecting emerging pressures on State finances. India reduced its general government debt-to-GDP ratio by about 7.1 percentage points since 2020, even while maintaining high public investment.

<strong>Category:</strong> Economy - Reports<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImages/india-economy-and-financial-market-growth-concept-3d-render_economy.jpeg" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Symphony surges after registering PAT of Rs 34 crore in Q3]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/symphony-surges-after-registering-pat-of-rs-34-crore-in-q3/1668531</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668531</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Revenue from operations remained flat at Rs 182 crore during the quarter.

Revenue from operations remained flat at Rs 182 crore during the quarter. Total operating expenditure for Q3 FY26 was Rs 151 crore, down 22.6% YoY. This was due to lower finished goods purchases (down 35.8% YoY) and lower other expenses (down 70.8% YoY). The company posted a pre-tax profit of Rs 43 crore in Q3 FY26. It had recorded a pre-tax loss of Rs 7 crore in Q3 FY25. Symphony, an Indian multi-national company with presence in over 60 countries is the world’s leading air cooler company. The company delivers market-leading products that comprise of design innovation, energy efficiency, distinctive styling, and customer-centricity.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/Symphony_96999644438_3465.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Axis Bank Ltd spurts 1.96%, gains for third straight session]]></title>
    <link>https://www.capitalmarket.com/markets/news/live-news/axis-bank-ltd-spurts-196-gains-for-third-straight-session/1668516</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">cm-1668516</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <category>Hot Pursuit</category>
    <description><![CDATA[Axis Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row.

Axis Bank Ltd is up for a third straight session in a row. The stock is quoting at Rs 1345.7, up 1.96% on the day as on 12:49 IST on the NSE. The benchmark NIFTY is down around 0.16% on the day, quoting at 25302.45. The Sensex is at 82334.29, down 0.01%. Axis Bank Ltd has risen around 8% in last one month. Meanwhile, Nifty Bank index of which Axis Bank Ltd is a constituent, has risen around 1.02% in last one month and is currently quoting at 59598.8, up 0.29% on the day. The volume in the stock stood at 71.34 lakh shares today, compared to the daily average of 70.83 lakh shares in last one month. The benchmark February futures contract for the stock is quoting at Rs 1352.5, up 2.18% on the day. Axis Bank Ltd is up 36.66% in last one year as compared to a 8.83% spurt in NIFTY and a 21.22% spurt in the Nifty Bank index. The PE of the stock is 16.74 based on TTM earnings ending December 25.

<strong>Category:</strong> Hot Pursuit<br/><img src="https://www.capitalmarket.com/IImagesNew/AxisBank_99376846491_5554.png" alt="News Image" style="max-width:100%; height:auto;" />]]></description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>