<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex Edges Lower as Midcaps Lead Gains; IT Sector Drags Market</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-edges-lower-as-midcaps-lead-gains-it-sector-drags-market-3781138</link><description>Indian equity benchmarks closed the day with marginal losses as midcap and smallcap segments showed resilience, offsetting weakness in the IT sector. The Sensex traded just 0.04% lower at 85,731.40, hovering close to its 52-week high, while the Nifty mirrored this cautious sentiment amid mixed global cues and subdued foreign institutional investor activity.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>aecad1ab261f3d3210df62a40d0462b4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3781136</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, continues to attract investor attention as it maintains its position within the Nifty 50 index. Despite recent underperformance relative to the benchmark Sensex, the company’s evolving institutional shareholding and market cap dynamics underscore its significance in India’s financial landscape.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>b912e267240ce22d97215b9e1e33a791</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Faces Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-faces-challenges-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3781137</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, continues to navigate a challenging market environment despite its prestigious inclusion in the Nifty 50 index. Recent data reveals a downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell, reflecting growing concerns among institutional investors and analysts about its valuation and near-term performance prospects.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>cb7f96d8e34e3858804b01da1155b3dc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd Faces Downgrade Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-faces-downgrade-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3781135</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently undergone a notable downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell, reflecting growing concerns over its valuation and performance relative to the broader market and sector peers. Despite its large-cap status and significant institutional interest, the hospital sector stock has struggled to keep pace with benchmark indices, prompting investors to reassess its outlook amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>68a0c036dd56753f329dd03e80ac1aee</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-company-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3781131</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading insurance player in India. Despite recent mixed performance signals and a modest upgrade in its Mojo Grade, the stock’s large-cap status and institutional interest underscore its critical role in the benchmark index and the broader insurance sector.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>63caac89c7c7925aa90adaa5a1b5aab9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3781134</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Indian equity landscape, bolstered by its status as a Nifty 50 constituent and robust institutional interest. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Hold', the stock has demonstrated resilience, outperforming its sector and the broader Sensex over multiple time frames, underscoring its significance as a benchmark stock in the insurance sector.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>bdaf41991e338e8fec3ce838fd935cc5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3781132</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd., a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market dynamics. Recent institutional holding changes and its benchmark status underscore the stock’s strategic importance for investors and index trackers alike.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>3ac250c68f27ff4258e058edee6e77dd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd: Sustained Momentum and Nifty 50 Membership Reinforce Market Confidence</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-sustained-momentum-and-nifty-50-membership-reinforce-market-confidence-3781133</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd continues to demonstrate robust performance within the Nifty 50 index, hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹17,000.25. The stock’s sustained gains over the past week, coupled with its significant market capitalisation and evolving institutional holdings, underscore its pivotal role in India’s automobile sector and broader benchmark indices.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>7181ca201f43ea249650c422b572286e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd: Navigating Market Challenges Amidst Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-navigating-market-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3781130</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd, a stalwart in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, continues to command significant attention as a Nifty 50 constituent. Despite recent short-term underperformance, the company’s robust fundamentals, institutional holding dynamics, and benchmark status underscore its pivotal role in India’s equity landscape.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>db317cdcb52fc7f4b301b96e49ed921f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd: Navigating Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-navigating-challenges-amid-nifty-50-membership-3781129</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to navigate a challenging market environment with a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell. Despite its large-cap status and significant market presence, the stock’s performance over the past year has lagged behind the broader Sensex benchmark, raising questions about its near-term prospects and institutional investor sentiment.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>25bcae20b95416ef1bf75238beb0ad99</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3781128</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, continues to command attention as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index. Despite recent price fluctuations and a modest downgrade in its mojo grade, the company’s position within the benchmark index underscores its significance for institutional investors and market watchers alike.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>1dec60a2178fbcaa424b6b0b8523dc75</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts Amid Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steel-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-amid-market-dynamics-3781125</link><description>JSW Steel Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience and strategic significance within the Indian equity market. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, the steel giant maintains robust market capitalisation and outperforms key benchmarks, underscoring its pivotal role in the ferrous metals sector and the broader market landscape.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>067adaae4ffe686a70f5d8906f2f8e69</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. Strengthens Position as a Key Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-strengthens-position-as-a-key-nifty-50-constituent-amid-robust-performance-3781122</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (L&amp;T), a stalwart in India’s construction sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate robust performance and growing institutional confidence. With a recent upgrade to a ‘Buy’ Mojo Grade and sustained gains pushing it close to its 52-week high, L&amp;T’s market stature and benchmark significance remain firmly intact as it outpaces broader market indices and sector peers.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>2177024ca756d4d71565bf9d230b87ed</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3781120</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd, a prominent holding company and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention from investors amid evolving market conditions. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Hold' from 'Buy', the company’s long-term performance and institutional interest remain pivotal factors influencing its market trajectory and benchmark status.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>6ae1fdccbfd99d660cbffd4f2076c7f7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3781124</link><description>Adani Enterprises Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to face a complex market environment marked by shifting institutional holdings and valuation pressures. Despite recent short-term gains, the stock’s long-term performance lags behind benchmark indices, raising questions about its role within India’s premier equity index and the implications for investors.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>786c5bd44ca425329f17774db794094a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-performance-3781127</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd., a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index and a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently experienced a nuanced market performance. Despite a slight dip in daily trading, the company’s upgraded Mojo Grade to 'Buy' and its sustained large-cap status underscore its enduring significance in India’s benchmark index and among institutional investors.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>fbbe8b73bbe6a215a89710b5030c7790</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Ltd Faces Sell Downgrade Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-ltd-faces-sell-downgrade-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3781126</link><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd (HUL), a cornerstone of the Nifty 50 index and a dominant player in the FMCG sector, has recently experienced a downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell, reflecting growing concerns over its near-term performance and valuation. Despite its large-cap status and benchmark significance, the stock’s recent underperformance relative to the Sensex and sector peers has prompted a reassessment by market analysts, highlighting shifts in institutional holdings and broader market dynamics.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>af1d15aa7c4e8bb37cc5555b8d7c6d12</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grasim Industries Ltd Strengthens Position as Key Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grasim-industries-ltd-strengthens-position-as-key-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-interest-3781119</link><description>Grasim Industries Ltd, a key player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, continues to solidify its stature within the Nifty 50 index, buoyed by robust institutional holdings and a recent upgrade in its investment grade. The stock’s performance and benchmark status underscore its growing appeal among investors seeking large-cap exposure in India’s cement industry.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>8bec460c26e1dd8df2420f925354d79e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kotak-mahindra-bank-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3781123</link><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd continues to solidify its stature as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, underscoring its pivotal role in India’s private sector banking landscape. Despite a modest dip in daily trading, the bank’s robust fundamentals, institutional holding dynamics and benchmark status collectively highlight its enduring appeal to investors navigating a complex market environment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>30804302907749a3f283bf84e508dd07</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Heavyweight Amid Robust Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-heavyweight-amid-robust-institutional-interest-3781121</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd (RIL), a cornerstone of the Indian oil sector and a key Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate formidable market strength, underpinned by strong institutional backing and consistent outperformance against benchmark indices. Recent upgrades in its investment grade and sustained price momentum highlight the company’s pivotal role in shaping market dynamics.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>e83df690fca0101291182304b32f156e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>