<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>GRP Stock Evaluation Revised Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/grp-stock-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-on-27-may-2025-3764758</link><description>GRP, a small-cap player in the Industrial Products sector, has undergone a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting nuanced shifts across key financial and technical parameters. This update highlights the company's current position amid challenging market conditions and evolving investor sentiment.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>18f5ee2c0d5e81527fdf18722e128603</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fredun Pharma Sees Revised Market Evaluation Amid Strong Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/fredun-pharma-upgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-on-strong-financial-and-valuation-metrics-3764756</link><description>Fredun Pharma, a microcap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent developments in its financial and technical outlook. This shift highlights evolving investor perceptions amid robust growth indicators and valuation metrics.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>91f9a3046f39aba6a00a3c187f806709</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kellton Tech Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kellton-tech-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-weak-performance-and-bearish-technicals-3764757</link><description>Kellton Tech, a microcap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment follows a detailed reassessment of the company’s quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators, highlighting both strengths and challenges in its recent performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>21487d9f829509281035294b4f539801</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agarwal Indl. Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amidst Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/agarwal-indl-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3764753</link><description>Agarwal Indl., a small-cap player in the petrochemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent financial and technical developments. The company’s assessment metrics have shifted following a series of operational challenges and market performance indicators that have influenced investor sentiment.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d4ea29364ab2100e34490590ac9d58e4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Confidence Petro’s Evaluation Revised Amidst Challenging Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/confidence-petro-downgraded-to-sell-as-mojo-score-declines-to-46-3764755</link><description>Confidence Petro has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting shifts across key analytical parameters amid a backdrop of sustained underperformance and sector-specific challenges.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>506a9d409e491fb36693f301b6350490</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Australian Prem Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/australian-prem-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-declining-mojo-score-3764754</link><description>Australian Prem, a microcap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of mixed performance indicators and evolving market conditions.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f3a698b6f239c7bd5ae9b61eca4c5320</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Amines Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indo-amines-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-declining-mojo-score-3764752</link><description>Indo Amines, a microcap player in the specialty chemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation metrics, reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of subdued stock performance and contrasting fundamental indicators.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>bebacb916df88858dc41e7cc69579860</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I G Petrochems Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Challenging Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/i-g-petrochems-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-on-16-dec-2025-3764751</link><description>I G Petrochems has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting changes in its fundamental and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of subdued financial performance and sector-specific challenges within the commodity chemicals industry.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f280316b053e4ba01cb21ffbde4f1645</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhunseri Vent. Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amidst Challenging Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dhunseri-vent-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-worsening-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3764750</link><description>Dhunseri Vent., a microcap player in the diversified sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment reflecting recent financial and technical developments. The company’s evaluation metrics have shifted in response to ongoing operational challenges and market performance trends.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a1b9c2d6a186666cb84d5d42635ec319</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IZMO’s Evaluation Metrics Revised Amid Mixed Financial and Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/marketsmojo-upgrades-izmo-from-sell-to-hold-on-improved-score-3764749</link><description>IZMO, a microcap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently undergone a revision in its evaluation metrics, reflecting nuanced shifts across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook. This update offers investors a fresh perspective on the company’s current standing amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e4006985d0ee2c0f268c58d4d0d4e785</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beekay Steel Ind Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/beekay-steel-ind-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-3764746</link><description>Beekay Steel Ind has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting nuanced changes across multiple analytical parameters. Despite persistent headwinds in financial performance and technical indicators, the stock's valuation metrics present a contrasting perspective, highlighting the complexities investors face in assessing this microcap within the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d0d5b15203f96538ff69fc0d501c6c75</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arihant Capital Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/arihant-capital-upgraded-from-sell-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-on-28-oct-2025-3764748</link><description>Arihant Capital's market evaluation has undergone a revision reflecting nuanced changes across key financial and technical parameters. The capital markets micro-cap company’s recent assessment highlights a complex interplay of valuation attractiveness, financial challenges, and technical indicators, offering investors a detailed perspective on its current standing.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b0eaf3b5b8fd65b38e22ab0f9fa2d9d9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairchem Organic Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amid Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/fairchem-organic-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-outlook-3764747</link><description>Fairchem Organic, a microcap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting ongoing challenges in its financial and technical outlook. The recent assessment highlights shifts across key analytical parameters, signalling caution for investors amid persistent underperformance and subdued operational metrics.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>17731bb56f447e5fab304970b5f4dd38</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eco Recyc. Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amidst Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/eco-recyc-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-on-9-sep-2025-3764745</link><description>Eco Recyc., a microcap player in the Other Utilities sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting nuanced changes across key financial and technical parameters. This shift comes despite ongoing challenges in stock performance and valuation metrics, highlighting a complex investment landscape for the company.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>92a6ae988434c243e45bb6adfd809da7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kuantum Papers Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amidst Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kuantum-papers-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3764743</link><description>Kuantum Papers has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting shifts in key analytical parameters that influence investor sentiment. This adjustment comes amid ongoing financial challenges and a subdued performance trajectory within the Paper, Forest &amp; Jute Products sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>baedeccc37e9e8b8e977f97ef4a06454</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashika Credit Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ashika-credit-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-risky-valuation-3764741</link><description>Ashika Credit, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation metrics, reflecting shifts in its fundamental and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of mixed financial signals and a challenging market environment for the stock.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>447f0160a84a86ad2a4e15484e270f23</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 09:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>