<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>SML Mahindra Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.53% Surge on 10 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sml-mahindra-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-853-surge-on-10-feb-2026-3830492</link><description>SML Mahindra Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 10 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 4,278.75, marking an 8.85% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting heightened trading activity and strong momentum within the automobile segment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>bc4ce8efaf83d63732ae539b816abcd1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel Ltd. Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steel-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3830493</link><description>JSW Steel Ltd., a leading player in the ferrous metals industry, has reached an all-time high in its stock price, underscoring a period of robust performance and sustained growth. The stock’s recent surge reflects a culmination of consistent gains and strong market positioning within its sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7e30eac7f05bcab38e635ab0d9856516</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lakhotia Polyesters (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/lakhotia-polyesters-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830410</link><description>Lakhotia Polyesters (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>b6c153aa80d22ce0d8fa80a1f549f5d6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/360-one-wam-ltd-is-rated-hold-3830411</link><description>360 ONE WAM Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the most recent insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>798b4b888d9212c358e91303c6aa9f35</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nrb-industrial-bearings-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830412</link><description>NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>21918f3ccc52a7ff1395abc4f4423a4b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Super Tannery Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/super-tannery-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830409</link><description>Super Tannery Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the most recent insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>5119b1f4e9e1b7d00ebf8c8f8f4273b9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dynavision Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dynavision-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830408</link><description>Dynavision Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 12 August 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here are based on the company’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and valuation.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>e23352d0f27700012ca6fde7a6cd16b5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ritesh International Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ritesh-international-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3830406</link><description>Ritesh International Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 25 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>0dface9c644a04c281971cf14ec6e898</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonu Infratech Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sonu-infratech-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830404</link><description>Sonu Infratech Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>237557125887dbc5800e2062ff751c08</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Photo Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jindal-photo-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3830407</link><description>Jindal Photo Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>edba764b82d4037c8ce5c4941946a538</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ABB India Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/abb-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3830405</link><description>ABB India Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>918fd117699e99dae1a3a0f09605b5b4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comfort Fincap Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/comfort-fincap-ltd-is-rated-sell-3830403</link><description>Comfort Fincap Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>89aff916598cd18bfd7d18be4c689b75</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Containers Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gujarat-containers-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830400</link><description>Gujarat Containers Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>bff3e81e779ee773c2eb996fe516c99f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Insurance Corporation of India is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/life-insurance-corporation-of-india-is-rated-sell-3830401</link><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>dc1baa7e41795ef965d8bd0692e946e7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Haryana Capfin Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/haryana-capfin-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830399</link><description>Haryana Capfin Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>cc49e23f8e13ae22a45f58b552259649</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nirlon Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nirlon-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3830397</link><description>Nirlon Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 January 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>2d48c174715aaef0617d89ffa8cfab96</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanrhea Technical Textile Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sanrhea-technical-textile-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830398</link><description>Sanrhea Technical Textile Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>23aeead1295388547decdbc2fcf89648</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Spinners Ltd. is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/deepak-spinners-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830395</link><description>Deepak Spinners Ltd. is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 06 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>28bd659dfc09798f09a114045efca8f9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Accel Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/accel-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830394</link><description>Accel Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>003a557834394eefd4696cc0ddd85e6a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pioneer Embroideries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pioneer-embroideries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3830396</link><description>Pioneer Embroideries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 28 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 10 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>c9e68ff04a1a01214ff64711a0d1d10f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>