<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Jupiter Life Line Hospitals Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jupiter-life-line-hospitals-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3768436</link><description>Jupiter Life Line Hospitals has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price movement.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>6b97063a3b43bf326f4aa7ae52ff0b30</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fusion Finance Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fusion-finance-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768432</link><description>Fusion Finance has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock’s long-term momentum.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>96e4f46397aeb026ede82afca8235b4a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvoco-vistas-corporation-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3768433</link><description>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation, a key player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>bf10d0af2b09a4a330b1381d41a349d8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laxmi Goldorna House Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/laxmi-goldorna-house-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768428</link><description>Laxmi Goldorna House, a small-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the medium to long term.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>0b7d63d15c8f00a4535cb43649f015f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solara Active Pharma Sciences Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solara-active-pharma-sciences-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3768430</link><description>Solara Active Pharma Sciences has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, often interpreted as a signal of potential long-term weakness and bearish momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>d1309d2be086b92f8a94eb723bb1bf78</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banka Bioloo Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/banka-bioloo-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768435</link><description>Banka Bioloo, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and highlights potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>8799bb30e91d089a24f68932f8b39e6b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Cement Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/star-cement-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768434</link><description>Star Cement has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>68400d30497230c6945849c0040df665</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Optiemus Infracom Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/optiemus-infracom-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768429</link><description>Optiemus Infracom, a player in the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>3f25d413b5cc1468dbfa024511fd8391</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khaitan (India) Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/khaitan-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768427</link><description>Khaitan (India), a player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>7ddb47b39f6572825e976d55db04474e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aegis Logistics Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aegis-logistics-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768431</link><description>Aegis Logistics, a key player in the gas sector, has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed below the 200-day moving average, forming what is commonly known as a Death Cross. This event is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a possible shift towards a prolonged downtrend and signalling caution for investors monitoring the stock’s trajectory.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>e8ceb0b86cd67bbdbc69c9772b240f0f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yuvraaj Hygiene Products Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yuvraaj-hygiene-products-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768419</link><description>Yuvraaj Hygiene Products, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>e20d59bae8bfa963dbc2e6f81bbad501</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Corp. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/welspun-corp-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768425</link><description>Welspun Corp., a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>c4c18a194fd421aed51a19d6067955a4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godrej Properties Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godrej-properties-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768423</link><description>Godrej Properties, a prominent player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>8c25429bdd8d5ee5e484968fb85e305d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ugro Capital Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ugro-capital-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768426</link><description>Ugro Capital, a player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>94eb6f1b34a87ca95cd3d8c662e9719d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aeroflex Industries Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aeroflex-industries-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3768422</link><description>Aeroflex Industries, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, suggesting a potential shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>56507a5b4e457085c7589aced51b4995</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanla Platforms Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanla-platforms-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768420</link><description>Tanla Platforms, a key player in the Software Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>dda274c04414ae67984ce4c2d2ddd130</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axtel Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axtel-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3768421</link><description>Axtel Industries, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and may indicate a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>3abb05447f02b44f86ecdf8475d3b654</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Ambuja Exports Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-ambuja-exports-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3768418</link><description>Gujarat Ambuja Exports has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend, suggesting a possible long-term momentum change for the stock within the Other Agricultural Products sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>2f76d687319f1e64759115c50bd95733</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amrutanjan Health Care Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amrutanjan-health-care-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3768424</link><description>Amrutanjan Health Care has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price over the longer term.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>846f782d5ed41e15bb335110343f825d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Shaily Engineer Lead Market Trends in Sep 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-4005-stocks-in-sep-2025-quarter-3768417</link><description>The September 2025 quarter earnings season has seen 4,005 companies report their results, revealing nuanced trends across market capitalisations and sectors. Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, and Shaily Engineer have emerged as notable performers within their respective categories, while aggregate data points to a cautious but steady market environment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6d6dbee35fda72f5e0b02df70cb1aec1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>