<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>SRM Contractors Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srm-contractors-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842819</link><description>SRM Contractors Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—suggesting a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>6d5a2370ece3eda4a698bf7b51f9604e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Metropolis Healthcare Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/metropolis-healthcare-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842818</link><description>Metropolis Healthcare Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>36dcd8d8705fbde3e38714648877c16f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salasar Techno Engineering Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/salasar-techno-engineering-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3842817</link><description>Salasar Techno Engineering Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>91821330e83f9367045043956254ba5d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukand Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukand-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842811</link><description>Mukand Ltd, a player in the ferrous metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term price trajectory.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>6d94bb6eb2148c4a3492ef94323b9656</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precision Electronics Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/precision-electronics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3842816</link><description>Precision Electronics Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>cd5ebbbda52c57ae4f9cb3dc07416359</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3842814</link><description>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting renewed investor confidence and a possible trend reversal in the capital markets sector.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>3d126ff24592988d220bd04468461385</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orchid Pharma Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orchid-pharma-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842809</link><description>Orchid Pharma Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term prospects amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>18c9afb36285d5f82ba1d62e4bfcd579</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orosil Smiths India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orosil-smiths-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842813</link><description>Orosil Smiths India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about its long-term price strength.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>bfbfecf051c6035b407fc3f1378dc8e3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zeal Aqua Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zeal-aqua-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3842812</link><description>Zeal Aqua Ltd, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, marking a possible trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>a85f91cc826ff3586d106af3331fe273</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sikozy Realtors Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sikozy-realtors-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3842810</link><description>Sikozy Realtors Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that investors may want to closely monitor the stock for emerging opportunities despite its current Sell Mojo Grade.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>97c5082ebc777b816fa668f12aa49d9a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modi Rubber Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/modi-rubber-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3842815</link><description>Modi Rubber Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Tyres &amp; Rubber Products sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that investors may want to closely monitor the stock for emerging opportunities despite its current challenges.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>df43b0c1fd70aa3fd0b9a0f99c192b2b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Autoline Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/autoline-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3842808</link><description>Autoline Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently witnessed a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed above the 200-day moving average, forming a Golden Cross. This event is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>a940d064cf2370a100a06d7de33c5687</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3842806</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture as 4,053 companies declared results, revealing a modest improvement in positive earnings surprises but persistent sectoral disparities. While mid-cap stocks continue to outperform their large-cap counterparts in terms of profit growth and beat ratios, the overall market sentiment remains cautious amid mixed financial performances.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>ba17c1eeb3fe6841257d335968711059</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.27</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs27-3842736</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.27, marking a significant downturn amid a series of negative financial indicators and sustained underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>15e6e9ff0d461e1822fad92e6e0ef00d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dollar Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dollar-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3842737</link><description>Dollar Industries Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, closing just 0.79% above its lowest price of Rs 302.6, marking a significant point in its recent trading performance as the stock continues to face downward pressure.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2a9d95cda9b063f8bcd03f3022858a51</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VIP Clothing Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vip-clothing-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3842732</link><description>VIP Clothing Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently touched a 52-week low price of ₹22.76, marking a significant decline in its stock performance amid persistent challenges and subdued financial metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bfe25acb6a6e17dd73527acf44ced04b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allied Digital Services Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allied-digital-services-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3842733</link><description>Shares of Allied Digital Services Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 110.6, marking a significant milestone in the stock's ongoing downward trajectory. This development reflects a series of recent price declines amid broader market movements and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>777a924e5c6e788e0d70446494bca616</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shreyans Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.147.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shreyans-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1475-3842730</link><description>Shares of Shreyans Industries Ltd, a player in the Paper, Forest &amp; Jute Products sector, declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.147.5 on 16 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s recent performance trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ee23affb0f16ef000a2e1833e7ddfd03</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RPP Infra Projects Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rpp-infra-projects-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3842729</link><description>Shares of RPP Infra Projects Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 75.16, marking a significant downturn amid persistent negative returns and underperformance relative to the broader market and sector indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1cc911be0a24ab486a8cc5d91d0fe276</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEAMEC Ltd Reaches New 52-Week High, Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/seamec-ltd-reaches-new-52-week-high-marking-significant-milestone-3842734</link><description>SEAMEC Ltd, a key player in the Transport Services sector, has reached a new 52-week high, touching an intraday peak of ₹1,408.60. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust momentum, reflecting a sustained upward trajectory over recent sessions and signalling a notable milestone for the company’s market performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>01682a1fd18717d1285a8c5b388d69b6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>