<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Upsurge Investment &amp; Finance Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/upsurge-investment-finance-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3827175</link><description>Upsurge Investment &amp; Finance Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 12 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>d15484b95d854e54299142ca8bb177a0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Destiny Logistics &amp; Infra Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/destiny-logistics-infra-ltd-is-rated-sell-3827176</link><description>Destiny Logistics &amp; Infra Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7a914aec80ac41c30c96d1e31964bd65</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ramco Cements Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/the-ramco-cements-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3827173</link><description>The Ramco Cements Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>21e7f37eb921c084292aa9b5584d2758</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stratmont Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/stratmont-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3827174</link><description>Stratmont Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on its performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>9de3d01f25cd1f35a7ce380171be3657</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhagwati Autocast Ltd is Rated Strong Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bhagwati-autocast-ltd-is-rated-strong-buy-3827172</link><description>Bhagwati Autocast Ltd is rated Strong Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>31407f9e136ccb47ddd830fd99f86b70</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atishay Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/atishay-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3827170</link><description>Atishay Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>39f2124a268a2f4f88f7cfdcb625cf4f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>W H Brady &amp; Co Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/w-h-brady-co-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3827171</link><description>W H Brady &amp; Co Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 14 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest view of the company’s position.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>02b1ea2724722be414db600eb9c7c3af</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G S Auto International Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/g-s-auto-international-ltd-is-rated-sell-3827169</link><description>G S Auto International Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>1517d91e0a74ebf487d5fe01af6fb213</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ruchi Infrastructure Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ruchi-infrastructure-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3827168</link><description>Ruchi Infrastructure Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>8a7f73d89b60bdd7a43d10da7f9158b2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pritika Engineering Components Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pritika-engineering-components-ltd-is-rated-sell-3827167</link><description>Pritika Engineering Components Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the most recent and relevant data to assess the company's outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>485c951b478af6b5ef6ed851f22c3578</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TeleCanor Global Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/telecanor-global-ltd-is-rated-hold-3827165</link><description>TeleCanor Global Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>ccb9e674a3c6e613f567fccc258a99d9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Enterprises Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/welspun-enterprises-ltd-is-rated-sell-3827166</link><description>Welspun Enterprises Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>9f03137490f25b5a8056fa3fd0763200</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RDB Infrastructure and Power Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rdb-infrastructure-and-power-ltd-is-rated-hold-3827164</link><description>RDB Infrastructure and Power Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>3f3cf1c570755b3e573e4963a87af948</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kritika Wires Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kritika-wires-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3827163</link><description>Kritika Wires Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 July 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>08f701364c5dd5176a9a0c033708e3d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silgo Retail Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/silgo-retail-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3827161</link><description>Silgo Retail Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>ed02d6d08508e7986276af649c7fedae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonal Mercantile Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sonal-mercantile-ltd-is-rated-sell-3827162</link><description>Sonal Mercantile Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>71d17acbfec50201cf91c940618f09cd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMJ Land Holdings Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/amj-land-holdings-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3827160</link><description>AMJ Land Holdings Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>ff5477548b25c7c6e568781d213468d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhav Copper Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/madhav-copper-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3827158</link><description>Madhav Copper Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>c5421bdd110ed27d0621f1b4d65e2594</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Binayaka Tex Processors Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/binayaka-tex-processors-ltd-is-rated-sell-3827159</link><description>Binayaka Tex Processors Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>fd4a602b047f39fbe6801b741657ff23</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vipul Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vipul-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3827157</link><description>Vipul Ltd is rated 'Strong Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 February 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 08 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>11dc02e15c755559282ea320aede4dce</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>