<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Chamunda Electrical Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-chamunda-electrical-ltd-fallingrising-3823432</link><description>On 05-Feb, Chamunda Electrical Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.41% to ₹45.30, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over recent weeks and months.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0c24724d401c1bd4788b2810298204a2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Standard Enginnering Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-enginnering-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3823431</link><description>On 05-Feb, Standard Engineering Technology Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.63% to close at ₹118.30. This drop follows two consecutive days of gains and reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>85e4b3f4a2af0003c6a426d8a3fc3215</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajputana Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajputana-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3823430</link><description>On 05-Feb, Rajputana Industries Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.25% to close at ₹75.80. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor participation, despite some positive operational metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ff565fd2c6fe453b2cbfae4e459d7aaa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awfis-space-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3823429</link><description>On 05-Feb, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹373.40, down ₹12.55 or 3.25%. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market indices and sector peers, despite the company’s strong operational growth and improving profitability metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d131dc7202f1f06fba0972f7b97e39c7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Megatherm Induction Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-megatherm-induction-ltd-fallingrising-3823428</link><description>On 05-Feb, Megatherm Induction Ltd's stock price fell sharply by 5.69%, closing at ₹215.65, reflecting a notable underperformance relative to its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a21ed471744430f79ca9a2e3342c0df5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is HP Adhesives Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hp-adhesives-ltd-fallingrising-3823427</link><description>On 05-Feb, HP Adhesives Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 2.47% to close at ₹39.86. This gain reflects a short-term positive momentum despite the company’s challenging performance over longer periods.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>274158b934a1d3490827bf95e96bfc0a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cohance Lifesciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cohance-lifesciences-ltd-fallingrising-3823426</link><description>On 05-Feb, Cohance Lifesciences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹356.95, down ₹9.8 or 2.67% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend influenced by disappointing financial results, underperformance relative to benchmarks, and market concerns over promoter share pledging.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>634418b7535743ac02945c8eb7045c10</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anuroop Packaging Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anuroop-packaging-ltd-fallingrising-3823425</link><description>On 05-Feb, Anuroop Packaging Ltd's stock price rose by 5.17% to ₹10.57, marking a notable rebound despite the company’s challenging long-term fundamentals and a weak sector performance. This article analyses the factors behind the recent price movement and the broader context of the stock’s performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>77768e42b9288f264c3599a7981a4566</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nila Spaces Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nila-spaces-ltd-fallingrising-3823424</link><description>As of 05-Feb, Nila Spaces Ltd’s stock price surged by 5.23% to ₹15.50, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. This rise follows a series of positive financial indicators and consistent long-term growth, despite some concerns over valuation and management efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b0a04711b36e19a694d0143ea66b6bc3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ambani Orgochem Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ambani-orgochem-ltd-fallingrising-3823423</link><description>On 05-Feb, Ambani Orgochem Ltd’s stock price surged by 4.96% to close at ₹114.20, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7d6e2cf6a281e392a5e359eeb6052e9c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Hardwyn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hardwyn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3823422</link><description>On 05-Feb, Hardwyn India Ltd's stock price rose by 3.62% to ₹16.89, outperforming its sector and broader market indices despite some underlying challenges in its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>50b5a40123f26cde8aa23f50952bebd8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GCM Securities Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gcm-securities-ltd-fallingrising-3823421</link><description>On 05-Feb, GCM Securities Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 2.63% to close at ₹0.78. This movement reflects a short-term positive momentum driven by increased investor interest and recent consecutive gains, despite the stock's longer-term underperformance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>807af3a422d1ec01efa23bbefa98ff94</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omfurn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omfurn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3823420</link><description>On 05-Feb, Omfurn India Ltd's stock price fell to ₹48.30, marking a decline of 0.92% and hitting a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges in both short-term and long-term performance metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fd2ac51cfe95babba1c9fa9a33f207d5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-educational-initiatives-ltd-fallingrising-3823419</link><description>On 05-Feb, Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, closing at ₹175.85 with an 8.25% gain, reflecting robust investor confidence and notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>767541eace97e8dd05e6846c18178c15</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Prime Fresh Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-prime-fresh-ltd-fallingrising-3823418</link><description>On 05-Feb, Prime Fresh Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 7.58% to close at ₹253.15. This drop comes amid a period of heightened volatility and waning investor participation, despite the company’s robust long-term growth and recent positive quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ffcbdcb82f7a852e33d9e6fa556fd5f5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jash Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jash-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3823417</link><description>As of 05-Feb, Jash Engineering Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply by 5.05% to ₹387.35, reflecting investor concerns over recent financial performance and valuation metrics despite some positive operational indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e07e424b2f0241af39d0a48d8817c9ce</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-tirupati-balajee-fibc-ltd-fallingrising-3823416</link><description>On 05-Feb, Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 4.12%, closing at ₹588.80. This rise comes despite the stock's underperformance over longer time frames and subdued investor participation, reflecting a complex market dynamic.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9fa322caebe9737ae77bf0647b106568</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-housing-development-infrastructure-ltd-fallingrising-3823415</link><description>On 05-Feb, Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its stock price, climbing 4.6% to ₹2.50 by 09:03 PM, reflecting a short-term rally despite persistent long-term underperformance and fundamental weaknesses.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ad210d866bacdf6771d3e5fdb265b5be</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vivanta Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vivanta-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3823414</link><description>On 05-Feb, Vivanta Industries Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹1.77, down 5.85% from the previous session. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including weak long-term fundamentals and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e4de37fb469a20a418906e3a2d718a9c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anand Rayons Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anand-rayons-ltd-fallingrising-3823413</link><description>As of 05-Feb, Anand Rayons Ltd experienced a significant decline in its share price, falling 5.0% to ₹255.55. This drop continues a downward trend over the past week, despite the company’s recent strong quarterly results and impressive long-term returns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9bebad4f34ae809b3891893b739abb05</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>