<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Adani Green Energy Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 13 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-green-energy-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-13-feb-2026-3836985</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 955.55, reflecting a 4.18% drop from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market amid a generally negative trading session, weighed down by broader market pressures and technical factors.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>b92f7e322601ae1be2e177c022d60e16</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 13 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-13-feb-2026-3836984</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 13 Feb 2026, touching a new 52-week low of Rs 824.4 as the stock faced intense price pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>2586db5b657382946ab6a24d99dd191e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Hume Pipe Company Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-hume-pipe-company-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3836983</link><description>Indian Hume Pipe Company Ltd experienced significant intraday weakness on 13 Feb 2026, with its stock price touching a low of Rs 366.95, marking an 8.11% decline from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment within the industrial manufacturing space.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>ab4a9f4d0d1bfa3a2d82729cc496c331</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 13 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-13-feb-2026-3836981</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd. experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 1,463.8, reflecting a 4.72% drop as the stock faced sustained selling pressure amid broader market weakness and sectoral downturns.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>bb8db90b298de1164aa454671bfde1e3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DLF Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 13 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dlf-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-13-feb-2026-3836980</link><description>Shares of DLF Ltd. declined sharply on 13 Feb 2026, hitting an intraday low of Rs 627, reflecting sustained price pressure amid broader market weakness and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>c81201a14b8bfc9a7345905c8ccfefe7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3836979</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC) experienced a notable intraday decline on 13 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 266.4, reflecting a 3.57% drop from its previous close. This downturn occurred amid broader market weakness and sector-specific pressures, marking a reversal after three consecutive days of gains.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>bf5cf6daeb2e07c67425ea360576c1c9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Hotels Co Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 13 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-hotels-co-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-13-feb-2026-3836976</link><description>Indian Hotels Co Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 13 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 683.95, down 3.89% from its previous close. This drop occurred amid broader market weakness and sectoral pressures, reflecting immediate selling interest and a break in the stock’s recent upward momentum.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>33119065a75cfa645c01aecde1de5eb9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesh Infraworld Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganesh-infraworld-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3836978</link><description>Shares of Ganesh Infraworld Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily loss of 4.96%. The stock closed at ₹98.60, down ₹5.15 from the previous close, as intense selling pressure and panic selling gripped investors, leaving a significant volume of unfilled supply on the order books.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>93883347146b8a6ae4dfe5780c80ee47</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cool Caps Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cool-caps-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3836982</link><description>Cool Caps Industries Ltd surged to its upper circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.97% as robust buying interest propelled the stock to ₹28.50. This sharp rally occurred despite the broader market and sector indices closing in negative territory, underscoring the stock’s distinct momentum and investor enthusiasm.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>f81898808f527fbcfb6996c55054f0ac</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaxtex Cotfab Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaxtex-cotfab-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3836974</link><description>Vaxtex Cotfab Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, reflecting robust buying interest and a maximum daily gain of 4.21%. This notable price action comes amid a broader market downturn, underscoring the stock’s relative strength and investor enthusiasm despite sectoral headwinds.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>ecb991ed4d2a3c671cc35772f785e68b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axita Cotton Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axita-cotton-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3836977</link><description>Axita Cotton Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, propelled by strong investor demand and sustained buying momentum. The stock outperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting renewed market confidence amid a backdrop of rising volumes and positive technical indicators.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>454cb80c9ba525e8a018b39c8fa1f962</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kore Digital Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kore-digital-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3836975</link><description>Shares of Kore Digital Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Telecom Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and investor panic. The stock closed at ₹140.2, down 4.98% intraday, marking a maximum daily loss that underscores growing concerns about the company’s near-term prospects.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>1d5451d5e8244318e525f48cf5930db0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gayatri Highways Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gayatri-highways-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3836973</link><description>Gayatri Highways Ltd (NSE: EQ) surged to its upper circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, closing at ₹2.88, marking a robust 4.73% gain on the day. This rally was driven by intense buying pressure, with the stock outperforming its sector and broader indices despite subdued investor participation. The micro-cap transport infrastructure company has now recorded eight consecutive days of gains, accumulating a remarkable 44.72% return over this period.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>08b0c716e0f331988f09c8e9e7b1c5b8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrenik Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shrenik-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3836971</link><description>Shrenik Ltd, a micro-cap player in the miscellaneous sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.76%. This sharp price movement was driven by robust buying interest, resulting in a regulatory freeze on further trading and signalling unfilled demand at the upper price band.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>e08e837e1a29f0dcbe58a467f4e29861</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nirman-agri-genetics-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3836970</link><description>Shares of Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, closing at ₹62.90 with a sharp decline of 4.98% in a single trading session. The micro-cap stock witnessed intense selling pressure, reflecting investor panic and a significant drop in participation, signalling a challenging outlook for the company in the Other Agricultural Products sector.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>01130dc91399a532501b514fe240cb7f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Declining Momentum and Institutional Caution</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-declining-momentum-and-institutional-caution-3836967</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 13 Feb 2026, registering one of the highest value turnovers on the day. Despite this liquidity and investor interest, the stock has faced downward pressure, reflecting a cautious stance among institutional investors amid broader sectoral weakness.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>fe4ee9d7ee7cdd11e25c2c991bc2dec4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laxmi Cotspin Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/laxmi-cotspin-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3836972</link><description>Laxmi Cotspin Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 13 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 9.99%. The stock closed at ₹24.44, marking a significant turnaround amid strong buying pressure and heightened investor interest, outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>b83244129649c2629e13848f68ad1a89</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-aeronautics-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3836969</link><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL), a heavyweight in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 13 Feb 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹37,799 lakhs. Despite a modest day gain of 0.33%, the stock outperformed its sector and the broader Sensex, reflecting sustained institutional interest and robust liquidity in a challenging market environment.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>66df405186d566815add7fb1857c40cd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Auri Grow India Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/auri-grow-india-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3836966</link><description>Auri Grow India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the industrial manufacturing sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 13 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit price limit of ₹0.34. The stock faced intense selling pressure, culminating in a maximum daily loss of 2.86%, underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices. This downturn reflects mounting investor concerns amid persistent unfilled supply and deteriorating technical indicators.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>8db60e9ce265205dc773de10ca6f9391</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JITF Infra Logistics Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jitf-infra-logistics-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-momentum-3836968</link><description>JITF Infra Logistics Ltd witnessed a robust surge in investor interest on 13 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a maximum daily gain of 4.99%. The stock closed at ₹374.25, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing rally, driven by strong buying pressure and heightened market participation despite a broader sector and market downturn.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>153827a3f212ebd4eca943979c7f0826</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>