<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Fineotex Chemical Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fineotex-chemical-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787418</link><description>Fineotex Chemical Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns over the stock’s near-term outlook.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>663b53b402eca36e482c11598114e1ba</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd. Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apollo-hospitals-enterprise-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787417</link><description>Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd., a leading player in the hospital sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term strength despite its strong fundamentals and large-cap status.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>15fd6cf48af3bd8a39ef9f207c80203a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhav Copper Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhav-copper-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3787419</link><description>Madhav Copper Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting renewed investor interest despite the company’s current Mojo Grade of Sell.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>7ac39ec040ac7d4e97b556cadf284bb4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JM Financial Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jm-financial-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787421</link><description>JM Financial Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its near-term outlook amid broader market pressures.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>f8eefd78a7fa23315dd76a2c3ce96a3e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Niyogin Fintech Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Prolonged Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/niyogin-fintech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-prolonged-bearish-trend-3787416</link><description>Niyogin Fintech Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>e20f142b0f7600be7e2d196d97f80fc8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tilak Ventures Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tilak-ventures-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3787420</link><description>Tilak Ventures Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that investors may want to closely monitor the stock for possible trend reversals.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>457a624710a8dd2de4790393fcdec701</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.90.44</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs9044-3787370</link><description>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd achieved a significant milestone on 9 Jan 2026, reaching a new 52-week high of Rs.90.44. This marks a notable peak in the stock’s performance, reflecting sustained momentum over the past several weeks amid a broader market environment that has seen mixed trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b136bf5e55ffd8111336bf8c0d7dbf3a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zodiac Energy Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.281 Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zodiac-energy-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs281-amid-market-downturn-3787369</link><description>Zodiac Energy Ltd’s shares fell to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.281 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market weakness and sectoral pressures. The stock has now recorded a five-day losing streak, cumulatively shedding 8.46% over this period, reflecting ongoing challenges in the construction sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ff66323dc941ce19e9809f175381cae2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R K Swamy Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-k-swamy-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787368</link><description>Shares of R K Swamy Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 104.45, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>957f1244a04ab44f8b8e246890a77b03</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GTPL Hathway Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gtpl-hathway-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787366</link><description>Shares of GTPL Hathway Ltd., a key player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, have declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures on the stock. The latest low price marks a significant milestone in the company’s recent performance, underscoring a sustained downward trajectory over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>38ab961dfbd45ced9396ccc80361b054</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diligent Media Corporation Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 3.47</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/diligent-media-corporation-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-347-3787367</link><description>Diligent Media Corporation Ltd’s share price has fallen to a fresh 52-week low of ₹3.47, marking a significant downturn for the media and entertainment company. The stock closed 2.53% above this low on 9 Jan 2026, continuing a four-day losing streak that has seen a cumulative decline of 4.81% in recent sessions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e3ab1630624cd979d4749c86e10294e6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pudumjee-paper-products-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787365</link><description>Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd has reached a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 90.3, marking a significant decline amid persistent downward momentum. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures within the Paper, Forest &amp; Jute Products sector, with the share price now trading well below key moving averages and underperforming both its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f6fb46a8bae11e794fb5306266d5aa74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trigyn Technologies Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trigyn-technologies-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787359</link><description>Shares of Trigyn Technologies Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, touching an intraday price of Rs 63, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects sustained pressures on the company’s valuation amid subdued financial performance and broader market headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b2a82b1528ef9b1e65c766d6b3b4bd10</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donear Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/donear-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3787360</link><description>Donear Industries Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing at an intraday low of Rs 90.01 on 9 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b18b3f8ad555c8e7b303ce274a947011</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ducon Infratechnologies Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ducon-infratechnologies-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787364</link><description>Shares of Ducon Infratechnologies Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 3.25, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent pressures on the company’s valuation amid broader market weakness and sectoral headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8526e0b86d7b587626b3333a58e6c501</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greenply Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/greenply-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3787358</link><description>Greenply Industries Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 228.6, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock’s recent performance reflects a series of challenges impacting its valuation and market standing within the plywood boards and laminates sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8275cec5dabe1e3511c57d40485c654c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TTK Healthcare Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ttk-healthcare-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3787362</link><description>TTK Healthcare Ltd. has touched a new 52-week low, closing just 0.8% above its lowest price of Rs 991, reflecting a continuation of its subdued market performance amid broader sector declines and company-specific factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>47be878756cf151b9a1d7df87ee38928</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kohinoor Foods Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kohinoor-foods-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787357</link><description>Kohinoor Foods Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures on the stock which closed at its lowest price point in the past year. The stock’s recent performance highlights a sustained decline amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2599f4f921dad16264d547676134a8a8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Standard Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/standard-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787361</link><description>Standard Industries Ltd, a player in the realty sector, has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges in its financial performance and market valuation. The stock’s recent decline to this significant price level underscores persistent headwinds faced by the company amid a broader market downturn.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9ebe5854c6d68359f2142abad8c69a55</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>