<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:19:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rudra-global-infra-products-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3793028</link><description>Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 16.67% to ₹136.44 crores, but net profit plummeted by 75.41% to ₹1.19 crores due to declining profit margins and rising interest expenses, indicating significant operational challenges. Overall, the results are concerning for profitability and financial sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>276c9c0992d3286bb5650d5e83443262</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Comfort Intech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-comfort-intech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3793027</link><description>Comfort Intech Ltd's latest results are mixed; while there was a significant quarter-on-quarter sales recovery, the company reported a net loss of ₹2.12 crores and a year-on-year revenue decline, indicating ongoing operational challenges and concerns about financial health. Investors should watch for improvements in profitability and revenue consistency in future quarters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d5bdd1f4f7e631119f144e3eba203d1e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mangalam Drugs and Organics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mangalam-drugs-and-organics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3793026</link><description>Mangalam Drugs and Organics Ltd's latest results are poor, reporting a net loss of ₹7.35 crores and a 38.03% decline in net sales to ₹49.54 crores, indicating severe operational distress and ongoing structural issues.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>55de4af27a1f89e23314fb646f02c31f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are GEE Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gee-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3793025</link><description>GEE Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show significant operational recovery with a 7.92% increase in net sales and a 329.59% rise in net profit, indicating positive trends. However, ongoing challenges like negative ROE, high debt levels, and modest year-on-year growth suggest that the company still faces substantial risks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>aee809a3df047475633755bbe3401825</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Capfin India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-capfin-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3793024</link><description>Capfin India Ltd's latest results show a positive turnaround in profitability with a PAT of Rs 0.09 crore, up from a loss of Rs -0.49 crore last year. However, the company faced significant declines in net sales and profit margins, indicating operational challenges that warrant close monitoring in future quarters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>641644f2be24280208a34139c0156a04</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>