<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sunflag Iron &amp; Steel Company Ltd: Valuation Shifts Signal Renewed Price Attractiveness Amid Sector Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sunflag-iron-steel-company-ltd-valuation-shifts-signal-renewed-price-attractiveness-amid-sector-challenges-3841430</link><description>Sunflag Iron &amp; Steel Company Ltd has witnessed a notable improvement in its valuation parameters, shifting from a fair to an attractive rating, despite ongoing sector headwinds. This change reflects a more compelling price proposition for investors, supported by favourable price-to-earnings and price-to-book value metrics relative to its peers and historical averages.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4abda0a83d6c7952f74495510535b0c7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ADC India Communications Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adc-india-communications-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downturn-3841428</link><description>ADC India Communications Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bearish stance to a more pronounced bearish trend. Despite a strong long-term return profile, recent technical indicators such as MACD, RSI, and moving averages signal caution for investors as the stock price faces downward pressure amid sector headwinds and broader market volatility.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>04902024f4b0816edfd167b0c3240de1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aptech Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Bearish Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aptech-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-bearish-signals-3841426</link><description>Aptech Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a transition from mildly bearish to bearish trends. Despite a recent downgrade in its technical trend, the stock’s price action and momentum metrics reveal a complex picture that investors should carefully analyse amid broader market conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>003284d1359980a80bbf8054c2b3d25e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scoobee Day Garments India Ltd Valuation Shifts Signal Heightened Risk</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/scoobee-day-garments-india-ltd-valuation-shifts-signal-heightened-risk-3841427</link><description>Scoobee Day Garments India Ltd has experienced a marked shift in its valuation parameters, moving from an expensive to a risky classification. This transition, underscored by deteriorating price-to-earnings (P/E) and price-to-book value (P/BV) ratios, raises concerns about the stock’s price attractiveness relative to its historical averages and industry peers within the Garments &amp; Apparels sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d5886d57ddb652477a81d2f5f3833a2e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanla Platforms Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Downgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanla-platforms-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downgrade-3841429</link><description>Tanla Platforms Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a transition from mildly bearish to a more pronounced bearish trend. This change comes amid a broader market context where the stock has underperformed the Sensex across multiple timeframes, raising concerns about its near-term outlook within the software products sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a29a2dfbf717a26f4391f9496c55dc0a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kingfa Science &amp; Technology (India) Ltd: Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Indicator Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kingfa-science-technology-india-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-indicator-signals-3841424</link><description>Kingfa Science &amp; Technology (India) Ltd has experienced a nuanced shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bullish to a mildly bullish trend as of mid-February 2026. Despite a slight dip in daily price, the stock’s technical indicators present a complex picture, with some signals pointing to caution while others suggest underlying strength. This analysis delves into the recent technical parameter changes, evaluating key momentum indicators such as MACD, RSI, moving averages, and volume trends to provide a comprehensive view of the stock’s near-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2005565e84deca0758eada2f874d4371</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KDDL Ltd Valuation Shifts: Price Attractiveness Dims Amid Elevated Multiples</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kddl-ltd-valuation-shifts-price-attractiveness-dims-amid-elevated-multiples-3841425</link><description>KDDL Ltd, a key player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector, has experienced a notable shift in its valuation parameters, moving from a very expensive to an expensive rating. This change, coupled with a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Strong Sell, reflects evolving market perceptions and raises questions about the stock’s price attractiveness relative to its historical and peer benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>560a3fb97228056e3b15e3830fadbfe5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Indicator Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/poonawalla-fincorp-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-indicator-signals-3841423</link><description>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has experienced a nuanced shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish signals across multiple timeframes. Despite a recent downgrade in daily price performance, the company’s long-term trend remains robust, supported by strong moving averages and a significant outperformance relative to the Sensex over the past year and beyond.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e0aafea887401938e6e56e66db160f28</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Royale Manor Hotels &amp; Industries Ltd: Valuation Shift Signals Price Attractiveness Change</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/royale-manor-hotels-industries-ltd-valuation-shift-signals-price-attractiveness-change-3841422</link><description>Royale Manor Hotels &amp; Industries Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its valuation parameters, moving from a very expensive to an expensive rating. This change, reflected in key metrics such as the price-to-earnings (P/E) and price-to-book value (P/BV) ratios, signals a subtle improvement in price attractiveness relative to its historical and peer averages. However, the company’s overall financial health and market performance continue to warrant a cautious stance from investors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>39e963da30dcf6ee1d469a99909c7d69</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Srichakra Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Indicator Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-srichakra-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-indicator-signals-3841421</link><description>TVS Srichakra Ltd, a key player in the Tyres &amp; Rubber Products sector, has experienced a nuanced shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish signals across multiple timeframes. Despite a recent downgrade in daily price performance, the stock’s longer-term outlook remains positive, supported by a strong MarketsMOJO Mojo Score upgrade to 74.0 and a Buy rating, signalling renewed investor confidence.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>27719a92f9189f81f1862867d1a2392e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saint-Gobain Sekurit India Ltd Valuation Shifts Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saint-gobain-sekurit-india-ltd-valuation-shifts-amidst-market-volatility-3841420</link><description>Saint-Gobain Sekurit India Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has experienced a notable shift in its valuation parameters, moving from a 'very expensive' to an 'expensive' rating. This change reflects evolving market perceptions amid fluctuating price-to-earnings (P/E) and price-to-book value (P/BV) ratios, alongside a broader peer comparison and recent stock performance trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>949a01de6f98d661737d1f4d1f234764</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIE Automotive India Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cie-automotive-india-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-market-signals-3841418</link><description>CIE Automotive India Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bearish stance to a more sideways trend, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish signals across key technical indicators. This development comes as the stock outperforms the Sensex over recent weeks, prompting a reassessment of its near-term outlook within the auto components sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>730c6278a29d6c93bc91d8f1e1f65034</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys Ltd Valuation Shifts Signal Renewed Price Attractiveness Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infosys-ltd-valuation-shifts-signal-renewed-price-attractiveness-amid-market-pressure-3841419</link><description>Infosys Ltd has witnessed a notable shift in its valuation parameters, moving from a fair to an attractive rating, reflecting a more compelling price point for investors despite recent market headwinds. This recalibration comes amid a broader sectoral and market context where the company’s price-to-earnings (P/E) and price-to-book value (P/BV) ratios have adjusted favourably relative to historical averages and peer benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f27cbb200b2d29f197ef95a8bed8f8ed</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Indicator Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kirloskar-pneumatic-company-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-indicator-signals-3841416</link><description>Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Ltd (Kirl.Pneumatic) has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, transitioning from a sideways trend to a mildly bearish stance. Despite this, the stock continues to outperform the Sensex over multiple time horizons, reflecting underlying resilience amid mixed technical indicator signals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e930e848716385fadfe8b427f4cc05e5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gufic BioSciences Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Downgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gufic-biosciences-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downgrade-3841415</link><description>Gufic BioSciences Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a bearish trend. The stock’s recent downgrade to a Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO reflects deteriorating price action and weakening market sentiment within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d94b9795ae61a9a3075f2c24b7cb30cb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Petronet LNG Ltd. Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Indicator Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/petronet-lng-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-indicator-signals-3841413</link><description>Petronet LNG Ltd. has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a sideways trend to a mildly bearish stance as of February 2026. Despite a recent downgrade in its technical outlook, the stock’s mixed signals across key indicators such as MACD, RSI, and moving averages suggest a complex market environment for investors to navigate.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5236befba0b3792ecdbddd5d587371ce</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gokaldas Exports Ltd: Valuation Shift Signals Expensive Terrain Amid Strong Price Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gokaldas-exports-ltd-valuation-shift-signals-expensive-terrain-amid-strong-price-rally-3841417</link><description>Gokaldas Exports Ltd has seen a marked shift in its valuation parameters, with its price-to-earnings (P/E) and price-to-book value (P/BV) ratios moving from fair to expensive territory. This change raises questions about the stock’s price attractiveness amid a mixed performance backdrop and peer comparisons within the garments and apparels sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7f929d06d5ae219b6769ee2cbabe61ef</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VRL Logistics Ltd Valuation Shifts to Very Attractive Amid Strong Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vrl-logistics-ltd-valuation-shifts-to-very-attractive-amid-strong-financial-metrics-3841414</link><description>VRL Logistics Ltd has seen a significant shift in its valuation parameters, moving from an attractive to a very attractive rating, driven by improved price-to-earnings and price-to-book value metrics. This re-rating comes amid a mixed performance in the transport services sector and offers investors a compelling opportunity to reassess the stock’s price attractiveness relative to its peers and historical benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e7051829c6ab9cf465b556c3fcdb8d1e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>