<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Integrity Infrabuild Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-integrity-infrabuild-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3779400</link><description>On 02-Jan, Integrity Infrabuild Developers Ltd witnessed a notable increase in its share price, rising by 3.6% to close at ₹136.75. This upward movement outpaced the broader market and sector indices, reflecting a robust performance in the face of mixed market conditions.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d2e8b02754b69ad9d8a35f6378ac0444</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sanathan Textiles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanathan-textiles-ltd-fallingrising-3779399</link><description>On 02-Jan, Sanathan Textiles Ltd witnessed a notable price increase of 3.15%, closing at ₹443.40. This rise comes despite a complex backdrop of both encouraging short-term performance and concerning long-term fundamentals, reflecting a nuanced investor sentiment.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>39cbae1859e84649e8d9271461594271</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Unilex Colour &amp; Chemical Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-unilex-colour-chemical-ltd-fallingrising-3779398</link><description>On 02-Jan, Unilex Colour &amp; Chemical Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 5.41% to ₹39.00 by 09:22 PM. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong short-term returns and heightened investor participation, despite the stock’s challenging longer-term performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d0a3621a829e68b01992508466fc2c57</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-krn-heat-exchanger-and-refrigeration-ltd-fallingrising-3779397</link><description>As of 02-Jan, KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd’s stock price has risen sharply by 3.63% to ₹771.20, reflecting a notable rebound driven by robust quarterly performance and increased institutional participation despite some longer-term valuation concerns.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f37768597d2d148f42a47bb41a66f0cc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ola Electric Mobility Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ola-electric-mobility-ltd-fallingrising-3779396</link><description>On 02-Jan, Ola Electric Mobility Ltd’s stock price surged by 9.06% to ₹40.91, marking a notable rebound after a prolonged period of underperformance. This rise comes amid growing investor participation and institutional interest, despite the company’s ongoing operational challenges and weak long-term fundamentals.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>81e052a77f7c78534a604b00162b2ac9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shivalic Power Control Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shivalic-power-control-ltd-fallingrising-3779395</link><description>On 02-Jan, Shivalic Power Control Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 12.7%, closing at ₹112.25. This sharp rise reflects a notable outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks, driven primarily by strong short-term momentum despite lingering longer-term challenges.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>cba09da376e04a9b3f3940779ece2976</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dindigul Farm Product Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dindigul-farm-product-ltd-fallingrising-3779394</link><description>On 02-Jan, Dindigul Farm Product Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.93% to ₹15.75, reflecting a combination of short-term positive momentum and heightened investor participation despite a challenging longer-term performance backdrop.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>fe6b80daff281329f6f64bc2b5fccd07</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aimtron Electronics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aimtron-electronics-ltd-fallingrising-3779393</link><description>On 02-Jan, Aimtron Electronics Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹884.00 with a gain of ₹24.55 or 2.86%. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust short-term performance, increased investor participation, and favourable technical indicators that have contributed to the stock’s outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>88dfaf9f7ea0af93959a5b3927777ca8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree OSFM E-Mobility Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-osfm-e-mobility-ltd-fallingrising-3779392</link><description>On 02-Jan, Shree OSFM E-Mobility Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 8.63% to ₹85.00 by 09:18 PM. This sharp uptick contrasts with the stock’s mixed performance over longer timeframes and highlights a notable short-term rebound amid subdued investor participation.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d0294e4d4c10c56a0b557d13a2b3d741</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Happy Forgings Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-happy-forgings-ltd-fallingrising-3779391</link><description>On 02-Jan, Happy Forgings Ltd saw its share price rise by 2.45% to ₹1,184.95, reaching a new 52-week high of ₹1,190. This upward momentum reflects a combination of robust financial performance, favourable market positioning, and sustained investor interest despite some signs of waning participation.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>69b85cf31bf3f0a813659fdb18404306</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is ARCL Organics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arcl-organics-ltd-fallingrising-3779390</link><description>On 02-Jan, ARCL Organics Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.73% to close at ₹368.60. This drop comes amid a three-day losing streak and contrasts with the broader market's modest gains, raising questions about the factors behind the stock's recent underperformance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>726282c7a24b0e96ff599443299c60b7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is R R Kabel Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-r-r-kabel-ltd-fallingrising-3779389</link><description>On 02-Jan, R R Kabel Ltd's stock price rose by 2.97% to ₹1,511.80, reflecting investor confidence driven by solid quarterly results, sustained growth metrics, and favourable valuation metrics relative to its earnings growth.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a6450db0f5830a62ec7a083172ca658e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Concord Biotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-concord-biotech-ltd-fallingrising-3779388</link><description>On 02-Jan, Concord Biotech Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.87% to close at ₹1,312.00, marking a continuation of its downward trend amid disappointing financial results and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>fbd5a7cd5c7c341966fa201b0f06f2a2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Khazanchi Jewellers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-khazanchi-jewellers-ltd-fallingrising-3779387</link><description>As of 02-Jan, Khazanchi Jewellers Ltd has seen its share price rise by 0.69% to ₹782.75, continuing a sustained upward trend driven by robust financial results and market-beating returns.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a755e0dfe1415d39e9cbeca186abd1ae</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is RBM Infracon Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rbm-infracon-ltd-fallingrising-3779386</link><description>On 02-Jan, RBM Infracon Ltd’s stock price rose by 4.45% to ₹434.25, outperforming its sector and the broader market benchmarks despite a challenging longer-term performance record.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>0f95ba73245fa82a6ada72434415ce6c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Five-Star Business Finance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-five-star-business-finance-ltd-fallingrising-3779385</link><description>As of 02-Jan, Five-Star Business Finance Ltd’s stock price has experienced a modest decline, continuing a downward trend that contrasts with the broader market’s gains. Despite strong fundamental indicators, the stock has underperformed key benchmarks and its sector in recent periods.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>5c0313ee9e9680a3e73894e7776037c7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tamilnad-mercantile-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3779384</link><description>On 02-Jan, Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd’s stock price rose by 1.48% to ₹525.60, reflecting a combination of robust financial metrics and positive market sentiment that has supported the stock’s upward trajectory in recent sessions.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e4c8da52b504dbab98cf7c8bfe96a34a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rhetan TMT Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rhetan-tmt-ltd-fallingrising-3779383</link><description>As of 02-Jan, Rhetan TMT Ltd’s stock price has risen by 3.86% to ₹25.59, hitting a new 52-week high of ₹25.89. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong recent price momentum and sectoral gains, despite underlying fundamental challenges.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d3409ae3c11f83d9f3aed75e6dc0353d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is CWD Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cwd-ltd-fallingrising-3779382</link><description>On 02-Jan, CWD Ltd's stock price rose sharply by 5.33% to close at ₹415.00, continuing a robust upward trend that has seen the share gain nearly 13.3% over the past week, significantly outperforming the Sensex and its sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>65962d8216bf86f63621c75326c4b253</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sansera Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sansera-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3779381</link><description>On 02-Jan, Sansera Engineering Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, closing at ₹1,880.00, up by ₹114.20 or 6.47%. This surge reflects a combination of robust financial results, strong investor confidence, and sustained outperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e10d0356b175b9fa7fba7e373cde2b52</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>