<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Mamata Machinery Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mamata-machinery-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815020</link><description>Mamata Machinery Ltd's latest results show a significant sequential profit improvement, but year-on-year sales and profit declines raise concerns about demand sustainability and margin pressures. Investors should remain cautious and monitor future performance closely.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4d079fe3d0af27e2aa0e84a27411b47b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are R R Kabel Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-r-r-kabel-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815019</link><description>R R Kabel Ltd's latest results are strong, with net sales growing 42.29% year-on-year and net profit increasing 72.45%. The company shows solid operational efficiency and improved margins, indicating a robust financial position.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>da7f2712cf9848bfa0b4f6cc6fec42d7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ratnaveer-precision-engineering-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815018</link><description>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth, with net sales up 24.30% year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure as margins have contracted. While the company has solid liquidity and improved return on equity, challenges in maintaining profit margins and managing working capital require careful attention.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>219e5d9087d2b45c44f97600dcb3eefb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are IKIO Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ikio-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815017</link><description>IKIO Technologies Ltd's latest results show mixed performance: a net profit of ₹9.19 crore reflects a 16.62% year-on-year growth but an 8.37% decline from the previous quarter, while revenue increased by 19.81% year-on-year but fell 11.34% quarter-on-quarter, indicating potential volatility and operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4e3109cb22279ac4bace7dc5f8b82f96</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Delhivery Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-delhivery-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815016</link><description>Delhivery Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a significant turnaround with net sales growing 17.94% year-on-year and a net profit of ₹39.61 crores, recovering from a loss in the previous quarter. However, concerns about the sustainability of profitability and low return metrics indicate ongoing challenges for the company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c2530abe622046f90adc4256c9a2e16c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dj-mediaprint-logistics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815015</link><description>DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong year-on-year revenue growth of 35.16%, but a sequential decline in profit and revenue raises concerns about operational challenges and margin pressures, indicating a mixed performance overall.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0bb88f6f4f13eeb00b538527eb2673b2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ellenbarrie-industrial-gases-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815014</link><description>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show mixed performance, with a net profit decline of 28.93% sequentially but a 35.88% year-on-year increase. Concerns arise from margin compression, reliance on other income, and rising costs, indicating operational challenges despite positive annual growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>13f6f4e86690662cdd4715fdbae00efd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indo-rama-synthetics-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815013</link><description>Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, with net sales declining 3.16% sequentially and net profit dropping 64.24% due to rising interest costs and reduced non-operating income, raising questions about the company's financial stability and operational efficiency. Despite a year-on-year revenue increase, the overall outlook is negative, with the stock trading near its 52-week low.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d1895e4313ef3b36805e5579a7d723ab</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Unick Fix-A-Form And Printers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-unick-fix-a-form-and-printers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815012</link><description>Unick Fix-A-Form And Printers Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹0.56 crores and a 16.10% decline in revenue from the previous quarter, indicating significant operational challenges and pressure on profitability. The company needs to address these issues to stabilize operations and restore profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5e09a8bccc2bd5a5cc57ff7120454add</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Twamev Construction &amp; Infrastructure Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-twamev-construction-infrastructure-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815011</link><description>Twamev Construction &amp; Infrastructure Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 38.22% year-on-year, but a decline in net profit and significant margin pressures raise concerns about operational efficiency and sustainability. Overall, while there are signs of improvement year-to-date, the recent quarter highlights critical challenges that need to be addressed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6098b9b2c74a0d82e878813f14989302</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Steel City Securities Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-steel-city-securities-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815010</link><description>Steel City Securities Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 6.14% decline in net sales and a 23.30% drop in net profit year-on-year, indicating ongoing operational challenges and pressure on profitability. Investors should be cautious and monitor future results for potential improvements.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>20fe3a9bd05f255d26c568be47893082</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nath Bio-Genes (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nath-bio-genes-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815009</link><description>Nath Bio-Genes (India) Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 78.90% to ₹65.96 crores, but net profit fell 39.62% to ₹1.60 crores, indicating significant profitability issues and operational challenges. The company's declining margins and rising interest costs raise concerns about its financial health and sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a5b7df5792db67a0fa1f8ba5ba4a3578</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sumuka-agro-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815008</link><description>Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth, with net sales up 40.56% year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure, as operating margins have contracted significantly. While net profit has increased year-on-year, it has declined sequentially, indicating challenges in sustaining growth amidst rising costs.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cdf2151b9ee467b27f2f94c4fbce54a5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are High Energy Batteries (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-high-energy-batteries-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815007</link><description>High Energy Batteries (India) Ltd's latest results show a 30.24% increase in net sales but a negative operating margin of -4.23%, indicating operational challenges despite a 157.69% rise in net profit due to increased other income. Overall, the company faces significant issues that could affect its long-term sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>59e1a0c5203e3ab40f26c58ade6c773b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are GAIL (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gail-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815006</link><description>GAIL (India) Ltd's latest results are concerning, with a 56.97% year-on-year decline in net profit and a decrease in net sales, indicating ongoing operational challenges and declining profitability. Investors should monitor future quarters for potential recovery signs.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2048c53e6dedac7f91ebfaffc0f2c7cd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Zen Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-zen-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815005</link><description>Zen Technologies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong year-on-year growth in sales and profit, but sequential declines in net profit and profit margins, along with rising costs, indicate operational challenges that need monitoring. Overall, the performance is mixed, reflecting both positive growth and areas of concern.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2749baf313c7ce49c788ca0256adf917</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Incap Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-incap-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815004</link><description>Incap Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a significant decline in net sales and profit, alongside ongoing operational challenges and low profitability metrics. The company faces critical hurdles that need to be addressed for future stability and growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cc88787ab8cb62dfcf3997848f90a14e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ind-swift-laboratories-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815003</link><description>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd's latest results show impressive revenue growth of 1,176.25% and a net profit increase of 1,848.78%, but operational challenges persist with low operating margins and reliance on non-operating income, raising concerns about the sustainability of its earnings. Overall, while recovery is evident, significant operational issues remain.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>41959f5f96b5f3e7f45498ce9bf2f0eb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vishnu Chemicals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vishnu-chemicals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815002</link><description>Vishnu Chemicals Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 10.80% year-on-year, but profitability has declined, with net profit down 1.86% due to rising costs and margin compression. Overall, while sales performance is robust, the company faces significant challenges in maintaining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>761015928841f83a676fd989b8ceab36</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Finolex Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-finolex-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3815001</link><description>Finolex Industries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit increase of 23.46% year-on-year but a 6.05% decline quarter-on-quarter, alongside a significant revenue drop of 10.35% year-on-year. While operating margins improved, concerns about ongoing revenue challenges and reliance on non-operating income remain.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2bb3ce105f227f4471a51e634fb4d391</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>