<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marine Electricals (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/marine-electricals-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3816810</link><description>Marine Electricals (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term prospects.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c65b103e1d8d56387b8984c49ed6199a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frontier Springs Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/frontier-springs-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3816811</link><description>Frontier Springs Ltd, a notable player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>2c4cdf2bc1fed6a94383a30b6b62b7c6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cemindia Projects Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cemindia-projects-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3816807</link><description>Cemindia Projects Ltd, a prominent player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its near to medium-term price trajectory.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>ecff0d2f47f85ffc60f8f1d66b0f7581</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBCC (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nbcc-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3816802</link><description>NBCC (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>5ed2b8fd62ddfddfb3ba32cb1a7bed97</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amba Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amba-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3816809</link><description>Amba Enterprises Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>900489880fbd062eae112458e933eebd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KRBL Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krbl-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3816801</link><description>KRBL Ltd., a key player in the Other Agricultural Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term outlook.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>ce06f8cac5fe431f4690751fc22a36da</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gagan Gases Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gagan-gases-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3816808</link><description>Gagan Gases Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Other Chemical products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>aff20e4aa7c32d71c639bdb02a8c8b02</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P B A Infrastructure Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/p-b-a-infrastructure-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3816804</link><description>P B A Infrastructure Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its medium to long-term prospects amid already challenging fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>cfaae4825b881f12cc6de7685b001d44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajmera-realty-infra-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3816805</link><description>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>7abdc1d12e83abb843834659233f84cc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanghvi Movers Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanghvi-movers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3816806</link><description>Sanghvi Movers Ltd, a key player in the automobile sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>ba248aa7ce0c695f52e4995d17844673</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dhampur-bio-organics-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3816803</link><description>Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd has recently witnessed a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed above the 200-day moving average, forming a classic Golden Cross pattern. This event is widely regarded by market analysts as a bullish signal, indicating a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock within the sugar sector.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>a49b2d47d914dfcfe26f6253f478e832</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3816799</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 49.0% of the 983 stocks declaring results reporting positive outcomes. This marks a notable improvement from the preceding quarters, reflecting a gradual recovery in corporate profitability amid varied sectoral performances and market capitalisation segments.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>b9212f854c8313713d7aece2cec3f3c4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sundaram Finance Q3 FY26: Robust Growth Momentum Continues with 19% Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sundaram-finance-q3-fy26-robust-growth-momentum-continues-with-19-profit-surge-3816800</link><description>Sundaram Finance Ltd., a prominent non-banking financial company within the TVS Group, delivered a strong performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit surging 18.86% year-on-year to ₹541.36 crores. The Chennai-based NBFC, commanding a market capitalisation of ₹55,943 crores, saw its stock rally 7.35% on February 02, 2026, closing at ₹5,348.50 as investors responded positively to the quarter's robust operational metrics and sustained growth trajectory.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>5f127e5d83739293f7d03825d6995ba9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyundai Motor India Q3 FY26: Margin Pressure Weighs Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/hyundai-motor-india-q3-fy26-margin-pressure-weighs-despite-revenue-growth-3816782</link><description>Hyundai Motor India Ltd., the country's second-largest passenger vehicle manufacturer, reported a mixed performance for Q3 FY26, with net profit declining 21.49% quarter-on-quarter to ₹1,234.40 crores despite revenue growth of 2.94% to ₹17,973.49 crores. The stock traded at ₹2,196.50 on February 02, 2026, representing a market capitalisation of ₹1,74,058 crores, as investors digested margin compression concerns that overshadowed the company's solid year-on-year revenue expansion of 7.96%.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cf0fc87ecbebbb6bba0b019284c169cd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Campus Activewear Q3 FY26: Strong Quarter Masks Deeper Structural Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/campus-activewear-q3-fy26-strong-quarter-masks-deeper-structural-concerns-3816781</link><description>Campus Activewear Ltd., the domestic footwear manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹7,915.00 crores, delivered its strongest quarterly performance on record in Q3 FY26, with net profit surging to ₹63.68 crores. However, the impressive headline numbers conceal troubling structural issues that continue to plague the small-cap company, raising serious questions about its long-term growth trajectory and premium valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3c3256da202495fbf904c6aaa11d7c22</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Touch Technologies Q3 FY26: Stellar Profit Surge Masks Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/silver-touch-technologies-q3-fy26-stellar-profit-surge-masks-valuation-concerns-3816780</link><description>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd., an Ahmedabad-based IT services and consulting company, reported a remarkable 109.32% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to ₹11.01 crores for Q3 FY26, significantly outpacing its 29.52% revenue growth to ₹96.34 crores. The micro-cap company, valued at ₹1,804 crores, delivered its strongest quarterly performance to date, with operating margins expanding to 19.94% from 13.29% a year ago. However, the stock retreated 1.94% on February 02, 2026, to close at ₹1,426.60, as investors grappled with stretched valuations at 71x trailing twelve-month earnings.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7b20c62d321e53633aa04b33fa88cd89</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jet Freight Logistics Q2 FY26: Profit Slumps 51% Despite Revenue Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/jet-freight-logistics-q2-fy26-profit-slumps-51-despite-revenue-resilience-3816779</link><description>Jet Freight Logistics Ltd., a Mumbai-based freight forwarding and logistics solutions provider, reported a sharp 51.12% sequential decline in net profit for Q2 FY26, falling to ₹0.87 crores from ₹1.78 crores in Q1 FY26. Despite maintaining year-on-year profitability growth of 47.46%, the quarter exposed underlying margin pressures that weighed heavily on bottom-line performance. The stock, trading at ₹17.55 with a modest market capitalisation of ₹78 crores, has delivered a robust 22.56% return over the past year, significantly outperforming its transport services sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9dc63d1ee9ab1d8ce85d521b41dfcc8f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WPIL Ltd Q3 FY26: Strong Quarter Masked by Technical Weakness and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/wpil-ltd-q3-fy26-strong-quarter-masked-by-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-3816778</link><description>WPIL Ltd., formerly known as Worthington Pump India Ltd., delivered a robust third quarter for FY26, with consolidated net profit surging 73.36% year-on-year to ₹54.33 crores, despite the stock languishing in a bearish technical trend. The Kolkata-based industrial manufacturing company, with a market capitalisation of ₹3,580 crores, posted net sales of ₹538.72 crores in Q3 FY26, marking a strong 41.17% YoY growth, though investors remain cautious given the stock's 38.76% decline over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>488b722577d4ee8c4b427f379d62e642</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Q3 FY26: Margin Pressures Amid Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/indian-toners-developers-q3-fy26-margin-pressures-amid-revenue-growth-3816777</link><description>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Ltd., India's largest manufacturer and exporter of compatible toners for laser printers and digital machines, has delivered mixed results for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), with the stock trading at ₹243.45 as of February 02, 2026, reflecting a market capitalisation of ₹248.00 crores. The company reported net sales of ₹42.11 crores for the quarter, marking the highest quarterly revenue on record, yet profitability metrics have raised concerns amongst investors as margins contracted sequentially despite robust top-line growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b07d984bf4e0e42ffe260e3fbfee2cc4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Q3 FY26: Strong Revenue Surge Masks Underlying Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mahindra-lifespace-q3-fy26-strong-revenue-surge-masks-underlying-profitability-concerns-3816776</link><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers Ltd., the real estate development arm of the Mahindra Group, reported a dramatic revenue surge in Q3 FY26, with net sales skyrocketing to ₹459.16 crores—a staggering 2,514.81% quarter-on-quarter increase and 174.49% year-on-year growth. However, the impressive top-line expansion failed to translate into sustainable bottom-line improvement, with consolidated net profit reaching ₹108.88 crores, reflecting volatile profitability patterns that continue to plague the small-cap realty developer. The stock responded positively to the results, surging 4.69% on February 02, 2026, to close at ₹383.15, though it remains 10.55% below its 52-week high of ₹428.35.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a22236471b4749986123f45f88d04055</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>