<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sturdy Industries Falls 17.24% Amidst 52-Week Low and Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sturdy-industries-falls-1724-amidst-52-week-low-and-market-pressure-3780286</link><description>Sturdy Industries endured a challenging week, with its stock price declining sharply by 17.24% from Rs.0.29 to Rs.0.24, significantly underperforming the Sensex, which rose 1.35% over the same period. The week was marked by a fresh 52-week low, a sharp gap down at the open, and sustained bearish momentum amid weak fundamentals and subdued trading activity.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>7fe114ccdd7c8f846e796faf59c87f64</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajesh Exports Drops 15.01%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rajesh-exports-drops-1501-6-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3780285</link><description>Rajesh Exports Ltd. endured a challenging week from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026, with its stock price plunging 15.01% from ₹212.20 to ₹180.35. This sharp decline contrasted starkly with the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period, underscoring company-specific pressures amid a broadly resilient market. The week was marked by consecutive lower circuit hits, heavy selling pressure, and a downgrade to a Sell rating, reflecting a shift in technical momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>8d42d65bc9a83c3060a07ecbc4367302</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piccadily Agro Industries Gains 9.66%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piccadily-agro-industries-gains-966-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3780283</link><description>Piccadily Agro Industries Ltd delivered a volatile yet ultimately positive week, closing at Rs.615.00 on 2 January 2026, marking a 9.66% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.560.80. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period, reflecting a week of sharp intraday swings, technical shifts, and a significant rating downgrade that shaped investor sentiment and trading activity.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>3e9e58cd4d83c921f7e91d43701f42c1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalam Drugs Surges 27.52% in Five Days: 6 Key Factors Behind the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalam-drugs-surges-2752-in-five-days-6-key-factors-behind-the-rally-3780284</link><description>Mangalam Drugs and Organics Ltd delivered a remarkable 27.52% gain over the week ending 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.35% rise. The stock’s rally was marked by consecutive upper circuit hits from 29 December through 2 January, reflecting intense buying interest despite a backdrop of cautious fundamental ratings and subdued delivery volumes.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>59e018db41539cbbe682b1f85cb1e0f8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kairosoft AI Solutions Gains 9.72%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kairosoft-ai-solutions-gains-972-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3780281</link><description>Kairosoft AI Solutions Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 9.72% from Rs.43.02 to Rs.47.20 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.35% gain over the same period. The week was marked by notable intraday volatility, including a sharp rebound after a steep decline, two gap-up openings signalling positive market sentiment, and persistent technical challenges amid a 'Strong Sell' rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>065ec2dce4f6ebbadb31816c43f72881</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd Surges 23.52%: Mixed Technical Signals Amid Strong Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhuveer-com-18-network-ltd-surges-2352-mixed-technical-signals-amid-strong-momentum-3780282</link><description>Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd surged 23.52% over the week ending 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% gain. The stock’s rally was marked by a strong price momentum shift, a new 52-week high, and mixed technical signals that reflect both optimism and caution among investors. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped the week for this media and entertainment sector stock.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>8ae1f3e8619a6811e4444ca4ef5c0b71</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pacific Industries Ltd Falls 5.53% Amidst Persistent Downtrend and Valuation Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pacific-industries-ltd-falls-553-amidst-persistent-downtrend-and-valuation-shift-3780280</link><description>Pacific Industries Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week, declining 5.53% from Rs.160.90 to Rs.152.00, sharply underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.35% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid sustained bearish momentum and deteriorating financial metrics, while valuation shifts signalled changing market sentiment. Despite some late-week gains, the overall trend remained negative, reflecting persistent operational and liquidity concerns.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>08ff9f837412a07ad6ab0629bb1373c3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Embassy Developments Ltd Falls 9.51% Amidst Persistent Downtrend and Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/embassy-developments-ltd-falls-951-amidst-persistent-downtrend-and-heavy-selling-pressure-3780278</link><description>Embassy Developments Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 2 January 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 9.51% from Rs.62.57 to Rs.56.62, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows and faced intense selling pressure, culminating in a lower circuit lock on the final trading day despite a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>1ae7c5aef212bb9833b2ed2f1f4f456c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Norben Tea &amp; Exports Ltd Gains 20.41%: 10 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/norben-tea-exports-ltd-gains-2041-10-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3780279</link><description>Norben Tea &amp; Exports Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 20.41%, significantly outperforming the Sensex's modest 1.35% rise from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026. The stock surged from Rs.82.64 to Rs.99, hitting multiple new 52-week and all-time highs amid strong buying momentum and technical strength, despite maintaining a cautious Mojo Grade of 'Sell'.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>2c88f71d973855d57b5526075822bf05</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CCL Products Declines 2.82% Amid Mixed Technical Signals and Attractive Valuation Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ccl-products-declines-282-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-attractive-valuation-shift-3780277</link><description>CCL Products (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 2 January 2026, with its share price falling 2.82% from Rs.941.80 to Rs.915.25, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. The week was marked by a shift in technical momentum to a mildly bullish stance and a notable upgrade in valuation attractiveness despite recent price weakness, reflecting a complex interplay of market dynamics and fundamental reassessment.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>2aff6611a1329d48151e562c513f398d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BGR Energy Systems Ltd Gains 10.35%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bgr-energy-systems-ltd-gains-1035-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3780276</link><description>BGR Energy Systems Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 10.35% from ₹326.20 to ₹359.95 between 29 Dec 2025 and 2 Jan 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by two consecutive upper circuit hits on 30 and 31 Dec, followed by a sharp correction with a lower circuit hit on 1 Jan 2026. Despite the strong price momentum, the company retains a Strong Sell rating, reflecting ongoing fundamental concerns amid volatile trading.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>00c1cabb21ad37e88adae29b018278c9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NACL Industries Ltd’s Volatile Week: 0.21% Gain Amid Circuit Hits and Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nacl-industries-ltds-volatile-week-021-gain-amid-circuit-hits-and-mixed-signals-3780274</link><description>NACL Industries Ltd’s stock exhibited a volatile week from 29 Dec 2025 to 2 Jan 2026, closing marginally higher by 0.21% at Rs.167.95 despite sharp intraday swings. The stock underperformed the Sensex, which gained 1.35% over the same period, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid heavy selling pressure early in the week and a strong rebound at the start of the new year.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>e5fa74108789f9015bd2b843f5d51df1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanfac Industries Gains 4.67%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanfac-industries-gains-467-2-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780273</link><description>Tanfac Industries Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 4.67%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026. The stock rebounded strongly after early losses, driven by a sharp intraday surge on 31 December and a bullish momentum shift in early January, reflecting renewed investor confidence amid mixed technical signals.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>dc10cf09a4e5831f56de4e65b9d2a1e9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Visa Steel Ltd Gains 9.92%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/visa-steel-ltd-gains-992-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3780275</link><description>Visa Steel Ltd delivered a volatile yet strong performance this week, rising 9.92% from Rs.48.90 to Rs.53.75, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period. The stock experienced sharp upward moves on 30 and 31 December, hitting upper circuit limits on consecutive days, before a sharp reversal on 1 January saw it hit the lower circuit. This rollercoaster week was marked by intense buying and selling pressures, regulatory trading halts, and mixed technical signals, reflecting both renewed investor interest and underlying fundamental concerns.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>5f07773aa9bba640b4b44fe03907d3c3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Count Industries Gains 5.63%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-count-industries-gains-563-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780271</link><description>Indo Count Industries Ltd closed the week with a 5.63% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026. The stock experienced significant volatility, including a sharp 14.61% surge on 30 December, reflecting a complex interplay of technical shifts, rating upgrades, and market dynamics within the garments and apparels sector.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>15f8c9ef69d4a3c0fe66f6d7e97666a7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everest Organics Surges 15.44%: 5 Key Factors Behind This Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/everest-organics-surges-1544-5-key-factors-behind-this-weeks-rally-3780272</link><description>Everest Organics Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 15.44% from Rs.458.25 to Rs.529.00 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s modest 1.35% gain over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, reflecting strong momentum amid a mixed broader market environment. Key events including record intraday highs, technical strength, and upgraded ratings contributed to this notable rally.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>b75673d9f6188e2034943b8b73a9ec5f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Petroleum Gains 4.14%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-petroleum-gains-414-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780270</link><description>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd (BPCL) delivered a solid weekly gain of 4.14%, closing at Rs.381.30 on 2 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong resilience and momentum, hitting new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, supported by robust financial results, increased market participation, and favourable sector dynamics.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>2eade96506d5b2b1201e0f41be1bb125</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prakash Industries Gains 7.85%: Technical Shift and Mixed Fundamentals Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prakash-industries-gains-785-technical-shift-and-mixed-fundamentals-shape-week-3780269</link><description>Prakash Industries Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.85% from Rs.136.90 to Rs.147.65 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a notable upgrade in the company’s investment rating from 'Strong Sell' to 'Sell' driven by improved technical indicators, despite ongoing fundamental challenges including subdued profitability and declining quarterly earnings. Mixed technical signals and sector headwinds shaped investor sentiment as the stock showed signs of stabilisation amid cautious optimism.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>03fe30a5e25242d8b3557da140d63fc0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B.L.Kashyap &amp; Sons Gains 4.97%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blkashyap-sons-gains-497-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3780268</link><description>B.L.Kashyap &amp; Sons Ltd recorded a mixed week ending 2 January 2026, closing at Rs.52.64, up 4.97% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.50.15. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period, driven by a sharp rebound on 29 December followed by a technical downturn early in the new year. The stock’s volatility reflected shifting market sentiment amid broader sector challenges and technical signals.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>e3e7147c61be7e241bb54ef9b145cbab</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Declines 2.65% Despite 52-Week High; Sensex Gains 1.35%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brahmaputra-infrastructure-declines-265-despite-52-week-high-sensex-gains-135-3780266</link><description>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 2 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 2.65% from Rs.132.20 to Rs.128.70, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. Despite hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.135.5 on 29 December 2025, the stock faced selling pressure in subsequent sessions, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid broader market gains.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>083678ce05405a8ce9fc35346c21c202</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>