<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.46.95</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/magnus-steel-infra-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs4695-3798330</link><description>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd has surged to a new all-time high of Rs.46.95, reflecting a sustained period of robust gains and outperformance within the Other Electrical Equipment sector. This milestone caps a remarkable rally that has seen the stock deliver exceptional returns across multiple time frames, underscoring its strong market momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c4459451cc6e35bd7d6f3c244308962f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saptak Chem &amp; Business Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.40.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saptak-chem-business-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs408-3798332</link><description>Saptak Chem &amp; Business Ltd has reached a new milestone by hitting an all-time high of Rs.40.8, reflecting a sustained period of robust performance and significant gains across multiple time frames. This achievement underscores the company’s strong momentum within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6a0913c575566f41e5104ad2a40ba5e9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.257.95, Marking a Milestone in Trading &amp; Distributors Sector</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs25795-marking-a-milestone-in-trading-distributors-sector-3798325</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd has reached a new all-time high of Rs.257.95, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and underscoring the company’s robust performance within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector. This milestone highlights sustained growth and significant market outperformance over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a2be88bbdd03e8901172aa3c0e623b6e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicswallah Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 21 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/physicswallah-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-21-jan-2026-3798324</link><description>Physicswallah Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 114.95, reflecting a 3.04% drop from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, continuing a downward trend amid prevailing market pressures and subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>32b4f61d138022807c31e67e95d3b816</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trade-Wings Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.766.9, Marking a Remarkable Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trade-wings-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs7669-marking-a-remarkable-rally-3798327</link><description>Trade-Wings Ltd has reached an unprecedented peak, hitting an all-time high of Rs.766.9 on 21 Jan 2026. This landmark achievement reflects a remarkable rally, with the stock outperforming its sector and broader market indices over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6b1f4f01741f0eeae460dd91e8d1ddee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LTI Mindtree Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 21 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lti-mindtree-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-21-jan-2026-3798331</link><description>LTI Mindtree Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 21 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 5,781.1, reflecting a 3.29% drop as the stock faced significant price pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1ede10517d004a46577715c0880b6a7c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murae Organisor Ltd Hits Day Low Amid Price Pressure on 21 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/murae-organisor-ltd-hits-day-low-amid-price-pressure-on-21-jan-2026-3798329</link><description>Murae Organisor Ltd witnessed a significant decline today, hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.0.22 as it underperformed its sector and the broader market amid persistent selling pressure and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9cb1a135d0b8b58563126e1330ab3e30</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.227.75, Marking Remarkable Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaghani-techno-build-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs22775-marking-remarkable-market-performance-3798326</link><description>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd, a prominent player in the FMCG sector, achieved a significant milestone today by reaching its all-time high stock price of Rs.227.75. This landmark reflects the company’s sustained strong performance and robust market presence, underscored by impressive returns across multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6eaf1e952759be85057555ada2085641</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd Hits Record High of Rs.161.55, Marking a Historic Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yuranus-infrastructure-ltd-hits-record-high-of-rs16155-marking-a-historic-milestone-3798328</link><description>Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd, a key player in the construction sector, has reached a new all-time high of Rs.161.55, reflecting a significant achievement in its market journey. This milestone underscores the company’s sustained upward momentum and robust performance across multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>28e45caba4d78416b34cf4d69ec19976</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credo Brands Marketing Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/credo-brands-marketing-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3798173</link><description>Shares of Credo Brands Marketing Ltd have fallen to an all-time low, closing just 0.11% above their 52-week low of ₹87.6, marking a significant downturn in the garment and apparel sector. The stock has experienced a sustained decline over recent months, underperforming both its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>731db6ccd33236607985e51978403d94</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3798171</link><description>Shares of TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd have declined to a new all-time low of Rs.97.2, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s extended period of underperformance. The transport services company’s stock has been on a steady downward trajectory, reflecting a combination of subdued financial metrics and market pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>58dc0abf837202017e2d0fcb32eb10da</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Vision Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aditya-vision-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3798134</link><description>Aditya Vision Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 21 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>da77b2adee7b19fe439aceaf4204e3d8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avalon Technologies Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/avalon-technologies-ltd-is-rated-buy-3798130</link><description>Avalon Technologies Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 21 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>39e89c499e5800fcf9b17799aa9597ea</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grauer &amp; Weil (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/grauer-weil-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3798132</link><description>Grauer &amp; Weil (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 21 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>beb3f49a6c48600420e73a81a6ea65ca</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/akums-drugs-pharmaceuticals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3798128</link><description>Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 17 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the company’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 21 January 2026, providing investors with the latest view of the stock’s position.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>55e2873b38368ab0287699cfe2803961</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>