<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Arfin India Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Remarkable Growth Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arfin-india-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-remarkable-growth-milestone-3787314</link><description>Arfin India Ltd, a key player in the Non - Ferrous Metals sector, has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high stock price, reflecting a sustained period of robust performance and market confidence.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9974bb856d8258c7d95b4623167b9a9f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.127.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apeejay-surrendra-park-hotels-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs12705-3787312</link><description>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.127.05, marking a significant decline amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific factors. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting ongoing pressures within the Hotels &amp; Resorts industry.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>fcce635f52c2ce1c05c77076b65d16fa</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vinny Overseas Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vinny-overseas-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3787311</link><description>Vinny Overseas Ltd, a company operating in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.1.11 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing challenges reflected in its financial and market performance.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>878c2dd83e1be935cc77ceca72a14e5e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palash Securities Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.101.35 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/palash-securities-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs10135-amid-continued-downtrend-3787310</link><description>Palash Securities Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs 101.35 on 9 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing market pressures and company-specific headwinds.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>8bf2074ea48c0f10b5e1a35571de1531</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thinkink Picturez Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thinkink-picturez-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3787309</link><description>Shares of Thinkink Picturez Ltd have declined to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector. The stock’s recent price action underscores the severity of its challenges, with key financial metrics and market indicators signalling continued pressure on the company’s valuation.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>185f6667390ec6efe4daba50805d2fdb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaizen Agro Infrabuild Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaizen-agro-infrabuild-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787306</link><description>Kaizen Agro Infrabuild Ltd’s stock declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.11.1 on 9 Jan 2026, marking a significant downturn amid broader market volatility and sector underperformance.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>92fcb97a895406533796621c6eb8e48b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liberty Shoes Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/liberty-shoes-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3787300</link><description>Liberty Shoes Ltd’s stock price declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.259.75 on 9 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting a series of financial setbacks and valuation pressures over the past year.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>7dabb6ef6131e56c9416f5c986e82924</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 9 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lodha-developers-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-9-jan-2026-3787304</link><description>Lodha Developers Ltd witnessed a notable decline on 9 Jan 2026, touching an intraday low of ₹1,054.25, reflecting a 3.17% drop as the stock faced sustained selling pressure amid broader market weakness and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>1473915c057542857b5a74b3d5680be2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AD Manum Finance Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.54.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ad-manum-finance-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs545-3787302</link><description>AD Manum Finance Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.54.5 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its valuation and performance metrics.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>5633efb82b583a4bcdc2d38dc66b8589</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-energy-solutions-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3787305</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 09 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 960, reflecting a 3.41% drop as the stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid prevailing negative sentiment.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>9b3e18e00cd5dfe5a213d1354560eb11</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G K Consultants Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.10.7</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-k-consultants-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs107-3787301</link><description>G K Consultants Ltd, a player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.10.7 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>873e462fd5e3ce60c826f013a958389d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Compucom Software Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.14.9</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/compucom-software-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs149-3787307</link><description>Compucom Software Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.14.9 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting ongoing pressures on its valuation and performance metrics.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>82c6f2814941a080f0f0ccc3f32c0b5e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DE Nora India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 650 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/de-nora-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-650-amid-continued-downtrend-3787303</link><description>Shares of DE Nora India Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs 650, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects a sustained period of price weakness amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral pressures.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>5cc19307bc58ac085a295bf92ac5d111</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solid Stone Company Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.26 Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solid-stone-company-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs26-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3787308</link><description>Solid Stone Company Ltd has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.26, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a broader market downturn and persistent underperformance relative to benchmarks and peers.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>337332e31aed41e38da61b58323bd1ff</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Green Energy Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-green-energy-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3787291</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 955.4 as the stock faced sustained selling pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>25719233bdac7f57364f025d2964a2b5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Force Motors Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 9 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/force-motors-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-9-jan-2026-3787293</link><description>Force Motors Ltd experienced significant intraday weakness on 09 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 18,625, reflecting a sharp decline of 7.25% amid broader market pressures and sector underperformance.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>32e36d9fe89a43a0c2fc1e82fd0c8fd0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DLF Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amidst Price Pressure on 9 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dlf-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amidst-price-pressure-on-9-jan-2026-3787292</link><description>DLF Ltd. experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 670.4, reflecting sustained price pressure amid broader sector weakness and a subdued market environment.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>4e00f9460c19432da6222353c8d4b7d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HP Adhesives Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hp-adhesives-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3787288</link><description>HP Adhesives Ltd, a player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.40.02 on 9 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and investor sentiment.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>ba355c9627a05b36a1a8ee04d56a2e61</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Online Services Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.4.86 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-online-services-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs486-amidst-continued-downtrend-3787280</link><description>City Online Services Ltd, a player in the Telecom - Services sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.4.86 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial health and market positioning.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>780878489996cb9e856134e38ac450b5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-energy-exchange-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3787286</link><description>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd experienced a notable decline today, hitting an intraday low of Rs 138.75, reflecting a sharp price correction amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance. The stock closed with a significant loss of 7.23%, underperforming its capital markets sector and the broader Sensex index.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>36783921810db52aa90d4688b248a245</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>