<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Metropolis Healthcare Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-metropolis-healthcare-ltd-fallingrising-3786123</link><description>On 08-Jan, Metropolis Healthcare Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 3.65%, closing at ₹1,916.00, reflecting a continuation of recent downward momentum despite the company’s strong fundamentals and positive financial results.
Time: 1 seconds ago</description><guid>d172015bec2b36f19ec09a02c7580ba6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Prakash Pipes Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-prakash-pipes-ltd-fallingrising-3786122</link><description>As of 08-Jan, Prakash Pipes Ltd. witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹225.50, down ₹9.60 or 4.08% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by a combination of disappointing financial results and subdued investor interest.
Time: 19 seconds ago</description><guid>17a5b156e8e4bba09fd36f607b411e58</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-affordable-robotic-automation-ltd-fallingrising-3786121</link><description>On 08-Jan, Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹199.10, down ₹5.55 or 2.71% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 24 seconds ago</description><guid>121952a628501409e35b674e1142759c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mihika Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mihika-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3786120</link><description>On 08-Jan, Mihika Industries Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, closing at ₹13.38, down ₹1.32 or 8.98% from the previous close. This drop marks a continuation of a prolonged downtrend, with the stock hitting a new 52-week and all-time low during the trading session.
Time: 30 seconds ago</description><guid>fbe10f9cec6430107b49f788fa700895</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Halder Venture Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-halder-venture-ltd-fallingrising-3786119</link><description>On 08-Jan, Halder Venture Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.98% to close at ₹245.05. This drop comes amid a backdrop of disappointing quarterly results, rising debt levels, and weakening operational performance, which have collectively weighed on investor sentiment despite the stock's impressive long-term returns.
Time: 39 seconds ago</description><guid>d1c057e94144201e4c3a16289c54f161</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-fallingrising-3786118</link><description>As of 08-Jan, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd’s stock price has inched up by 0.73% to ₹48.50, despite a backdrop of prolonged underperformance and deteriorating fundamentals. This modest rise contrasts with the company’s sustained struggles over recent years, reflecting a complex interplay of valuation appeal and promoter confidence amid weak operational metrics.
Time: 47 seconds ago</description><guid>3460bb686d5f2c83500fa2550492d90c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solex Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solex-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3786117</link><description>On 08-Jan, Solex Energy Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.56% to close at ₹1,136.20. This downturn reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and diminished investor participation.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>80cd96395a8cca941362d7e7a0f84125</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aspira Pathlab &amp; Diagnostics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aspira-pathlab-diagnostics-ltd-fallingrising-3786116</link><description>On 08-Jan, Aspira Pathlab &amp; Diagnostics Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.48% to close at ₹64.90. This upward movement follows two consecutive days of decline and reflects a combination of strong long-term fundamentals and intraday volatility that has captured investor attention.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>6f426b4e91a1acf700033941ed385eba</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Eiko Lifesciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-eiko-lifesciences-ltd-fallingrising-3786115</link><description>On 08-Jan, Eiko Lifesciences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.67% to close at ₹51.00. This drop comes despite the company’s recent positive earnings performance, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment, valuation concerns, and longer-term underperformance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>35178bf34c9a68d4b800f8b634b14613</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Zota Health Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-zota-health-care-ltd-fallingrising-3786114</link><description>On 08-Jan, Zota Health Care Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.16% to ₹1,463.00, reflecting investor concerns over deteriorating fundamentals despite the company’s impressive long-term returns.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>d88323355ed1e62c74576451e44e273b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omfurn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omfurn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3786113</link><description>On 08-Jan, Omfurn India Ltd's stock price surged by 5.75% to ₹73.55, reflecting a notable intraday recovery despite the stock's recent underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>67dde9755bfcc5921459dd33b94e08bc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-magadh-sugar-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3786112</link><description>As of 08-Jan, Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of disappointing recent financial results, subdued investor interest, and underwhelming long-term growth prospects.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>321480ac958f442cf4da1c081524742a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-educational-initiatives-ltd-fallingrising-3786111</link><description>On 08-Jan, Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd experienced a decline in its share price, falling by 1.11% to close at ₹177.70. This drop comes amid a broader short-term downtrend, contrasting with the company’s impressive long-term performance.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>6620599115fb1f680aaf5095b4fb9720</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Overseas (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-overseas-india-ltd-fallingrising-3786110</link><description>On 08-Jan, Shanti Overseas (India) Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹8.10, down 5.26% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a prolonged downtrend driven by weak financial performance, deteriorating investor confidence, and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>9df1a6ac5d4b2c56527e3728f001abf9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-icici-lombard-general-insurance-company-ltd-fallingrising-3786109</link><description>As of 08-Jan, ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.0% to close at ₹1,909.25. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum despite the company’s robust long-term fundamentals and positive quarterly results.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>2482edfa06c954a690ebaf78e83878ad</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Constronics Infra Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-constronics-infra-ltd-fallingrising-3786108</link><description>On 08-Jan, Constronics Infra Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 10.97% to close at ₹46.41, marking a continuation of a significant downtrend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and broader market indices over recent periods.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>86d0c106a492f3a8e68693e7b14cf9f8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Amit Securities Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-amit-securities-ltd-fallingrising-3786107</link><description>On 08-Jan, Amit Securities Ltd witnessed a sharp 10.0% rise in its share price, closing at ₹33.22. This notable intraday gain followed two consecutive days of decline, marking a significant trend reversal despite the broader Aluminium &amp; Aluminium Products sector falling by 4.07% on the same day.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>055ffb687c927337360171c21c4140ad</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Deep Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-deep-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3786106</link><description>On 08-Jan, Deep Industries Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, closing at ₹403.95, down ₹20.75 or 4.89%. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, driven by valuation pressures and subdued investor participation despite the company’s strong operational metrics.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>22a33c85feeb618956d924a7a8cf0a16</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rossari Biotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rossari-biotech-ltd-fallingrising-3786105</link><description>As of 08-Jan, Rossari Biotech Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, closing at ₹567.45, down 1.09% for the day and hitting a new 52-week low. This decline reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by a combination of disappointing financial results and sustained negative returns over multiple time horizons.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>89c14cfca66b379766cef4cb4523a069</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nureca Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nureca-ltd-fallingrising-3786104</link><description>On 08-Jan, Nureca Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.37% to close at ₹292.20, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance relative to key market benchmarks and subdued investor participation despite the company’s recent positive financial results and rising promoter confidence.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>f28b86bb197ff294d8d7cdb3524ea63e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>