<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs 3,350</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shriram-pistons-rings-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs-3350-3779130</link><description>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week high, reaching an intraday peak of Rs.3350 on 2 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone for the auto components company amid a broadly bullish market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3f69a10b3e4fc7ca8f3c2de8a20e0a1a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atal Realtech Ltd Hits New 52-Week High, Marking Significant Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/atal-realtech-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-marking-significant-rally-3779129</link><description>Atal Realtech Ltd has reached a new 52-week high, reflecting a robust rally in the realty sector. The stock’s latest peak underscores its strong performance over the past year, significantly outpacing broader market indices and demonstrating sustained momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1cc1c10998378c76cd4b3baea22686ac</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSB Bank Ltd Hits New 52-Week High, Marking Significant Market Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/csb-bank-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-marking-significant-market-milestone-3779127</link><description>CSB Bank Ltd has reached a new 52-week high, closing just 0.97% shy of its peak price of ₹490.20, underscoring a robust rally in the private sector banking space. This milestone reflects sustained momentum driven by strong market performance and favourable technical indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d929ea7288bdbdb7c8b73ad0dc2af001</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dynemic Products Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dynemic-products-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3779128</link><description>Dynemic Products Ltd, a player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recently touched a new 52-week low, closing near Rs 241.2, marking a significant decline in its stock price over the past year amid subdued financial performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>da484d51f37c0d552c5abd74c0a501f9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Surge to New Highs as Broad Market Advances on Strong Sectoral Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-surge-to-new-highs-as-broad-market-advances-on-strong-sectoral-gains-3779126</link><description>Indian equity benchmarks extended their upward momentum on 2 January 2026, with the Sensex gaining 573.41 points (0.67%) to close at 85,762.01 and the Nifty hitting a fresh 52-week high of 26,328.55, up 182 points (0.7%). Broad-based sectoral gains and robust market breadth underscored investor confidence, even as select pockets of weakness emerged in defensive segments.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>71de4c59a4d759e063b4798728d00138</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IDream Film Infrastructure Company Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.236.35</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/idream-film-infrastructure-company-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs23635-3779119</link><description>IDream Film Infrastructure Company has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.236.35, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting strong momentum within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d6b820ddbd7e2c4dd7e1b8ab6d8d253d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.618.25 Mark</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedanta-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs61825-mark-3779122</link><description>Vedanta Ltd., a leading player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, reached a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.618.25 on 2 Jan 2026, reflecting robust momentum and strong market performance. This milestone underscores the company’s sustained growth and resilience amid sectoral gains and broader market optimism.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7503931dcf7dbee6e5d70b6d0a32d0c1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Callista Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.120</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/callista-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs120-3779120</link><description>Callista Industries Ltd reached a significant milestone on 2 Jan 2026, hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.120. This achievement marks a continuation of the stock’s strong upward momentum, reflecting sustained gains over the past nine trading sessions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>989b83b724a17e95b114f28f4edfc57d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Future Market Networks Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.8.4 Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/future-market-networks-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs84-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3779121</link><description>Future Market Networks Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.8.4 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a broader market environment that remains buoyant. This fresh low underscores ongoing concerns regarding the company’s financial health and performance metrics over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>57f7fc819ea7ae5210d014f6eb981bdc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1594.45</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs159445-3779123</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.1594.45 today, marking a continuation of its strong upward momentum in the oil sector. This achievement reflects the stock’s robust performance over recent sessions and its sustained strength relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6c3c10478a627813b9e42b53c1a5cfb7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AIA Engineering Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.4095 Marking Strong Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aia-engineering-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs4095-marking-strong-momentum-3779118</link><description>AIA Engineering Ltd, a prominent player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.4095. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust momentum, supported by consistent gains and favourable market conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>60b61ec532be72a9eadc92c45a950f17</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suraj Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Weak Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suraj-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-weak-performance-3779124</link><description>Suraj Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.234.75 on 2 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline amid persistent downward momentum. The stock’s recent performance highlights ongoing pressures within the company’s financial and market metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c7a04419e80c2e660dc5dc5e6ab5b8de</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Offshore Services Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.55.17</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/global-offshore-services-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs5517-3779116</link><description>Global Offshore Services Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.55.17 on 2 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline amid a broader market environment where the Sensex continues to trade near its yearly highs. The stock’s recent performance contrasts sharply with the overall market trend, reflecting ongoing pressures within the company’s financial and operational metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>18f6746efad8ca9d0eca52f7500d327d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Bank of India Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1009.3</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/state-bank-of-india-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs10093-3779117</link><description>State Bank of India (SBI) reached a significant milestone on 2 Jan 2026, hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs. 1009.3. This achievement marks a continuation of the stock’s strong upward momentum, reflecting robust market performance and favourable trading conditions within the public sector banking space.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1c7c40e4fbfef64e90ffc3f43aee0d16</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KMC Speciality Hospitals (India) Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.86.3</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kmc-speciality-hospitals-india-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs863-3779125</link><description>KMC Speciality Hospitals (India) Ltd reached a significant milestone on 2 Jan 2026, hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.86.3. This achievement marks a notable surge in the stock’s momentum, reflecting strong market performance and robust financial metrics within the hospital sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>160f546e3212db026fcff8bc9f0a19f2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Leads Market Rally with 908% Return in Six Months</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/smt-engineering-leads-market-rally-with-908-return-in-six-months-3779111</link><description>In a remarkable display of market outperformance, SMT Engineering, a micro-cap stock in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has delivered an extraordinary 908.42% return over the past six months, vastly eclipsing benchmark indices and peers alike. This surge underscores a potent combination of bullish technicals, outstanding financials, and sector-specific catalysts that have propelled the stock into the spotlight.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>cbcb53778876eb04702f8401d0d432bc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dabur India Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.1% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dabur-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-51-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3779114</link><description>Dabur India Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 524.6, marking a 4.91% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed the FMCG sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum throughout the session.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9f44ea858dc2de61f4aa03aeedc32b1f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NHPC Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 5.01% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nhpc-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-501-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3779115</link><description>NHPC Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 2 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 83.86, marking a 5.21% increase. This performance outpaced the broader power sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable momentum in the stock’s trading activity.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>63f5d553b204b5c8cfa89882ebcf9e83</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Leads Exceptional Stock Returns in One-Year Period</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/smt-engineering-leads-exceptional-stock-returns-in-one-year-period-3779112</link><description>In a remarkable display of market outperformance, SMT Engineering, a micro-cap stock in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has delivered an extraordinary return of 2091.6% over the past year, vastly surpassing benchmark indices and peers. This surge highlights the stock’s strong fundamentals, bullish technical outlook, and investor enthusiasm despite its expensive valuation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2a1010efe50c47566be85a70a0fd7e12</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>