<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3826767</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 1687 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings surprises has improved marginally to 46.0%, the distribution across market capitalisation segments and sectors highlights divergent performance trends that investors should carefully consider.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>7155092eeee7c040a1c1651f1c3ea312</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Petronet LNG Gains 2.33%: Mixed Technical and Valuation Signals Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/petronet-lng-gains-233-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-shape-weekly-performance-3826766</link><description>Petronet LNG Ltd. recorded a 2.33% gain over the week ending 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock showed resilience amid mixed technical momentum and a shift in valuation perception, closing at Rs.296.15 on Friday after a week of moderate gains and cautious investor sentiment. Key events included a sideways technical trend emerging midweek and a valuation grade downgrade reflecting evolving sector dynamics.
Time: 43 minutes ago</description><guid>9533f18dbead2f8bd99cdf192433d1af</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesh Housing Falls 2.15% Amid 52-Week Low and Revenue Drop: 3 Key Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganesh-housing-falls-215-amid-52-week-low-and-revenue-drop-3-key-factors-driving-the-decline-3826764</link><description>Ganesh Housing Corporation Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.713.80, down 2.15% from Rs.729.45, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp decline culminating in a 52-week low on 6 February 2026, driven by disappointing quarterly results and sustained selling pressure despite intermittent gains earlier in the week.
Time: 43 minutes ago</description><guid>6dcbf0ffee5b0ed6011f1f2a1a991437</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dredging Corporation of India Ltd Falls 12.73%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dredging-corporation-of-india-ltd-falls-1273-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3826765</link><description>Dredging Corporation of India Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 12.73% from Rs.1,127.90 to Rs.984.30, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by significant intraday volatility, a deepening loss in Q3 FY26 results, and a notable shift in valuation metrics signalling changing market sentiment.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>05358ed99902b9d1116a750e5be3c300</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd Gains 5.22%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-gains-522-5-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3826763</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. delivered a strong weekly performance, gaining 5.22% from Rs.1,130.70 to Rs.1,189.75 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock demonstrated consistent upward momentum, hitting multiple new 52-week and all-time highs amid improving technical indicators and robust market positioning within the ferrous metals sector.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>1ed0ead0921bfbb841d7ec2bccca5929</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gufic BioSciences Gains 1.27%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gufic-biosciences-gains-127-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3826762</link><description>Gufic BioSciences Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.27%, rising from Rs.306.05 on 30 January 2026 to Rs.309.95 on 6 February 2026. This performance slightly lagged the broader Sensex, which advanced 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp recovery following a fresh 52-week low on 2 February, driven by a strong gap up on 3 February amid positive sector momentum, though technical challenges and bearish longer-term indicators persisted.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>c0ee9ff817e11a4739bdc526fa8b93e6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>James Warren Tea Ltd. Declines 2.50% Amid Downgrade and Q3 Loss</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/james-warren-tea-ltd-declines-250-amid-downgrade-and-q3-loss-3826761</link><description>James Warren Tea Ltd. closed the week down 2.50% at Rs.321.30, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51%. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Sell rating amid technical weakness and flat financials, followed by a quarterly loss announcement reflecting seasonal pressures. Despite midweek gains, the stock struggled to maintain momentum against a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>24c02128709b1c2ff559e4e45d9f17d1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd Drops 4.22%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajmera-realty-infra-india-ltd-drops-422-4-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-slide-3826760</link><description>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd’s stock declined by 4.22% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.145.40 from Rs.151.80 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasts with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain during the same period, reflecting persistent bearish momentum and technical challenges for the small-cap realty firm amid sector headwinds and deteriorating fundamentals.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>4eb59888bb2c9f0a9b391fcceb0e872b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd Gains 5.06%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/transformers-rectifiers-india-ltd-gains-506-4-key-factors-driving-the-week-3826758</link><description>Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd (TRIL) closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a 5.06% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock experienced significant volatility, including a 52-week low early in the week and a strong rebound midweek, driven by a mix of technical shifts, valuation changes, and sector dynamics.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>1c547080b05a58ebedcab638d7bdeed3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Bank of India Dips 1.03% Despite New Highs: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/state-bank-of-india-dips-103-despite-new-highs-5-key-factors-driving-the-week-3826759</link><description>State Bank of India (SBI) experienced a volatile week from 2 to 6 February 2026, closing marginally lower by 1.03% at Rs.1,066.40 despite a strong midweek rally that saw the stock hit a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1,090. The broader Sensex outperformed with a 1.51% gain over the same period, highlighting a divergence between SBI’s price action and the market benchmark. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping SBI’s performance during the week.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>d87433d12b63af2df4acdbb20a342a7c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poonawalla Fincorp Gains 8.26%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/poonawalla-fincorp-gains-826-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3826757</link><description>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 8.26% from Rs.398.50 to Rs.431.40 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a mix of technical shifts, valuation reassessments, and notable price volatility, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and fundamental strength.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>743e8a4aed1064e619256acd8950a39f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DLF Ltd Gains 4.46%: Key Drivers Behind This Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dlf-ltd-gains-446-key-drivers-behind-this-weeks-rally-3826756</link><description>DLF Ltd. delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 4.46% from Rs.635.20 to Rs.663.55 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s rebound was driven primarily by a strong gap-up opening and intraday surge on 3 February, reflecting renewed investor interest amid a volatile market backdrop. Despite mixed technical signals and a cautious rating outlook, DLF demonstrated resilience within the real estate sector, supported by sector-wide gains and improving momentum.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>509cb2d98d9331eae9e187c49a76ee68</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astral Ltd’s Mildly Bullish Shift: 2.91% Weekly Gain Amid Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astral-ltds-mildly-bullish-shift-291-weekly-gain-amid-mixed-signals-3826755</link><description>Astral Ltd experienced a modestly negative week with its share price declining by 0.26% to close at ₹1,472.75 on 6 Feb 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by significant technical momentum shifts, a key earnings release, and an upgrade in analyst rating from Sell to Hold by MarketsMOJO, reflecting a nuanced market sentiment amid mixed signals.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>9b135bffb63ec1a74fd6a19849d72e50</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AXISCADES Technologies Ltd Drops 8.73%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axiscades-technologies-ltd-drops-873-5-key-factors-behind-the-volatile-week-3826754</link><description>AXISCADES Technologies Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 2 to 6 February 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 8.73% to close at ₹1,122.30, while the Sensex gained 1.51%. The week was marked by extreme volatility, including two lower circuit hits and multiple upper circuit surges, reflecting intense swings in investor sentiment amid mixed technical signals and shifting analyst ratings.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>3c450f6938ed080886f2bc54fe0e8a44</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cosmo First Ltd Gains 3.47%: Key Factors Behind This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cosmo-first-ltd-gains-347-key-factors-behind-this-weeks-volatility-3826753</link><description>Cosmo First Ltd closed the week with a 3.47% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period from 2 to 6 February 2026. The stock’s performance was marked by a sharp rebound on 3 February, driven by a strong gap-up opening and intraday surge, followed by moderate corrections in the subsequent sessions. Despite the week’s positive return, technical indicators and volatility suggest a cautious outlook amid mixed signals.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>5404b8c99f22479a1261d89bca3d2bc9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U. Y. Fincorp Ltd Gains 16.94%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/u-y-fincorp-ltd-gains-1694-4-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3826752</link><description>U. Y. Fincorp Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 16.94% from Rs.12.40 to Rs.14.50 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain. The stock’s rally was marked by multiple upper circuit hits amid strong buying momentum, despite its current sell-grade rating and subdued delivery volumes, reflecting a complex interplay of technical strength and fundamental caution.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>232d4f16ea9ad85db5eed252a6572de5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winsome Yarns Ltd Falls 4.09%: 4 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/winsome-yarns-ltd-falls-409-4-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-decline-3826750</link><description>Winsome Yarns Ltd experienced a challenging week on the BSE, closing at ₹1.64 on 6 February 2026, down 4.09% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹1.71. This decline contrasted sharply with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, underscoring the stock’s underperformance amid a series of significant events including rating downgrades, upper circuit surges, and a lower circuit hit.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>000c664b777568576b35188e47ea2c2c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arihant Superstructures Gains 4.76%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arihant-superstructures-gains-476-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3826751</link><description>Arihant Superstructures Ltd closed the week with a 4.76% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise from 2 to 6 February 2026. The stock rebounded strongly from a 52-week low early in the week, driven by intense buying pressure and volatile trading sessions that saw it hit an upper circuit limit. Despite this short-term strength, the company’s fundamental challenges and technical downtrend remain significant considerations for investors.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>721c6597d0cdb7a87fe6427c0d792fa1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanla Platforms Ltd Falls 7.10%: Technical Downgrade and Growth Concerns Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanla-platforms-ltd-falls-710-technical-downgrade-and-growth-concerns-weigh-3826749</link><description>Tanla Platforms Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 7.10% from Rs.512.20 to Rs.475.85, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Sell rating amid technical weakness and concerns over the company’s growth prospects, which weighed heavily on investor sentiment and contributed to the stock’s bearish momentum.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>ea4a84d78dbeb10d0baee9bfe8be31be</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Falls 7.86%: Volatility and Institutional Interest Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-falls-786-volatility-and-institutional-interest-mark-the-week-3826747</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NATIONALUM) experienced a challenging week from 2 to 6 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 7.86% to close at Rs.354.45, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. Despite a strong intraday rally on 2 February, the stock faced selling pressure in the latter half of the week amid volatile trading and profit booking, reflecting mixed investor sentiment and sector dynamics.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>1f8ac671924c8f431e7abc43a6c84ed7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>