<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Aeroflex Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.47% Surge on 17 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aeroflex-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-847-surge-on-17-feb-2026-3844043</link><description>Aeroflex Industries Ltd demonstrated robust intraday momentum on 17 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 209.15, marking an 8.65% increase from its previous close. This strong performance outpaced the broader Iron &amp; Steel Products sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading activity and positive market sentiment around the stock.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>435b51635310993065d06156aa794e9b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quick Heal Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.88% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/quick-heal-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-888-surge-3844042</link><description>Quick Heal Technologies Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 17 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 192, marking a significant 8.88% increase from the previous close. This rally stands out amid a broadly flat Sensex, highlighting the stock’s notable rebound after a four-day decline.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>cdb8f35be571013a861e2eff2d2bb25d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goodluck India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.17% Surge on 17 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goodluck-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-717-surge-on-17-feb-2026-3844041</link><description>Goodluck India Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 17 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 1199.15, marking a 7.17% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, continuing its upward momentum over the past two sessions.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>62ffa0c321485b476220b5d67ff05a4b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.2% Surge on 17 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infosys-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-32-surge-on-17-feb-2026-3844038</link><description>Infosys Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 17 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 1,406.85, marking a 2.97% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting a notable rebound after four consecutive sessions of decline.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>943e5d4d13687174664fb52ebdd82f74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KFin Technologies Ltd Sees Robust Trading Activity Amid Mixed Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kfin-technologies-ltd-sees-robust-trading-activity-amid-mixed-market-sentiment-3844040</link><description>KFin Technologies Ltd (KFINTECH), a prominent player in the capital markets sector, has emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 17 Feb 2026, demonstrating strong investor interest despite a recent downgrade in its mojo rating. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting heightened trading volumes and significant institutional participation.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>1fdc3bf40102577452e4b02db12e8aa4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees Heavy Value Trading Amid Declining Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-heavy-value-trading-amid-declining-momentum-3844039</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, witnessed one of the highest value turnovers on 17 Feb 2026, trading over ₹171.75 crores worth of shares. Despite this robust trading activity, the stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting growing investor caution amid weakening technical signals and falling delivery volumes.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7b80fdbfa6caeb5a0e02efc46d24b3b5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesh Infraworld Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganesh-infraworld-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844037</link><description>Shares of Ganesh Infraworld Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, closing at ₹89.05, down 4.96% from the previous close. The sharp decline reflects intense selling pressure and panic among investors, marking the stock’s maximum permissible daily loss and underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>1fe5d552ce167257c316c3e0ae33fbf5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd Sees Robust Value Trading Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-aeronautics-ltd-sees-robust-value-trading-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3844036</link><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL), a heavyweight in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 17 Feb 2026, registering a total traded value of ₹154.997 crores on a volume of 3,62,977 shares. Despite a modest intraday gain of 0.93%, the stock’s recent performance and institutional interest reveal a nuanced picture for investors navigating this large-cap defence behemoth.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>689ea77bc03f99e6a0729a6e75b269c4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cochin Shipyard Ltd Sees Robust Trading Activity Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cochin-shipyard-ltd-sees-robust-trading-activity-amid-mixed-market-signals-3844034</link><description>Cochin Shipyard Ltd (COCHINSHIP) emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 17 Feb 2026, registering a robust intraday performance with a 5.12% gain. Despite a strong opening gap and significant volume turnover, the stock remains under pressure from a cautious institutional outlook, reflected in its recent downgrade to a Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This article analyses the trading activity, market context, and investment implications for this Aerospace &amp; Defense mid-cap.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>957e652d42f60fd4e97921d31d20ea9b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cool Caps Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cool-caps-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3844035</link><description>Cool Caps Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the diversified consumer products sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.85%. This sharp price movement was driven by robust buying interest, resulting in a regulatory freeze on further transactions and highlighting significant unfilled demand in the stock.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>5a3c69fea0f4a19313d1221725b64884</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BSE Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bse-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-market-sentiment-3844032</link><description>BSE Ltd, a prominent player in the capital markets sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 17 Feb 2026, registering one of the highest value turnovers in the equity segment. Despite a modest decline of 1.73% in its share price, the stock continues to attract strong institutional participation and maintains a robust fundamental outlook, as reflected in its recent upgrade to a Strong Buy rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>a206929712159763206ccfa4dcd7f8ad</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nirman-agri-genetics-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844033</link><description>Shares of Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, closing at ₹56.85 after a sharp decline of 4.93% in a single session. The micro-cap stock witnessed intense selling pressure, with volumes drying up and panic selling dominating trade, signalling deep investor concerns amid deteriorating fundamentals and negative market sentiment.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>74e36f9702bb709f9fc2c44eb6f4347a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-market-signals-3844031</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd, a key player in the non-ferrous metals sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 17 Feb 2026, emerging as one of the most actively traded stocks by value. Despite a notable decline in its share price, the stock attracted considerable institutional interest and large order flows, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces and investor sentiment.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>e60020069c82b565a044c10ed9ce4d2a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JITF Infra Logistics Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jitf-infra-logistics-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-momentum-3844030</link><description>JITF Infra Logistics Ltd surged to its upper circuit price limit on 17 Feb 2026, closing at ₹412.55 with a maximum daily gain of 4.99%. The stock demonstrated robust buying interest, outperforming its sector and broader market indices, while regulatory restrictions have temporarily frozen further price movement due to unfilled demand.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>087a194b8a3f3403e38aa6ae50c52825</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Engineering Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-engineering-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844029</link><description>Shares of Supreme Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, closing at ₹0.95, down 4.04% on the day. The stock underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting intense selling pressure and unfilled supply that triggered panic among investors.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>da7b076b9eef73a7f2eea23de58abb1a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Ltd. Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedanta-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-market-sentiment-3844028</link><description>Vedanta Ltd., a heavyweight in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 17 Feb 2026, registering one of the highest value turnovers on the day. Despite a modest decline in price, institutional interest and liquidity metrics underscore the stock’s continued appeal among investors navigating a cautious market environment.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>eabf1aee9039ec9b798a98f96ca2ecc0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gayatri Highways Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gayatri-highways-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844027</link><description>Shares of Gayatri Highways Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, succumbing to intense selling pressure that saw the stock lose 4.74% in a single session. The micro-cap transport infrastructure company witnessed panic selling and unfilled supply, reflecting investor concerns amid a broader sector underperformance.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>c8f0bed9c247058d7fe4af3f5accc8ca</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Auri Grow India Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/auri-grow-india-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844024</link><description>Shares of Auri Grow India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, closing at a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹0.32. The stock witnessed intense selling pressure, with a maximum daily loss of 3.03%, significantly underperforming its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>25738c0059366997fb83625bac52010a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lotus-eye-hospital-institute-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-momentum-3844026</link><description>Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd witnessed robust buying interest on 17 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 4.99% gain to close at ₹124.66. The stock outperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting heightened investor enthusiasm and a surge in demand that remains unfilled due to regulatory price band restrictions.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>3dc291986a8b57c620f18890fb94f770</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Amid Continued Price Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ola-electric-mobility-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-amid-continued-price-decline-3844022</link><description>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd (NSE: OLAELEC) witnessed extraordinary trading volumes on 17 Feb 2026, as the stock hit a fresh 52-week and all-time low of ₹27.6. Despite the surge in investor participation, the share price declined sharply by 4.09% intraday, extending a four-day losing streak that has eroded nearly 12% of its value. This heightened activity signals significant distribution pressure amid weak technicals and a negative market sentiment surrounding the electric vehicle manufacturer.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>3cc9fbae36c77a8e8ff8b1dc2d0d116a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>