<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Arunaya Organics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arunaya-organics-ltd-fallingrising-3771785</link><description>On 26 Dec, Arunaya Organics Ltd experienced a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.69% to close at ₹20.70. This drop comes despite the stock’s strong performance over the past week, highlighting a complex market dynamic affecting the company’s shares.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1d4753b3f7c2787f2176e5aa58e44f72</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Namo eWaste Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-namo-ewaste-management-ltd-fallingrising-3771784</link><description>On 26-Dec, Namo eWaste Management Ltd's stock price rose by 2.0% to ₹196.15, reflecting a notable short-term recovery despite a challenging longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>beb11a81174df0ea803a460ff2de7a55</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Voler Car Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-voler-car-ltd-fallingrising-3771783</link><description>As of 26 Dec, Voler Car Ltd’s stock price has risen by 3.47% to ₹209.00, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2cb6b6c9ee42e973bc963079aaf99eae</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bikewo Green Tech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bikewo-green-tech-ltd-fallingrising-3771782</link><description>On 26-Dec, Bikewo Green Tech Ltd's stock price rose by 4.5% to ₹20.90, reflecting a notable short-term recovery despite a challenging longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>66cf0627a786561fd7bab3b1a1de2b7f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kalana Ispat Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kalana-ispat-ltd-fallingrising-3771781</link><description>On 26-Dec, Kalana Ispat Ltd's stock price fell sharply by 5.92% to close at ₹23.05, marking a new 52-week and all-time low. This decline reflects a sustained negative trend for the company’s shares, which have significantly underperformed the broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a38cded49e18b1bdc50d0eac9f836dfe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is RNFI Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rnfi-services-ltd-fallingrising-3771780</link><description>On 26-Dec, RNFI Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.28% to close at ₹310.75. This movement reflects a short-term correction following a period of substantial gains over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e289539e7aa90d10f5e0922610b328ec</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aspire &amp; Innovative Advertising Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aspire-innovative-advertising-ltd-fallingrising-3771779</link><description>On 26 Dec, Aspire &amp; Innovative Advertising Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 4.96%, closing at ₹17.25, reflecting a continuation of a prolonged downward trend that has significantly underperformed the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ba936415be6b67c957196087161c5ed</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Maitreya Medicare Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-maitreya-medicare-ltd-fallingrising-3771778</link><description>On 26-Dec, Maitreya Medicare Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹210.05, down ₹9.10 or 4.15%, hitting a new 52-week low of ₹208.10. This decline reflects a continuation of the company’s prolonged underperformance relative to market benchmarks and deteriorating financial fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d023644b6073b44a375a0d53acb13fb7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Arabian Petroleum Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arabian-petroleum-ltd-fallingrising-3771777</link><description>On 26-Dec, Arabian Petroleum Ltd's stock price rose by 2.71% to ₹75.85, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. This upward movement is supported by robust weekly returns, positive technical indicators, and heightened investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dffffaf8e429f2900ea52ed1a7532bb7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is HMA Agro Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hma-agro-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3771776</link><description>As of 26-Dec, HMA Agro Industries Ltd's stock price edged up by 0.69% to ₹29.00, reflecting a modest intraday gain despite a challenging broader performance trend. This article examines the factors influencing the stock’s recent price movement, contextualising it within its financial results, valuation metrics, and market positioning.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b99fe96e91df3be3483895a6785ac72e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Prospect Consumer Products Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-prospect-consumer-products-ltd-fallingrising-3771775</link><description>On 26-Dec, Prospect Consumer Products Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹64.00, down ₹2.00 or 3.03% from the previous close, reflecting ongoing challenges faced by the stock in both short and long-term performance metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>05b6fef37de5cf35475d7dbf56d7ad82</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Viaz Tyres Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-viaz-tyres-ltd-fallingrising-3771774</link><description>On 26-Dec, Viaz Tyres Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹64.50, down ₹2.00 or 3.01% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to key benchmarks and technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a3b5829498b62c54e5029184f8dc5de1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is SKP Bearing Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-skp-bearing-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3771773</link><description>On 26-Dec, SKP Bearing Industries Ltd recorded a modest rise in its share price, climbing 1.37% to ₹177.40. This uptick comes despite a backdrop of significant long-term underperformance and deteriorating profitability, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term market dynamics and persistent fundamental challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>81b9a53c00bebe7bc5683edc3a32b00e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jeena-sikho-lifecare-ltd-fallingrising-3771772</link><description>As of 26-Dec, Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd’s stock price experienced a slight dip of 0.02%, closing at ₹710.90. Despite robust quarterly earnings growth and increased institutional interest, the stock has faced downward pressure, reflecting concerns over its lofty valuation and recent underperformance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>09c92e00837ddaab5f7094e689e1187a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Star Health &amp; Allied Insurance Company Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-star-health-allied-insurance-company-ltd-fallingrising-3771771</link><description>As of 26-Dec, Star Health &amp; Allied Insurance Company Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting mounting concerns over its deteriorating sales performance and profitability, despite some long-term operational strengths.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>10454b01560604ece2fefaead9301d07</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Landmark Cars Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-landmark-cars-ltd-fallingrising-3771770</link><description>As of 26-Dec, Landmark Cars Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting persistent challenges in both its financial performance and investor sentiment. The share price closed at ₹481.20, down marginally by 0.11%, extending a losing streak that has seen the stock fall nearly 5% over the past week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1c0791bdb9fe4a8fb5cef183523c0e0f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Railtel Corporation of India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-railtel-corporation-of-india-ltd-fallingrising-3771769</link><description>On 26-Dec, Railtel Corporation of India Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 6.03% to close at ₹378.05. This surge reflects a combination of robust financial performance, strong market momentum, and favourable technical indicators that have attracted investor interest despite some lingering valuation concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f100f10038fa9f6ba4a29c3a3b266ad7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jainam Ferro Alloys (I) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jainam-ferro-alloys-i-ltd-fallingrising-3771768</link><description>On 26-Dec, Jainam Ferro Alloys (I) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.61% to ₹236.25. This movement reflects a complex interplay of recent market performance, valuation concerns, and operational metrics that have influenced investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a6277e043a82123dc4825bc1ae8dbc77</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Borosil Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-borosil-ltd-fallingrising-3771767</link><description>As of 26-Dec, Borosil Ltd’s stock price has declined by 1.23% to ₹284.15, continuing a downward trend influenced by a combination of underwhelming market performance and cautious investor sentiment despite some positive operational metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1edb212f470fc6fff6fc7104203522b9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Siddhika Coatings Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-siddhika-coatings-ltd-fallingrising-3771766</link><description>On 26-Dec, Siddhika Coatings Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.98% to close at ₹198.55. This drop reflects a short-term correction despite the company’s strong longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>78eed9e27f54db22bf4d7193237ec0a7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>