<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Valiant Laboratories Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.57.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/valiant-laboratories-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs578-3806447</link><description>Valiant Laboratories Ltd, a player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.57.8 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a challenging market environment and subdued long-term fundamentals.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>8ea5ac77cf0f747b09526f817042cd59</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piramal Pharma Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piramal-pharma-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3806446</link><description>Piramal Pharma Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.150.15 today, marking a significant decline amid subdued quarterly earnings and ongoing financial pressures. The stock’s performance over the past year has lagged considerably behind the broader market, reflecting challenges in profitability and debt servicing metrics.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>91601b2f92db08ce9ee8bfe4c4fd7d74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electronics Mart India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.84.95</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/electronics-mart-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs8495-3806444</link><description>Electronics Mart India Ltd has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.84.95, marking a significant decline in its share price amid ongoing financial pressures and subdued performance metrics. This latest low reflects a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory over the past year.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>37f7d91f14b4fa10fb3c17383973e420</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spencers Retail Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.29.95</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spencers-retail-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2995-3806445</link><description>Spencers Retail Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.29.95 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing pressures. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>298358cfde7e2732fd9d4a71083fcd98</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Add-Shop E-Retail Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/add-shop-e-retail-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3806440</link><description>Add-Shop E-Retail Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.7.36 on 27 Jan 2026, marking a significant downturn for the e-commerce company amid persistent underperformance and subdued financial results.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>58bf417717b42833d1f0488d93824611</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samrat Forgings Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.200.1 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samrat-forgings-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2001-amidst-continued-downtrend-3806442</link><description>Samrat Forgings Ltd, a player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.200.1 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid ongoing downward momentum and underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>fcb60024fe9d3b9c797746b18bf09df2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aadhar-housing-finance-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806441</link><description>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term price trajectory amid mixed fundamental and technical signals.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>3032b3a04c045b587c9dea414e3f183a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Angel One Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/angel-one-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806443</link><description>Angel One Ltd, a prominent player in the Capital Markets sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>7f24bba3a1ba003a63017ba83e8b93c4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806438</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>83ceabad46e2f39500487228d10e31ef</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/welspun-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3806437</link><description>Welspun Enterprises Ltd, a key player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near-term prospects.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>4de61eeff1feb76adb6c232624a4ba33</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adcon Capital Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adcon-capital-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3806436</link><description>Adcon Capital Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>d2d6f819d28ab071783e8c583af06554</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goldiam International Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goldiam-international-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3806439</link><description>Goldiam International Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development points to a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid ongoing bearish momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>89120cf9cb26a88f7826a7520962639c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Century Extrusions Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/century-extrusions-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3806435</link><description>Century Extrusions Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b12a3efc97ab816a0157e0ba0df248ad</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ramky Infrastructure Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ramky-infrastructure-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3806434</link><description>Ramky Infrastructure Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6affe17de7ae4e285975510efc6a640c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apcotex Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apcotex-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806429</link><description>Apcotex Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, highlighting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum amid broader market challenges.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>d083ee9c60fbdc800e895a918e5443c2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intellect Design Arena Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/intellect-design-arena-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806430</link><description>Intellect Design Arena Ltd., a notable player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>a6dc83bb6fec5b2701cab97489d8e617</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITI Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iti-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806428</link><description>ITI Ltd, a key player in the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>04387d9e9ff9d070c8c2a3d853c3146c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vimta Labs Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vimta-labs-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806427</link><description>Vimta Labs Ltd, a prominent player in the Healthcare Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6f514c86ac1a36de4ef5e20d37886d20</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siemens Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3806433</link><description>Siemens Ltd., a major player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average crossed below the 200-day moving average. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>0be188fae297cbae0b151127dab28de0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Count Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-count-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3806431</link><description>Indo Count Industries Ltd, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>64b09bd6111e919d3f11fcccd513a9a8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>