<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3819043</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 1,115 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings surprises has improved to 49.0%, this marks a modest recovery from the previous quarter’s 42.0%, reflecting ongoing sectoral and market cap divergences in performance.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>186d2fd4bd4ff98c8c0be2db35aa5cf1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Q3 FY26: Profit Growth Masks Margin Pressure and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mankind-pharma-q3-fy26-profit-growth-masks-margin-pressure-and-valuation-concerns-3819040</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd., one of India's leading pharmaceutical companies with a market capitalisation of ₹87,785 crores, delivered a mixed performance in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), with consolidated net profit rising 7.50% year-on-year to ₹408.75 crores but declining 20.09% sequentially from ₹511.51 crores in Q2 FY26. The stock surged 4.30% to ₹2,155.90 following the results announcement, though it remains down 16.56% over the past year, significantly underperforming both the Sensex and the pharmaceutical sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb232907136307ccb1b3d8e878aa66ac</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NMDC Steel Q3 FY26: Losses Widen as Operational Challenges Persist Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/nmdc-steel-q3-fy26-losses-widen-as-operational-challenges-persist-despite-revenue-growth-3819039</link><description>NMDC Steel Ltd., the Central Public Sector Undertaking under the Ministry of Steel, reported a net loss of ₹243.97 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a substantial deterioration from the ₹25.56 crore profit recorded in Q2 FY26. The loss represents a quarter-on-quarter reversal and a year-on-year improvement of 67.82% from the ₹757.78 crore loss in Q3 FY25. The stock closed at ₹41.64 on February 03, 2026, down 1.68% from the previous close, reflecting investor concerns about the company's persistent profitability challenges despite improving top-line performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>023f47ca9a3e24d6f24dec608a3a3038</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Restaurant Brands Asia Q3 FY26: Losses Deepen Despite Revenue Growth as Expansion Costs Bite</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/restaurant-brands-asia-q3-fy26-losses-deepen-despite-revenue-growth-as-expansion-costs-bite-3819038</link><description>Restaurant Brands Asia Limited, the master franchisee for Burger King in India and Indonesia, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹43.54 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a 13.61% deterioration from the ₹50.40 crores loss in the year-ago quarter. Despite posting its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹714.65 crores—up 11.83% year-on-year—the company continues to grapple with mounting depreciation and interest costs that have kept profitability elusive. The stock, currently trading at ₹63.57, has tumbled 16.56% over the past year and remains 29.00% below its 52-week high of ₹89.53, reflecting sustained investor pessimism about the quick-service restaurant operator's path to profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9310fb55bba75ffdc9599b24f51aa428</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Anup Engineering Q3 FY26: Profit Decline Amid Revenue Growth Raises Margin Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/the-anup-engineering-q3-fy26-profit-decline-amid-revenue-growth-raises-margin-concerns-3819037</link><description>The Anup Engineering Limited, a small-cap industrial manufacturing company with a market capitalisation of ₹3,929.00 crores, reported a challenging third quarter for FY2026 that exposed underlying profitability pressures despite sustained topline momentum. Net profit for Q3 FY26 declined 20.34% quarter-on-quarter to ₹25.53 crores, marking a 15.49% year-on-year contraction, whilst revenue grew 20.48% year-on-year to ₹206.92 crores. The divergence between revenue growth and profit contraction has raised questions about margin sustainability and cost management effectiveness. Following the results announcement, the stock surged 16.18% to ₹2,070.00 on February 03, 2026, though this recovery comes after a brutal one-year decline of 29.64%, significantly underperforming the Sensex's 8.49% gain during the same period.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>306b6398d1d8f4c3c1c600010fd326db</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godrej Agrovet Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Underlying Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/godrej-agrovet-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-underlying-margin-pressures-3819036</link><description>Godrej Agrovet Ltd., a diversified agribusiness conglomerate with a market capitalisation of ₹10,673 crores, reported consolidated net profit of ₹114.82 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sequential growth of 24.01% over Q2 FY26 and a modest 2.99% year-on-year increase. The stock, trading at ₹548.65 as of February 03, 2026, has declined 0.94% post-results, reflecting investor caution despite the profit recovery. The company's performance reveals a tale of two narratives: robust topline momentum offset by persistent margin compression and elevated debt levels that continue to weigh on investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5c9fd0f4718b004529be8dfe449b1ad9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Svarnim Trade Udyog Q3 FY26: Zero Revenue, Mounting Losses Signal Deepening Distress</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/svarnim-trade-udyog-q3-fy26-zero-revenue-mounting-losses-signal-deepening-distress-3819035</link><description>Svarnim Trade Udyog Ltd., a micro-cap textile trading company with a market capitalisation of ₹3.00 crores, reported its Q3 FY26 results, revealing a troubling pattern of operational inactivity and persistent losses. The company recorded a net loss of ₹0.02 crores for the quarter ended December 2025, with zero revenue generation for the seventh consecutive quarter—a stark indicator of complete business stagnation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>091f46b1fedd8fc51d7d7058e447f430</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SAL Automotive Q3 FY26: Profitability Pressures Mount Amid Volume Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sal-automotive-q3-fy26-profitability-pressures-mount-amid-volume-decline-3819034</link><description>SAL Automotive Ltd., the Punjab-based automotive components manufacturer, reported a concerning third quarter for FY2026, with net profit plunging 67.20% quarter-on-quarter to ₹0.61 crores from ₹1.86 crores in Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, profitability declined 56.43% from ₹1.40 crores in Q3 FY25, marking the weakest quarterly performance in recent periods. The micro-cap company, with a market capitalisation of ₹100 crores, saw its stock react positively on February 3, 2026, rising 5.48% to ₹205.95, though this appears more technical in nature given the sharp decline from its 52-week high of ₹346.65.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>870fd815471c3634933928a79733c6ca</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Q3 FY26: Profit Decline Amid Rising Costs Raises Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bajaj-finance-q3-fy26-profit-decline-amid-rising-costs-raises-concerns-3819033</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd., India's largest non-banking financial company with a market capitalisation of ₹5,89,549 crores, reported a concerning 18.41% quarter-on-quarter decline in consolidated net profit for Q3 FY26, posting ₹3,977.85 crores compared to ₹4,875.36 crores in Q2 FY26. The year-on-year performance painted an even grimmer picture, with profits falling 6.33% from ₹4,246.54 crores in Q3 FY25. The stock surged 6.68% to ₹964.75 on February 3, 2026, following the results announcement, despite the profit decline signalling underlying operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>732ea9dd7800c27ace89497c70251e07</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beryl Securities Q3 FY26: Strong Revenue Surge Masks Underlying Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/beryl-securities-q3-fy26-strong-revenue-surge-masks-underlying-profitability-concerns-3819032</link><description>Beryl Securities Ltd., a micro-cap non-banking financial company registered with the Reserve Bank of India, reported a net profit of ₹0.22 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a dramatic recovery from the previous quarter's loss of ₹0.21 crores. Despite the impressive 98.25% year-on-year revenue growth, the stock has plunged 23.44% over the past three months, with shares trading at ₹23.35 as of February 3, 2026—a market capitalisation of just ₹12.00 crores.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9ffe98a0752871064e5d7a4d124902ae</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Q3 FY26: Profit Plunge Overshadows Revenue Growth as Margins Remain Resilient</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/firstsource-solutions-q3-fy26-profit-plunge-overshadows-revenue-growth-as-margins-remain-resilient-3819031</link><description>Firstsource Solutions Ltd., a leading business process management company in the RP-Sanjiv Goenka Group, reported a sharp 32.97% quarter-on-quarter decline in consolidated net profit to ₹120.33 crores for Q3 FY26 ended December 2025, despite posting its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹2,443.08 crores. The profit contraction comes as a surprise given the company's strong top-line momentum, which grew 5.66% sequentially and 16.21% year-on-year, raising questions about cost management and operational efficiency during the quarter.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8a40ac02c3d0762816cdaf02318f23d5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dynamic Industries Q3 FY26: Profit Plunges 86% as Revenue Pressures Mount</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/dynamic-industries-q3-fy26-profit-plunges-86-as-revenue-pressures-mount-3819030</link><description>Dynamic Industries Limited, the Ahmedabad-based specialty chemicals manufacturer, reported a sharp deterioration in its Q3 FY26 financial performance, with net profit collapsing 86.11% quarter-on-quarter to just ₹0.05 crores from ₹0.36 crores in Q2 FY26. The micro-cap company, valued at ₹36 crores, saw its revenue decline 21.14% sequentially to ₹14.10 crores, marking the lowest quarterly sales in the past two years. Despite the disappointing results, the stock surged 9.67% on February 3, 2026, closing at ₹122.50, though it remains 35.49% below its 52-week high of ₹189.90.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7850b7d7b23d449504d06d792515b695</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JK Lakshmi Cement Q3 FY26: Margin Pressures Weigh on Profitability Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/jk-lakshmi-cement-q3-fy26-margin-pressures-weigh-on-profitability-despite-revenue-growth-3819029</link><description>JK Lakshmi Cement Ltd., a leading manufacturer of cement and cementitious products, reported a challenging third quarter for FY2026, with consolidated net profit declining 29.64% quarter-on-quarter to ₹56.92 crores, despite posting modest revenue growth. The stock has underperformed significantly, trading at ₹762.10 as of February 3, 2026, down 25.35% from its 52-week high of ₹1,020.85, reflecting investor concerns over sustained margin compression and operational headwinds.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>128d2591e86819217b78e6a187f8cc27</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>M K Exim (India) Ltd: Struggling Micro-Cap Faces Steep Decline Despite Solid Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/m-k-exim-india-ltd-struggling-micro-cap-faces-steep-decline-despite-solid-fundamentals-3819028</link><description>M K Exim (India) Ltd., a Jaipur-based micro-cap engaged in fabric exports and cosmetics distribution, finds itself in turbulent waters despite maintaining a respectable fundamental profile. With a market capitalisation of ₹209.00 crores, the stock currently trades at ₹50.30, reflecting a modest 1.86% gain in today's session but masking a deeper crisis—a devastating 40.66% decline over the past year that has eroded shareholder wealth and raised serious questions about the company's near-term prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2b228187b1b73706f6f397158e1bce4b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lee &amp; Nee Software Q3 FY26: Operational Losses Persist Despite Sequential Profit Recovery</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/lee-nee-software-q3-fy26-operational-losses-persist-despite-sequential-profit-recovery-3819027</link><description>Lee &amp; Nee Software (Exports) Ltd., a Kolkata-based IT-enabled services company with a market capitalisation of ₹47.00 crores, reported a net profit of ₹0.11 crores in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sharp 266.67% sequential recovery from the previous quarter's ₹0.03 crores. However, the company continues to grapple with persistent operational losses, with operating profit (excluding other income) remaining negative at ₹0.07 crores despite marginal improvement. The stock, currently trading at ₹8.37, has declined 30.25% over the past year, significantly underperforming both the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b63f6d384eb4fbc4387263db06276f73</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neo Infracon Q3 FY26: Profit Recovery Masks Deeper Volatility Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/neo-infracon-q3-fy26-profit-recovery-masks-deeper-volatility-concerns-3819024</link><description>Neo Infracon Ltd., a Mumbai-based micro-cap real estate construction and development company, reported a return to profitability in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025) with consolidated net profit of ₹0.30 crores, reversing a loss of ₹0.37 crores in the previous quarter. However, the 7.14% year-on-year profit growth and sharp sequential revenue surge of 275.76% reveal a company grappling with extreme quarterly volatility that raises serious questions about earnings sustainability for this ₹21 crore market capitalisation entity.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a82c00f0f19f3dbdc4ac7dd66d8ab062</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid India Industries Q3 FY26: Operational Turmoil Deepens as Losses Mount</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mid-india-industries-q3-fy26-operational-turmoil-deepens-as-losses-mount-3819021</link><description>Mid India Industries Ltd., the Mandsaur-based textile manufacturer, reported a net loss of ₹0.06 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sharp deterioration from the marginal profit of ₹0.04 crores recorded in the same quarter last year. The company's shares traded at ₹7.20 on February 3, 2026, down 0.55% from the previous close, reflecting persistent investor concerns over the company's operational viability. With a diminutive market capitalisation of just ₹12.00 crores and a negative book value of ₹-2.76 per share, Mid India Industries finds itself trapped in a cycle of chronic underperformance that has eroded shareholder wealth by 14.29% over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cd8a59d42c284a1de1988963afb50ed8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suraj Products Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Margin Concerns and Technical Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/suraj-products-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-margin-concerns-and-technical-weakness-3819020</link><description>Suraj Products Limited, a micro-cap iron and steel products manufacturer based in Odisha, reported a net profit of ₹4.04 crores for Q3 FY26 (Oct-Dec'25), marking a sequential improvement of 26.25% over Q2 FY26's ₹3.20 crores. However, the quarterly performance reveals underlying challenges that have contributed to a sharp 56.83% decline in the stock price over the past year, with shares currently trading at ₹181.30 and a market capitalisation of ₹207 crores. Despite the quarter-on-quarter profit growth, the company faces persistent margin pressures and a bearish technical setup that has eroded investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2c8fa74a9eac8de79a016439f3e2b0c0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>