<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Gains 3.04%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rashi-peripherals-gains-304-2-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3787856</link><description>Rashi Peripherals Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 3.04% from Rs.358.05 to Rs.368.95 between 5 and 9 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s early-week surge, including a new 52-week high, was driven by strong intraday rallies and robust financial results, while the latter part of the week saw profit-taking amid broader market weakness.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>f414fad8c41a1ae7f03644aefa1ef3d7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alpex Solar Ltd Falls 7.46%: 3 Key Technical Signals Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alpex-solar-ltd-falls-746-3-key-technical-signals-driving-the-weekly-decline-3787859</link><description>Alpex Solar Ltd endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 7.46% to close at ₹763.75, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The week was marked by a series of bearish technical developments, including a notable Death Cross formation and deteriorating momentum indicators, which weighed heavily on investor sentiment and contributed to the stock’s downward trajectory.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>179e0f08b668befee26772f7ce25bd83</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Platinum Industries Ltd Drops 10.25%: 2 Key Events Mark a Steep Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/platinum-industries-ltd-drops-1025-2-key-events-mark-a-steep-downtrend-3787854</link><description>Platinum Industries Ltd endured a challenging week, with its stock price tumbling 10.25% from Rs.245.45 to Rs.220.30, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% decline. The week was marked by intensified bearish technical signals and the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low, reflecting sustained downward momentum amid weak financial metrics and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>55985d6ae6dfcdf8fc67ed049bbb4e04</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukka Proteins Ltd Falls 5.86%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukka-proteins-ltd-falls-586-6-key-factors-driving-the-continued-downtrend-3787858</link><description>Mukka Proteins Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price declining by 5.86% to close at Rs.22.66, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows amid persistent financial pressures, elevated leverage, and declining institutional interest, underscoring a sustained bearish momentum despite some operational profit growth.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>b5d36cde0974b437cd80f0a57770785f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R K Swamy Ltd Falls 2.46% This Week: 3 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-k-swamy-ltd-falls-246-this-week-3-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3787857</link><description>R K Swamy Ltd’s stock declined by 2.46% over the week ending 9 January 2026, marginally outperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The stock faced sustained selling pressure, hitting a fresh 52-week low twice during the week amid weak financial results and deteriorating technical indicators. Despite a modest recovery midweek, the overall trend remained bearish, reflecting ongoing challenges in the company’s fundamentals and market sentiment.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>384d151a5cb34b798219fe94dcbbf765</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd Falls 3.43%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/go-digit-general-insurance-ltd-falls-343-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3787851</link><description>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 3.43% from ₹346.80 on 2 January 2026 to ₹334.90 on 9 January 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell by 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a shift in technical momentum, a downgrade in analyst ratings, and mixed signals from key financial and valuation metrics, all contributing to the stock’s subdued performance.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>5e76fd9d95dcb710bec11d0e416039cb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Scientific Ltd’s Mixed Week: -1.05% Price, Outperforms Sensex by 1.57%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-scientific-ltds-mixed-week--105-price-outperforms-sensex-by-157-3787852</link><description>Borosil Scientific Ltd closed the week ending 9 January 2026 at ₹118.25, down 1.05% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹119.50. This modest decline came amid a broader market sell-off, with the Sensex falling 2.62% over the same period. Despite the negative weekly return, Borosil Scientific outperformed the benchmark index, reflecting some resilience amid challenging market conditions and mixed technical signals.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>0b01d34ab2e8cc3a28576b58f3722bba</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd Falls 6.83%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-falls-683-4-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3787855</link><description>Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price declining by 6.83% to close at Rs.132.25, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s downward trajectory was marked by a series of bearish technical signals, culminating in a fresh 52-week and all-time low of Rs.129 on the final trading day. This review analyses the key events and technical developments that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>2b4c8ed578c56685565d574393961d5f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Travenues Technology Declines 9.41%: Downgrade and Technical Weakness Drive Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/le-travenues-technology-declines-941-downgrade-and-technical-weakness-drive-sell-off-3787853</link><description>Le Travenues Technology Ltd experienced a challenging week as its stock price declined by 9.41%, closing at Rs.219.10 on 9 January 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a 'Sell' rating amid deteriorating technical indicators and disappointing quarterly financial results, signalling growing investor caution despite the company’s strong longer-term returns.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>514899f4dff8a9a0e8f3d476413e418e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DEE Development Engineers Ltd Gains 4.30%: Key Technical Shifts and Intraday Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dee-development-engineers-ltd-gains-430-key-technical-shifts-and-intraday-surge-3787849</link><description>DEE Development Engineers Ltd closed the week at Rs.224.25, marking a 4.30% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.215.00, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s performance was characterised by a sharp intraday rally on 8 January, reversing earlier losses and signalling a potential short-term momentum shift amid mixed technical signals and sector headwinds.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>cd748fc95412eb5589396c2762f77773</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade Falls 9.06%: 2 Key Lows Mark a Challenging Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akme-fintrade-falls-906-2-key-lows-mark-a-challenging-week-3787848</link><description>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 9.06% to close at Rs.5.92, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit both a 52-week low and an all-time low on 9 January, reflecting sustained downward momentum amid mixed financial results and a cautious market environment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>7efcb5d018dacd38837231db44d0b5e7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Peroxide Ltd Falls 6.29% Amidst Prolonged Downtrend and Weak Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-peroxide-ltd-falls-629-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-and-weak-financials-3787850</link><description>National Peroxide Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, falling 6.29% to close at Rs.440.35, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% decline over the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows multiple times amid deteriorating financial metrics and sustained bearish momentum, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s fundamentals and market sentiment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>35fc0a86279693fa4916add65df76c7b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stanley Lifestyles Gains 2.28%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stanley-lifestyles-gains-228-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3787846</link><description>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 2.28%, rising from Rs.192.95 on 2 January to Rs.197.35 on 9 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by a sharp intraday rally midweek, offset by some profit-taking towards the end, reflecting a mixed but cautiously optimistic trading environment amid ongoing technical and fundamental challenges.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>0aae528f7e46b7d3a958cd0fed3d5f6a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Gains 7.70%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/emcure-pharmaceuticals-gains-770-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3787844</link><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.70% from Rs.1,430.00 to Rs.1,540.10 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week highs amid a backdrop of mixed broader market conditions, buoyed by positive technical momentum, solid financial results, and increased institutional interest.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>dbb925a36b8fe4a04eb5eb9911f62a51</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd Falls 3.17%: Key Factors Behind the 52-Week and All-Time Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bansal-wire-industries-ltd-falls-317-key-factors-behind-the-52-week-and-all-time-low-3787842</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd experienced a difficult week ending 09 Jan 2026, with its stock price declining 3.17% from Rs.311.15 to Rs.301.30, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by the stock hitting a fresh 52-week and all-time low of Rs.286 on the final trading day, reflecting ongoing downward momentum amid broader market weakness and company-specific financial pressures.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>ab03cbf8e9546d9990797cba24faf4b7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd’s 3.47% Weekly Decline: Volume Surges Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ola-electric-mobility-ltds-347-weekly-decline-volume-surges-amid-mixed-market-signals-3787847</link><description>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 3.47% to close at Rs.39.49, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite a strong start marked by a 7.36% gain on Monday, the stock faced persistent selling pressure amid mixed market signals and a Strong Sell rating from MarketsMOJO, reflecting investor caution in a volatile automobile sector environment.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>eb7be26701ea7653dad1eab383bc48e5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd Falls 6.86%: Four Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saraswati-saree-depot-ltd-falls-686-four-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3787841</link><description>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd’s stock experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, declining 6.86% to close at Rs.73.77, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows amid sustained bearish momentum, despite the company reporting record quarterly sales and profits. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>6967d98dabb6fc1e20e76a1f76085d2a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Technologies Ltd Falls 11.17%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orient-technologies-ltd-falls-1117-5-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3787845</link><description>Orient Technologies Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing down 11.17% to Rs.357.50, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The week began with a strong gap-up surge and heavy institutional interest but ended with sharp declines and a lower circuit hit amid heavy selling pressure and elevated volatility.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>eab8faee546eb3cb061735815bc29a4d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Ltd Drops 15.18%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-ltd-drops-1518-6-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3787843</link><description>Premier Energies Ltd endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price plunging 15.18% to close at Rs.717.90, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% decline. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows amid sustained selling pressure, technical weakness, and heightened derivatives market activity, reflecting a complex interplay of valuation concerns and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>9c78bfdb500e0e041d91734d266f4418</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Ltd Falls 11.21%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/waaree-energies-ltd-falls-1121-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-decline-3787839</link><description>Waaree Energies Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 11.21%, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure, technical weakness below all major moving averages, and heightened bearish sentiment reflected in derivatives activity, despite a recent upgrade to a Buy rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>23fe499c6313bc3b22f9c83753dee5c7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>