<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Acutaas Chemical Joins Mojo Stocks on Strong Financial Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/acutaas-chemical-joins-mojo-stocks-on-strong-financial-momentum-3808306</link><description>Acutaas Chemical, a small-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has been added to the prestigious Mojo Stocks list on 28 January 2026, reflecting its remarkable financial performance and strong growth trajectory. The stock’s recent bullish upgrade and impressive quarterly results underscore its potential as a compelling investment opportunity within the current market landscape.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>3ea8708e445935284fcede3dabecec58</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GE Vernova T&amp;D India Q3 FY26: Record Profits Propel Stock 6.5% as Transmission Boom Continues</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/ge-vernova-td-india-q3-fy26-record-profits-propel-stock-65-as-transmission-boom-continues-3808308</link><description>GE Vernova T&amp;D India Ltd., a leading player in India's power transmission and distribution infrastructure sector, delivered an outstanding third-quarter performance for FY2026, with net profit reaching ₹290.80 crores—a decline of 2.90% quarter-on-quarter but a remarkable 103.78% surge year-on-year. The market responded enthusiastically, with shares jumping 6.52% to ₹2,909.05 on January 28, 2026, pushing the company's market capitalisation to ₹72,726 crores. Despite trading at elevated valuations with a P/E ratio of 81x, the stock's momentum reflects strong investor confidence in India's ongoing power infrastructure expansion.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>0fb375a98b3e71d15a03a39fd6c86c7e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries Q3 FY26: Margin Pressures Mount as Profitability Slides 21%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/balkrishna-industries-q3-fy26-margin-pressures-mount-as-profitability-slides-21-3808307</link><description>Balkrishna Industries Ltd., one of the world's leading manufacturers of off-highway tyres, reported a challenging third quarter for FY2026, with net profit declining 21.26% year-on-year to ₹273.19 crores. The ₹47,020-crore market capitalisation company, which commands the second-largest position in India's tyres and rubber products sector, witnessed sequential profit contraction of 5.24% from Q2 FY26's ₹288.30 crores, highlighting persistent margin pressures despite relatively stable revenue performance.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>524f28d00564eeb18a599de69f76249e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Checkpoint Trends Q3 FY26: Explosive Revenue Surge Masks Wafer-Thin Margins in Trading Pivot</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/checkpoint-trends-q3-fy26-explosive-revenue-surge-masks-wafer-thin-margins-in-trading-pivot-3808305</link><description>Checkpoint Trends Limited (formerly Rubra Medicaments Ltd.), a micro-cap pharmaceutical company with a market capitalisation of ₹66.00 crores, reported a net profit of ₹0.57 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a decline of 56.82% quarter-on-quarter but a turnaround from losses recorded in the corresponding quarter last year. The company's stock, trading at ₹123.95, has surged 1089.54% over the past year, reflecting extraordinary investor enthusiasm despite fundamental concerns about profitability and business model sustainability.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>1266d32cefead9035b0b11527bc2e759</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dolat Algotech Q3 FY26: Sharp Recovery Masks Persistent Half-Year Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/dolat-algotech-q3-fy26-sharp-recovery-masks-persistent-half-year-weakness-3808304</link><description>Dolat Algotech Limited, a technology-driven quantitative trading house with a market capitalisation of ₹1,427 crores, reported consolidated net profit of ₹38.89 crores for Q3 FY26, marking an impressive 762.31% quarter-on-quarter surge from the depressed ₹4.51 crores in Q2 FY26. However, the year-on-year comparison reveals a more modest 4.04% growth, whilst the nine-month performance for FY26 paints a concerning picture with net profit declining 58.31% compared to the same period last year. The stock responded positively to the quarterly recovery, gaining 8.77% on January 28, 2026, to close at ₹86.70, though it remains 21.89% below its 52-week high of ₹111.00.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>101397ad0fc93c64be51f4a5feaa218f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AksharChem (India) Q3 FY26: Loss-Making Quarter Triggers Sharp Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/aksharchem-india-q3-fy26-loss-making-quarter-triggers-sharp-concerns-3808303</link><description>AksharChem (India) Ltd., a Gujarat-based speciality chemicals manufacturer, has plunged into losses in Q3 FY26, posting a net loss of ₹4.62 crores compared to a profit of ₹0.05 crores in the previous quarter—marking an alarming deterioration of 8,500%. The stock, trading at ₹226.00 on January 28, 2026, has declined 1.20% in the latest session and remains under severe pressure, down 31.68% from its 52-week high of ₹330.80. With a market capitalisation of ₹185.00 crores, the micro-cap company faces mounting operational challenges that have triggered a "Strong Sell" rating from analysts.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>22cb13099e1d66ab50a296f18692d9c0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>T T Ltd Q2 FY26: Marginal Profit Recovery Masks Deeper Revenue Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/t-t-ltd-q2-fy26-marginal-profit-recovery-masks-deeper-revenue-concerns-3808302</link><description>T T Limited, a Delhi-based garment and apparel manufacturer, reported net profit of ₹0.18 crores in Q2 FY26, representing a sharp 58.14% decline sequentially from ₹0.43 crores in Q1 FY26, whilst posting a year-on-year decline of 63.27% from ₹0.49 crores in Q2 FY25. The micro-cap company, with a market capitalisation of ₹182 crores, saw its stock surge 9.13% following the results announcement, though this appears to be a technical bounce rather than fundamental strength, as the shares remain 56.41% below their 52-week high of ₹17.00.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>8b10fb1b21ea5c24216db6dd665f79d1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are NIIT Learning Systems Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-niit-learning-systems-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808277</link><description>NIIT Learning Systems Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 19.29% year-on-year and a net profit increase of 58.30%, but declining operating margins raise concerns about profitability sustainability amidst rising costs. Overall, while the financial position is solid, challenges in maintaining margins warrant attention.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b50d1235345d0071780568b01d4dd751</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gopal Snacks Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gopal-snacks-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808276</link><description>Gopal Snacks Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a mixed performance, with net sales up 14.86% sequentially but down 7.23% year-on-year. While net profit significantly improved, ongoing revenue decline and below-industry return on equity raise concerns about the company's competitive position.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>06b8aa6ab3d4ee4932010ff67ee1e591</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bikaji Foods International Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bikaji-foods-international-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808275</link><description>Bikaji Foods International Ltd's latest results show strong growth for the quarter ended September 2025, with a 33.19% increase in net profit and a 27.22% rise in revenue, driven by festive demand. However, the following quarter saw declines in both net sales and profit, indicating potential challenges ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>491f58c463d69c0cce3776ebaf0d9a21</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-international-gemmological-institute-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808274</link><description>International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd's latest results are strong, with a net profit increase of 18.42% and net sales growth of 21.43% year-on-year. However, the stock price has declined by 39.55% over the past year, indicating market concerns despite solid operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c25b354d974c77243e044349cbffd8e4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Piramal Pharma Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-piramal-pharma-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808273</link><description>Piramal Pharma Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹99.22 crores and an 8.83% decline in net sales year-on-year, alongside a significant drop in operating margins. The company's financial challenges raise doubts about its ability to generate sustainable profits and manage its high debt levels.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6993e1113902112cd70e0ecc36cc26e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vishal Mega Mart Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vishal-mega-mart-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808272</link><description>Vishal Mega Mart Ltd's latest results are strong, with a 23.11% increase in net sales and a 105.45% rise in net profit for the quarter ending December 2025, driven by festive season demand. However, concerns remain regarding its return on equity and the need for consistent performance beyond seasonal peaks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>998417813599e3ce9a079e98756de8fe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Metro Brands Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-metro-brands-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808271</link><description>Metro Brands Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show revenue growth of 11.22% year-on-year, but significant margin compression led to a 31.29% decline in net profit, raising concerns about profitability sustainability amid rising costs. The company's strong return on equity and healthy balance sheet are positive, but upcoming results will be crucial to assess if these challenges are temporary or indicative of deeper issues.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>272216fcc294a16c9821b4fb872b316f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Prudent Corporate Advisory Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-prudent-corporate-advisory-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808270</link><description>Prudent Corporate Advisory Services Ltd's latest results show steady revenue growth with an 11.78% increase to ₹319.79 crore, but profitability is challenged by declining margins, with net profit rising only 3.92% to ₹53.54 crore. While the company maintains a strong return on equity and a debt-free balance sheet, the pressures on operating margins and high valuations warrant careful monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9eca9d2f4ef195ca27d34d2876a93659</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are S J S Enterprises Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-s-j-s-enterprises-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808269</link><description>S J S Enterprises Ltd's latest results are strong, with record quarterly revenue of ₹243.53 crores and a net profit of ₹44.61 crores, reflecting year-on-year growth of 36.39% and 61.87%, respectively. The company also achieved an all-time high operating margin of 29.31%, indicating effective cost management and a solid business model.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>11d82001518de89d68afbb24c969ee0d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rainbow-childrens-medicare-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808268</link><description>Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong sequential growth with a net profit increase of 40.65% and revenue up 26.03%, but year-on-year comparisons reveal a decline in profitability and modest revenue growth, indicating challenges in sustaining long-term growth. Investors should monitor future performance closely due to these mixed trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5093e3407aa19039805abb3852e5aabe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Cartrade Tech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-cartrade-tech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808267</link><description>Cartrade Tech Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year growth in net sales and profit, with record quarterly revenue and improved margins. However, there was a decline in net sales and profit in the subsequent quarter, suggesting a potential softening in momentum that investors should monitor.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7999d029172e9836a4a11c4a162f066c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Acutaas Chemicals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-acutaas-chemicals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808266</link><description>Acutaas Chemicals Ltd's latest results are strong, with a 42.98% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹393.18 crores and a net profit increase of 140.18% to ₹107.96 crores, indicating effective cost management and a solid position in the pharmaceutical sector. The company also boasts a strong balance sheet with no long-term debt and record-high operating margins.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>69086d134a9691bab9634a16a01c1940</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Jayatma Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jayatma-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3808265</link><description>Jayatma Industries Ltd's latest results show significant revenue growth with net sales increasing by 190.48% quarter-on-quarter, but the company continues to face profitability challenges, posting a net loss and negative operating margins, indicating a difficult financial outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d75430081e11a74b777149b673697903</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>