<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Mixed Results Mark Dec-2025 with Mid Caps Leading Profit Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-mark-dec-2025-with-mid-caps-leading-profit-growth-3827615</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has delivered a mixed bag of results as 1,744 companies declared their financials, with the proportion of positive outcomes inching up to 46.0%, marking a modest improvement from the previous quarter’s 42.0%. While mid-cap firms continue to outperform with a 52.0% positivity rate, large caps lag behind at 38.0%, reflecting sectoral and size-based divergences in corporate profitability and growth trends.
Time: Feb 08 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>c2cddf1ab672cb0d3277d1708ba4e25c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Shradha AI Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-shradha-ai-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827604</link><description>Shradha AI Technologies Ltd's latest results show significant revenue volatility and declining profitability, with a 26.53% drop in net sales and an 18.48% decrease in net profit in Q2 FY26. While there is year-on-year growth in sales, the company faces challenges in stabilizing revenue and managing costs, which could impact future investor confidence.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>2648037a24d3b26bd68740adb7186dff</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are TARC Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tarc-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827603</link><description>TARC Ltd.'s latest results show significant revenue growth of 458.66% quarter-on-quarter, but the company continues to face operational challenges with a net loss of ₹21.03 crores and a negative operating margin of 47.45%, indicating concerns about its long-term profitability and financial stability.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>04e3df04248df213f8c9db2490c7497d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vl-e-governance-it-solutions-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827602</link><description>VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd's latest results are poor, showing a 70.55% year-on-year decline in net sales, a net loss of ₹0.71 crores, and a negative operating margin, indicating significant operational challenges and a weakened financial position.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>182e2e9f76465d8d523e126fb20c68d4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are MRP Agro Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mrp-agro-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827601</link><description>MRP Agro Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 19.79% decline in net profit and a 41.69% drop in revenue, the lowest this fiscal year, despite improved operating margins. The company's negative cash flow and reduced promoter holding raise questions about its growth prospects and investor confidence.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>5e1d28236466bc1903042d6088aecffe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Assam Entrade Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-assam-entrade-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827600</link><description>Assam Entrade Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 23.46% revenue increase to ₹2.00 crores but a net loss of ₹-0.01 crores, down from a profit of ₹0.48 crores in Q1 FY26, indicating significant operational challenges and reliance on non-operating income. Overall, the company's financial health appears weak, with declining profitability and a low return on equity.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>d4a2eb794037265ea30813f3d278b8e1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sikko Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sikko-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827599</link><description>Sikko Industries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong year-on-year growth in net profit and revenue, but significant quarter-on-quarter declines in both profitability and operating margins raise concerns about operational challenges and capital efficiency. Overall, the results are mixed, indicating both growth potential and current difficulties.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>4c5177f2876b919d55e3e874bf551961</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Alphalogic Techsys Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-alphalogic-techsys-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827598</link><description>Alphalogic Techsys Ltd's latest results show mixed performance, with a sequential profit increase but a year-on-year decline in sales, indicating ongoing operational challenges and reliance on non-operating income. Overall, the results reflect a difficult environment and market skepticism about the company's growth potential.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>edaf29eaefa5076f6ff53b470aa86be7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are General Insurance Corporation of India latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-general-insurance-corporation-of-india-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827597</link><description>General Insurance Corporation of India's latest results show mixed performance, with a 12.97% year-on-year sales growth but a 39.95% decline in net profit compared to the previous quarter, primarily due to a drop in other income. While the company maintains a strong balance sheet and efficient capital deployment, it faces challenges from competitive pricing and fluctuating investment income.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>373093510f8a8e2d5de98c3cfb0b9983</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-veer-global-infraconstruction-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827596</link><description>Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd's latest results show a 30.57% increase in revenue to ₹2.05 crores, but a concerning 52.17% drop in net profit to ₹0.33 crores, indicating serious challenges in profitability and operational efficiency despite revenue growth. Overall, the financial outlook appears cautious due to declining profit margins and low returns on equity and capital employed.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>a44a4f6efb1c7a3aeb66cafb8529b701</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bella-casa-fashion-retail-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827595</link><description>Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd's latest results show year-on-year growth in net sales and profit, but a significant sequential decline highlights challenges in maintaining performance during slower demand periods. Overall, the results reflect a mixed outlook with positive long-term growth potential but near-term volatility.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>f9a20f61e1b09a876ed80e54fbfc1227</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-l-g-balakrishnan-bros-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827594</link><description>L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 20.63% year-on-year, but net profit declined by 5.54% sequentially, indicating challenges in operational efficiency and rising costs. Overall, while revenue performance is positive, the drop in profitability suggests the company is facing some operational headwinds.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>08120209bd07c03da3dd0346ae88552e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Madhucon Projects Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-madhucon-projects-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827593</link><description>Madhucon Projects Ltd's latest results show a 7.67% increase in net sales to ₹139.33 crores, but the company still faces significant operational challenges with a net loss of ₹106.64 crores and a negative operating profit, raising concerns about its financial sustainability.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>6914889cafee02f37700060efe2968b7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mahanagar Gas Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mahanagar-gas-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827592</link><description>Mahanagar Gas Ltd.'s latest results show mixed performance: while revenue increased by 11.52% year-on-year to ₹2,060.24 crore, net profit declined by 9.08% to ₹201.15 crore, indicating ongoing profitability challenges despite some recovery from the previous quarter. The company faces margin pressures, raising concerns about sustaining profitability in a competitive market.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>9bacbbb86db56477d5ff6b9105293f89</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-balkrishna-paper-mills-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3827591</link><description>Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 47.05% increase in net sales but a net loss of ₹1.89 crores and negative operating margins, indicating significant operational challenges and a decline in market position. The company has also underperformed in stock returns and lacks institutional interest, suggesting a need for strategic restructuring.
Time: Feb 08 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>1090fb464dce93ee40bd59497ae647bc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>