<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-virtual-galaxy-infotech-ltd-fallingrising-3846159</link><description>On 18-Feb, Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.43% to ₹136.35 as of 09:26 PM. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and diminished investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b30ee64f34e5ca3c5bcaaf8e8a5606a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Azad Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-azad-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3846158</link><description>On 18-Feb, Azad Engineering Ltd’s stock price surged by 3.67% to ₹1,717.35, reflecting robust investor confidence driven by consistent quarterly performance, strong sales growth, and significant outperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bf1fab6ebcee620877f058af3ec00168</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Samhi Hotels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-samhi-hotels-ltd-fallingrising-3846157</link><description>As of 18-Feb, Samhi Hotels Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 1.21% to ₹163.00, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices. Despite some positive long-term growth indicators, the stock has faced downward pressure due to concerns over management efficiency and debt servicing capabilities.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b545261d41325ded3ca9e9e524144c09</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anuroop Packaging Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anuroop-packaging-ltd-fallingrising-3846156</link><description>On 18-Feb, Anuroop Packaging Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 7.73% to ₹12.40 by 09:12 PM. This upward movement reflects a strong short-term performance that significantly outpaces both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1765553bd4e84bcffcca6c0d4c5931f2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Acutaas Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-acutaas-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3846155</link><description>On 18-Feb, Acutaas Chemicals Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹2,134.40 with a gain of ₹59.95 or 2.89%. This upward momentum reflects a combination of robust financial performance, market-beating returns, and positive technical indicators that have attracted investor interest despite some signs of reduced participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5babd6a8eaa0eceb6fbc13c80f20ee16</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bazel International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bazel-international-ltd-fallingrising-3846154</link><description>On 18-Feb, Bazel International Ltd's stock price rose by 3.66% to close at ₹38.53, continuing a notable upward trend supported by robust returns over recent periods and heightened investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2d4ab78d3860e9aa85cc887ecde674b5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Easun Capital Markets Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-easun-capital-markets-ltd-fallingrising-3846153</link><description>On 18-Feb, Easun Capital Markets Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.0% to close at ₹49.24. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by erratic trading activity and shifting investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>624b35ab8c97a7fc310604831f01c54e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sikko Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sikko-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3846152</link><description>On 18-Feb, Sikko Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.93% to close at ₹4.82. This drop contrasts with the stock's impressive long-term performance and recent positive financial results, signalling a short-term correction rather than a fundamental weakness.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5481f5c2902f72ba5b31ca676417839b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Elnet Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-elnet-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3846151</link><description>On 18-Feb, Elnet Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.15% to ₹356.90 by 8:55 PM. This upward movement reflects a combination of sustained positive momentum, increased investor participation, and technical strength relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3e2f672e92d7fc94b40ab5ee3d92fe56</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bajaj Auto Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bajaj-auto-ltd-fallingrising-3846150</link><description>On 18-Feb, Bajaj Auto Ltd. witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹9,978.25, up by ₹148.7 or 1.51%, reaching a new 52-week high of ₹10,005.9. This upward momentum reflects a combination of robust long-term fundamentals, consistent market outperformance, and positive technical indicators despite some cautionary signals on investor participation and valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>de24956bb9806769582d4a12f9d3ffac</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vivanta Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vivanta-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3846149</link><description>On 18-Feb, Vivanta Industries Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹1.85 with a decrease of 1.07%, reflecting ongoing challenges in both short-term and long-term performance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fab40ef4c37b5bb82ba24851c1c6f46d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Expleo Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-expleo-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3846148</link><description>On 18-Feb, Expleo Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.59% to close at ₹830.00. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks, with the stock underperforming both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a01c625e5aed443d81a77fc9feccd925</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pix Transmission Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pix-transmission-ltd-fallingrising-3846147</link><description>On 18-Feb, Pix Transmission Ltd’s stock price rose by 3.14% to ₹1,539, reflecting a positive market response to its recent quarterly performance and growing institutional participation despite some concerns over long-term growth prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>51e1572b2ccb75154e46839f50369232</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kama Holdings Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kama-holdings-ltd-fallingrising-3846145</link><description>As of 18-Feb, Kama Holdings Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 6.04% to ₹2,811.40. This upward momentum reflects a combination of robust quarterly financial performance and increased investor participation, positioning the stock well above recent benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8ae318df7a3653fb2e168fdb839c506c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Capital Trade Links Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-capital-trade-links-ltd-fallingrising-3846146</link><description>On 18-Feb, Capital Trade Links Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.68% to close at ₹19.16. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5aadb06d1e2ae5cf340b1b39365ff1d5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is VTM Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vtm-ltd-fallingrising-3846144</link><description>On 18 Feb, VTM Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 8.45% to close at ₹86.75, marking a continuation of a three-day losing streak amid heightened volatility and declining investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>62ef51ec16ddfde75982b169c2fd13d0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Emergent Industrial Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-emergent-industrial-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3846143</link><description>On 18-Feb, Emergent Industrial Solutions Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹379.00, down ₹5.80 or 1.51% from the previous session, continuing a recent pattern of underperformance against broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a1ea0f04476144a9aeaa5960d2f6cd28</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is 3P Land Holdings Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-3p-land-holdings-ltd-fallingrising-3846142</link><description>On 18-Feb, 3P Land Holdings Ltd experienced a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.92% to close at ₹33.87. This drop reflects a broader underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by heightened intraday volatility and weakening investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0f8b16d5d468ceb498b14bfcd6d5db28</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gokul-refoils-and-solvent-ltd-fallingrising-3846141</link><description>On 18-Feb, Gokul Refoils and Solvent Ltd witnessed a significant price surge, rising by 19.86% to close at ₹40.74. This sharp increase reflects a robust short-term rally that has outpaced both its sector and benchmark indices, signalling renewed investor interest despite mixed longer-term performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4bb884f34b90f5e40f98be58af62c952</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is VST Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vst-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3846140</link><description>On 18-Feb, VST Industries Ltd saw its share price rise by 2.48% to ₹245.40, reflecting a short-term positive momentum despite ongoing challenges in its longer-term performance and relative underperformance against major benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8c40cb6dfb34bfddb9be9f08aa688af4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>