<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>One 97 Joins Reliable Performers List Following Stellar Q4 Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/one-97-joins-reliable-performers-list-following-stellar-q4-financials-3811985</link><description>One 97, a mid-cap leader in the financial technology sector, has been added to the prestigious Reliable Performers list as of 30 January 2026, following an exceptional quarter ending December 2025. The company’s robust financial metrics and sustained growth trajectory underpin its inclusion, signalling strong potential for investors seeking consistent fundamental strength and reliable price appreciation.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>535f88ca32f91a7696cf4b6cde88eb07</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Golkunda Diamonds Q2 FY26: Strong Revenue Growth Masks Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/golkunda-diamonds-q2-fy26-strong-revenue-growth-masks-margin-pressures-3811991</link><description>Golkunda Diamonds &amp; Jewellery Ltd. reported a net profit of ₹3.18 crores for Q2 FY26, marking a modest sequential improvement of 1.27% from the previous quarter's ₹3.14 crores. However, the company delivered an impressive year-on-year surge of 202.86% compared to ₹1.05 crores in Q2 FY25, underscoring a remarkable recovery trajectory in profitability. The micro-cap gem and jewellery manufacturer, with a market capitalisation of ₹143.00 crores, saw its stock rally 4.63% to ₹206.85 following the results announcement, reflecting investor optimism about the revenue momentum despite lingering margin concerns.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>735cd8d99edea675c1ea06f8853065e3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NTPC Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Margin Pressures as India's Power Giant Navigates Growth Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/ntpc-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-margin-pressures-as-indias-power-giant-navigates-growth-challenges-3811990</link><description>NTPC Ltd., India's largest power utility with a market capitalisation of ₹3.44 lakh crores, delivered a mixed performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit rising 8.42% year-on-year to ₹5,488.67 crores despite flat sequential growth of 8.33%. The quarter's results reveal a company grappling with margin pressures even as it maintains revenue momentum, raising questions about operational efficiency in an increasingly competitive power sector. Following the results announcement, the stock traded at ₹355.80, down 0.64% from the previous close, reflecting investor caution about the sustainability of profit growth amidst rising costs.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>4e192add263233c9595dc4f90d8fa6e0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maithan Alloys Q3 FY26: Recovery Stalls Amid Volatile Other Income</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/maithan-alloys-q3-fy26-recovery-stalls-amid-volatile-other-income-3811989</link><description>Maithan Alloys Ltd., India's second-largest ferro alloys manufacturer, reported consolidated net profit of ₹88.90 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a modest 2.12% year-on-year decline but a significant 173.50% quarter-on-quarter recovery from the previous quarter's loss of ₹120.95 crores. Despite the sequential improvement, the Kolkata-headquartered company continues to grapple with volatile other income and subdued operating performance, raising concerns about earnings quality and sustainability.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>051952676bd25b572501eec21a4561d6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Synthetics Q2 FY26: Modest Recovery Masks Deep Structural Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/garware-synthetics-q2-fy26-modest-recovery-masks-deep-structural-challenges-3811988</link><description>Garware Synthetics Ltd., the Mumbai-based manufacturer of nylon monofilaments and bristles, reported a net profit of ₹0.12 crores for Q2 FY26, maintaining its profitability from Q1 FY26 (₹0.12 crores) whilst delivering a four-fold improvement from ₹0.03 crores in Q2 FY25. The small-cap company, with a market capitalisation of just ₹12.00 crores, saw its shares plunge 5.00% on January 30, 2026, closing at ₹20.33, as investors reacted to the company's persistently weak fundamentals and bearish technical signals despite the quarterly profit stabilisation.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>766e0d1862ddf2ca9379016a31af8f35</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steelcast Ltd Q3 FY26: Strong Profitability Amid Revenue Moderation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/steelcast-ltd-q3-fy26-strong-profitability-amid-revenue-moderation-3811987</link><description>Steelcast Limited, a Gujarat-based castings manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹1,907 crores, delivered a mixed performance in Q2 FY26 (Jul-Sep'25), with net profit rising 16.75% quarter-on-quarter to ₹23.21 crores whilst revenue remained virtually flat at ₹106.65 crores. Despite the sequential revenue stagnation, year-on-year comparisons paint a more robust picture, with net sales surging 41.54% and net profit climbing 74.62% compared to Q2 FY25. The stock, trading at ₹185.50 as of January 30, 2026, has declined 2.45% following the results announcement, reflecting investor concerns about near-term growth momentum even as profitability metrics remain strong.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>0f14bc5ffeb158be53e9ee5d7e37d771</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are ACME Solar Holdings Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-acme-solar-holdings-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811956</link><description>ACME Solar Holdings Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 42.34% year-on-year, but a slight decline in net profit raises concerns about operational efficiency and high debt levels, indicating potential risks to financial stability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>df7b60eb67256ad5720e223b4da19118</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are NTPC Green Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ntpc-green-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811955</link><description>NTPC Green Energy Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year growth with a net profit increase of 130.26%, but a significant sequential decline of 60.27% due to rising financial costs and operational challenges, raising concerns about profitability and increasing debt levels.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1512055a2f96db698ac5325b825156ed</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-allied-blenders-distillers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811954</link><description>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Ltd's latest results show strong profit growth and improved operational efficiency, with a 35.22% year-on-year net profit increase. However, investor sentiment is cautious due to valuation pressures, as the stock trades below its 52-week high.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e2edd9a38ba68a33c75cc8880deea9a8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jasch-gauging-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811953</link><description>Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong sequential growth in revenue and net profit, but long-term challenges persist with a decline in annual sales and recent setbacks in the latest quarter. Overall, the performance is mixed, indicating potential sustainability issues despite recent improvements.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7bd4174947119bd6b139c58209d95973</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Kross Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kross-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811952</link><description>Kross Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 6.06% decline in net sales and a 24.49% drop in net profit, indicating operational challenges in the auto components sector. While the company has improved its balance sheet to a net cash position, profitability metrics suggest ongoing pressures that could impact future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7d23d16beacab50b78ca602a0a384403</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Niva Bupa Health Insurance Company Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-niva-bupa-health-insurance-company-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811951</link><description>Niva Bupa Health Insurance Company Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 17.21% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹35.27 crores, marking its second consecutive quarterly loss, indicating ongoing profitability challenges despite improving operational margins.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8d324c27ef87b9dd876f20cb06fe16d1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indegene Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indegene-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811950</link><description>Indegene Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 5.70% sequentially and 17.09% year-on-year, but net profit declined by 12.29%, and profitability margins have contracted, indicating operational challenges. Overall, while revenue growth is positive, the declining margins and cautious investor sentiment suggest mixed results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1baf6526fb07a6fe4ce71f8cc689be09</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aadhar-housing-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811949</link><description>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are generally positive, showing strong growth in net profit and revenue, with an all-time high operating margin. However, there are concerns about a slowdown in growth rates and a lack of detailed asset quality metrics, which may affect investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>93d3deef69d0d24e162786e7d791b5ee</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Flair Writing Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-flair-writing-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811948</link><description>Flair Writing Industries Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth and a significant profit increase, but concerns about operational efficiency and working capital management persist. Overall, while the financial performance is positive, sustainability of earnings remains a question.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>902bcfdccdf402b7c4479c02b498f492</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Syrma SGS Technology Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-syrma-sgs-technology-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811947</link><description>Syrma SGS Technology Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are strong, with a 37.60% year-on-year revenue increase and a 76.77% rise in net profit, indicating robust operational performance. However, challenges in capital efficiency and working capital management remain, suggesting areas for improvement.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4f60dcd3c240a73df19b747682a4d269</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are One 97 Communications Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-one-97-communications-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811946</link><description>One 97 Communications Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 24.23% year-on-year, but a significant decline in net profit raises concerns about sustainable earnings, highlighting challenges in establishing a consistent profit-generating model. While operational efficiency has improved, the reliance on non-operating income and low return on equity indicate ongoing financial uncertainties.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>01840268ed9adda2c101ad7d4154e653</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nila Spaces Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nila-spaces-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811945</link><description>Nila Spaces Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales increasing by 32.18% year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure with a decline in net profit and operating margins. Additionally, negative cash flow raises concerns about revenue quality, indicating the company faces significant challenges despite its operational potential.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e5d3aeaeb22057de177fccb56de47cf3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-motherson-sumi-wiring-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811944</link><description>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 18.55% year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure, with net profit margins declining to 6.00% due to rising employee costs and operational challenges. Overall, the company is experiencing robust sales but struggles with maintaining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>36d21dac48451b1a2f73e9385a1c7f9a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are MTAR Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mtar-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3811943</link><description>MTAR Technologies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 28.71% decline in revenue and a 77.36% drop in net profit, indicating significant operational challenges. However, the stock price has increased recently, suggesting that investors may be optimistic about future recovery in the aerospace and defence sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>81d51488d1a4976e51a56e16924f05ee</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>