<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Madhya Bharat Agro Products Ltd Hits All-Time High, Marking a Milestone in Fertilizers Sector</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhya-bharat-agro-products-ltd-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-milestone-in-fertilizers-sector-3842700</link><description>Madhya Bharat Agro Products Ltd has reached an all-time high, closing just 0.05% shy of its 52-week peak at Rs 477.95, underscoring a remarkable performance in the fertilizers sector. The stock’s recent surge reflects sustained growth and robust financial metrics, positioning it prominently within its industry.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>f8c296ab49cf0894455dfe1abb32f9f2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pashupati-cotspin-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-on-16-feb-2026-3842695</link><description>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high, reflecting a robust performance trajectory in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector. The stock’s recent surge underscores the company’s resilience and sustained momentum in a competitive market environment.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>c5423b0296c02a2d664ede7dc433fc18</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/concord-enviro-systems-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-decline-3842692</link><description>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd has reached an all-time low, closing near its 52-week bottom at Rs 350.5, marking a significant decline amid sustained underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f5bb03f7f3b123c2456ffed36c7b244b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siemens Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 3.16% Surge on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-316-surge-on-16-feb-2026-3842691</link><description>Siemens Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 16 Feb 2026, touching a day’s high of Rs 3,217, marking a 3.16% gain. This surge outpaced the broader Sensex and the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, reflecting a notable rebound after two days of declines.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f54c243121dd933746c83861d9b239d8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Oil Exploration Company Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-oil-exploration-company-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3842686</link><description>Hindustan Oil Exploration Company Ltd experienced significant intraday weakness today, touching a fresh 52-week low of Rs 131.05 as the stock declined by 8.27%, underperforming its sector and broader market indices amid persistent selling pressure and heightened volatility.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>72f62253dbc27948d18092bea01b62e7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3842687</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd., a leading name in the construction sector, has reached an all-time high in its stock price, underscoring its robust performance and sustained growth over recent years. This milestone reflects the company’s strong fundamentals and market leadership within its industry.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>1201fe4a1ae6769096cfa424eb8adc8b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astral Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astral-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3842684</link><description>Astral Ltd, a key player in the plastic products industrial sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock recently hit a new 52-week high of Rs 1,641.2, supported by robust volume and positive price action, reflecting growing investor confidence amid a broader sectoral uptrend.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>e39aee958b607ef2d94b63ae70a218ad</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TCI Finance Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tci-finance-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3842688</link><description>Shares of TCI Finance Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and a sharp decline in investor confidence. The stock recorded a maximum daily loss of 2.61%, closing at ₹14.43, down from its previous close, amid panic selling and unfilled supply in the market.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>3cc2f585d9f92f1b206a909ef7149f70</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-pharmaceuticals-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3842689</link><description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and a potential shift in investor sentiment. The stock’s recent price action, coupled with robust volume and rising delivery volumes, suggests growing bullish positioning among traders and investors.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>48bbd65281528ad32bc3c1064fcfc70d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Seats Ltd Surges 20% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-seats-ltd-surges-20-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3842683</link><description>Bharat Seats Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, witnessed a remarkable surge on 16 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 20.0% gain to close at ₹196.26. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, substantial trading volumes, and a wide intraday price range, signalling renewed investor confidence after a brief correction phase.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>1e810dbaf41449d622b15492ddd7fb03</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Bank Ltd: High-Value Trading Amid Narrow Price Range and Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-bank-ltd-high-value-trading-amid-narrow-price-range-and-institutional-interest-3842685</link><description>ICICI Bank Ltd., one of India’s leading private sector banks, witnessed significant trading activity on 16 Feb 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹5,243 crores. Despite this high liquidity and investor interest, the stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a cautious stance among traders amid recent price volatility and a modest downgrade in its investment grade.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>7ce964a291ba19c2f1fa309d25d556a0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Faces Downward Pressure Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-faces-downward-pressure-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-3842679</link><description>The BSE Midcap index has experienced a notable decline over recent sessions, reflecting a cautious investor sentiment amid uneven sectoral contributions and mixed stock performances. Despite some bright spots, the segment’s overall momentum has weakened, with key stocks showing divergent returns and breadth indicators signalling moderate market participation.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>fd2f15f57bbdd91079a543acd7b811e6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Stocks Rally as Power Grid Leads Gains; Hero MotoCorp Lags</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-stocks-rally-as-power-grid-leads-gains-hero-motocorp-lags-3842680</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, demonstrated steady gains on 16 Feb 2026, rising 0.74% amid a broad-based advance. While heavyweight stocks such as Power Grid Corporation led the rally with a 4.40% return, some cyclical names like Hero MotoCorp lagged, declining 1.67%. The advance-decline ratio of 3.0x underscores the segment’s overall positive momentum, reflecting a market environment where defensive sectors outperformed cyclical counterparts.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>48faedc9f064ce1e49c8255da3b66dbe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Faces Downward Pressure Amid Broad Market Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-faces-downward-pressure-amid-broad-market-weakness-3842681</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index has experienced a notable decline of 1.58% on the day and a sharper 1.66% drop over the past five trading sessions, signalling a period of consolidation and pressure within the small-cap segment. Despite this overall weakness, select stocks have bucked the trend, highlighting a mixed performance landscape that investors must carefully navigate.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>c91d8ad739d3f1bbf07c90fd67bba582</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Ltd Delivers Multibagger Returns Amid Strong Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shriram-finance-ltd-delivers-multibagger-returns-amid-strong-fundamentals-3842672</link><description>Shriram Finance Ltd has emerged as a standout performer in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, delivering multibagger returns exceeding 100% over the past year. Outpacing the Sensex by a wide margin, the stock’s robust fundamentals, consistent growth trajectory, and strong institutional backing have propelled it into the spotlight as a compelling buy for investors seeking sustainable wealth creation.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>572553478f031d41b526e8395f5c022b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bluestone Jewellery &amp; Lifestyle Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bluestone-jewellery-lifestyle-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3842668</link><description>Bluestone Jewellery &amp; Lifestyle Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 16 Feb 2026, touching a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹406.1, reflecting persistent price pressure amid broader market dynamics and sector underperformance.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>d8100418ab87d78aec23acbce489c91b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BN Agrochem Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amidst Significant Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bn-agrochem-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amidst-significant-price-pressure-3842669</link><description>BN Agrochem Ltd experienced significant intraday weakness on 16 Feb 2026, with its share price plunging to a day low of Rs 250, marking a decline of 7.97% from the previous close. Despite opening with a positive gap of 6.59%, the stock faced sustained selling pressure, underperforming its sector and the broader market amid heightened volatility and technical headwinds.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>d8f10d0d790e2d8d8890f8c95bd39fd5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Muthoot Finance Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/muthoot-finance-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-16-feb-2026-3842666</link><description>Muthoot Finance Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 16 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 3,450, reflecting a 3.54% drop from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, weighed down by immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment despite a recovering Sensex.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>45c5f976a4fec251ee703f50ba9bbe11</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.15% Surge on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-holdings-investment-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-315-surge-on-16-feb-2026-3842663</link><description>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 16 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of ₹11,194.65, marking a 2.88% increase during the session and closing with a notable 3.15% gain. This rally outpaced the broader Sensex, which rose 0.39% after a volatile start, reflecting strong trading momentum in the holding company’s stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>44acda7ca32cb3748d3c8cb7bf004afe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gufic BioSciences Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amidst Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gufic-biosciences-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amidst-price-pressure-3842665</link><description>Gufic BioSciences Ltd experienced a notable decline today, hitting an intraday low of Rs 284.1, reflecting sustained price pressure amid broader market dynamics. The stock underperformed its sector and the benchmark Sensex, continuing a recent downward trend that has weighed on investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9c645d69ae0f045c13b4482eafc3429b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>