<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd Gains 11.90%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mishra-dhatu-nigam-ltd-gains-1190-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3779549</link><description>Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd (MIDHANI) delivered a strong weekly performance from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026, rising 11.90% from Rs.318.50 to Rs.356.40. This gain significantly outpaced the Sensex’s 1.35% advance over the same period, reflecting robust investor interest amid mixed technical signals and elevated trading volumes. The week was marked by notable intraday highs, heavy institutional participation, and a complex technical landscape signalling both momentum and caution.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>6716231b6f89529129e5f9ba2f2c4469</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>E2E Networks Ltd Falls 1.14%: 2 Key Technical Signals Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/e2e-networks-ltd-falls-114-2-key-technical-signals-driving-the-week-3779548</link><description>E2E Networks Ltd closed the week marginally lower by 1.14%, ending at Rs.2,027.50 on 2 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. The week was marked by significant bearish technical developments, including the formation of a Death Cross and intensified downtrend signals, which weighed on investor sentiment despite some short-term price recoveries.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>82591794226d0082a0f1a6f0ab449397</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Asset Management Gains 0.43%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-asset-management-gains-043-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3779546</link><description>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd (HDFCAMC) closed the week ending 2 January 2026 with a modest gain of 0.43%, rising from ₹2,647.55 to ₹2,659.00. This performance trailed the broader Sensex, which advanced 1.35% over the same period, reflecting a mixed week marked by significant derivatives activity, a key rating upgrade, and evolving technical signals. The stock’s price movements and market dynamics throughout the week reveal a nuanced interplay of investor sentiment and fundamental developments.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>1ca69dd1b56631cf1810a03cc23b3f77</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tembo Global Industries Ltd Falls 14.30%: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tembo-global-industries-ltd-falls-1430-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3779547</link><description>Tembo Global Industries Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 29 Dec 2025 to 2 Jan 2026, with its stock price plunging 14.30% from ₹709.15 to ₹607.75, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. The week was marked by multiple lower circuit hits, heavy selling pressure, and a late surge to the upper circuit, reflecting intense volatility and shifting investor sentiment amid mixed technical signals and declining delivery volumes.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>d18a31c97999ae749562684732e981f5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Engineering Gains 15.52%: 5 Key Events Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-engineering-gains-1552-5-key-events-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3779545</link><description>Supreme Engineering Ltd experienced a highly volatile week from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026, ultimately gaining 15.52% to close at ₹1.34, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise. The stock’s journey was marked by sharp swings, including multiple circuit hits amid intense selling and buying pressures, reflecting a turbulent sentiment in this micro-cap Iron &amp; Steel Products player.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>300a4e74052a1267efeb63fe26fd81d5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd Falls 2.78%: Mixed Technical Signals Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spectrum-electrical-industries-ltd-falls-278-mixed-technical-signals-mark-the-week-3779544</link><description>Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd closed the week down 2.78% at Rs.1,225.00, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. The stock faced significant selling pressure on 29 Dec 2025, hitting an intraday low amid weak technical signals, before stabilising into a sideways trend by early January 2026. Mixed technical momentum and cautious market sentiment characterised the week’s trading activity.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>e3d1e13219ad763f5433d37779a9250f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aavas Financiers Declines 2.40% Amid Valuation Concerns and 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aavas-financiers-declines-240-amid-valuation-concerns-and-52-week-low-3779542</link><description>Aavas Financiers Ltd. closed the week ending 2 January 2026 at Rs.1,443.95, down 2.40% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,479.50. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period, reflecting mounting valuation pressures and a fresh 52-week low for the stock amid a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>ca5f829db0ce87bb5283935f79129ca2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manorama Industries Gains 5.50%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manorama-industries-gains-550-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-momentum-3779543</link><description>Manorama Industries Ltd delivered a solid weekly gain of 5.50%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026. The week was marked by a series of technical shifts and rating changes, reflecting a complex interplay between strong fundamentals and emerging bearish momentum. Despite a late-week rally pushing the stock to ₹1,388.30 (+4.20% on 2 Jan), mixed technical signals and a downgrade to Hold tempered enthusiasm, underscoring a cautious market stance amid robust financial performance.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>5d1181f2f8ad7a055ec21476a455a71a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A-1 Ltd Surges 1205.82% in a Week: Key Drivers Behind the Remarkable Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/a-1-ltd-surges-120582-in-a-week-key-drivers-behind-the-remarkable-rally-3779541</link><description>A-1 Ltd delivered an extraordinary weekly performance, soaring 1205.82% from Rs.35.07 to Rs.457.95 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, vastly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.35% gain over the same period. This remarkable rally was marked by a series of significant price milestones, technical momentum shifts, and rating changes that shaped investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>16bacf53ae9c23f477b83ce059d71e92</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Total Gas Ltd Gains 3.11%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-total-gas-ltd-gains-311-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3779540</link><description>Adani Total Gas Ltd closed the week ending 2 January 2026 with a 3.11% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock showed notable volatility and strong intraday rallies, particularly on 1 January, driven by robust trading volumes and mixed technical signals. Despite a recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, the stock’s price momentum and trading activity highlighted a week of significant market interest and dynamic price action.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>125caf319f23bbc7126cfc3fe779692e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axita Cotton Ltd Falls 10.58%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axita-cotton-ltd-falls-1058-3-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-decline-3779539</link><description>Axita Cotton Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 29 Dec 2025 to 2 Jan 2026, ending with a significant 10.58% decline in its stock price, closing at Rs.11.75 from Rs.13.14 the previous Friday. This sharp fall contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period, highlighting company-specific challenges amid broader market resilience. The week featured a new 52-week high, followed by two consecutive sessions where the stock hit its lower circuit limit amid heavy selling pressure and panic among investors.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>de33a500c700e5727c2238620ec98d32</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPI Green Energy Ltd Gains 16.87%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpi-green-energy-ltd-gains-1687-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3779538</link><description>KPI Green Energy Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 16.87% from Rs.416.65 to Rs.486.95 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period. The week was marked by sharp intraday rallies, heavy institutional trading, and mixed technical signals, reflecting a volatile but bullish sentiment amid cautious fundamental assessments.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>87ae50444136cbf75e8ca078c6305d62</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chalet Hotels Ltd Gains 4.22%: 4 Key Technical and Fundamental Developments This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chalet-hotels-ltd-gains-422-4-key-technical-and-fundamental-developments-this-week-3779537</link><description>Chalet Hotels Ltd recorded a 4.22% gain over the week ending 2 Jan 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise. Despite early-week technical setbacks signalling bearish momentum, the stock rebounded strongly in the final sessions, closing at Rs.903.80. This week’s price action was shaped by a mix of technical signals, a downgrade to Sell by MarketsMOJO, and a notable shift in momentum indicators, reflecting a complex market environment for the hospitality sector player.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9e3b7b3663bf1292a48554d59befdba0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kranti Industries Falls 3.57%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kranti-industries-falls-357-3-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3779535</link><description>Kranti Industries Ltd experienced a difficult week from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026, with its share price declining by 3.57% to close at Rs.78.50, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. The stock faced a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid weak fundamentals and bearish technicals, compounded by hitting fresh 52-week lows twice during the week, reflecting sustained investor caution despite some positive quarterly results.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>cf7b6b4579d53f6b7841fdc44f77863a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Osia Hyper Retail Ltd Gains 6.93%: 4 Key Events Driving the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/osia-hyper-retail-ltd-gains-693-4-key-events-driving-the-volatile-week-3779536</link><description>Osia Hyper Retail Ltd delivered a volatile yet strong performance over the week ending 2 Jan 2026, rising 6.93% from Rs.14.57 to Rs.15.58. This outpaced the Sensex’s modest 1.35% gain, driven by three consecutive days of upper circuit hits followed by a sharp lower circuit plunge on the final session. The week was marked by intense buying momentum, regulatory trading halts, and a sudden reversal amid heavy selling pressure, reflecting a complex interplay of speculative interest and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>f1a78414117e59bf0847d558c0f2d491</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Falls 5.70%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rail-vikas-nigam-ltd-falls-570-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3779534</link><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) experienced a turbulent week ending 2 January 2026, with its share price declining by 5.70% from Rs.387.95 to Rs.365.85. This contrasted sharply with the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid mixed market signals, heavy trading volumes, and a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating. The week was marked by significant intraday volatility, active options market positioning, and fluctuating institutional interest, all set against a backdrop of cautious sector sentiment.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>0244ccac714643b5e398155684f6bf5e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBC Exports Ltd: 1.73% Weekly Gain Highlights Key Milestones and Market Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbc-exports-ltd-173-weekly-gain-highlights-key-milestones-and-market-resilience-3779533</link><description>SBC Exports Ltd closed the week unchanged at Rs.28.35, despite a volatile trading session that saw the stock hit a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.28.89 on 2 January 2026. While the broader Sensex advanced 1.35% over the same period, the stock’s sideways weekly performance masks underlying strength demonstrated by its technical positioning and milestone achievements.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>c5472b0e123fc61debdb986dfae9fd47</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seacoast Shipping Services Falls 20.69% Amid All-Time Low and Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/seacoast-shipping-services-falls-2069-amid-all-time-low-and-market-concerns-3779531</link><description>Seacoast Shipping Services endured a challenging week ending 2 January 2026, with its stock price plummeting 20.69% to close at Rs.0.92, marking a new 52-week and all-time low. This sharp decline starkly contrasted with the broader market’s resilience, as the Sensex gained 1.35% over the same period. The stock’s underperformance was driven by a combination of technical weakness, erratic trading patterns, and deteriorating market sentiment, underscored by a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating from MarketsMOJO.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>cc2e86d21732ff4925e2a792f42d5da7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Ltd Gains 1.71%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/360-one-wam-ltd-gains-171-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-momentum-3779532</link><description>360 ONE WAM Ltd closed the week ending 2 January 2026 with a modest gain of 1.71%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock exhibited a volatile week marked by technical momentum shifts, a downgrade to a Hold rating, and a notable surge in derivatives open interest. Despite mixed signals from technical indicators and valuation concerns, the company’s strong fundamentals and active market positioning kept investor interest alive amid a cautious market backdrop.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>f925cc84ae59f1fe7abb6b092011fad4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IIFL Capital Services Ltd Gains 16.95%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iifl-capital-services-ltd-gains-1695-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3779530</link><description>IIFL Capital Services Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 16.95% from ₹325.05 on 29 December 2025 to ₹380.15 on 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.35% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by notable intraday highs, technical momentum shifts, and a downgrade in analyst sentiment reflecting mixed financial signals. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s trajectory during the week and their impact on price action.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>961a76179f34b6df474b88147091ebe0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 03:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>