<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 22.57</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-2257-3855883</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd’s stock price declined sharply to a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.22.57 on 25 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid continued underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2012fce9803a0d3191705e2e97dde7de</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uma Exports Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uma-exports-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3855884</link><description>Uma Exports Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, with its share price touching an intraday low of ₹27.51, just 1.98% above its lowest level of ₹27.25 recorded over the past year. This marks a significant decline for the stock, which has been on a downward trajectory for the last nine consecutive trading sessions, losing 15.91% in returns during this period.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>45c9d1bb29ea583de9e005816f3605e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abbott India Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/abbott-india-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3855882</link><description>Abbott India Ltd. has recently touched a 52-week low, closing just 1.49% above its lowest price point of Rs 26,006.3. This marks a significant moment for the pharmaceutical and biotechnology company as it continues to face headwinds reflected in its stock performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7d18485710c45d17f37a33618f1932e6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integra Essentia Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/integra-essentia-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3855875</link><description>Integra Essentia Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing at ₹1.32 on 25 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent headwinds faced by the FMCG company amid broader market dynamics and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ff3b3988de8f4f5a7bf54aaa7588b61b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Geecee Ventures Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/geecee-ventures-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3855877</link><description>Geecee Ventures Ltd, a player in the Realty sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.284.2, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting ongoing financial pressures and subdued performance metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0e2fcab83823fee0c450cc0d8e00d37c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Landmark Property Development Company Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low on 25 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/landmark-property-development-company-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-on-25-feb-2026-3855879</link><description>Landmark Property Development Company Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures within the realty sector and the company’s financial performance. The stock’s decline to this significant price level underscores a challenging period for the company amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>cc77b18e1bcab7e27a97c28febeb4371</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Country Club Hospitality &amp; Holidays Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/country-club-hospitality-holidays-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3855881</link><description>Shares of Country Club Hospitality &amp; Holidays Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures on the company’s financial performance and market valuation. The stock closed at a new low price, marking a significant downturn over the past year amid subdued growth and profitability concerns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e21c7258e45dd45de269eb01aa280c1e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GSS Infotech Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gss-infotech-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3855876</link><description>Shares of GSS Infotech Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 14.28 on 25 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn for the software and consulting company amid persistent financial headwinds and market underperformance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2d73d0c2576864bd338067a63e38fa27</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RPP Infra Projects Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rpp-infra-projects-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3855878</link><description>RPP Infra Projects Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near Rs 75.16, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained downward trend. The stock’s performance over the past year has been notably weak, reflecting a combination of financial pressures and market dynamics within the construction sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a904319f9b3248b6215b863610dddd81</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asahi Songwon Colors Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.210</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asahi-songwon-colors-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs210-3855880</link><description>Asahi Songwon Colors Ltd, a player in the Dyes and Pigments sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.210 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>27adc359e5997e0246738ada810ec86a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Mild Correction Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-mild-correction-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-3855872</link><description>The mid-cap segment experienced a modest decline on 25 Feb 2026, with the BSE Midcap index slipping 0.42% on the day and registering a sharper 1.81% drop over the past five sessions. Despite this overall softness, select stocks and sectors demonstrated resilience, underscoring a nuanced market environment for mid-caps.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0b7df8aa9ba8d76cd9b43f5321032d35</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Sees Modest Gains Led by Vedanta; Adani Power Lags</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-sees-modest-gains-led-by-vedanta-adani-power-lags-3855874</link><description>The large-cap segment demonstrated a cautiously optimistic performance on 25 Feb 2026, with the BSE 100 index edging up by 0.33% amid a backdrop of selective sectoral strength and stock-specific movements. Vedanta emerged as the standout performer, delivering a robust 4.64% return, while Adani Power struggled, declining 2.57%. The advance-decline ratio of 71 advancing stocks to 29 decliners underscored a broadly positive market breadth within the large-cap universe.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8104d6c10bae42d7c9de0ee3de94c32e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Faces Pressure Amid Mixed Market Signals on 25 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-faces-pressure-amid-mixed-market-signals-on-25-feb-2026-3855873</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index has experienced a modest decline of 0.9% today, extending a recent five-day slide of 2.03%, signalling a cautious phase for the small-cap segment. Despite this, select stocks within the index have delivered notable returns, underscoring a mixed performance landscape marked by sectoral divergences and a narrow advance-decline ratio.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>64bceac58f732e44a55a0d42c5891056</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Ltd Hits Intraday High with 5.29% Surge on 25 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-529-surge-on-25-feb-2026-3855869</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 25 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 2,165.8, marking a 5.47% increase. The stock outpaced the broader Sensex, which recorded a modest 0.06% gain, reflecting significant buying momentum within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5fccd550985cea4c35c589cf185663b8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SpiceJet Ltd Hits Day High with Strong Intraday Surge on 25 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spicejet-ltd-hits-day-high-with-strong-intraday-surge-on-25-feb-2026-3855868</link><description>SpiceJet Ltd witnessed a robust intraday rally on 25 Feb 2026, surging to its day high despite recent downward trends. The airline stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, marking a notable reversal after six consecutive days of decline.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2ac93c19318f0b6a0d9322b65aa0b8d9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Micro and Small Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Half-Year Returns Amid Bullish Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/micro-and-small-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amid-bullish-market-sentiment-3855867</link><description>Titan Biotech, a micro cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has delivered an exceptional return of 173.57% over the past six months, outpacing its peers and the broader market benchmarks by a significant margin. This remarkable performance underscores the stock’s strong fundamentals, bullish technical outlook, and sector-specific catalysts that have driven investor enthusiasm.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c55cfae24a995a3f38c1310ef0376ab9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top-Performing Stocks Deliver Exceptional Returns Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/top-performing-stocks-deliver-exceptional-returns-amid-market-volatility-3855866</link><description>Valiant Communications has delivered an exceptional return of 325.68% over the past year, outpacing key benchmark indices and peers across sectors. This remarkable performance, driven by robust fundamentals and bullish technical indicators, positions the micro-cap telecom equipment player as a standout in a challenging market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ed47133e788ccee491d6e947099798be</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spectrum-electrical-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3855865</link><description>Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 25 Feb 2026, with its stock price touching a low of Rs 1240.15, marking an 11.18% drop. This downturn reflects immediate selling pressure despite a broadly stable market environment, as the stock underperformed its sector and the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>56e9241051daaa163362aa58e8015834</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>