<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>India Shelter Finance Corporation Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-shelter-finance-corporation-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3761563</link><description>India Shelter Finance Corporation, a key player in the housing finance sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4c42a5a124ae7454bc897716e4e8154b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Health Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/global-health-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761562</link><description>Global Health, a prominent player in the hospital sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>54166662486187a3666ff725854e9ee8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NDR Auto Components Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ndr-auto-components-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761560</link><description>NDR Auto Components, a player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a possible weakening in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f399c640689474a0ffdd1b9652c0dae9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharpline Broadcast Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sharpline-broadcast-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761561</link><description>Sharpline Broadcast, a micro-cap player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price movement over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>09e925e9fdb57cf15a2d4226f6c33af0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New India Assurance Company Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/new-india-assurance-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3761559</link><description>New India Assurance Company has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed below the 200-day moving average, a pattern commonly referred to as a Death Cross. This event often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>03760a8e9df23d9c8448dd8b64a27f25</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bombay-dyeing-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761558</link><description>Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b119d5300d069076ee1531f318ec25c5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Fertilisers &amp; Petrochemicals Corp Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-fertilisers-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761557</link><description>Deepak Fertilisers &amp; Petrochemicals Corp has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential weakness in the stock's medium to long-term price momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>57b459489a59dd7e0add31ea9ed841b2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prism Johnson Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prism-johnson-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761549</link><description>Prism Johnson, a player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>799e3e20abe855c36ec21d2b8e56e8e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exide Industries Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/exide-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761548</link><description>Exide Industries, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>eb3f56eec1c9f321c09f99efa04929a9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Newtech Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/creative-newtech-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3761551</link><description>Creative Newtech has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a possible shift in long-term momentum and a potential trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8685436dca53df660d6135413f8f0ac6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aadi Industries Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aadi-industries-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3761550</link><description>Aadi Industries, a player in the petrochemicals sector, has recently witnessed a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed above the 200-day moving average, forming what is commonly known as a Golden Cross. This event is widely regarded by market analysts as a bullish signal, indicating a possible shift in long-term momentum and a potential trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5e8d424240b644735e700aae1ee5dd8b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Overseas Bank Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-overseas-bank-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761552</link><description>Indian Overseas Bank has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>faa2579688f9026e4a362ae64856b5e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gokaldas Exports Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gokaldas-exports-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3761553</link><description>Gokaldas Exports, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend and long-term momentum change, attracting attention from market participants and technical analysts alike.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>96b45fb441456e0a8c109de8e912fe5d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Centrum Capital Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/centrum-capital-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3761547</link><description>Centrum Capital, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>dda06fd15dce555bc7ee2f3f0b8b4f26</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flex Foods Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/flex-foods-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3761555</link><description>Flex Foods, a micro-cap player in the Other Agricultural Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and may indicate a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1587db7a16187379f506ddb5968c1469</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEAMEC Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/seamec-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3761554</link><description>SEAMEC, a key player in the Transport Services sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend and long-term momentum in the stock’s price movement.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8be666692461b6e667228003b53d7985</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trio Mercantile &amp; Trading Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trio-mercantile-trading-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3761556</link><description>Trio Mercantile &amp; Trading, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend and a long-term momentum change for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>95058ceac03a3ff28bba33a29b669bd1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>InfoBeans Technologies Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.799.85</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infobeans-technologies-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs79985-3761505</link><description>InfoBeans Technologies, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, reached a significant milestone today by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.799.85. This achievement marks a notable moment in the stock’s performance, reflecting sustained momentum over the past year.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b9f876ccd8cea5b42613d7de08146103</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3761507</link><description>Dev Information Technology has reached a new 52-week low, with its stock price touching an intraday low of ₹35.44, just 1.43% above its lowest level of ₹35.26 over the past year. This marks a significant point in the stock’s performance as it continues to trade below all major moving averages, reflecting ongoing pressures within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>93d0d49010add213021ddd47234e18f5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>