<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Vivimed Labs Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Indicators</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vivimed-labs-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-indicators-3776540</link><description>Vivimed Labs Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing at ₹17.58 on 31 Dec 2025, marking a significant drop amid subdued financial performance and deteriorating key metrics over the past year.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>120b429340d1d4c7a91cf3a08388c146</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kiri Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 10.13% Surge on 31 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kiri-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1013-surge-on-31-dec-2025-3776539</link><description>Kiri Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 31 Dec 2025, surging 10.13% to touch a day’s high of Rs 666, significantly outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and sustained buying momentum.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>fc9406e63e285d8c4076f03ae1aa11b3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Ltd. Hits Day Low Amidst Price Pressure on 31 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vodafone-idea-ltd-hits-day-low-amidst-price-pressure-on-31-dec-2025-3776538</link><description>Vodafone Idea Ltd. experienced a notable decline today, hitting its day low of Rs. 12.8 as the stock faced significant price pressure. Despite a broader market rally, the telecom services company underperformed its sector and the benchmark Sensex, reflecting immediate selling pressures and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>671397e4fbc4a1fcb256e0a550e32aa3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti Structures Ltd Hits Day High with 7.55% Intraday Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-structures-ltd-hits-day-high-with-755-intraday-surge-3776537</link><description>Jyoti Structures Ltd recorded a robust intraday rally on 31 Dec 2025, surging 7.55% to reach its day high, significantly outperforming the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector and broader market indices.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>a74a95d74af4ae24425508f93ccb2267</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Angel One Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/angel-one-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3776535</link><description>Angel One Ltd, a key player in the capital markets sector, witnessed a notable 10.9% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 31 Dec 2025, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning despite the stock underperforming its sector peers.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>399610a191febdadd52d0ebab8879b05</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Renewed Market Optimism</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-renewed-market-optimism-3776534</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened investor interest and potential shifts in market positioning. This development comes alongside a modest price recovery and increased delivery volumes, suggesting a nuanced change in sentiment within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>fa757c01950bd8b3f8f3ee0fa209d9b5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3776533</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd (SBILIFE) witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, supported by rising volumes and a strong technical setup near its 52-week high.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>95b359535379c1d21cabcc95fc94b788</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canara Bank Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/canara-bank-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-strong-market-momentum-3776532</link><description>Canara Bank has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price strength, coupled with rising volumes and improving technical indicators, suggests growing investor confidence in this public sector banking heavyweight.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>e0d05630d331c3514e04c450eff8241f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Oil Corporation Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-oil-corporation-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3776531</link><description>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd (IOC) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price action, combined with rising volumes and improved investor positioning, underscores a bullish sentiment in the oil sector as the company trades near its 52-week high.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>9c51b9fe1443fe199b7137b42385eead</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-forge-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3776530</link><description>Bharat Forge Ltd. (BHARATFORG), a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This development coincides with the stock hitting a new 52-week high of Rs 1,490.9, reflecting growing bullish sentiment despite a slight underperformance relative to its sector peers.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>676c914359f87c1a556ed6846529571c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi Commodity Exchange Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/multi-commodity-exchange-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3776529</link><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened investor interest and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector peers and the broader Sensex, supported by robust volume and rising investor participation, suggesting a positive shift in market positioning as it nears its 52-week high.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>1bba13b64ee374edb56f013123f04827</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Industries Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-industries-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3776528</link><description>Supreme Industries Ltd, a key player in the Plastic Products - Industrial sector, witnessed a notable 14.1% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 31 Dec 2025, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the company’s Mojo Grade was downgraded from Hold to Sell on 23 Oct 2025, reflecting cautious sentiment amid mixed technical and fundamental indicators.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>af07fae1d697f56c0537674bd2ec4938</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-derivatives-activity-3776526</link><description>Indian Bank has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s robust price performance, coupled with increased volumes and rising investor participation, suggests a growing directional conviction among traders.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f654d512a2d2f1388d28ca0826d629af</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sammaan Capital Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sammaan-capital-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3776527</link><description>Sammaan Capital Ltd, a small-cap player in the housing finance sector, witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 31 Dec 2025, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting increased investor participation and evolving market sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>882a230066e1abfcceae25746307ecfb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3776525</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NATIONALUM) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price action, combined with rising volumes and improved investor positioning, suggests a bullish sentiment taking hold in the non-ferrous metals sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>aa43a016905b2323b14d999c4f5f1150</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Petroleum Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-petroleum-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3776524</link><description>Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd. (HINDPETRO) witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 31 Dec 2025, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock also hit a fresh 52-week high of ₹496, outperforming its sector peers and reflecting robust investor confidence amid rising volumes and positive technical indicators.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>d0cb2343f833c0aa1871c0e38fac1de2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nirman-agri-genetics-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3776518</link><description>Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 31 Dec 2025, registering a robust daily gain of 4.92% and signalling intense buying interest despite subdued investor participation. The stock closed at ₹62.7, near its high of ₹62.9, reflecting strong demand that outpaced supply and triggered a regulatory freeze on further upward price movement.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>42919dba56a4d7cc7b921897b6d03247</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KEI Industries Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kei-industries-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-derivatives-activity-3776519</link><description>KEI Industries Ltd, a prominent player in the Cables - Electricals sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. This development comes as the stock trades near its 52-week high, supported by robust volume and positive price momentum.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>8dde9e2ecb2a64a1b9617dbd6c54afe3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dabur India Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dabur-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-bullish-momentum-3776521</link><description>Dabur India Ltd. has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and shifting investor positioning. This development comes alongside a series of consecutive gains and rising volumes, reflecting growing bullish sentiment despite a cautious overall rating from MarketsMOJO.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>fb5548dd0135bbadcb5017032b4d5442</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/simbhaoli-sugars-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3776517</link><description>Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd witnessed a significant surge in its share price on 31 Dec 2025, hitting the upper circuit limit as strong buying interest propelled the stock to its maximum daily gain. The sugar sector stock demonstrated robust investor participation despite its micro-cap status and a recent downgrade in its mojo grade, reflecting a complex market sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>bf33eea6247931f1dfaa8963887799a4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>