<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Shree Rama Newsprint Q2 FY26: Mounting Losses Deepen as Revenue Plunges 24%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/shree-rama-newsprint-q2-fy26-mounting-losses-deepen-as-revenue-plunges-24-3826269</link><description>Shree Rama Newsprint Ltd., India's largest private sector newsprint manufacturer, reported alarming financial results for Q2 FY26, with net losses widening to ₹7.95 crores despite marginal sequential improvement. The company's revenue collapsed 24.11% year-on-year to ₹6.83 crores, whilst operating margins excluding other income plummeted to a mere 3.22%, signalling severe operational distress in India's beleaguered newsprint sector.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>2968f162ca1fc08df09a442842fea35f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atul Auto Q2 FY26: Strong Quarter Masks Underlying Structural Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/atul-auto-q2-fy26-strong-quarter-masks-underlying-structural-concerns-3826268</link><description>Atul Auto Ltd., the Gujarat-based three-wheeler commercial vehicle manufacturer, reported a robust second quarter for FY2026, with consolidated net profit surging 210.85% quarter-on-quarter to ₹9.17 crores. The impressive sequential recovery, however, masks deeper structural challenges that continue to weigh on the company's long-term investment appeal. Despite the strong quarterly showing, the stock has declined 17.54% over the past year, significantly underperforming the Sensex's 7.07% gain and the automobile sector's 25.74% advance.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>a8ce469018dd78b26caf081b0fb88bf0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surana Telecom Q2 FY26: Sharp Profit Decline Amid Revenue Surge Raises Sustainability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/surana-telecom-q2-fy26-sharp-profit-decline-amid-revenue-surge-raises-sustainability-concerns-3826267</link><description>Surana Telecom and Power Ltd. reported a troubling quarter in Q2 FY26, with consolidated net profit plunging 71.64% sequentially to ₹0.76 crores despite a massive 126.33% surge in revenue. The micro-cap power sector company, with a market capitalisation of ₹242.00 crores, saw its shares trading at ₹17.52, down 40.25% from its 52-week high of ₹29.32, reflecting investor scepticism about earnings quality and operational sustainability.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>8862c44f7f02af24d0bfb76f46880ab3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Confidence Petroleum India Ltd Drops 3.73% Amid Mixed Signals and Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/confidence-petroleum-india-ltd-drops-373-amid-mixed-signals-and-volatility-3826263</link><description>Confidence Petroleum India Ltd’s shares declined by 3.73% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.31.26 from Rs.32.47 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain during the same period, reflecting a challenging week marked by a fresh 52-week low and a sharp gap up rally that failed to sustain momentum.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>5dcc4ec8a10965b509fbe04d5ab0899d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys Ltd Gains 14.01%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-metals-ferro-alloys-ltd-gains-1401-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-surge-3826262</link><description>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 14.01% from Rs.1,166.05 to Rs.1,329.45 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was supported by a series of positive technical upgrades, robust quarterly results, and renewed investor interest amid a recovering ferrous metals sector, despite some short-term margin volatility and valuation concerns.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>8431eca43ad5691abc9290d0494d570d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Gains 8.04%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-forge-gains-804-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3826261</link><description>Bharat Forge Ltd delivered a strong performance in the week ending 6 February 2026, rising 8.04% from Rs.1,440.75 to Rs.1,556.55, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week highs, driven by robust financial results, technical momentum, and increased market interest, despite some profit booking towards the week’s close.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>7463a8451d694b152e948aae6e242ca8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goodyear India Ltd Gains 7.16%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goodyear-india-ltd-gains-716-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3826260</link><description>Goodyear India Ltd’s shares rebounded strongly this week, gaining 7.16% from Rs.787.30 to Rs.843.70, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock’s volatile journey included a fresh 52-week low early in the week, followed by a robust rally capped by a 10.59% intraday surge on Friday, reflecting a mix of financial results, technical shifts, and market sentiment that shaped investor behaviour.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>b498f586cfe597a32216fbd2ca53f5df</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Gains 8.08%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sarda-energy-minerals-gains-808-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3826259</link><description>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Ltd delivered a robust weekly gain of 8.08%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise from 2 to 6 February 2026. The stock’s price advanced from Rs.485.35 to Rs.528.95 amid a backdrop of improved valuation metrics and mixed technical signals, reflecting a complex but cautiously optimistic market sentiment for the ferrous metals company.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>626a80398dc871ff7051f6595b9b0277</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Ltd Falls 9.11%: Earnings and Valuation Shift Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/firstsource-solutions-ltd-falls-911-earnings-and-valuation-shift-shape-the-week-3826258</link><description>Firstsource Solutions Ltd experienced a challenging week on the BSE, closing at Rs.290.25 on 6 February 2026, down 9.11% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.319.35. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid mixed corporate news and valuation adjustments. Key events including the Q3 FY26 earnings release and a valuation reassessment influenced investor sentiment and price action throughout the week.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>fdf900167510369f1aafafe31a55bbd7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanpur Plastipack Gains 12.89%: Key Valuation Shifts and Earnings Drive Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kanpur-plastipack-gains-1289-key-valuation-shifts-and-earnings-drive-momentum-3826257</link><description>Kanpur Plastipack Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 12.89% from Rs.174.10 to Rs.196.55, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s volatile week featured a sharp rebound after an initial decline, driven by a strong quarterly profit report and a favourable valuation reassessment that attracted renewed investor interest.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>e42975dd6c935cfa6f801f8554d579ff</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gallantt Ispat Surges 13.36%: Valuation and Technical Shifts Define the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gallantt-ispat-surges-1336-valuation-and-technical-shifts-define-the-week-3826256</link><description>Gallantt Ispat Ltd delivered a robust weekly gain of 13.36%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise during 2–6 February 2026. The stock’s strong momentum was fuelled by a series of technical shifts, valuation recalibrations, and a rebound in quarterly profitability, all contributing to heightened investor attention despite lingering valuation concerns.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>160899cc07c1e36ffd62c5951eaec96b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Skipper Ltd Gains 7.00%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/skipper-ltd-gains-700-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3826255</link><description>Skipper Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.00% from Rs.361.20 to Rs.386.50 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a significant intraday surge and a notable gap up on 3 February, followed by a mixed technical and fundamental backdrop culminating in a rating downgrade by MarketsMOJO. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s price action and market sentiment during the week.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>cc0bbaa612839088be626c076ccd0809</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sterlite Technologies Ltd Gains 24.60%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sterlite-technologies-ltd-gains-2460-5-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3826253</link><description>Sterlite Technologies Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 24.60% from Rs.106.30 to Rs.132.45 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock exhibited strong intraday volatility, marked by a sharp intraday low on 2 February followed by a robust gap-up and sustained rally on 3 February. Despite a slight pullback on the final trading day, Sterlite Technologies maintained a commanding lead over the benchmark index, reflecting a week of intense market activity and shifting technical momentum.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>3e14e0f049261ade7cad6e23c6d0618b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J Kumar Infraprojects Ltd’s Volatile Week: 0.09% Gain Amid Bearish Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/j-kumar-infraprojects-ltds-volatile-week-009-gain-amid-bearish-technical-signals-3826252</link><description>J Kumar Infraprojects Ltd closed the week with a marginal gain of 0.09%, ending at Rs.570.00 on 6 February 2026, despite a turbulent trading week marked by sharp intraday swings and a pronounced bearish technical outlook. While the Sensex advanced 1.51% over the same period, the stock’s price action reflected mixed momentum signals, a significant 52-week low breach, and a downgrade to a Sell rating, underscoring ongoing challenges amid sector headwinds.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>ae5611f606552e430e73a618f4914de5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nilkamal Ltd Gains 4.99%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nilkamal-ltd-gains-499-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3826251</link><description>Nilkamal Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 4.99% from ₹1,395.40 to ₹1,465.00 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a subtle shift in technical momentum, a strong quarterly financial turnaround, and mixed long-term return metrics that continue to temper investor enthusiasm.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>f9a7d7955b5367032e65c7582403e465</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Terce Laboratories Falls 3.80%: Margin Pressures and Flat Quarterly Results Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-terce-laboratories-falls-380-margin-pressures-and-flat-quarterly-results-weigh-3826250</link><description>Gujarat Terce Laboratories Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its stock price declining by 3.80% from ₹46.00 to ₹44.25, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by disappointing quarterly results and margin pressures that weighed heavily on investor sentiment, despite some intraday recoveries. The stock’s volatility was accentuated by a sharp 5.40% drop on 5 February following the release of flat quarterly performance data, signalling operational headwinds amid a competitive pharmaceutical sector environment.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>ea3521445e3c6d957f66d9a013824e16</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ADF Foods Surges 28.55% in a Week: Key Drivers Behind the Sharp Rebound</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adf-foods-surges-2855-in-a-week-key-drivers-behind-the-sharp-rebound-3826254</link><description>ADF Foods Ltd delivered a remarkable turnaround in the week ending 6 February 2026, surging 28.55% from Rs.176.55 to Rs.226.95, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain. The week was marked by a dramatic recovery from a 52-week low, strong intraday rallies, and technical momentum shifts amid mixed market conditions, reflecting renewed investor interest and volatility in this FMCG stock.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>0a1d3f26a7a9a29c8f82ce03239aea5b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emami Paper Mills Ltd Gains 3.57%: Technical Shifts Amid Persistent Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/emami-paper-mills-ltd-gains-357-technical-shifts-amid-persistent-challenges-3826249</link><description>Emami Paper Mills Ltd recorded a 3.57% gain over the week ending 6 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.87.00, outperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% during the same period. The stock exhibited mixed technical signals with a shift from a strongly bearish to a mildly bearish trend, reflecting cautious optimism despite ongoing financial challenges and operational headwinds.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>41a5e6a5920a05f4364447f3d9adc76d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goyal Associates Ltd Falls 14.14%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goyal-associates-ltd-falls-1414-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3826248</link><description>Goyal Associates Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week, declining 14.14% from ₹0.99 to ₹0.85, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week lows twice amid deteriorating fundamentals, bearish technical signals, and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, underscoring persistent headwinds for the NBFC.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>9b01b6294c0cadb2cb94c1634ca28c84</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaizen Agro Infrabuild Ltd Drops 14.83%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaizen-agro-infrabuild-ltd-drops-1483-3-key-factors-driving-the-decline-3826247</link><description>Kaizen Agro Infrabuild Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 14.83% from Rs.11.26 to Rs.9.59 between 2 and 6 February 2026. This underperformance contrasted sharply with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, reflecting persistent bearish momentum amid operational and valuation pressures. The stock hit fresh 52-week lows twice during the week, underscoring ongoing investor caution despite pockets of financial improvement.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>5e910eda6e1edeee01732ef34937d3a6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>