<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Route Mobile Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/route-mobile-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-underperformance-3845978</link><description>Route Mobile Ltd, a player in the Telecom - Services sector, has witnessed its stock price fall to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers. The stock closed just 0.93% above its 52-week low of ₹530, marking a significant decline over recent years.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>afe4acc0792c6aefedacc7baca18048c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.02% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-company-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-302-surge-3845976</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 18 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 728.6, marking a 3.26% increase. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum amid a positive market environment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>41f56e51dae6114a65c2cf330d8e647c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Ltd Sees Sharp Surge in Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/waaree-energies-ltd-sees-sharp-surge-in-open-interest-amid-mixed-market-signals-3845975</link><description>Waaree Energies Ltd, a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a significant 23.05% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This sudden spike in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and price movements, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets by traders.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>6b824a4004635dd4ff7bee4c6fb53609</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-weak-price-action-3845974</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a major player in the E-Retail sector, has witnessed a significant 18.7% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This spike in open interest, coupled with falling prices and subdued investor participation, suggests a complex positioning landscape with potential bearish bets gaining traction.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>79357138d91be45a1323b4e38d857f07</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3845973</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock recently hit a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs 23,680, supported by robust volume and positive price action, reflecting growing investor confidence in the heavy electrical equipment sector.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>ba67a0e7faaa88aadf84852537f69251</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-prudential-life-insurance-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3845971</link><description>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd (ICICIPRULI) has witnessed a notable 10.19% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.24% gain in the stock price, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and market sentiment within the insurance sector.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>50085ef650dbf15231cf4546d0fd6836</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-lombard-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3845967</link><description>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd (ICICIGI) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and sustained gains over the past three sessions underscore a growing bullish sentiment among investors and traders alike.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>e6ac01d7883c785a167928875dd2683d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge (India) Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3845969</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd (symbol: NAUKRI) has witnessed a notable 13.65% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low of ₹1,096.3 on 18 Feb 2026. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and subdued delivery volumes, suggests a complex interplay of market positioning and directional bets among traders in the e-retail and e-commerce sector.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>60d342c01ca128888c0cbb53ae290bb6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Strong Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-strong-market-positioning-3845972</link><description>Bank Of India (BANKINDIA) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened investor interest and a possible directional shift in market sentiment. The stock hit a new 52-week high of ₹172.9 on 18 Feb 2026, supported by robust volume and rising delivery participation, signalling strong bullish momentum in the public sector banking space.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>de4221dfebbbea50b925d9ad4a39165a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wipro Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wipro-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3845970</link><description>Wipro Ltd. has witnessed a significant 12.78% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and remains close to its 52-week low, reflecting cautious sentiment amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>3b0b8eed1794a6b203d517d68d3f7833</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cummins India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cummins-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3845965</link><description>Cummins India Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s recent price action, coupled with robust volume and rising delivery volumes, suggests a growing bullish sentiment in the compressors, pumps and diesel engines sector.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>b86ed8af9aa41355e47677429d8284d8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Osia Hyper Retail Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/osia-hyper-retail-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3845968</link><description>Shares of Osia Hyper Retail Ltd, a micro-cap player in the retailing sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 18 Feb 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit of 10% and closing at ₹11.39. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid intense selling pressure and panic among investors, marking a significant setback for the company’s market sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>af7ab0803d45eae94b59f0a07df5a683</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd Sees Robust Value Trading Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-sees-robust-value-trading-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3845966</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd (RELIANCE), a heavyweight in the Indian oil sector, demonstrated significant trading activity on 18 Feb 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹578 crore and volume surpassing 40 lakh shares. Despite a modest 1.21% gain on the day, the stock’s technical indicators and institutional participation reveal a nuanced picture for investors navigating the current market environment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>c8689522a8694921c88697ea1588fb82</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dabur India Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dabur-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3845964</link><description>Dabur India Ltd., a prominent FMCG player, has witnessed a notable 14.9% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay between bullish bets and short-term profit-taking.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>5c3d2f156b495b66c7bdb166c593bdfe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nirman-agri-genetics-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3845963</link><description>Shares of Nirman Agri Genetics Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 18 Feb 2026, propelled by strong buying interest and a significant daily gain of 4.92%. The stock closed at ₹59.75, marking a notable outperformance against its sector and the broader Sensex, as investor enthusiasm intensified amid rising delivery volumes and unfilled demand.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>bef4366d5233538360ae947ac9a9fb00</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dj-mediaprint-logistics-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3845959</link><description>Shares of DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 18 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a maximum daily gain of 4.98%. The stock closed at ₹95.50, marking a significant outperformance against its sector and the broader market, despite a backdrop of falling investor participation and high intraday volatility.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>1e5db8ecb84b417973ab78c678a4c95b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3845955</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has wrapped up with 4,079 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced landscape of corporate performance marked by modest improvement in positive earnings surprises and distinct sectoral trends. While mid-cap firms continue to outperform their large-cap counterparts in delivering positive results, the overall market sentiment remains cautious amid mixed profit growth and varied sectoral momentum.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>846b143d77be55ffba7a63e5aa0e81c8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yes Bank Ltd. Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amid Steady Gains and Market Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yes-bank-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amid-steady-gains-and-market-outperformance-3845962</link><description>Yes Bank Ltd. emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 18 Feb 2026, registering a remarkable volume surge that outpaced sector and benchmark indices. Despite a modest price gain, the stock’s trading activity signals a complex interplay of accumulation and distribution, warranting close attention from investors and market analysts alike.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>71202f9a8c45ef34a8675a0f1cfb2bcc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axis Bank Sees Sharp Surge in Open Interest Signalling Increased Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axis-bank-sees-sharp-surge-in-open-interest-signalling-increased-market-positioning-3845960</link><description>Axis Bank Ltd. has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The 16.75% rise in OI, coupled with robust volume and price action near its 52-week high, reflects evolving investor sentiment and positioning in this large-cap private sector bank.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>6ea11b538c8185a0407d93bf1c67df08</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jaiprakash-associates-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3845958</link><description>Shares of Jaiprakash Associates Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 18 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and investor panic. The stock closed at ₹3.23, down 4.42% on the day, marking its maximum permissible daily loss and signalling unfilled supply overwhelming demand.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>784f2c897165eefd0959c0a0c65c3ffa</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>