<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Global Surfaces Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/global-surfaces-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3796941</link><description>Global Surfaces Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>47555a6c34565dfc26291cce728ddc19</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fino-payments-bank-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3796940</link><description>Fino Payments Bank Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average, forming a Death Cross. This event typically signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>092731d868d5f2130fae70874603256c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gamco Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Prolonged Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gamco-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-prolonged-bearish-trend-3796939</link><description>Gamco Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its long-term weakness amid already challenging fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>ef49089964bd3eed8049cb65ad616d13</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TGV Sraac Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tgv-sraac-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3796937</link><description>TGV Sraac Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Commodity Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>7c19b7ec323e47548bdc17f46f04d6da</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Pharmova Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jubilant-pharmova-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3796935</link><description>Jubilant Pharmova Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>0596285294db8e6cbc3111abe644c3d3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Renewables Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-renewables-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3796931</link><description>Borosil Renewables Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s momentum, raising concerns about its near- to medium-term performance prospects.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>964f45ee065094e7405408f41a6e47b5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arman Financial Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arman-financial-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3796934</link><description>Arman Financial Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>8b3e3f799b2efb96af3b2b79bd28e37f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>International Conveyors Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/international-conveyors-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3796932</link><description>International Conveyors Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>6524b98efce8147c577b33984f538c63</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Explosives Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-explosives-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3796936</link><description>Premier Explosives Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>5e50d6b42a4b1dbfd2cc9dff196f58e6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azad India Mobility Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/azad-india-mobility-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3796930</link><description>Azad India Mobility Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raises concerns about its long-term price strength amid already challenging fundamentals and technicals.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>824b89b82a332661655e960125bb60f2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aerpace Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aerpace-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3796933</link><description>Aerpace Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting investor attention despite the stock’s recent mixed performance.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>15510c374241e0ded04797dd7cc5b3d9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shalimar Wires Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shalimar-wires-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3796938</link><description>Shalimar Wires Industries Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift towards long-term upward momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory amid mixed recent performance.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>b11350d01f93949ba4039cc3bdc257a9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends with Mid Caps Leading Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-with-mid-caps-leading-growth-3796929</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a cautiously optimistic picture across Indian equities, with 220 companies reporting results. Positive earnings surprises have increased notably compared to previous quarters, driven primarily by mid-cap stocks, while large caps continue to lag. This report analyses the key trends, sectoral performances, and standout companies shaping the market narrative.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>bf0889cd0550442429ae8d821d0fa74b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Q3 FY26: Strong Revenue Growth Meets Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/persistent-systems-q3-fy26-strong-revenue-growth-meets-margin-pressure-3796945</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd. delivered robust top-line growth in Q3 FY26, with net sales rising 23.38% year-on-year to ₹3,778.21 crores, marking the highest quarterly revenue in the company's history. However, net profit of ₹439.45 crores declined 6.79% sequentially despite growing 17.82% year-on-year, as margin pressures and elevated employee costs weighed on profitability. The stock traded at ₹6,335.50 on January 20, 2026, down 1.56% from the previous close, reflecting investor concerns about the profit decline despite strong revenue momentum.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>1c64be48f6f231932162e39c8c48c407</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zodiac Energy Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zodiac-energy-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3796911</link><description>Zodiac Energy Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.246.9 on 20 Jan 2026, marking a significant drop amid broader market weakness and sectoral pressures. The stock has underperformed its peers and the wider market over the past year, reflecting a challenging period for the construction sector and the company’s valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>818c8f65b3b007bd3781f5eb07954d36</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-instrumentation-gujarat-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-market-downturn-3796913</link><description>Shares of Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd have declined sharply to near their 52-week low, closing at Rs 105.7 on 20 Jan 2026, marking a significant drop of 4.99% on the day and underperforming its sector and the broader market. This marks a continuation of a downward trend that has seen the stock lose over 70% in value over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>10d40fc6edf42bdf566588aec6ce2068</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jash Engineering Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.365.65 Amidst Declining Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jash-engineering-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs36565-amidst-declining-financial-metrics-3796909</link><description>Jash Engineering Ltd, a player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.365.65, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market pressures and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5a694e57615efb5508d1f6a3ba384757</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airan Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.15 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/airan-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs15-amidst-continued-downtrend-3796912</link><description>Airan Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.15 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b7eb5f2a2feec0f9936fab15399dc5ed</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AVG Logistics Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avg-logistics-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3796914</link><description>Shares of AVG Logistics Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 153.55, marking a significant downturn for the transport services company amid broader market weakness and company-specific headwinds.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d7e787b961650d8b7618f5d7cc6de569</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>