<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>HBL Engineering Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/hbl-engineering-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771905</link><description>HBL Engineering Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2ad7dfba3a39367cfd46ea0ff0095cc4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wheels India Ltd. is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/wheels-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3771903</link><description>Wheels India Ltd. is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4b363cb628719e47d63506d0fb798bd7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aether Industries Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aether-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771904</link><description>Aether Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>df206cf54fdb5ddc37a32b846acd3cd9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jio-financial-services-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771900</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Dec 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>821d66b83551eb4b48f4c2230a12f7fa</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ratnaveer-precision-engineering-ltd-is-rated-buy-3771902</link><description>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>404f3134865aeb4e987bd7961f6e5b1a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHI Magnesita India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rhi-magnesita-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771898</link><description>RHI Magnesita India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a52f0a7a07090a3e57fd6f690fe77a76</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cholamandalam-financial-holdings-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771901</link><description>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 15 Dec 2025, reflecting a change from a previous Hold rating. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s position in the market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>27eb0dab4288f2887df6210ba88c3d94</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd. is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/godfrey-phillips-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771897</link><description>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd. is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Dec 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>06d532bdaae31bbf30fd294c5bb323e8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Scott India Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/thomas-scott-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771899</link><description>Thomas Scott India Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the most recent insights into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bd19e44e09d0f997dcca5367f8dbb724</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/prestige-estates-projects-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771896</link><description>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4ab0fe9481e41e9ad02cd40c6778ff25</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kennametal India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kennametal-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771895</link><description>Kennametal India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>96f139f506f5ac5d934e5b77b47a7f05</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Scientific Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/borosil-scientific-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771893</link><description>Borosil Scientific Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 24 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are based on the company’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest comprehensive view of the stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cdd068169db1cd65b6fff59d20f56d87</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BN Agrochem Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bn-agrochem-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771894</link><description>BN Agrochem Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company's fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f6ab7a3c463362bb173e12727a5aaa17</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nureca Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nureca-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3771891</link><description>Nureca Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>949f189d4ab4550c74baec30e691dccd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lloyds Metals &amp; Energy Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/lloyds-metals-energy-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771892</link><description>Lloyds Metals &amp; Energy Ltd is rated Hold by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Dec 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6fbf045324759d140ecb9d5760df9384</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S.A.L Steel Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sal-steel-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3771890</link><description>S.A.L Steel Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Dec 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8b00addb0d0a8c36ab0e8863073c895d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Terminals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/allcargo-terminals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771889</link><description>Allcargo Terminals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 22 December 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the company’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are based on the stock’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date analysis.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>76daba31a1fcfa010ab83c518f57b58d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Escorp Asset Management Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/escorp-asset-management-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771887</link><description>Escorp Asset Management Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0fabfedf1a9f66dab7a9ea344a0dc68d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Control Print Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/control-print-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771886</link><description>Control Print Ltd. is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e1f57cb12b1b3cde9682a0a71c7c03a7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monte Carlo Fashions Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/monte-carlo-fashions-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771888</link><description>Monte Carlo Fashions Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 22 December 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest view of the company’s position in the market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a08e99e6882545ed355c5cf9c81b8820</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>