<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sigachi Industries Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sigachi-industries-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3809577</link><description>Shares of Sigachi Industries Ltd have declined to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. The stock closed just 0.21% above its 52-week low of ₹19.43 on 29 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its downward trajectory.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>5fe022f986975e71652d9f4d6460ed92</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D.P. Abhushan Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amidst Significant Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dp-abhushan-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amidst-significant-price-pressure-3809576</link><description>Shares of D.P. Abhushan Ltd, a key player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, declined sharply today, touching an intraday low of Rs 1191.4. The stock underperformed the broader market and its sector peers, reflecting sustained selling pressure and a challenging trading environment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6801bf31b64fdd3eb4424c01e9bff0fb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ramco Systems Ltd Hits Intraday High with 9.3% Surge on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ramco-systems-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-93-surge-on-29-jan-2026-3809574</link><description>Ramco Systems Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 29 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 457.3, marking a 7.71% rise during the session and closing with an impressive 9.3% gain. This strong upward movement outpaced the broader Software Products sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum despite a generally subdued market environment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>31c77326b6680ed75de095ba919ad609</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.56% Surge on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eclerx-services-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-756-surge-on-29-jan-2026-3809575</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 29 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 4,813.65, marking an 8.88% rise from its previous close. The stock closed with a notable gain of 7.56%, significantly outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and sustained buying momentum.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>e70a7debedd5edfba20b265d2edfca89</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3809572</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent outperformance against its sector and sustained gains over the past three sessions have attracted heightened attention from traders and investors alike.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>03633b88c9cd8cdaca41c7772320b906</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rail-vikas-nigam-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3809573</link><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 29 Jan 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices, the sharp 34.3% increase in open interest alongside rising volumes suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and hedging strategies among traders.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>02e2252c0e4e40ef8b77b34d801c6c41</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ABB India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/abb-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-rally-3809571</link><description>ABB India Ltd, a heavyweight in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This development comes amid a volatile trading session where the stock outperformed its sector peers and posted robust gains over consecutive days.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>5b0e938d2bc708b4cbfc938b878045bc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canara Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/canara-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3809570</link><description>Canara Bank (CANBK) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market interest and a potential shift in investor sentiment. The stock hit a new 52-week high of ₹160.79 on 29 Jan 2026, supported by sustained buying momentum and improving technical indicators, signalling a bullish outlook in the near term.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>1f53ef4d1e749213344e408878b8436c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cyber Media Research &amp; Services Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cyber-media-research-services-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3809566</link><description>Cyber Media Research &amp; Services Ltd witnessed a robust surge in its share price on 29 Jan 2026, hitting the upper circuit limit of 5%, closing at ₹71.30. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, resulting in a maximum daily gain of 4.93%, significantly outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>2e452a7dd27c8ca6065b28906d3a6188</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/multi-commodity-exchange-of-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3809569</link><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened investor participation and a potential shift in market sentiment. The stock has not only hit a new 52-week high of Rs 2,705 but also outperformed its sector and broader indices, signalling strong bullish momentum.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>d481b952c95c843244d4e891f5ad9f47</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhucon Projects Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhucon-projects-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3809568</link><description>Madhucon Projects Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 29 Jan 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.59%. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest despite the stock trading below all key moving averages, signalling a potential trend reversal after two consecutive days of decline.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>3fb23071fcb228e59a4f7ec89004f8f1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Communications Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-communications-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3809567</link><description>Shares of Reliance Communications Ltd (RCom) tumbled sharply on 29 Jan 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit of ₹1.07 after enduring intense selling pressure throughout the trading session. The stock recorded a maximum daily loss of 4.46%, underperforming its sector and the broader market as panic selling gripped investors amid unfilled supply and deteriorating sentiment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>89abddfc96406594a8b60539e5f3f4fb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3809564</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NATIONALUM) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price action, coupled with robust volume and improving fundamentals, suggests a strong bullish sentiment among investors and traders alike.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>7cfc7c876239d9758f7ea583487c8db3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-rally-3809565</link><description>Oil India Ltd. (OIL) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock has concurrently hit a new 52-week high of ₹520, outperforming its sector and demonstrating strong bullish momentum over recent sessions.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>704b6549c5a2473e736880ac4b02f745</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sri Adhikari Brothers Television Network Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sri-adhikari-brothers-television-network-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3809562</link><description>Shares of Sri Adhikari Brothers Television Network Ltd (SABTN) plunged to their lower circuit limit on 29 Jan 2026, closing at ₹1,737.2, down 5.0% on the day. The stock witnessed intense selling pressure, with panic selling and unfilled supply dominating trade, marking a fourth consecutive day of decline and a cumulative loss of 18.41% over this period.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>643e834789471c51d3b07d6807acde75</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modi Rubber Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/modi-rubber-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3809563</link><description>Modi Rubber Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Tyres &amp; Rubber Products sector, witnessed a robust rally on 29 Jan 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit of 5%, closing at ₹118.26. This surge was driven by intense buying interest, resulting in the stock outperforming its sector and broader market indices despite subdued investor participation and a regulatory freeze on further trades.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>ee3c24712af6108179b90c6c2352cf23</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Gradual Improvement Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-gradual-improvement-across-market-caps-3809552</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a cautious but discernible improvement in corporate profitability across India’s stock market, with 52.0% of the 600 companies reporting positive results. This marks a steady rise from the previous quarters, reflecting a gradual recovery in business conditions despite ongoing macroeconomic challenges.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>b836558f633b1979ce3eecfce267b65f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winsome Yarns Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/winsome-yarns-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3809560</link><description>Shares of Winsome Yarns Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 29 Jan 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors. The stock closed at ₹1.64, down 1.8% on the day, marking a maximum daily loss and signalling a challenging phase for the company amid subdued market sentiment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>14b34855509ba941c1aa202555ccbc8f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Sees Heavy Put Option Activity Amid Bearish Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-sees-heavy-put-option-activity-amid-bearish-market-sentiment-3809558</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector, has witnessed a notable spike in put option trading, signalling increased bearish positioning among investors ahead of the 24 February 2026 expiry. The surge in activity at the ₹3,300 strike price, combined with the stock’s recent underperformance and technical weakness, suggests heightened hedging and cautious sentiment in the market.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a2f71b13f2dfd1cbf8f44fbab4b40c52</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NMDC Ltd Surges on Exceptional Volume Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nmdc-ltd-surges-on-exceptional-volume-amid-strong-market-momentum-3809561</link><description>NMDC Ltd, a leading player in the Minerals &amp; Mining sector, has witnessed a remarkable surge in trading volume and price momentum, signalling renewed investor interest and positive market sentiment. The stock’s recent upgrade to a 'Buy' rating, coupled with robust volume metrics and technical strength, positions it as a key focus for market participants amid a mixed broader market backdrop.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>587e7d2778ab86caf983453ff55ced52</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>