<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prime Focus Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.74% Surge on 5 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prime-focus-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-874-surge-on-5-feb-2026-3822629</link><description>Prime Focus Ltd surged to a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs 275.65 on 5 Feb 2026, marking a robust intraday performance with an 8.74% gain. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and sustained buying interest.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>f53cbe09616211a89d532cc43bdcc761</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cummins India Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.0% Surge on 5 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cummins-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-50-surge-on-5-feb-2026-3822627</link><description>Cummins India Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 5 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 4,420.6, marking a 5.23% increase from its previous close. This performance stands out amid a broadly negative market backdrop, with the stock outperforming its sector and the Sensex index.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>8c81fa25b7e8d777a244814d201df21a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sakar Healthcare Ltd Reports Outstanding Quarterly Performance, Upgrades Financial Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sakar-healthcare-ltd-reports-outstanding-quarterly-performance-upgrades-financial-trend-3822628</link><description>Sakar Healthcare Ltd has delivered an exceptional quarterly performance for the December 2025 quarter, prompting an upgrade in its financial trend rating from positive to outstanding. The pharmaceutical and biotechnology company has demonstrated robust revenue growth, margin expansion, and improved capital efficiency, signalling a strong turnaround and enhanced investor confidence.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>78f6ee462246bdcad904d0b66ebbbcff</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaynes Technology India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaynes-technology-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3822626</link><description>Kaynes Technology India Ltd (KAYNES) witnessed a significant 15.08% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment on 5 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of directional bets and volatility in the industrial manufacturing space.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>d605dda8a3ceb325d7fe3909eb0224b3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-market-volatility-3822623</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd (POLICYBZR) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices on 5 Feb 2026, reflecting renewed investor interest despite a prevailing cautious outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>760ceca8c05dd01e53c25b746d96ef6b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3822624</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd, the parent company of NYKAA, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock has outperformed its sector peers and continues to attract investor attention amid a backdrop of strong price momentum and improving technical indicators.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>b036bb336ef10760de33b128a5ac79c4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Terrain Fashions Ltd Reports Very Positive Quarterly Financial Performance Amid Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-terrain-fashions-ltd-reports-very-positive-quarterly-financial-performance-amid-market-challenges-3822625</link><description>Indian Terrain Fashions Ltd has delivered a very positive financial performance in the December 2025 quarter, marking significant improvements across key metrics such as net sales, operating profit margins, and earnings per share. Despite this strong quarterly showing, the company’s longer-term stock returns continue to lag behind the broader market benchmarks, reflecting ongoing challenges in sustaining growth momentum.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>c2959f5fb59b6b5d9b13797b5536de64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3822620</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting a shift in market sentiment and positioning. The 13.6% increase in OI alongside robust volume activity suggests investors are taking fresh directional bets amid the stock’s outperformance of its sector and broader indices.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>14aebd2f7851dd138617cb78e0fe93f8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3822621</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd., a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a notable 14.03% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>a6636d22587641a34d094db7a7052723</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-dynamics-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-momentum-3822618</link><description>Bharat Dynamics Ltd (BDL), a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defence sector, has witnessed a notable 10.02% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s continued price weakness. This spike in OI, coupled with subdued investor participation and falling prices, suggests a complex market positioning scenario with potential directional bets emerging ahead of upcoming catalysts.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>16bcb6d2078d104414a61e9762fabc7d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Oil Corporation Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-oil-corporation-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3822617</link><description>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd (IOC) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This development coincides with the stock hitting a new 52-week high and outperforming its sector, reflecting robust bullish sentiment and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>31befe5d08c05b6b0dd865b6eb3cc74a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uno Minda Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Shifts in Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uno-minda-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-shifts-in-market-positioning-3822622</link><description>Uno Minda Ltd (UNOMINDA), a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, witnessed a significant 30.7% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 5 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This increase comes alongside a 2.55% rise in the stock price, outperforming its sector and broader indices, yet accompanied by mixed volume and delivery trends that suggest cautious optimism among traders.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>0e5c7d4fc8ff20770cdb2e064be70bcb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-holdings-investment-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3822619</link><description>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd (BAJAJHLDNG) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, with a 29.38% increase to 9,403 contracts from 7,268 previously. This spike, coupled with rising volumes and nuanced price action, signals evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders, despite the stock hovering close to its 52-week low.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>e7e542424b533ed22a80fc2f548ea816</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lupin-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3822616</link><description>Lupin Ltd., a leading player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market interest and potential directional bets. The stock recently hit a new 52-week high of Rs 2,244.5, supported by robust volume and positive price momentum, reflecting growing investor confidence despite a backdrop of subdued sectoral performance.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>c610b22968c793fb0d152674a8a0c3ca</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suzlon Energy Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suzlon-energy-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3822612</link><description>Suzlon Energy Ltd (SUZLON), a key player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, witnessed a significant 10.97% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 5 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of directional bets and market sentiment.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>4f08b3a797634f50c1e9314c931df00a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cummins India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cummins-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3822615</link><description>Cummins India Ltd. has witnessed a significant 15.22% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving positioning among traders. Despite a volatile trading session marked by an opening gap down and intraday swings, the stock has maintained a strong technical footing, trading above all major moving averages and nearing its 52-week high. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and price action, offers valuable insights into potential directional bets and investor sentiment in the compressors, pumps and diesel engines sector.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>8b7d24a94c8c513aa68145b9e153adb2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3822605</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 1,295 companies declared results revealing a modest improvement in positive earnings surprises. While mid-cap stocks continue to outperform with a 53.0% beat rate, large caps lag behind at 36.0%, underscoring a divergence in corporate profitability and investor sentiment heading into 2026.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>c8fdfec9bed30ea425d1af7d1cd537a5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filatex Fashions Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/filatex-fashions-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-amid-mixed-price-action-3822611</link><description>Filatex Fashions Ltd (FILATFASH), a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 5 Feb 2026, registering a remarkable volume of 2.79 crore shares. Despite a stagnant price movement, the surge in trading activity signals heightened investor interest amid a broader market downturn, with the Sensex and sector indices declining by 0.56% and 1.09% respectively.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>6a7bccb527ea18e767d645faab24b6a2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gretex-corporate-services-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3822609</link><description>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd, a micro-cap player in the capital markets sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 5 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a significant intraday price rally. The stock outperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting heightened investor enthusiasm despite a backdrop of subdued delivery volumes and regulatory trading restrictions.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>23546b11316db077d40e79be712a189f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jubilant-foodworks-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3822608</link><description>Jubilant Foodworks Ltd (JUBLFOOD) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock has outperformed its sector peers, gaining nearly 6% in a single day, while open interest rose by almost 12%, reflecting increased speculative interest and potential directional bets.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>c5ddaccbf4c64c531060f5242697c35f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>