<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is EMA Partners India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ema-partners-india-ltd-fallingrising-3825458</link><description>On 06-Feb, EMA Partners India Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, falling by 7.46% to close at ₹85.00. This decline reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>907f8056c95583fe43a1bc712e6647a2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Tata Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tata-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3825457</link><description>On 06-Feb, Tata Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹617.50, down ₹24.95 or 3.88%. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends driven by disappointing financial results and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d447186809fc5cb752d9671340855635</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dollex Agrotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dollex-agrotech-ltd-fallingrising-3825456</link><description>On 06-Feb, Dollex Agrotech Ltd's stock price fell sharply by 6.26% to ₹34.45, reflecting mounting concerns over its deteriorating financial performance and elevated leverage, despite some long-term growth indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9e3be597e656a2aa544fa0043788018e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gayatri-rubbers-and-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3825455</link><description>On 06-Feb, Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.99% to ₹418.90 by 09:12 PM. This upward movement reflects a robust short-term performance that significantly outpaces broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ef59997a7b9518779ce3fbd1d1a769a0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nazara Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nazara-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3825454</link><description>On 06-Feb, Nazara Technologies Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.14% to close at ₹260.00. This drop comes amid a series of mixed financial indicators and market pressures that have weighed on investor sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3447b6bc539585202957c5cac1510206</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solara-active-pharma-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3825453</link><description>On 06-Feb, Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 10.1% to close at ₹471.20. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends driven by weak financial performance, deteriorating investor confidence, and underwhelming market returns relative to benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7c6276ee7c84e9349486682ba58fccc7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omega Interactive Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omega-interactive-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3825452</link><description>On 06-Feb, Omega Interactive Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹52.80 with a gain of ₹2.52 or 5.02%. This upward movement reflects sustained investor enthusiasm and outperformance relative to key benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>450b3a29280358331bba3308be99015f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solex Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solex-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3825451</link><description>On 06 Feb, Solex Energy Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 8.13%, closing at ₹1,002.30, reflecting a strong intraday performance driven by heightened investor participation and outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>180fe21e7506d4faf8eb29a88710e628</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gloster Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gloster-ltd-fallingrising-3825450</link><description>On 06-Feb, Gloster Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 5.47%, closing at ₹590.60, reflecting a continuation of recent downward momentum and underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f72479a8b2a15f50d5be378aaec8a5fa</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aspira Pathlab &amp; Diagnostics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aspira-pathlab-diagnostics-ltd-fallingrising-3825449</link><description>On 06 Feb, Aspira Pathlab &amp; Diagnostics Ltd witnessed a significant uptick in its share price, closing at ₹66.87, up ₹4.05 or 6.45% from the previous close. This rise outpaced both the broader market and its sector peers, reflecting a strong performance in the context of recent trading activity and technical indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>04408a1af86730ec3f17d1cd78073329</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Lexus Granito (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-lexus-granito-india-ltd-fallingrising-3825448</link><description>On 06-Feb, Lexus Granito (India) Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 12.33%, closing at ₹26.97. This sharp rise comes despite the company’s challenging long-term fundamentals and recent underperformance against market benchmarks, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term positive results and market sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b4db66856d5c29b56d961ca6c2e1d97c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Suryalata Spinning Mills Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-suryalata-spinning-mills-ltd-fallingrising-3825447</link><description>On 06-Feb, Suryalata Spinning Mills Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹348.00 with an increase of ₹6.65 or 1.95%. This upward movement reflects a broader trend of outperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, supported by rising investor participation and positive technical indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>36e60d88191f890cd035aca10eb65297</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rander Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rander-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3825446</link><description>On 06-Feb, Rander Corporation Ltd's stock price fell by 1.92% to close at ₹10.73, continuing a recent downward trend driven by subdued investor participation and consistent underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d2be7f316d9c5005c5bd64dcb3bdd5ef</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is LTI Mindtree Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-lti-mindtree-ltd-fallingrising-3825445</link><description>On 06-Feb, LTI Mindtree Ltd's stock price fell by 2.26% to close at ₹5,556.50, continuing a downward trend over recent sessions amid valuation pressures and relative underperformance compared to key benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8803af5858e886f67ddedeb8b334277c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Disa India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-disa-india-ltd-fallingrising-3825444</link><description>On 06-Feb, Disa India Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 10.33%, closing at ₹13,645.00, driven by robust quarterly financial performance and notable outperformance against both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>40955a3e2dc71a02da5e74fe95b682d8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-iris-regtech-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3825443</link><description>On 06-Feb, IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling 5.92% to close at ₹246.35. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid broader sector weakness and valuation pressures despite the company’s strong profit growth.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>03800742cb9906b8b6f98f926dcc7d66</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jagan Lamps Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jagan-lamps-ltd-fallingrising-3825440</link><description>On 06-Feb, Jagan Lamps Ltd recorded a modest rise in its share price, closing at ₹64.65 with a gain of ₹0.84 or 1.32%. This increase comes despite the company’s prolonged underperformance relative to key benchmarks and persistent fundamental weaknesses.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0628ab4dbdb0d8667f9416f2d7bad7b3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Emerald Leisures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-emerald-leisures-ltd-fallingrising-3825439</link><description>On 06-Feb, Emerald Leisures Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹192.50, down ₹2.70 or 1.38% from the previous close. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s recent underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>648679c5e5e6ae37cd880dedc00f976d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Suven Life Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-suven-life-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3825438</link><description>As of 06-Feb, Suven Life Sciences Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 2.97% to ₹160.30, continuing a downward trend over the past two days. Despite strong longer-term returns, the recent decline reflects mounting concerns over the company’s deteriorating financial health and weak operational performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1e095762c66f6ef37da2cd786d35e589</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rishi Laser Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rishi-laser-ltd-fallingrising-3825437</link><description>On 6 February, Rishi Laser Ltd’s stock price rose by 3.79% to close at ₹130.00, marking a notable outperformance relative to its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b1e113d894dbf251430f6df78f0c0115</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>