<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Arkade Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arkade-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3836237</link><description>As of 12-Feb, Arkade Developers Ltd’s stock price has declined by 2.07% to ₹120.80, continuing a downward trend that reflects both short-term underperformance and longer-term challenges relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ca4a48e4fa30a7013ed3dda8845d6c5b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3836236</link><description>On 12-Feb, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.45% to close at ₹26.00. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>11deb5480e82413ae30faa502af854ba</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nova Agritech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nova-agritech-ltd-fallingrising-3836235</link><description>On 12-Feb, Nova Agritech Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 9.71% to close at ₹31.05, continuing a sustained downward trajectory that has seen the share price lose significant ground over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1a0c81abf19059ca5d6840143c3f2c39</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Yatra Online Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-yatra-online-ltd-fallingrising-3836234</link><description>On 12-Feb, Yatra Online Ltd's stock price rose sharply by 10.68% to ₹166.35, reflecting robust investor confidence driven by strong financial performance and significant market outperformance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d37a49b89a8cc7fe63777baa1cb0487a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-fallingrising-3836233</link><description>As of 12-Feb, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd’s stock price has experienced a notable decline, falling 1.06% to ₹1,309.00. This movement reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to benchmarks and sector peers, driven by a combination of valuation pressures, recent flat earnings, and market sentiment surrounding promoter share pledges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>18a41ae53bb7ebce7c749d615a267d7b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is eMudhra Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-emudhra-ltd-fallingrising-3836232</link><description>As of 12-Feb, eMudhra Ltd's stock price has declined by 2.29% to ₹501.40, continuing a downward trend despite the company’s robust financial performance and healthy long-term growth metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d1b89806f134621dc779b5ed9d079bb1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Acutaas Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-acutaas-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3836231</link><description>On 12-Feb, Acutaas Chemicals Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹2,100.00 with a gain of ₹69.6 or 3.43%. This upward movement reflects the company’s robust financial performance and sustained market outperformance relative to benchmarks and peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>048e9b436a65238a7a113dbefb84bd7c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nuvoco Vistas Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nuvoco-vistas-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3836230</link><description>On 12-Feb, Nuvoco Vistas Corporation Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.82% to close at ₹346.50. This downward movement reflects a combination of weak long-term fundamentals, disappointing recent quarterly results, and subdued investor participation, despite some attractive valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>95dedf4797d548aef86f72a22afc312f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-affordable-robotic-automation-ltd-fallingrising-3836229</link><description>On 12-Feb, Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 2.59% to close at ₹205.00. This drop followed a three-day rally and came amid a broader context of mixed performance against market benchmarks and sector trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>825009aa477223ef687fe1c568129d32</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Hardwyn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hardwyn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3836228</link><description>On 12-Feb, Hardwyn India Ltd's stock price rose by 1.65% to ₹17.25, outperforming its sector and the broader market benchmarks, reflecting a combination of positive technical indicators and relative strength despite some recent volume decline.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>01f02b0a7fe2a369a1bfa20b9383f1e0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-fallingrising-3836227</link><description>On 12-Feb, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹58.86 with a gain of ₹2.79 or 4.98%. This upward movement reflects a significant positive shift in investor sentiment despite some underlying challenges in trading patterns and technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cf50afd90dbafa227244163217526a58</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Beta Drugs Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-beta-drugs-ltd-fallingrising-3836226</link><description>On 12-Feb, Beta Drugs Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹1,344.30, down by ₹9.20 or 0.68%. This drop reflects a continuation of underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4967b8aeb3ef1250eade39051e34ea5a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ascom-leasing-investments-ltd-fallingrising-3836225</link><description>On 12-Feb, Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, reaching a fresh 52-week high of ₹180.00, reflecting a 2.86% increase or ₹5.00 gain by 9:05 PM. This upward momentum is supported by robust returns across multiple timeframes and technical indicators signalling sustained strength.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9ed98f979f42bd7136e9eeb6af3ec4a9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Parin Enterprises Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-parin-enterprises-ltd-fallingrising-3836224</link><description>On 12-Feb, Parin Enterprises Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹690.00, up ₹19.25 or 2.87% from the previous close. This upward movement reflects a continuation of the stock’s robust performance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d54842bcf5ab04da7c49034eb301f95c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dhruv-consultancy-services-ltd-fallingrising-3836223</link><description>On 12-Feb, Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd experienced a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 15.24% to close at ₹28.82. This drop marks a continuation of a downward trend that has seen the stock underperform significantly against benchmark indices and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c024f9909e9bba494003bb7c6a08d3b7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-indo-rama-synthetics-india-ltd-fallingrising-3836222</link><description>On 12-Feb, Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd experienced a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.69% to close at ₹37.51. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dc4e0bea7975b80c795a957608df20d1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Creative Newtech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-creative-newtech-ltd-fallingrising-3836221</link><description>On 12-Feb, Creative Newtech Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹650.05, down ₹25.95 or 3.84% from the previous close. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends, with the stock nearing its 52-week low and underperforming both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6bb3b43b4283e06cf57b5246d8b68f00</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is IGC Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-igc-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3836220</link><description>On 12 Feb, IGC Industries Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 9.79% to close at ₹2.58. This drop comes despite the stock’s positive returns over recent weeks and months, highlighting a complex interplay of market factors influencing investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6e3a95e44494874e17ea83ce5f9eaa50</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enkei Wheels India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enkei-wheels-india-ltd-fallingrising-3836219</link><description>On 12-Feb, Enkei Wheels India Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹440.40, down ₹26.55 or 5.69% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>55060a3cb53b7eb0d8850b877b8c8ac6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Usha Martin Education &amp; Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-usha-martin-education-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3836218</link><description>On 12-Feb, Usha Martin Education &amp; Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 6.61% to close at ₹4.66. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, signalling ongoing challenges for the stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fab2cd0b87509931e5ce1054c79cd16f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>