<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Data Patterns (India) Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.3270</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/data-patterns-india-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs3270-3858338</link><description>Data Patterns (India) Ltd, a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.3270. This marks a remarkable rally for the stock, reflecting strong momentum and robust market performance over the past year.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>aa041d3aeeb8fef68a2d7843faf1f352</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atam Valves Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/atam-valves-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3858334</link><description>Atam Valves Ltd, a player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.62.17 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial pressures and market headwinds. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting a challenging period for the company.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>5ee8d5b1fa8a7023289f0d6f85f6d2dd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.120.75</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-jammu-kashmir-bank-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs12075-3858337</link><description>The Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd. has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.120.75, marking a notable surge in its stock price amid a period of sustained momentum and robust market performance.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>58c7f1d380fb403c589b6674926dd602</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Primo Chemicals Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.18.91 Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/primo-chemicals-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1891-amid-continued-underperformance-3858329</link><description>Primo Chemicals Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.18.91 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. The stock’s recent trajectory reflects a combination of subdued financial results and market pressures within the commodity chemicals industry.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>cc4041f5d1adf54e696972eb06798680</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs 8,173.3 on 26 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eicher-motors-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs-81733-on-26-feb-2026-3858336</link><description>Eicher Motors Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.8173.3 today, reflecting robust momentum in the stock’s performance amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>5401c028aa6b0122d719e5db3850a26e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashima Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.14.59 Amid Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashima-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1459-amid-weak-financial-metrics-3858328</link><description>Ashima Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed its stock price decline sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.14.59 today, marking a significant downturn amid subdued financial performance and broader market pressures.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>fc72dbafae4e4b014e03de8aa2ba3027</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.5.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/last-mile-enterprises-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs58-3858332</link><description>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.5.8 today, marking a significant decline amid sustained downward momentum. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>eaf37393a6e1beb78a367018b4114d8b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alphageo (India) Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.197.6</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alphageo-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs1976-3858330</link><description>Alphageo (India) Ltd’s stock declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.197.6 today, marking a significant downturn as the oil sector company continues to face headwinds reflected in its financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>3daf32041e1bde98c111561153e4e552</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Syngene International Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.426.25</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/syngene-international-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs42625-3858331</link><description>Syngene International Ltd’s stock declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.426.25 today, marking a significant downturn amid sustained underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. The stock has now recorded a three-day consecutive fall, losing 4.55% over this period, and continues to trade below all key moving averages, reflecting persistent market pressures.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>2c878a3941d7a6fd727c4bf55c93f453</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alankit Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.8.7 Amidst Weak Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alankit-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs87-amidst-weak-performance-3858335</link><description>Alankit Ltd, a player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.8.7 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>77bce99818f7552f43df8b39d1c90f27</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSL Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.900 Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsl-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs900-amidst-continued-underperformance-3858333</link><description>JSL Industries Ltd, a player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.900 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid persistent underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>23349007ced0995e5d0c1e429c7fb32f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parag Milk Foods Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.12% Surge on 26 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/parag-milk-foods-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-712-surge-on-26-feb-2026-3858325</link><description>Parag Milk Foods Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 26 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 209.7, marking an 8.57% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its FMCG sector peers and the broader market, registering a notable 7.12% gain during the trading session amid heightened volatility.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>90cecfbfe284a41fe0d2b7ee0e6e6c99</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Poly Films Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 26 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-poly-films-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-26-feb-2026-3858321</link><description>Jindal Poly Films Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 26 Feb 2026, with its share price falling sharply to an intraday low of Rs 593.3, marking a 7.38% drop from the previous close. This downturn reflects immediate price pressures and a shift in market sentiment despite the stock’s recent positive momentum.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>a200cd09ca7dbb2f9f79f0b4b643ca84</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3858324</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd (MANKIND) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, supported by robust volume and delivery trends, as investors recalibrate their directional bets amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>cc4290831aa4586486430029b487d1b3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Angel One Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/angel-one-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3858323</link><description>Angel One Ltd, a key player in the capital markets sector, witnessed a significant 15.18% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 26 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader benchmarks, reflecting a complex interplay of volume patterns and bearish technical cues.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>11767102d92a1d0240b92cf93688911c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KFin Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kfin-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-action-3858320</link><description>KFin Technologies Ltd (KFINTECH), a small-cap player in the Capital Markets sector, witnessed a notable 10.66% rise in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 26 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in OI, coupled with declining prices and subdued investor participation, suggests a complex interplay of positioning and sentiment among traders.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>fa07e12fede09b86cd86de2f6a02690e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tube-investments-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3858322</link><description>Tube Investments of India Ltd (TIINDIA) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, supported by a 21.8% rise in open interest and robust volume patterns, reflecting renewed investor confidence and evolving market positioning.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>18d5719b6a40e24fc356eba8bf20a962</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Increased Derivative Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bandhan-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-increased-derivative-market-activity-3858318</link><description>Bandhan Bank Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market interest and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price momentum, combined with a 12.17% increase in open interest, reflects evolving market positioning that investors and traders should carefully analyse.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>a98e54f8e4291874395db4e45e4c0f3f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortis Healthcare Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fortis-healthcare-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3858319</link><description>Fortis Healthcare Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s recent outperformance against its sector and the broader Sensex, coupled with rising volumes and delivery volumes, suggests growing bullish sentiment among traders and investors alike.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>8bf10a31ea2fe1d220e7cf7df51de2e2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Page Industries Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/page-industries-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3858317</link><description>Page Industries Ltd, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has witnessed a notable 10.3% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance and proximity to its 52-week low. This development reflects evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders, warranting a closer examination of volume patterns, price trends, and investor sentiment.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7f5e5e0376142b8e83fde13d3a74ffc0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>