<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Vijay Solvex Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vijay-solvex-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768499</link><description>Vijay Solvex Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 October 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>a2c14a749a01adee3a5bca4342abfaef</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unison Metals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/unison-metals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768496</link><description>Unison Metals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 01 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest view on the company’s position in the market.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>32b5aa591de3b63375231a4e80e106fc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aptus-value-housing-finance-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768492</link><description>Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 08 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position in the market.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>d8b4ff95267ee0a000e6421c1a7ff3fb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multibase India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/multibase-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768494</link><description>Multibase India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>e48fd2608d9df79c45f9d9500c616822</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>M K Proteins Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/m-k-proteins-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3768488</link><description>M K Proteins Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>962de1974dd2d97976a460ca0c90de52</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid East Portfolio Management Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mid-east-portfolio-management-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768493</link><description>Mid East Portfolio Management Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 01 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>2163eb8155190d786cd313b0e0b42aec</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Syschem (India) Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/syschem-india-ltd-is-rated-buy-3768491</link><description>Syschem (India) Ltd is rated Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>0790fbd34fb50392e72781b02c3e7b50</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sinclairs Hotels Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sinclairs-hotels-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768490</link><description>Sinclairs Hotels Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 02 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest view of the company’s position in the market.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>339c0947733cec66fdae8ae77349f77f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liberty Shoes Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/liberty-shoes-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3768486</link><description>Liberty Shoes Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>6a9dacca53112d7e151223bd81f7ffad</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aveer Foods Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aveer-foods-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768487</link><description>Aveer Foods Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>ec924d8db47f01125da3cb82b154dd43</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/last-mile-enterprises-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768489</link><description>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>c4d5c1da4774d2490b8067b47e345eee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veritas (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/veritas-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768482</link><description>Veritas (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>78b6bdf8a3f65e1fd0396c790ad6ba0c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BMW Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bmw-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768484</link><description>BMW Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>75f84d3c1331dda115689692343e1ed1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ircon International Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ircon-international-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768485</link><description>Ircon International Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>5cd9aaf5f7bc9a7f18ae9f3cc6ffba24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kamdhenu-ventures-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768483</link><description>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 28 Oct 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>768d59af5ac05cda3e36c69d6c217098</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indostar-capital-finance-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768481</link><description>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 11 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>450ba8a9aaef99eca6d4becbf237a0b9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manaksia Coated Metals &amp; Industries Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/manaksia-coated-metals-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-3768510</link><description>Manaksia Coated Metals &amp; Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 11 Nov 2025, reflecting a change from a previous 'Buy' rating. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here represent the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>26d2e979e7a11ce866cf9035be799bcb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/smt-engineering-ltd-is-rated-buy-3768508</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 Dec 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>fc1203036c48f80b0c6e5d6ecedef76a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simplex Infrastructures Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/simplex-infrastructures-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768507</link><description>Simplex Infrastructures Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>e816b79cecd9da464f4c7b4e46e3692f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/centenial-surgical-suture-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768503</link><description>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>3b3ac02d52a0d9f9c6dc6bacda5eb006</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>