<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Nuvama Wealth Management Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvama-wealth-management-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3860485</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.7% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s underperformance and bearish price trends. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining delivery volumes and weakening moving averages, suggests a complex market positioning that may indicate directional bets by traders amid cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>180c88a9c5e041da1937eda4a4006139</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Capital Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-capital-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3860479</link><description>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd (ABCAPITAL) has witnessed a notable 12.9% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>20ac129113b66294f80a75d62e0ae406</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bandhan-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3860478</link><description>Bandhan Bank Ltd. has witnessed a notable 10.4% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite the stock’s recent underperformance relative to its sector and a dip after a five-day rally, the surge in open interest and volume suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and liquidity dynamics.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>41b1ee5e3396b82043e00d36ae7d10b9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Finance Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-finance-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3860480</link><description>L&amp;T Finance Ltd (LTF) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent price decline, the sharp increase in open interest and volume suggests that traders are recalibrating their directional bets amid broader sector weakness and market volatility.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>f5b1ab6f7f6142ee79a5ac19d98955f6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coal India Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Stable Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coal-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-stable-price-action-3860476</link><description>Coal India Ltd. has witnessed a notable 13.4% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among traders. Despite this surge, the stock price remains largely steady, trading above all major moving averages, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and cautious sentiment in the Minerals &amp; Mining sector.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>4efc62a7ccd3ff681fb242505e0518d7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oberoi Realty Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oberoi-realty-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3860477</link><description>Oberoi Realty Ltd has witnessed a notable 11.4% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest decline in the stock price, the increase in open interest and volume patterns suggest complex directional bets as investors reassess the realty sector’s near-term outlook.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>317da990a4efa60c8c8b38ba51d8e961</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Petronet LNG Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/petronet-lng-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3860481</link><description>Petronet LNG Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s recent outperformance, coupled with rising volumes and a strong technical setup, has attracted renewed attention from traders and investors alike.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>8442da538e8d1f83630c5a4242e8a080</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3860463</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results across market capitalisations, sectors, and individual companies. With 4,094 stocks having declared their results, the overall trend indicates a modest improvement in profitability and sales growth, though challenges persist in certain segments. This comprehensive review analyses the key trends, sectoral performances, and standout performers shaping the current market landscape.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>4ba3f8ca8eabb1bb6a3fc41983914d01</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siemens Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3860475</link><description>Siemens Ltd., a heavyweight in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 27 Feb 2026, signalling a potential shift in market positioning. The stock outperformed its sector peers and the broader Sensex, hitting a fresh 52-week high of ₹3,440, as investors recalibrated their directional bets amid evolving volume and price dynamics.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>d5c4d2ee94a926b8e49101c33c0b5913</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Agrolife Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/best-agrolife-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3860474</link><description>Best Agrolife Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 27 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit and registering a maximum daily loss of 4.43%. The stock’s sharp decline reflects mounting investor concerns amid sustained negative momentum and unfilled supply, marking its 11th consecutive day of losses.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>1933fed73057f672d8505f844520c18c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flexituff Ventures International Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/flexituff-ventures-international-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3860471</link><description>Flexituff Ventures International Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 27 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit of 9.91% and closing at a new 52-week low of ₹8.73. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market amid intense selling pressure, signalling growing investor concerns and panic selling.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>4f33d7ba56bacda096e625b261bd60dd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parsvnath Developers Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/parsvnath-developers-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3860470</link><description>Parsvnath Developers Ltd (NSE: EQ) surged to its upper circuit limit on 27 Feb 2026, registering a remarkable 17.13% gain to close at ₹8.07. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, with the stock outperforming its Realty sector peers and broader benchmarks despite a challenging market environment.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>be1c71927cd581d76685cd5f642d389a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Breadth and Selective Upgrades</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-breadth-and-selective-upgrades-3860465</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index edged higher by 0.31% on 27 Feb 2026, maintaining its position as the best-performing market capitalisation segment amid a broadly cautious market. Despite the modest gain, the small-cap space exhibited a mixed breadth with 474 stocks advancing against 726 decliners, reflecting selective buying interest and sectoral divergences.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>54e8ab3c998998dbe3c08c05ccbba87c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vesuvius India Ltd Reports Strongest Quarterly Performance, Upgrades Financial Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vesuvius-india-ltd-reports-strongest-quarterly-performance-upgrades-financial-trend-3860473</link><description>Vesuvius India Ltd has demonstrated a marked improvement in its financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, with record-high revenue, profit before depreciation and interest, and net profit figures. This robust quarterly showing has prompted an upgrade in the company’s financial trend from flat to positive, signalling renewed investor confidence and a potential shift in market sentiment.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>dc3b87a45ee2f15d2a0fe91c780ca02f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indrayani Biotech Ltd Reports Flat Quarterly Performance Amid Mixed Financial Indicators</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indrayani-biotech-ltd-reports-flat-quarterly-performance-amid-mixed-financial-indicators-3860472</link><description>Indrayani Biotech Ltd has posted a flat financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, signalling a stabilisation after a period of negative trends. While net sales surged impressively by over 100%, key profitability and operational metrics reveal a complex picture, with margin pressures and liquidity concerns persisting. The company’s recent upgrade in financial trend score from -9 to -2 reflects this nuanced recovery, yet challenges remain in inventory and debtor management alongside elevated debt levels.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>25c33a1d8401142ac1c9fb0a46759ebf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>