<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Solarium Green Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solarium-green-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3847587</link><description>On 19-Feb, Solarium Green Energy Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹160.10, marking a 5.6% decline and hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹159 during intraday trading. This drop continues a pronounced downward trend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market over multiple timeframes.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7199d4d1b49c434b847310d079c6e612</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vishwas-agri-seeds-ltd-fallingrising-3847586</link><description>On 19-Feb, Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, falling by 5.9% to close at ₹39.05. This decline reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>49f16ddaf6bf95c41287581c24db9bda</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3847585</link><description>On 19-Feb, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 17.53%, closing at ₹32.85. This sharp rise reflects a combination of robust short-term performance, heightened investor participation, and favourable technical indicators that have propelled the stock well above its recent moving averages.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9e2f8aa7e65b097720759efd70786115</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anand-rathi-wealth-ltd-fallingrising-3847584</link><description>As of 19-Feb, Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd’s stock price has risen by 0.84% to ₹3,035.00, reflecting a positive market response driven by robust long-term fundamentals and growing institutional interest despite some short-term volume declines.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d7ba18c379842896bc4fbc2b97504a44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Megatherm Induction Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-megatherm-induction-ltd-fallingrising-3847583</link><description>On 19-Feb, Megatherm Induction Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.14% to ₹213.20, reflecting ongoing challenges as the share underperformed both its sector and key market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8619d55c34bd573b372d8154655a6321</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mega Flex Plastics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mega-flex-plastics-ltd-fallingrising-3847582</link><description>On 19-Feb, Mega Flex Plastics Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.02% to ₹126.00, reflecting robust investor confidence and sustained upward momentum in the stock’s performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>72d0f4517b9381133a85331f7f50162b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ameya Precision Engineers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ameya-precision-engineers-ltd-fallingrising-3847581</link><description>On 19-Feb, Ameya Precision Engineers Ltd witnessed a notable 5.0% increase in its share price, closing at ₹92.40. This rise comes despite the stock's mixed performance over longer timeframes and subdued investor participation, highlighting a complex market dynamic for the precision engineering firm.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>66425cf61c1a1465d2fe3e98e0110697</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AB Cotspin India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ab-cotspin-india-ltd-fallingrising-3847580</link><description>On 19-Feb, AB Cotspin India Ltd’s stock price surged by 5.18% to close at ₹444.00, reflecting a notable outperformance against both its sector and the broader market benchmarks despite underlying concerns about management efficiency and debt servicing capacity.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8ce5497834d670da7fc930a7506f5341</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Medplus Health Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-medplus-health-services-ltd-fallingrising-3847578</link><description>On 19-Feb, Medplus Health Services Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 2.13% to close at ₹828.40. This movement reflects a combination of short-term technical pressures and waning investor participation despite the company’s solid fundamental performance over recent quarters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6a31937f91f2ef09fc1f55683263b947</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ddev-plastiks-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3847579</link><description>As of 19-Feb, DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹276.00, down 1.55% on the day, reflecting a continuation of recent downward momentum amid a complex interplay of valuation, performance, and market sentiment factors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c48c58552ce9d74b274ce03803298e79</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-upsurge-seeds-of-agriculture-ltd-fallingrising-3847577</link><description>On 19-Feb, Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.0% to close at ₹117.80. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0052eaa851d3b55a88637b32d643621d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Alivus Life Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-alivus-life-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3847576</link><description>On 19-Feb, Alivus Life Sciences Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.1% to close at ₹889.35. This movement reflects a combination of short-term market pressures despite the company’s strong operational performance and attractive valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a537bd8b19ce29c3c2e6f770124ab521</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Moksh Ornaments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-moksh-ornaments-ltd-fallingrising-3847575</link><description>As of 19-Feb, Moksh Ornaments Ltd has experienced a notable decline in its share price, reflecting a broader pattern of underperformance relative to key benchmarks and technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b51e3e6948ea9f175ccc5b164328f3b7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Zota Health Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-zota-health-care-ltd-fallingrising-3847574</link><description>On 19-Feb, Zota Health Care Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.87% to ₹1,327.80, reflecting investor concerns over recent quarterly performance and weakening fundamentals despite strong long-term returns and institutional interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>81e7f280d003b601f443f6757e600c96</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Navneet Education Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-navneet-education-ltd-fallingrising-3847573</link><description>On 19-Feb, Navneet Education Ltd’s stock price declined by 1.53% to close at ₹151.05, continuing a three-day losing streak that has seen the share fall by 4.52%. Despite this short-term weakness, the company’s longer-term performance remains robust relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>51f693d59b3fec34cada1409743efce7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Polo Queen Industrial and Fintech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-polo-queen-industrial-and-fintech-ltd-fallingrising-3847572</link><description>On 19-Feb, Polo Queen Industrial and Fintech Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹23.30, down ₹1.02 or 4.19% from the previous session. This drop marks a continuation of a persistent downward trend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e3957837d8e92d1708e53086855b5898</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-tirupati-balajee-fibc-ltd-fallingrising-3847571</link><description>On 19-Feb, Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.0% to close at ₹523.60. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0ac50628fc89d9df54f8b8487fc24a58</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kemistar Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kemistar-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3847570</link><description>On 19-Feb, Kemistar Corporation Ltd’s stock price rose by 3.71% to close at ₹69.89, marking a notable intraday gain despite broader challenges in its recent performance and sector activity.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7482755ba8436857d23d87fa559c2414</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is K G Denim Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-k-g-denim-ltd-fallingrising-3847569</link><description>On 19-Feb, K G Denim Ltd's stock price rose by 3.39% to ₹16.78, reflecting a notable uptick in investor participation and outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over the past week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6dd39a8a6090f6ac1b1d0915b2fad202</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Prima Plastics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-prima-plastics-ltd-fallingrising-3847568</link><description>On 19-Feb, Prima Plastics Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.35% to close at ₹118.60. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum, influenced by subdued investor interest and technical factors impacting the stock's performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bfd040a6ad24876305ea8a0ec383f669</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>