<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Kirloskar Electric Declines 8.30%: Valuation Reset and Bearish Momentum Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kirloskar-electric-declines-830-valuation-reset-and-bearish-momentum-shape-week-3850052</link><description>Kirloskar Electric Company Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 8.30% from Rs.98.90 to Rs.90.69, sharply underperforming the Sensex which rose modestly by 0.39%. The week was marked by a significant valuation recalibration and a shift towards bearish technical momentum, reflecting growing investor caution amid sector headwinds and mixed market signals.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>0cafc978948fc9ff30fde2a07d895264</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Petroleum Falls 4.25%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-petroleum-falls-425-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3850051</link><description>Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd. (HPCL) closed the week ending 20 Feb 2026 at Rs.431.15, down 4.25% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.450.30. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period, highlighting HPCL’s underperformance amid sector-specific pressures and heightened market volatility. The week was marked by a sharp intraday low on 19 Feb and a surge in derivatives open interest on 20 Feb, signalling shifting investor sentiment and increased trading activity.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>b81f6fbd83051646c81e602c9550d0c4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IB Infotech Enterprises Ltd Surges 27.61%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ib-infotech-enterprises-ltd-surges-2761-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3850050</link><description>IB Infotech Enterprises Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance from 16 to 20 February 2026, surging 27.61% from Rs.395.00 to Rs.504.05, vastly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. The stock consistently hit new 52-week and all-time highs throughout the week, reflecting strong momentum and sustained investor interest despite a cautious Mojo Grade of Sell. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped the stock’s exceptional week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>4a8c49a047996cf6aa281817bdfac48b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hexaware Technologies Falls 7.03%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hexaware-technologies-falls-703-4-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3850049</link><description>Hexaware Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its share price declining by 7.03% to close at Rs.521.50, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a 'Sell' rating, valuation concerns, technical weakness, and a fresh 52-week low, all contributing to heightened investor caution amid mixed financial signals.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>e59bb9c875cefe6eb65e543eccc450e6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Gains 4.02%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-pharmaceuticals-gains-402-7-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3850048</link><description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. delivered a solid weekly gain of 4.02%, closing at Rs.4,237.80 on 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The week was marked by multiple new 52-week and all-time highs, robust institutional interest, and strong derivatives activity, underscoring sustained bullish momentum despite some intraweek volatility.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>5f6b417105af73cdb4f4dd4071014984</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aurionpro Solutions Ltd Gains 1.39%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aurionpro-solutions-ltd-gains-139-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3850047</link><description>Aurionpro Solutions Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.39%, closing at Rs.944.90 on 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise over the same period. The week was marked by a significant intraday surge on 18 February, followed by a technical momentum shift amid mixed market signals, reflecting a complex trading environment for the stock.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>54df9858107b62824b6379d253d4c4cf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spice Islands Industries Ltd Falls 9.32%: Valuation Upgrade Amidst Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spice-islands-industries-ltd-falls-932-valuation-upgrade-amidst-weekly-decline-3850046</link><description>Spice Islands Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 9.32% from ₹302.65 on 13 February 2026 to ₹274.45 on 20 February 2026. This underperformance contrasted sharply with the Sensex, which rose modestly by 0.39% over the same period. Despite the stock’s recent upgrade to a Hold rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting improved valuation and financial metrics, the week’s trading reflected investor caution amid mixed fundamental signals and persistent valuation premiums.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>d44079a63bf85d56dde6fb6ac91ab53c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd Falls 6.41%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pritish-nandy-communications-ltd-falls-641-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3850042</link><description>Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 6.41% from ₹27.13 to ₹25.39, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant valuation shift and a downgrade to a strong sell rating amid mixed financial and technical signals, reflecting investor caution despite some operational improvements.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>27fc6a121c3a677d43977b3ab8718152</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baba Arts Ltd Gains 12.60%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baba-arts-ltd-gains-1260-6-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3850043</link><description>Baba Arts Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 12.60% from Rs.10.87 to Rs.12.24 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by multiple new 52-week highs, a notable technical breakout with a Golden Cross formation, and an upgrade in its Mojo Grade from ‘Strong Sell’ to ‘Sell’. Despite a slight pullback on the final trading day, Baba Arts Ltd demonstrated strong momentum and resilience amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>9758c15f9ab5d5534042e126323ab8db</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goodluck India Ltd Gains 11.50%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goodluck-india-ltd-gains-1150-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3850044</link><description>Goodluck India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 11.50% from Rs.1,085.75 to Rs.1,210.65 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock’s momentum was driven by a series of positive technical developments, an upgrade in investment rating, and robust relative returns amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>111f4b45bacac11d9a27fcc9148dd83a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanjivani Paranteral Ltd Falls 6.96%: Valuation Shifts and Rating Upgrade Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanjivani-paranteral-ltd-falls-696-valuation-shifts-and-rating-upgrade-shape-the-week-3850045</link><description>Sanjivani Paranteral Ltd experienced a challenging week on the BSE, closing at Rs.195.85 on 20 Feb 2026, down 6.96% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.210.50. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid mixed financial and valuation developments. Key events during the week included an upgrade to a 'Hold' rating by MarketsMOJO and a notable shift in valuation metrics, both influencing investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>c311ba7d88b8e04ea457cb1ff4cb57bb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineers India Ltd Gains 6.54%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/engineers-india-ltd-gains-654-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3850041</link><description>Engineers India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, closing at Rs.215.05 on 20 February 2026, marking a 6.54% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.201.85. This outpaced the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period, reflecting robust investor interest and positive momentum amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>68c15674c5771c13e435b556b8c3ae9f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Toolroom Falls 7.58%: Key Financial Struggles and Downgrade Impact Weekly</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-toolroom-falls-758-key-financial-struggles-and-downgrade-impact-weekly-3850039</link><description>Gujarat Toolroom Ltd’s stock declined by 7.58% over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.0.61 from Rs.0.66 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted sharply with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% during the same period. The week was marked by a series of negative developments including mixed quarterly results, a significant downgrade in quality ratings, and persistent operational challenges that weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>207144817ec44ba67b435322d4711c2a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ahmedabad Steelcraft Falls 13.96%: Valuation Shifts and Q3 Results Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ahmedabad-steelcraft-falls-1396-valuation-shifts-and-q3-results-shape-the-week-3850040</link><description>Ahmedabad Steelcraft Ltd experienced a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its share price declining by 13.96% to close at ₹167.05, significantly underperforming the Sensex, which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a slip in quarterly profits and a recalibration of valuation metrics that, while signalling renewed price attractiveness, coincided with heightened market volatility and investor caution.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>363179d45e3acf767595d1e16d2fb9a1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novartis India Surges 25.79% Despite Strong Sell Downgrade: Key Weekly Developments</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/novartis-india-surges-2579-despite-strong-sell-downgrade-key-weekly-developments-3850038</link><description>Novartis India Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 25.79%, closing at Rs.996.50 on 20 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock’s performance was marked by a strong intraday rally and a notable gap up on the final trading day, despite a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. This week’s price action reflects a complex interplay of valuation concerns, financial challenges, and technical momentum.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>ad9708bb66b085028c6024972681022f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Petronet LNG Gains 5.47%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/petronet-lng-gains-547-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3850037</link><description>Petronet LNG Ltd. delivered a robust weekly gain of 5.47%, closing at Rs.306.50 on 20 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock’s performance was shaped by a series of technical momentum shifts, heightened derivatives market activity, and valuation recalibrations amid evolving sector dynamics. This review analyses the key events and market signals that influenced Petronet LNG’s price trajectory over the week.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>8d1980fb9a580cad5c625af1d84368d7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dynamatic Technologies Gains 5.07%: 4 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dynamatic-technologies-gains-507-4-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3850035</link><description>Dynamatic Technologies Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 5.07%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise during the week ending 20 February 2026. The stock exhibited strong intraday rallies midweek, hitting new highs before a slight pullback on the final trading day. This week’s price action was supported by a combination of robust technical momentum, an upgrade in investment rating, and solid quarterly financial results, all contributing to renewed investor interest despite some mixed technical signals.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>f2a2fa0b71c268b61546da2ecdfdfba8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Gains 2.82%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-gains-282-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3850033</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 2.82% from Rs.1,183.55 to Rs.1,216.90 between 16 and 20 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a series of new 52-week and all-time highs, reflecting robust technical momentum and improved market sentiment amid mixed broader market conditions.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>a4cdde653ab4bc23bea35dfe120c9811</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gufic BioSciences Declines 6.29%: Four Key Factors Behind the Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gufic-biosciences-declines-629-four-key-factors-behind-the-downtrend-3850032</link><description>Gufic BioSciences Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.288.30, down 6.29% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.307.65, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by fresh 52-week lows, technical downgrades, and persistent bearish momentum amid subdued financial results and rising costs, reflecting ongoing challenges for the company despite a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>03efb5bb249931269cbce8798aaa6b4d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ador Welding Gains 4.14%: 3 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ador-welding-gains-414-3-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3850034</link><description>Ador Welding Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 4.14% from ₹1,046.05 on 13 February to ₹1,089.40 on 20 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a mix of technical momentum shifts, a cautious rating downgrade, and resilient financial results, reflecting a nuanced market sentiment amid broader volatility.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>ff48b8d0e18f20d1cae2af86e853c50a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>