<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Eureka Forbes Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eureka-forbes-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3847498</link><description>Eureka Forbes Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength amid underwhelming market performance.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>9cc99240db534cff20e969a027f5df3c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anand Rayons Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anand-rayons-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3847496</link><description>Anand Rayons Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- and long-term outlook.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>0ca4175fe52ef8d604f4ebb9f5f4987f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Healthcare Global Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/healthcare-global-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3847499</link><description>Healthcare Global Enterprises Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>5eb1534e65fe7859aafb33624a702838</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texmaco Infrastructure &amp; Holdings Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/texmaco-infrastructure-holdings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3847497</link><description>Texmaco Infrastructure &amp; Holdings Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>c0dd7870e58be870eb9da7f20e486783</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suprajit Engineering Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suprajit-engineering-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3847487</link><description>Suprajit Engineering Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>b5d0eb83b7737849c7c0f08182767d1a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salona Cotspin Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/salona-cotspin-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3847495</link><description>Salona Cotspin Ltd., a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained weakness in the near to medium term.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>3435b1e461db3205a3d990146c7ead95</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/narbada-gems-jewellery-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3847492</link><description>Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook within the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>041fa55097036494285bf855885ee432</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3847494</link><description>Bosch Ltd., a leading player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term strength.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>ff2f2eeef425cc40c33264e00eb7c5d7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prajay Engineers Syndicate Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prajay-engineers-syndicate-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-outlook-3847490</link><description>PraJay Engineers Syndicate Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action within the Realty sector.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>9c7b9e7be6a5fb9ac7acd341a5990bb3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/divgi-torqtransfer-systems-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3847488</link><description>Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the auto components company, suggesting renewed investor confidence and a possible trend reversal.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>3a67122a5caa22060d5bcdb86aaac9d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AKG Exim Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akg-exim-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3847491</link><description>AKG Exim Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded by market analysts as a bullish signal, indicating a potential long-term trend reversal and a shift in momentum favouring upward price movement.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>913b4bca64ae6069d303e263d97dc98c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICE Make Refrigeration Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ice-make-refrigeration-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3847489</link><description>ICE Make Refrigeration Ltd, a micro-cap player in the industrial manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical event where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>8f0a588486b38de66fd744d6dbd9c8e1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baba Arts Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baba-arts-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3847493</link><description>Baba Arts Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>f6b9c737fca58d6797e6c67b687a3fe2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3847486</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded for 4,083 stocks, revealing a nuanced picture of corporate performance across market capitalisations and sectors. While the proportion of companies reporting positive results has edged up slightly to 46.0%, the overall trend remains subdued, reflecting ongoing challenges in the broader economic environment.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>0e863deac1e0a42ce460f6a3930037ec</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ecos-india-mobility-hospitality-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3847468</link><description>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing just 1.2% above its lowest price of Rs 160.95. This significant price level reflects a period of sustained underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a799e54e98ca1e0286a97c6e818a9c57</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3847467</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 2,029.35, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance over the past year. This decline reflects a combination of subdued financial results and valuation concerns amid broader market pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f02b8251e79fe32eb172963d1bdd0182</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreamfolks Services Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dreamfolks-services-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3847471</link><description>Dreamfolks Services Ltd has reached a significant milestone by touching its 52-week low, closing just 0.58% above the lowest price of Rs 86. This marks a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory, reflecting ongoing challenges within the transport infrastructure sector and the company’s recent financial performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8945a3f7b58757da9474ed44fb3866a6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Home Finance Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-home-finance-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3847466</link><description>Reliance Home Finance Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near ₹2.53, marking a significant downturn for the housing finance company. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures, with the price now just 2.69% above this low point, underscoring a challenging period for the firm within the sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e66b37cfc6b5dce3ed029b7875b37621</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Cook (India) Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thomas-cook-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-market-downturn-3847470</link><description>Thomas Cook (India) Ltd’s shares have declined to a new 52-week low, closing just 0.64% above the lowest price of Rs 108.9. This marks a significant milestone for the stock, reflecting a year of underwhelming performance relative to broader market indices and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ca03c1d62abd6f99c29fda8463f0d20d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indiabulls Limited Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.9.38 Amidst Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indiabulls-limited-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs938-amidst-weak-fundamentals-3847469</link><description>Indiabulls Limited, a key player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.9.38 today, reflecting ongoing pressures in both the company’s performance and broader market conditions. The stock’s decline comes amid a sector-wide downturn and follows a series of financial indicators that have weighed on investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3d49e165b65f09f0d89be0ada80940e0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>