<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iykot-hitech-toolroom-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3848542</link><description>Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd’s stock price touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.10 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing concerns over the company’s financial health and market performance. This new low comes despite a broadly positive market environment, highlighting the stock’s underperformance relative to its peers and the benchmark indices.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>72d06a70e3c516a27152e258bcb372b0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SpiceJet Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.16.3 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spicejet-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs163-amid-continued-downtrend-3848543</link><description>SpiceJet Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.16.3 today, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The airline sector stock has underperformed its peers and broader market indices, reflecting persistent financial and market pressures.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>4c0111c944ab2dcc271542c15716a7f3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KEI Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs 4,677.7 on 20 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kei-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs-46777-on-20-feb-2026-3848544</link><description>KEI Industries Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs 4,677.7, reflecting robust momentum in the electrical cables sector and underscoring the company’s sustained performance over the past year.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>11821805f0a9c8e8c278f45406525f66</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delhivery Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/delhivery-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3848537</link><description>Delhivery Ltd, a key player in the transport services sector, has witnessed a notable 10.8% rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.16% gain in the stock price, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests evolving directional bets that merit close attention from investors and analysts alike.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>d48b0c8dad1a1048af27d4740ccb220c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-rally-3848536</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock hit a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs 23,800 on 20 Feb 2026, outperforming its sector and broader indices, while open interest rose by 11.43% to 21,851 contracts, reflecting increased investor positioning ahead of anticipated market moves.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>6e55fcbaa39720d700e991a9a8814a87</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3848538</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd (POLICYBZR) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite outperforming its sector on 20 Feb 2026, the stock faces technical headwinds as it trades below key moving averages, prompting a reassessment of its near-term outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>984dc5550399b1808289bb679eb39abe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Capital Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-capital-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3848535</link><description>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd (ABCAPITAL) has witnessed a notable 10.1% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of factors influencing trader sentiment and potential directional bets.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>78379740d8267767d55fde252c72cab7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-prudential-life-insurance-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-signals-3848533</link><description>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd (ICICIPRULI) witnessed a significant 12.44% rise in open interest in its derivatives segment on 19 Feb 2026, signalling heightened investor interest and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, supported by robust volume and rising investor participation, indicating a bullish market stance.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>19e4561f3c9d7a9f0f3a1bc0cf3df079</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Investment Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cholamandalam-investment-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3848532</link><description>Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance Company Ltd (CHOLAFIN) has witnessed a notable 13.1% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.26% price gain on 20 Feb 2026, the stock underperformed its NBFC sector peers, reflecting a complex interplay of volume, liquidity, and technical factors that investors should carefully analyse.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7fbde2dda64d09d2eded88770a6af237</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UPL Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/upl-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3848528</link><description>UPL Ltd., a key player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, witnessed a notable 10.34% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 19 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices. This surge in OI, coupled with rising delivery volumes and mixed price action, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>af81fe571e9c1c2c2b3ccdae4df785e6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge (India) Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3848531</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.9% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and subdued delivery volumes, suggests a complex interplay of market positioning and directional bets among traders.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>3fd146b15c17d59a6485a92fd6ea84eb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Financial Services Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-financial-services-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3848530</link><description>Max Financial Services Ltd (MFSL) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock, trading close to its 52-week high, has shown resilience with rising volumes and improving technical indicators, prompting a reassessment of its market positioning and outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>2ecdbc96a49d21729dcc9c4243c66802</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Motor Company Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-motor-company-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3848534</link><description>TVS Motor Company Ltd (TVSMOTOR) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, with an 11.66% increase to 81,898 contracts from 73,346 previously. This rise in OI, coupled with evolving volume patterns and price movements, signals a shift in market positioning and potential directional bets among traders, despite the stock’s recent underperformance relative to its sector and broader indices.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>98fd05cddb1f5f2d5a6bbac03b43394a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pidilite Industries Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pidilite-industries-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3848529</link><description>Pidilite Industries Ltd, a stalwart in the specialty chemicals sector, has witnessed a notable 14.12% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling a significant shift in market positioning. Despite a modest price gain of 0.29% on 20 Feb 2026, the stock underperformed its sector by 0.9%, reflecting a complex interplay between investor sentiment and trading activity.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>c4499cc94c28dd0dffa13958f37d9f2b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indus Towers Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indus-towers-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3848527</link><description>Indus Towers Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling a notable shift in market sentiment. The telecom equipment giant’s open interest jumped by 16.75% to 75,595 contracts, accompanied by robust volume activity, suggesting increased directional bets and evolving investor positioning ahead of key market catalysts.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>cc63e6836684aa0d07cf29a924479d39</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jubilant-foodworks-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3848526</link><description>Jubilant Foodworks Ltd (JUBLFOOD) has witnessed a notable 11.05% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.71% gain in the stock price, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests evolving directional bets amid a backdrop of mixed technical indicators and subdued investor participation.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>bf9ddae327289e5b1c9625fff5c49ec1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Osia Hyper Retail Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/osia-hyper-retail-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3848523</link><description>Osia Hyper Retail Ltd witnessed a remarkable rally on 20 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 4.97% gain, closing at ₹10.98. This surge was driven by strong buying interest amid rising investor participation, despite the stock trading below its key moving averages. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader Sensex, signalling renewed market focus on this micro-cap retailing company.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>51b9ea0991a8a009b06614da1b100e3d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonu Infratech Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sonu-infratech-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3848521</link><description>Shares of Sonu Infratech Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, plunged sharply on 20 Feb 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit of ₹72.10. The stock recorded a maximum daily loss of 4.94%, underperforming both its sector and the broader market amid intense selling pressure and a marked decline in investor participation.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>a5e74874e680817296cefdbf533487f1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheetal Cool Products Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sheetal-cool-products-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3848520</link><description>Sheetal Cool Products Ltd, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 20 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit as panic selling gripped investors. The stock closed at ₹323.05, down 5.0% on the day, underperforming both its sector and the broader market amid unrelenting selling pressure and a significant drop in trading volumes.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>8aa20114b157166591523d8c18e7212f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Engineering Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-engineering-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3848522</link><description>Supreme Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 20 Feb 2026, reflecting robust buying interest despite its recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating. The stock closed at ₹0.93, marking a daily gain of 1.09%, supported by a maximum permissible price band of 5% and a notable spike in demand that outpaced available supply.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>262214f9da5974a53dccf723111961e9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>