<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>South Indian Bank Ltd Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/south-indian-bank-ltd-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3784637</link><description>South Indian Bank Ltd has reached a historic all-time high, reflecting a remarkable trajectory of growth and resilience in the private sector banking space. The stock’s recent surge underscores its strong fundamentals and sustained market outperformance.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>09f06c2bd7dd2cf83a8e3d85e12ffa1c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Go Fashion (India) Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/go-fashion-india-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-underperformance-3784636</link><description>Shares of Go Fashion (India) Ltd have declined to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers. The stock’s recent price action underscores ongoing pressures within the garments and apparels sector, as well as company-specific factors contributing to its diminished market valuation.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>b8df4436754569eaaa41906cbe41321c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliable Data Services Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.172</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliable-data-services-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs172-3784634</link><description>Reliable Data Services Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, achieved a significant milestone today by reaching a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.172. This marks a continuation of the stock’s robust momentum, reflecting strong financial performance and sustained investor confidence.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>45a9390e97cde94e71b88b5099abebe6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samrat Forgings Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.214 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samrat-forgings-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs214-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784635</link><description>Samrat Forgings Ltd’s stock price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.214 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has been under pressure for the past five trading sessions, cumulatively losing over 10% in value, reflecting persistent challenges within the company’s financial and operational metrics.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>ec85fe49db36824f7f57e7d997069bee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AGI Infra Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.302.55</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/agi-infra-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs30255-3784630</link><description>AGI Infra Ltd, a key player in the Realty sector, surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs.302.55 on 7 January 2026, reflecting robust momentum and a notable rally that has captured market attention. The stock’s performance today significantly outpaced its sector peers, underscoring a period of sustained gains and heightened volatility.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>426c1c13ead6b392a7a3da4a25d80b28</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rossell India Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rossell-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784626</link><description>Rossell India Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.47.8 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions. The stock’s performance contrasts sharply with broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial health and valuation metrics.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>0436aed3bc46519257238ae378ef11cd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AGI Infra Ltd Hits Intraday High with 11.95% Surge on 7 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/agi-infra-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1195-surge-on-7-jan-2026-3784633</link><description>AGI Infra Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 7 Jan 2026, surging to a new 52-week high of Rs 302.55, marking a significant 15.68% rise from its previous close. The stock outperformed its Realty sector peers and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum and heightened volatility throughout the session.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>d37220e41007e6f1a7737b62d9beb9c0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PC Jeweller Ltd Hits Day High with 7.03% Intraday Surge on 7 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pc-jeweller-ltd-hits-day-high-with-703-intraday-surge-on-7-jan-2026-3784632</link><description>PC Jeweller Ltd witnessed a robust intraday rally on 7 Jan 2026, surging to its day high with a notable gain of 7.03%, significantly outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>0ed872010adfae941cec7c80062c9d7b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lux Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lux-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784628</link><description>Lux Industries Ltd, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1049 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock has been under pressure for several sessions, reflecting a combination of subdued financial performance and market dynamics.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>da6072bfa285d286b2b50ccba2c22d88</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganesha-ecosphere-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3784627</link><description>Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.819.6 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on the company’s financial performance and market sentiment.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>d5d516fc5679cfc9b5a7fa1b581fd5f0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Hotels Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-hotels-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784625</link><description>Jindal Hotels Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.73.5 today, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has now recorded losses over the past three consecutive sessions, cumulatively falling by 5.53%, reflecting persistent pressures within the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>ec71d9a1b3ae2ff889c51537eea5679a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AGI Infra Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High of Rs.302.55 on 7 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/agi-infra-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-of-rs30255-on-7-jan-2026-3784624</link><description>AGI Infra Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high of Rs.302.55 on 7 Jan 2026, reflecting robust performance and sustained momentum in the Realty sector. This achievement underscores the company’s strong market presence and consistent upward trajectory over multiple timeframes.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>2c59aa3790d1582a3e51779b5dcf93a8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cipla Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 7 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cipla-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-7-jan-2026-3784629</link><description>Cipla Ltd. experienced a notable intraday decline on 7 Jan 2026, with its share price touching a low of Rs 1,479.2, reflecting a 3.34% drop from the previous close. This downturn marks a reversal after three consecutive days of gains, as the stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid prevailing market pressures.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>07a2b185fb2c6ef561d605220559d0a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elecon Engineering Company Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.81% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/elecon-engineering-company-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-781-surge-3784631</link><description>Elecon Engineering Company Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 7 January 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 517.85, marking an 8.1% increase from its previous close. This sharp uptick outpaced the broader industrial manufacturing sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum despite a subdued market backdrop.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>622a6c2f7fae368bfdd936139996cf53</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galada Power &amp; Telecommunication Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.3.38</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/galada-power-telecommunication-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs338-3784622</link><description>Galada Power &amp; Telecommunication Ltd reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.3.38, marking a notable moment in the stock’s recent performance amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 43 minutes ago</description><guid>805350e1d8c639e9a397c588a3621c03</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-builders-engineers-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3784618</link><description>Shares of Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.112.95, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance amid a challenging market environment and subdued financial results.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>5d7b3b1e29eccb5d205405dae0ca51a8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arnold Holdings Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arnold-holdings-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3784619</link><description>Arnold Holdings Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), recorded a fresh 52-week low today at Rs.12.57, marking a significant decline in its share price amid ongoing pressures. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial performance and investor sentiment.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>e114056fe1e972ab7e94985f796d1171</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piramal Finance Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.97% Surge on 7 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piramal-finance-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-397-surge-on-7-jan-2026-3784623</link><description>Piramal Finance Ltd surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time intraday high of Rs 1885.95 on 7 Jan 2026, marking a robust 4.11% gain during the trading session and extending its winning streak to six consecutive days with a cumulative return of 17.33%.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>f96a9e62fb2f3502d2a638d53e541b57</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salzer Electronics Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/salzer-electronics-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784620</link><description>Salzer Electronics Ltd, a player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.670.15 on 7 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline amid a sustained negative trend over recent sessions.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>6f4f589772af1ff7b83492f99477b254</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crestchem Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.108 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/crestchem-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs108-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784621</link><description>Crestchem Ltd, a player in the specialty chemicals sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.108 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amidst a broader market environment that remains relatively stable. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures that have weighed on investor sentiment and valuation metrics.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>efc457fb7bfb4d1b87dd4e57b8e3bd63</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>