<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-akums-drugs-pharmaceuticals-ltd-fallingrising-3829398</link><description>On 09-Feb, Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd saw its share price rise by 4.33% to ₹466.30, reflecting a notable short-term recovery despite longer-term challenges. This article analyses the factors behind the stock’s recent upward movement and its broader performance context.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>7694ecd76bbdff82041904edab05ff3e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Standard Enginnering Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-enginnering-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3829397</link><description>On 09-Feb, Standard Engineering Technology Ltd witnessed a significant uptick in its share price, rising by 7.84% to close at ₹132.80. This surge reflects a notable outperformance relative to its sector and broader market benchmarks, driven by increased investor participation and positive short-term momentum.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>623952767b722e6ea498878d082d2ef9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3829396</link><description>On 09-Feb, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing by 2.48% to ₹392.90, reflecting a strong short-term performance despite mixed longer-term returns and subdued investor participation.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>541d0e5fb580f198c19769fb163035bd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vishwas-agri-seeds-ltd-fallingrising-3829393</link><description>On 09-Feb, Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 12.47%, closing at ₹42.85. This sharp rise reflects a notable shift in investor sentiment, supported by strong trading volumes and outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>7637c5ebf94243b587862f232f6e619e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shipping-corporation-of-india-land-assets-ltd-fallingrising-3829392</link><description>On 09-Feb, Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 8.37% to close at ₹49.07. This surge comes despite the company’s challenging long-term fundamentals and recent financial performance, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and sector dynamics.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>0cd77a5c2fbf7ec36a683044e5404fbb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Epack Durable Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-epack-durable-ltd-fallingrising-3829391</link><description>On 09-Feb, Epack Durable Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 6.86% to ₹259.40, reversing a two-day decline and outperforming its sector and benchmark indices despite underlying fundamental challenges.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>0aa3496d36176d0316810f802fce5f4a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-fallingrising-3829390</link><description>On 09-Feb, Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd witnessed a notable intraday rise of 4.8%, closing at ₹422.40, reversing a two-day decline despite underlying challenges in its recent financial performance and longer-term market underperformance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>9a11d83678300c32dbb97179e525c3e0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Max Estates Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-max-estates-ltd-fallingrising-3829389</link><description>On 09-Feb, Max Estates Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 7.15% to ₹404.50, reversing a two-day decline and outperforming its sector and benchmark indices. This article analyses the factors behind this price movement, balancing the company’s operational metrics, sector trends, and market sentiment.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>0fa510f7da890e25ed690508148e11eb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GHCL Textiles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ghcl-textiles-ltd-fallingrising-3829388</link><description>On 09-Feb, GHCL Textiles Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 7.99%, closing at ₹84.02, reflecting a robust recovery and outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e0f85f311a00a899a7672fc19bb642f9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Muthoot Microfin Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-muthoot-microfin-ltd-fallingrising-3829387</link><description>On 09-Feb, Muthoot Microfin Ltd’s stock price surged by 4.48% to ₹188.95, reflecting robust market performance driven by strong quarterly earnings and sustained long-term growth metrics.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>6e34614cbf2ed166ec0bdfefc2fe515e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Annapurna Swadisht Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-annapurna-swadisht-ltd-fallingrising-3829386</link><description>As of 09 February, Annapurna Swadisht Ltd’s stock price has experienced a significant decline, falling by 8.93% to close at ₹188.75. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and technical indicators, signalling challenges for the company’s shares in the near term.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a9cd8cbcfd6bf4c49c86992e6099d41b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AB Cotspin India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ab-cotspin-india-ltd-fallingrising-3829385</link><description>On 09-Feb, AB Cotspin India Ltd witnessed a notable 3.0% increase in its share price, closing at ₹442.25. This rise reflects a combination of positive sector momentum, technical strength, and recent price action that has outperformed the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>403dc65814568bbbdc967cd7f77d151f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Euro Panel Products Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-euro-panel-products-ltd-fallingrising-3829384</link><description>On 09-Feb, Euro Panel Products Ltd recorded a modest increase in its share price, rising by 0.56% to close at ₹181.00. This movement reflects a nuanced market response influenced by sector performance, trading volumes, and moving average trends.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d683e6da06998ead1635bb0028d676a4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ddev-plastiks-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3829383</link><description>On 09-Feb, DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 5.44% to close at ₹310.30. This upward movement reflects the company’s robust performance relative to its sector and benchmark indices, supported by strong fundamentals and consistent returns over multiple time horizons.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>ecb0195a4d2d9182bded7daf72791aab</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EKI Energy Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-eki-energy-services-ltd-fallingrising-3829382</link><description>On 09 February, EKI Energy Services Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹102.92, up ₹5.41 or 5.55% from the previous session. This upward movement reflects a strong short-term performance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>030bd26b71754b442f2007952b8883f7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ksolves India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ksolves-india-ltd-fallingrising-3829381</link><description>On 09-Feb, Ksolves India Ltd witnessed a significant price rally, surging 14.68% to close at ₹293.30, marking a notable turnaround after three consecutive days of decline and outperforming its sector peers substantially.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>20380aeac506c7705654070e691ea6aa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is United Van Der Horst Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-united-van-der-horst-ltd-fallingrising-3829380</link><description>On 09-Feb, United Van Der Horst Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.94% to close at ₹36.58. This drop comes despite the engineering sector's positive performance, highlighting specific challenges faced by the stock in recent sessions.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>32e0bf9803d61d6f3417cdf318e0dce3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-focus-lighting-fixtures-ltd-fallingrising-3829379</link><description>On 09-Feb, Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹67.24, down ₹2.38 or 3.42% from the previous session. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, as evidenced by its recent financial results and market performance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a3d4def988e6b3b5fc7c5b6ee99885c3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bandhan Bank Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bandhan-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3829378</link><description>On 09-Feb, Bandhan Bank Ltd. witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹162.00 with a gain of ₹3.00 or 1.89%. This upward movement reflects a continuation of positive momentum driven by strong short-term returns and solid financial fundamentals.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>4e6f0db1e3eb1b75935e16200b302d5e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omfurn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omfurn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3829377</link><description>On 09-Feb, Omfurn India Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 14.89%, closing at ₹54.00, outperforming its sector and broader market indices despite a challenging longer-term performance record.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>4a570c317549493156242db39bc2b265</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>