<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3840257</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 3,658 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings outcomes has inched up to 46.0%, mid-cap stocks continue to outperform their large- and small-cap counterparts, signalling a shift in market dynamics amid ongoing economic challenges.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>ed2d8031a69f10e76d1dabd232263143</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pritish Nandy Communications Gains 1.61%: 2 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pritish-nandy-communications-gains-161-2-key-events-shaping-the-week-3840255</link><description>Pritish Nandy Communications Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.61%, closing at Rs.27.13 on 13 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by volatility midweek, culminating in a strong rebound on Friday following the release of its Q4 2025 financial results that revealed a remarkable turnaround. However, the week also saw a sharp sell-off triggered by a massive loss reported for Q3 FY26, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid operational challenges.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>8f6222a18ad5acf42e6b601ead4d035e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baba Arts Ltd Gains 27.28%: Technical Stabilisation Amid Fundamental Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baba-arts-ltd-gains-2728-technical-stabilisation-amid-fundamental-challenges-3840254</link><description>Baba Arts Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 27.28%, closing at Rs.10.87 on 13 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. This surge was driven primarily by a technical upgrade and stabilising price momentum despite persistent fundamental weaknesses and elevated valuation concerns. The week saw steady daily price advances, culminating in strong volume spikes on the final trading days, reflecting heightened market activity and investor attention.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>997c513892d5aa4eeb1962e11ef99332</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Capital Markets Ltd Gains 1.89%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/global-capital-markets-ltd-gains-189-4-key-factors-driving-the-week-3840252</link><description>Global Capital Markets Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.89%, closing at Rs.0.54 on 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a mix of positive financial developments, an upgrade in analyst ratings, and valuation shifts that together shaped the stock’s performance amid a challenging NBFC sector backdrop.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>9f135f94dfa8ee0453717f57d817cba8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goodluck India Ltd Falls 5.64%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goodluck-india-ltd-falls-564-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3840253</link><description>Goodluck India Ltd experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 5.64% to close at Rs.1,085.75, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant technical development signalling a bearish trend, a downgrade in analyst ratings, and mixed technical momentum despite a brief price recovery on the final trading day.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>77b6d7c7260da11574517589a8992603</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trident Ltd Falls 3.54%: Margin Pressures and Valuation Shift Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trident-ltd-falls-354-margin-pressures-and-valuation-shift-shape-weekly-trend-3840251</link><description>Trident Ltd’s stock declined by 3.54% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.26.70 from Rs.27.68, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54%. The week was marked by significant margin pressures revealed in Q3 FY26 results, a downgrade in mojo grade to Sell, and a shift in valuation from attractive to fair, all contributing to subdued investor sentiment despite some short-term resilience in price movements.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>57ff223a537cbd7f74fbe161b010c6a9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishanveer Forge Ltd Declines 1.83%: Valuation Shifts and Margin Expansion Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishanveer-forge-ltd-declines-183-valuation-shifts-and-margin-expansion-shape-week-3840250</link><description>Krishanveer Forge Ltd closed the week ending 13 February 2026 at Rs.131.50, down 1.83% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.133.95. This decline contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell 0.54% over the same period, indicating a relative underperformance by the stock amid mixed corporate developments and valuation shifts.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>b0466fb2483aa52ea70da2c4ea0637ab</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineers India Ltd Gains 17.80%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/engineers-india-ltd-gains-1780-5-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3840249</link><description>Engineers India Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance from 9 to 13 February 2026, surging 17.80% from Rs.171.35 to Rs.201.85, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong momentum driven by stellar quarterly results, a notable intraday surge on 13 February, and heightened institutional interest amid a broadly subdued market environment.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>29b6466b8d1f17b9f9a45013017b3e8f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Ltd Gains 0.18%: Valuation Shifts and Technical Challenges Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kirloskar-ferrous-industries-ltd-gains-018-valuation-shifts-and-technical-challenges-shape-the-week-3840248</link><description>Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Ltd closed the week marginally higher by 0.18%, ending at Rs.445.65 on 13 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock experienced notable volatility amid mixed fundamental and technical signals, including a sharp profit decline, a bearish technical downgrade, and a significant valuation reset that highlighted renewed price attractiveness.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>671fb9c17dbc3cd9e685b68d10e532fa</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shukra Jewellery Falls 4.42%: Financial Struggles and Bearish Signals Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shukra-jewellery-falls-442-financial-struggles-and-bearish-signals-weigh-on-stock-3840247</link><description>Shukra Jewellery Ltd’s stock declined by 4.42% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.7.35 from Rs.7.69. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall, reflecting investor concerns following disappointing quarterly results and a downgrade to a strong sell rating by MarketsMOJO. The week was marked by persistent revenue volatility and deteriorating financial and technical indicators, which weighed heavily on the stock’s performance.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>fcd84bbb64e03daf02acf384cb4af074</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Royal India Corporation Gains 0.63%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/royal-india-corporation-gains-063-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3840246</link><description>Royal India Corporation Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.63%, rising from Rs.6.33 to Rs.6.37 between 09 and 13 February 2026, marginally outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating fundamentals and bearish technicals, followed by a sharp revenue collapse in the company’s Q3 FY26 results, which weighed on investor sentiment and contributed to volatile price movements.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>cc85f645c0f29cf00968db1eaf5051a9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Petronet LNG Declines 1.87%: Mixed Signals Amid Margin Pressures and Valuation Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/petronet-lng-declines-187-mixed-signals-amid-margin-pressures-and-valuation-shifts-3840245</link><description>Petronet LNG Ltd’s stock closed the week down 1.87% at Rs.290.60, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54%. The week was marked by a shift in technical momentum to a mildly bearish stance, flat quarterly financial results amid margin pressures, and a notable improvement in valuation metrics signalling renewed price attractiveness despite ongoing challenges.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>98fdb95edfdbb2903bfbe22b9623c23c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quest Capital Markets Gains 5.69%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/quest-capital-markets-gains-569-2-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3840244</link><description>Quest Capital Markets Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, gaining 5.69% from Rs.260.15 to Rs.274.95 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s upward momentum was supported by stellar quarterly results announced midweek and an upgraded financial trend rating, which helped offset late-week profit booking amid broader market weakness.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>42569b33c5eed8bf84e44d89f9a9775e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Picturehouse Media Ltd’s 0.85% Weekly Decline: Flat Quarterly Performance and Margin Pressures Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/picturehouse-media-ltds-085-weekly-decline-flat-quarterly-performance-and-margin-pressures-weigh-3840240</link><description>Picturehouse Media Ltd’s stock declined by 0.85% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.7.04 from Rs.7.10 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s smaller 0.54% fall, reflecting investor caution amid flat quarterly results and margin pressures reported midweek. Despite a brief intraday recovery, the stock struggled to sustain gains as concerns over revenue stagnation and reliance on non-operating income weighed on sentiment.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>32afb08a95cc86ca27c4082868f82187</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dynamatic Technologies Gains 10.49%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dynamatic-technologies-gains-1049-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3840238</link><description>Dynamatic Technologies Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 10.49% from ₹8,563.45 to ₹9,461.55 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by robust intraday gains, a positive quarterly financial trend, valuation shifts, and mixed price movements amid broader market volatility.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>e8909da3b52980d7f75cff7266633b83</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dredging Corporation of India Ltd’s 1.70% Weekly Decline: Quality Concerns and Mixed Technical Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dredging-corporation-of-india-ltds-170-weekly-decline-quality-concerns-and-mixed-technical-signals-shape-the-week-3840243</link><description>Dredging Corporation of India Ltd (DCI) experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 1.70% to close at ₹967.60, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid deteriorating quality metrics, mixed technical signals, and volatile price movements. Despite a strong start with a 5.92% gain on Monday, the stock faced consistent selling pressure through the week, reflecting investor caution amid fundamental and technical concerns.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>46a27ed36c98312929ea301411a2281f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd. Edges Lower -0.52% Despite New 52-Week Highs and Strong Technical Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-edges-lower--052-despite-new-52-week-highs-and-strong-technical-momentum-3840242</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. closed the week marginally lower by 0.52% at Rs.1,183.55, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The stock demonstrated notable volatility, hitting fresh 52-week and all-time highs twice during the week, reflecting underlying strength amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>0417679f440f088c3e4a4562c96459d8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIE Automotive India Ltd Gains 6.87%: Key Technical Shifts and Market Moves This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cie-automotive-india-ltd-gains-687-key-technical-shifts-and-market-moves-this-week-3840241</link><description>CIE Automotive India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 6.87% from Rs.427.05 to Rs.456.40 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s gains were driven by a robust intraday surge on 10 February and a complex technical momentum shift midweek, reflecting a blend of bullish enthusiasm and cautious consolidation.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>6ce581a9b8dacb97639d28fc160abc71</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baid Finserv Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.44% Price, Key Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baid-finserv-ltds-mixed-week--044-price-key-financial-and-technical-signals-3840239</link><description>Baid Finserv Ltd experienced a modest decline of 0.44% in its share price over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.11.39 from Rs.11.44. This performance slightly outpaced the broader Sensex, which fell 0.54% during the same period. The week was marked by significant corporate developments including record quarterly financial results, a notable technical indicator formation, and a rating upgrade by MarketsMOJO, all contributing to a nuanced market sentiment around the stock.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>cd1d425c281433c8eea349c28a8f9325</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ramco Cements Ltd Dips 1.31% Despite New Highs: 3 Key Factors Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-ramco-cements-ltd-dips-131-despite-new-highs-3-key-factors-shaping-the-week-3840236</link><description>The Ramco Cements Ltd experienced a mixed week from 9 to 13 February 2026, opening at Rs.1,203.65 on Monday and closing at Rs.1,145.00 on Friday, marking a weekly decline of 1.31%. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s smaller drop of 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s early surge to a new 52-week and all-time high on 9 February was followed by a series of declines amid rising volumes and margin pressures, reflecting a complex interplay of positive milestones and emerging cautionary signals.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>b061d6574697310b49f8a3c920459bf2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>