<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Market Sentiment with Select Sectoral Strength</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-market-sentiment-with-select-sectoral-strength-3836000</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has delivered a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 2,800 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of companies posting positive results has inched up to 47.0%, mid-cap stocks continue to outperform their large- and small-cap counterparts, signalling a shift in market dynamics and sectoral performance.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>f047fd48dcecdef77e3c279b903d7cfd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Dar Credit &amp; Capital Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dar-credit-capital-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835983</link><description>Dar Credit &amp; Capital Ltd's latest results show a mixed performance, with a 40% increase in net profit and 25% growth in net sales, but concerns remain due to a low return on equity and high debt-to-equity ratio, indicating financial challenges ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>78d78619ba4f57bcd6e96009f1ce2a93</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Carraro India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-carraro-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835982</link><description>Carraro India Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year growth with a net profit increase of 91.27% and revenue growth of 26.95%, despite a quarter-on-quarter decline. The company has improved its operating margin, indicating operational efficiency, but faces challenges in maintaining profitability amid fluctuating costs.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7d5ed7b3c8ff8a742f7abea6a0015fd9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-garuda-construction-and-engineering-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835981</link><description>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are strong, featuring a record net profit of ₹32.90 crores and a revenue of ₹140.02 crores, alongside a high operating margin of 32.22%. However, the company faces challenges with negative operating cash flow of ₹110 crores for FY25, despite its impressive market performance and return on equity of 22.24%.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>17df64f28ad74dc71cfecb24ced22044</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ecos-india-mobility-hospitality-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835980</link><description>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a sequential decline in net sales and profit, raising concerns about sustainability, despite a strong year-on-year growth of 22.48% in revenue and a solid return on equity of 25%. Overall, the performance is mixed, indicating the need for careful monitoring of operational trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b2246fa74d9b83f9b58afbc2fb5355e4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Globale Tessile Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-globale-tessile-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835979</link><description>Globale Tessile Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are poor, showing a net loss of ₹0.37 crores, a 5.82% revenue decline from the previous quarter, and a staggering 78.47% year-on-year drop, indicating significant operational challenges and ongoing financial distress.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bc6ed4a7b8a4845eee39aabcb1a87ef5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are TBO Tek Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tbo-tek-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835978</link><description>TBO Tek Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 25.92% year-over-year, but declining operating margins and profit margins raise concerns about profitability sustainability. While the company maintains a solid market position and financial flexibility, ongoing margin pressures and high valuation multiples warrant careful monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>81c00dab2b7a55b340fafbf17d19242d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Borosil Scientific Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-borosil-scientific-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835977</link><description>Borosil Scientific Ltd's latest results show a net profit of ₹2.89 crores, indicating a recovery from previous losses, but year-on-year sales growth is limited at 3.81%, and operating margins have significantly contracted, raising concerns about operational efficiency and competitive positioning. Overall, while there is some improvement, the company faces ongoing challenges compared to its peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>34de56728e817de357478deea6916e0a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Yatra Online Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-yatra-online-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835976</link><description>Yatra Online Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a year-on-year revenue growth of 9.16% to ₹256.82 crores, but a significant sequential decline of 26.80% and a net profit drop of 41.60% raise concerns about profitability and operational challenges. While the operating margin improved, the overall performance indicates mixed results that may affect investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4be7328ab9e7e79adda9eb2224b62238</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835975</link><description>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd's latest results show strong revenue and profit growth, with net sales up 11.91% quarter-on-quarter and net profit increasing 13.67%. However, concerns about negative operating cash flow and modest return ratios suggest caution is needed regarding the company's financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>297dc68feaedc113a0ff62e736b12c9f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Platinum Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-platinum-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835974</link><description>Platinum Industries Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are concerning, showing an 18.78% decline in net profit year-on-year and a 14.73% drop in revenue from the previous quarter, indicating ongoing operational challenges and margin compression. Overall, the company is facing significant headwinds that require close monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1576c5581cb1fdf8a50de4f32aae994f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Inox India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-inox-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835973</link><description>Inox India Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 16.85% year-on-year, but net profit slightly declined sequentially, indicating margin pressures. Overall, the company demonstrates solid operational metrics and capital efficiency, despite some challenges in maintaining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ca1c324705fb3f8f392eb6e012263223</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nova Agritech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nova-agritech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835972</link><description>Nova Agritech Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 24.54% year-on-year decline in net sales and a 75.28% drop in net profit, indicating significant operational challenges and deteriorating financial performance. Investors should monitor future quarters for potential recovery or further decline.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>566ccfa370024abcfeff4288f16e8b73</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Valiant Laboratories Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-valiant-laboratories-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835971</link><description>Valiant Laboratories Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 115.08% to ₹46.20 crores, but a severe decline in net profit by 89.01% to ₹0.20 crores, indicating significant profitability challenges and operational inefficiencies. Despite the revenue increase, the company's low margins and rising debt raise concerns about its long-term viability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3d8d4b8ab007c9475ea385814f617189</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Protean eGov Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-protean-egov-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835970</link><description>Protean eGov Technologies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit decline of 5.70% sequentially and a revenue drop of 8.63%, raising concerns about profitability and operational stability despite a year-on-year revenue growth of 13.13%. The company's reliance on non-operating income and reduced institutional investor confidence indicate challenges ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c97e4e8f6a286f472d8e9f92c26d0aac</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Concord Biotech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-concord-biotech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835969</link><description>Concord Biotech Ltd's latest results show revenue growth of 12.43% quarter-on-quarter and 13.74% year-on-year, but profitability has declined significantly, with net profit down 15.07% year-on-year and operating margins compressed, indicating ongoing operational challenges. Overall, the performance is mixed, with revenue growth not enough to offset declining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>95bbd76ebbbfeee7c007db70dbfdd02b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Honasa Consumer Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-honasa-consumer-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835968</link><description>Honasa Consumer Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong year-on-year sales growth of 16.51% to ₹538.06 crores, but sequential declines in revenue and profit raise concerns about sustainability. While operational metrics have improved, ongoing challenges in the competitive landscape may impact future growth prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e5cd3b232c9b6f371e6ac60e21b3867f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are ARCL Organics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-arcl-organics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835967</link><description>ARCL Organics Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are poor, showing a net loss of -₹8.81 crores and a 37.96% drop in net sales to ₹53.47 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and raising concerns about the company's future sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>40de5f2f93c1dcff8b9cfdf1a0d813f3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Senco Gold Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-senco-gold-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835966</link><description>Senco Gold Ltd's latest results show a significant year-on-year profit increase of 302.48% to ₹48.78 crores, but a concerning sequential decline of 53.39%. While revenue grew modestly by 2.37% year-on-year, it fell 15.89% quarter-on-quarter, indicating operational challenges that investors should monitor closely.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0687b41a42be7473568b26c40a331e7a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-divgi-torqtransfer-systems-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3835965</link><description>Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth, with Q2 FY26 net sales up 15.75% sequentially and 53.76% year-on-year. However, concerns about margin compression, reliance on non-operating income, and declining return on equity suggest underlying operational challenges that stakeholders should consider.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>662399239351969aca3db0394f9e7009</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>