<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Astral Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astral-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3835516</link><description>Astral Ltd, a key player in the Plastic Products - Industrial sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting investor attention amid mixed fundamental ratings.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>2a54d068f7fe6d0c1e16a9dbeefe4aa3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Seats Ltd: A Multibagger Stock Delivering Exceptional Returns Amidst Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-seats-ltd-a-multibagger-stock-delivering-exceptional-returns-amidst-market-challenges-3835513</link><description>Bharat Seats Ltd has emerged as a standout performer in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, delivering multibagger returns of 112.87% over the past year, vastly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 9.85% gain. This remarkable growth trajectory, coupled with robust financial metrics and a recent upgrade to a Buy rating, positions the company as a compelling investment opportunity despite some near-term volatility.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>052abb652f8d23827804c39cb6544047</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ravinder Heights Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ravinder-heights-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3835496</link><description>Ravinder Heights Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>4913f4391e43500c8f966e39ff26e916</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trejhara Solutions Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trejhara-solutions-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3835497</link><description>Trejhara Solutions Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>e3cf2612dae6237fa92957d11d150d53</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gowra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gowra-leasing-finance-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-momentum-3835499</link><description>Gowra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>849522c2b227411c9f06ba1e59faff40</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goodluck India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goodluck-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3835498</link><description>Goodluck India Ltd, a prominent player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>b788a5decf92f54586d60f0371fb9a2d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balaji Telefilms Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balaji-telefilms-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3835495</link><description>Balaji Telefilms Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>dbdcddd7b51dca2b911a96ff301c309e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunshield Chemicals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sunshield-chemicals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3835494</link><description>Sunshield Chemicals Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>499f8768a1151756230435a67a917b67</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/himadri-speciality-chemical-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3835493</link><description>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, suggesting a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the specialty chemicals company.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>51f3edfe714bf87f28d2288b85c59058</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Market Sentiment with Select Sectoral Strength</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-market-sentiment-with-select-sectoral-strength-3835492</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 2,634 companies reported results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability and a varied performance across market capitalisation segments. While mid-cap stocks continue to lead in positive earnings surprises, large caps have shown signs of stabilisation, supported by select sectoral outperformers.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>0020733db8a5d17177e5f8887836aad7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Royal Cushion Vinyl Products Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Signal Deepening Distress</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/royal-cushion-vinyl-products-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-signal-deepening-distress-3835515</link><description>Royal Cushion Vinyl Products Ltd., a micro-cap manufacturer of PVC vinyl flooring products, reported a widening quarterly loss of ₹4.53 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a sharp deterioration from the ₹1.50 crore loss posted in the same quarter last year. The company's stock has plunged 31.33% over the past year and currently trades at ₹19.84, down 5.30% following the results announcement, reflecting mounting investor concerns over the company's deteriorating financial health and negative book value position.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>fc0b5e8d5a2c80513fe21ec0bd128fdb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mysore Petro Chemicals Q3 FY26: Operating Losses Deepen as Revenue Surge Fails to Translate into Profitability</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mysore-petro-chemicals-q3-fy26-operating-losses-deepen-as-revenue-surge-fails-to-translate-into-profitability-3835514</link><description>Mysore Petro Chemicals Ltd., a Bangalore-based manufacturer and trader of petrochemical products including Phthalic Anhydride and Maleic Anhydride, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹1.91 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a dramatic reversal from the ₹0.10 crore profit posted in Q2 FY26. Despite net sales surging 264.61% quarter-on-quarter to ₹18.34 crores, the company's operating losses widened significantly, raising serious concerns about the sustainability of its business model. The stock, trading at ₹101.48 with a market capitalisation of ₹65.00 crores, has declined 33.19% over the past year, substantially underperforming both the Sensex and its miscellaneous sector peers.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>c64fb92611802cd94732d161aafaeab1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Natco Pharma Q3 FY26: Sharp Revenue Decline Masks Underlying Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/natco-pharma-q3-fy26-sharp-revenue-decline-masks-underlying-volatility-3835512</link><description>Natco Pharma Ltd., the Hyderabad-based pharmaceutical company with a market capitalisation of ₹15,154 crores, reported consolidated net profit of ₹151.50 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sharp 70.78% decline quarter-on-quarter from ₹518.40 crores in Q2 FY26. Year-on-year, profits rose 13.91% from ₹133.00 crores in Q3 FY25, though this comparison is complicated by the highly volatile quarterly performance pattern that has characterised the company's recent financial trajectory.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>35c849296ca289a6523efb3221f5ab78</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aeroflex Enterprises Q3 FY26: Strong Revenue Growth Masks Margin Pressures and Technical Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/aeroflex-enterprises-q3-fy26-strong-revenue-growth-masks-margin-pressures-and-technical-weakness-3835509</link><description>Aeroflex Enterprises Ltd., a micro-cap player in the iron and steel products sector, reported consolidated net profit of ₹16.04 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a sequential increase of 14.82% from Q2 FY26's ₹13.97 crores and a year-on-year gain of 14.49% from Q3 FY25's ₹14.01 crores. However, the headline growth figure belies mounting operational challenges and deteriorating market sentiment, with the stock trading at ₹79.60 as of February 12, 2026—down 30.11% from its 52-week high of ₹113.90 and caught in a persistent bearish technical trend.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>aa347dca9d9886e2a464e35e8d106c66</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Choksi Asia Q3 FY26: Strong Profit Surge Masks Underlying Fundamental Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/choksi-asia-q3-fy26-strong-profit-surge-masks-underlying-fundamental-concerns-3835507</link><description>Choksi Asia Ltd., a micro-cap FMCG player with a market capitalisation of ₹66.00 crores, reported a remarkable net profit of ₹2.13 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sequential increase of 57.78% from ₹1.35 crores in Q2 FY26 and an impressive year-on-year surge of 868.18% from ₹0.22 crores in Q3 FY25. The stock responded enthusiastically to the results, surging 11.11% to close at ₹129.00 on February 12, 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.66% on the same day.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>985cd179679ec004669eb160761cab8c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sainik Finance &amp; Industries Q3 FY26: Micro-Cap Cement Player Struggles with Negative Revenue and Mounting Losses</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sainik-finance-industries-q3-fy26-micro-cap-cement-player-struggles-with-negative-revenue-and-mounting-losses-3835506</link><description>Sainik Finance &amp; Industries Ltd., a micro-cap player in the cement and cement products sector, reported deeply troubling quarterly results for Q3 FY26 (December 2025 quarter), with net sales of negative ₹1.29 crores and a consolidated net loss of ₹8.87 crores. The company, with a market capitalisation of just ₹42.00 crores, continues to struggle with operational viability, posting its second consecutive quarter of negative revenue. Following the results, the stock traded at ₹39.91 on February 12, 2026, down 37.64% from its 52-week high of ₹64.00, though it has gained 3.69% in the most recent trading session.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>462ac6a71f8198023996201d6684c176</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Breadth and Sectoral Divergence</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-breadth-and-sectoral-divergence-3835407</link><description>The mid-cap segment demonstrated modest gains on 12 Feb 2026, with the BSE Midcap index inching up by 0.1% amid a mixed market breadth and divergent sectoral performances. Despite a subdued advance-decline ratio, select stocks exhibited bullish momentum, signalling cautious optimism among investors ahead of a busy results week.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>71cfcb6e8fbf9517b0d6787a09efa1ec</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>