<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Axis Solutions Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.133.95 Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axis-solutions-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs13395-marking-significant-milestone-3820103</link><description>Axis Solutions Ltd reached a new all-time high of Rs.133.95 on 4 Feb 2026, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and underscoring the company’s strong market performance over recent months.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>052df59d52158236f963cda8f230ff4a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saraswati Commercial (India) Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saraswati-commercial-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3820104</link><description>Saraswati Commercial (India) Ltd commenced trading on 4 Feb 2026 with a pronounced gap down, opening at Rs 11,801, reflecting a 5.96% decline from its previous close. This weak start underscores prevailing market apprehensions surrounding the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector and the stock’s recent performance trends.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>a240b16953b6b7ab72b0e82c61081f33</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sigachi Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 12.46% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sigachi-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1246-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820101</link><description>Sigachi Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 23.25, marking a significant 12.75% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and sustained buying momentum.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>83a6f9585612ceeff5794d5a9c2c20e6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ABB India Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.16% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/abb-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-316-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820102</link><description>ABB India Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 5,865, marking a 3.44% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong buying momentum and sustained gains over recent sessions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>75485aa9d2d86ba4098e9e4cb06bdc16</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suven Life Sciences Ltd Hits Intraday High with 10.45% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suven-life-sciences-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1045-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820098</link><description>Suven Life Sciences Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 163.05, marking a significant 10.45% increase from the previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and positive trading momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b5b8815c03a09f87ef37e5fd886361ff</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avanti Feeds Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 7.25% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avanti-feeds-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-725-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820096</link><description>Avanti Feeds Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday momentum on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a new 52-week high of Rs 1040, marking an 8.27% rise from its previous close. The stock outperformed its FMCG sector peers and broader market indices, reflecting strong buying interest and sustained upward trading action.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6bde3563acb476528143eb10dabb8ba6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JBM Auto Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.56% Surge on 4 February 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jbm-auto-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-756-surge-on-4-february-2026-3820099</link><description>JBM Auto Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 611.25, marking a 7.21% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting strong buying momentum during the trading session.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>8fc069f7baebc70b6a78da59116d6bba</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Count Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 11.54% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-count-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1154-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820100</link><description>Indo Count Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 309.9, marking an 11.54% increase from the previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum and notable volatility throughout the session.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>3b9673b817c948fbaaf49abf1048a9e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nelcast Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 7.29% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nelcast-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-729-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820097</link><description>Nelcast Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday momentum on 4 February 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 119.39, marking a 9.48% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading activity and positive price action throughout the session.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>c9b126b74237fcaa8e5ba9fa234792e5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Consultancy Services Ltd. Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-consultancy-services-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3820094</link><description>Tata Consultancy Services Ltd. (TCS) commenced trading on 4 Feb 2026 with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price 3.15% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market apprehension following overnight developments. The stock’s weak start was accompanied by notable intraday volatility, underscoring investor caution in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6aa649a8e42174896c7fd013d102d748</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nelcast Ltd. Opens Strong with Significant Gap Up Amid Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nelcast-ltd-opens-strong-with-significant-gap-up-amid-positive-market-sentiment-3820095</link><description>Nelcast Ltd., a key player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, commenced trading today with a notable gap up, opening 8.21% higher than its previous close. This strong start underscores a positive market sentiment amid a sustained upward trend, as the stock continues to outperform its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>fa1635ffb582ed76ac50abfbd77e1b33</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infosys-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3820093</link><description>Infosys Ltd commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening 4.51% lower amid broader sector weakness and market apprehensions. The stock’s early session saw intensified selling pressure, reflecting investor caution following overnight developments.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>238f40d5c03d21f95d6a09c059250f77</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GPT Healthcare Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gpt-healthcare-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3820092</link><description>GPT Healthcare Ltd, a player in the hospital sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.123.15, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial metrics and investor sentiment.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>4b3048cdf194b32958c4042c7c9b4f5b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digidrive Distributors Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/digidrive-distributors-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3820091</link><description>Shares of Digidrive Distributors Ltd, a player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, plunged to a fresh all-time low of Rs. 20.11 on 4 Feb 2026, marking a significant decline of 9.74% on the day. This drop extends a sustained period of underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>f98c81668c3694a903f148688f30a7ac</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TruAlt Bioenergy Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trualt-bioenergy-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-4-feb-2026-3820088</link><description>TruAlt Bioenergy Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 4 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 366.35, down 9.34% from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure and heightened volatility despite a recovering Sensex.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>14b273ab206a8e66164d710edaf67041</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HMA Agro Industries Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hma-agro-industries-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3820089</link><description>HMA Agro Industries Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, recorded a new all-time low share price of Rs.23.55 on 4 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing market performance challenges. Despite a recent short-term uptick, the stock continues to trail broader market indices and sector benchmarks, reflecting persistent pressures on its financial and operational metrics.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>bfa01bc2edce2fad4680f478664c6162</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.34% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rashi-peripherals-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-734-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820090</link><description>Rashi Peripherals Ltd surged to a fresh 52-week intraday high of Rs 410.5 on 4 Feb 2026, marking a robust 12.65% gain during the trading session. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong intraday momentum and heightened volatility.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>c777e56d6f6187cfd34838f029a316ca</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-amid-robust-gains-3820087</link><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high, reflecting robust market performance and sustained investor confidence. The stock’s recent surge underscores its resilience and strong positioning within the private sector banking industry.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>10dba30fec0d8c766959a38cf0c21f33</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tarsons Products Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.99% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tarsons-products-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-799-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820085</link><description>Tarsons Products Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 219.75, marking a 7.38% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting heightened trading activity and volatility throughout the session.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>d6464adb65b185a327042477907c56cb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.22% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-822-surge-3820081</link><description>Network People Services Technologies Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 1299, marking an 8.22% gain. This notable uptick came amid a volatile trading session and contrasted with the broader sector's decline, underscoring the stock’s distinct market action today.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>1c73d4a0db92fa7f02598bdeb54f9521</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>