<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Vikram Aroma Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vikram-aroma-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831648</link><description>Vikram Aroma Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net profit of -₹0.04 crores and a 49.09% year-on-year revenue decline, indicating ongoing operational challenges and unprofitability. Despite a slight improvement in operating margin, the company has faced losses in six of the last seven quarters, raising significant concerns about its financial health and growth prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>01b0e048f304cd6e1f9e29a0411b1172</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Enviro Infra Engineers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-enviro-infra-engineers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831647</link><description>Enviro Infra Engineers Ltd's latest results show a strong net profit growth of 36.93% year-on-year, but revenue declined by 5.63% sequentially, indicating challenges in consistent revenue generation despite improved operational efficiency. The company faces potential issues with order execution and revenue volatility, raising concerns about the sustainability of its earnings growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9c3ed43c6aaf37ca5f6cb99e49dd7eb9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are JNK India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jnk-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831646</link><description>JNK India Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, showing a net profit increase of 540.14% and record revenue growth of 115.85% year-on-year. However, concerns about sustainability and declining annual revenue for FY25 indicate a mixed outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>110f765633fe99f7e206ef8e7289593f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mukka Proteins Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mukka-proteins-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831645</link><description>Mukka Proteins Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 43.22% quarter-on-quarter and net profit up 286.84%, but operational challenges like high interest costs and inconsistent profitability raise concerns about sustainability. Overall, the results are mixed, indicating both positive growth and underlying financial risks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0698c2cca5efd6d9e635d354190d1e97</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are RDB Real Estate Construction Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rdb-real-estate-construction-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831644</link><description>RDB Real Estate Construction Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 13.66% decline in net sales and a significant loss of ₹3.59 crores, driven by high interest costs and a troubling debt situation, indicating severe operational and financial challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8cc2dcdb71decca937e9f1fcdea0ebeb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-p-n-gadgil-jewellers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831643</link><description>P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd's latest results are positive, with a net profit of ₹79.31 crores for Q2 FY26, reflecting a 127.12% year-on-year growth and improved operational efficiency, indicated by a 4.92% operating margin. The company's performance shows strong demand and effective management strategies.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9d0427f58c448d0be9a4f6674a499e37</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Afcons Infrastructure Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-afcons-infrastructure-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831642</link><description>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd's latest results are concerning, with a sequential decline in net sales and profit, indicating operational challenges and increased cost pressures. The company's financial metrics suggest difficulties in maintaining profitability and growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ffaf6d2d23f150f3bd426e058628c699</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Alpex Solar Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-alpex-solar-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831641</link><description>Alpex Solar Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with net sales up 245.40% year-on-year and a net profit increase of 132.02%. However, declining operating and profit margins, along with rising costs, indicate potential challenges ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2c218eba4d87d7222f01a2eb794b4fea</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Signpost India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-signpost-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831640</link><description>Signpost India Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 26.85% year-on-year and a net profit increase of 215.30%, indicating robust operational performance. However, concerns over high valuation and rising debt have led to cautious investor sentiment despite the positive financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e92cc6c30394607ce8f395a80b2330f4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Happy Forgings Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-happy-forgings-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831639</link><description>Happy Forgings Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong operational performance with an 11.80% net profit increase and improved margins, but modest year-on-year revenue growth and a high valuation relative to peers may raise investor caution. Overall, the results are mixed, highlighting both strengths and potential concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>244dfafe4a4c8f0ef23d1b6a9abc87d0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Muthoot Microfin Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-muthoot-microfin-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831638</link><description>Muthoot Microfin Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a significant recovery with a net profit of ₹62.44 crores, up 104.52% from the previous quarter, despite ongoing challenges like low return on capital employed and a decline in year-on-year revenue. While the company is improving operational efficiency, it must address concerns about sustainability and investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7aafbed8398966f2cd9f1086bb7f3794</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Pyramid Technoplast Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-pyramid-technoplast-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831637</link><description>Pyramid Technoplast Ltd's latest results show a modest revenue growth of 0.42% to ₹161.49 crores, but net profit fell sharply by 22.93% to ₹4.74 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and rising costs. Overall, the results reflect declining profitability despite stable sales, suggesting a difficult financial landscape for the company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>46df65f2e4cbe26c8de9df57bbd7cd40</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Supreme Power Equipment Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-supreme-power-equipment-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831636</link><description>Supreme Power Equipment Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a mixed performance, with a net profit decline of 31.85% and a sequential revenue drop of 10.72%, despite a year-on-year sales growth of 16.98%. The operating margin also decreased significantly, indicating operational challenges, although the company maintains a healthy return on equity of 19.53%.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dbbfd6450249d89bca5a2937efc36b83</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Credo Brands Marketing Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-credo-brands-marketing-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831635</link><description>Credo Brands Marketing Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show mixed performance, with net sales up 15.13% year-on-year but down 1.49% sequentially, and a significant drop in net profit by 24.47%. While revenue growth is positive, declining profitability and operating margins raise concerns about operational efficiency and cost management.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4d3d67edf5b8a94af9d34722bd0150d7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Asarfi Hospital Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-asarfi-hospital-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831634</link><description>Asarfi Hospital Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit of ₹5.42 crores (up 102.24% year-on-year) and revenue of ₹46.10 crores (up 40.16% year-on-year), indicating robust growth and improved operational efficiency, despite a slight sequential revenue decline. Overall, the company's performance is encouraging for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2cb9d2d61f871a4100f304d717087b7f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-udayshivakumar-infra-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831633</link><description>Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show a 24.53% year-on-year decline in net sales to ₹57.71 crores, but a significant improvement in net profit to ₹0.82 crores from a loss in the previous quarter. Overall, while there are signs of short-term stabilization, long-term performance remains concerning due to structural issues and low investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dc5fc592d3b942804f21584971c95588</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ddev-plastiks-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831632</link><description>DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year growth with a net profit of ₹47.11 crores, but a sequential decline in both profit and revenue raises concerns about demand sustainability and margin pressures. While the company maintains a solid return on equity, ongoing operational challenges warrant careful monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1b69e0cc78d0e46b17fe0b7f559a90a5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Abans Financial Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-abans-financial-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831631</link><description>Abans Financial Services Ltd reported impressive revenue growth of 965.35% year-on-year for Q2 FY26, but faced significant challenges with profitability, as operating margins contracted sharply to 0.70%. While net profit increased by 50.41%, concerns about sustainability and liquidity risks remain, indicating a mixed financial performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cde9078cb208a9dd6f3aee3738a80ae7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aarti-pharmalabs-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831630</link><description>Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd's latest results show a 71.78% sequential increase in net profit to ₹47.96 crores, but a 35.18% year-on-year decline raises concerns. While net sales grew 3.33% sequentially, they fell 19.62% year-on-year, indicating ongoing revenue challenges despite improved operating margins.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>676d24d0b3cc02743ed250110aa785fb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Dharmaj Crop Guard Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dharmaj-crop-guard-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3831629</link><description>Dharmaj Crop Guard Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 36.03% year-on-year, but a concerning 46.82% decline in net profit and rising operational challenges suggest a cautious outlook for the company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e8ba86d42f211e1176cb09153933a2bd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>