<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3841233</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 3,956 companies declared results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability but persistent sectoral disparities. While mid-cap firms continue to outperform their large-cap counterparts in terms of positive earnings surprises, the overall market sentiment remains cautious amid mixed financial metrics and evolving macroeconomic conditions.
Time: Feb 15 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>aee0a451e73832a4244e82f74aca3c1f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3841219</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results across market capitalisation segments and sectors, as 3,956 companies declared their financials. While the proportion of companies reporting positive results has inched up slightly to 46.0%, the overall trend remains subdued compared to the previous quarter, reflecting ongoing challenges in the broader economy and sector-specific headwinds.
Time: Feb 15 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>38e59779025d9edbaabdef327bf3dfae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paragon Finance Ltd Gains 10.33%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paragon-finance-ltd-gains-1033-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3841217</link><description>Paragon Finance Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 10.33% from ₹45.32 to ₹50.00 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of valuation shifts, quarterly financial results, and an upgrade in analyst ratings, all contributing to the stock’s volatile yet upward trajectory amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:02 PM IST</description><guid>c99810e41e9f3452670daae938c5cc94</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Repro India Ltd Gains 15.74%: Key Technical Shifts and Q3 Profitability Spark Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/repro-india-ltd-gains-1574-key-technical-shifts-and-q3-profitability-spark-rally-3841216</link><description>Repro India Ltd. delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 15.74% from ₹412.30 to ₹477.20 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable technical momentum shift and a return to profitability in Q3 FY26, which together catalysed the sharp price appreciation despite broader market weakness.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:02 PM IST</description><guid>7147c195d0ba01e1f4a4f454efd69e88</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ircon International’s Mixed Week: -0.20% Price Change Amid Profit Concerns and Technical Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ircon-internationals-mixed-week--020-price-change-amid-profit-concerns-and-technical-headwinds-3841214</link><description>Ircon International Ltd’s stock closed the week marginally lower by 0.20% at Rs.152.95, slightly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp profit decline reported on 11 Feb and subsequent technical headwinds that weighed on investor sentiment, resulting in a volatile trading range and cautious market stance.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:02 PM IST</description><guid>162bbe59b6f0cbe9b9da11343b05c0ba</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Praj Industries Gains 8.38%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/praj-industries-gains-838-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3841215</link><description>Praj Industries Ltd delivered a volatile but ultimately positive week, closing at Rs.309.15 on 13 February 2026, up 8.38% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.285.25. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period, reflecting a week of sharp intraday swings, strong institutional interest, valuation concerns, and operational challenges that shaped investor sentiment.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:02 PM IST</description><guid>62897d759bdd955a6c1f440099a9ec27</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panth Infinity Ltd Edges Lower by 0.22%: 2 Key Factors Shaping This Week’s Movement</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/panth-infinity-ltd-edges-lower-by-022-2-key-factors-shaping-this-weeks-movement-3841213</link><description>Panth Infinity Ltd closed the week marginally lower by 0.22% at Rs.8.89, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54%. The week was marked by a significant upgrade to a Buy rating on 9 February, driven by strong financial results and improved technical indicators, followed by a mixed reaction to the company’s Q2 FY26 earnings report. Despite volatility, the stock demonstrated resilience with notable intraday gains and a sharp rebound midweek.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:02 PM IST</description><guid>689aa771db6b7fc7b3c6a2a296f845f2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Investments &amp; Commercials Ltd Gains 1.05%: Key Milestones and Market Dynamics This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/welspun-investments-commercials-ltd-gains-105-key-milestones-and-market-dynamics-this-week-3841204</link><description>Welspun Investments &amp; Commercials Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.05% from Rs.1,286.55 to Rs.1,300.00 between 9 and 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by a new 52-week and all-time high on 13 February, despite some volatility and a sharp intraday decline on the final trading day. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s trajectory during the week.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>ea905bf1f050a4e1c87f7f6c80b9d3d0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympia Industries Declines 1.80% Amid 52-Week Low and Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/olympia-industries-declines-180-amid-52-week-low-and-margin-pressures-3841206</link><description>Olympia Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 1.80% from Rs.31.11 to Rs.30.55, underperforming the Sensex which fell by 0.54%. Despite early gains on Monday and Tuesday, the stock faced selling pressure midweek, culminating in a steady downtrend amid fresh 52-week lows and mixed quarterly results.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>94d061053b3fb48fa2e2633f565ac6f4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ASM Technologies Ltd Gains 9.15%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asm-technologies-ltd-gains-915-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3841211</link><description>ASM Technologies Ltd recorded a robust weekly gain of 9.15%, closing at Rs.2,771.40 on 13 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s strong performance was driven by a combination of technical developments and valuation shifts that shaped investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>5a50f6c42b1f2bc2444ad3bda01fb103</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seasons Textiles Gains 1.41%: Valuation Shift and Mixed Weekly Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/seasons-textiles-gains-141-valuation-shift-and-mixed-weekly-signals-3841207</link><description>Seasons Textiles Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.41%, closing at Rs.18.00 on 13 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable valuation shift to very attractive levels amid persistent revenue pressures and cautious market sentiment, reflected in a strong sell mojo grade. Daily price movements showed initial strength followed by a late-week pullback, correlating with key corporate developments and market dynamics.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>da8973ca99329ac8f222dbabab12207a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Graphite India Gains 4.71%: Quarterly Turnaround and Market Resilience Highlight Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/graphite-india-gains-471-quarterly-turnaround-and-market-resilience-highlight-week-3841212</link><description>Graphite India Ltd. delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 4.71% from ₹619.20 to ₹648.35, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s gains were supported by a strong quarterly earnings report on 9 February and a subsequent upgrade in mojo grade, despite some operational challenges highlighted during the week.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>3f3f84b5c0337cf73736b8af0c84c0a0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVV Infra Ltd’s Subtle Decline of 0.58% Masks Strong Financial Upgrades</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pvv-infra-ltds-subtle-decline-of-058-masks-strong-financial-upgrades-3841210</link><description>PVV Infra Ltd experienced a mixed week from 9 to 13 February 2026, closing marginally lower by 0.58% at Rs.5.16, slightly underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54%. The week was marked by a strong quarterly earnings turnaround, an upgrade to a Strong Buy rating, and notable shifts in valuation and quality grades, reflecting both optimism and caution among investors.
Time: Feb 15 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>9d0cf261173b34a00941760423bed9b2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>