<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-international-gemmological-institute-india-ltd-fallingrising-3808549</link><description>On 28 Jan, International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd witnessed a significant price rally, with its shares rising by 9.9% to close at ₹319.70, marking a notable reversal after two days of decline and outperforming its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d9397cb8798889c4256b7858dff3a478</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-fallingrising-3808548</link><description>On 28-Jan, Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹404.55, down by ₹4.10 or 1.0%. This drop reflects ongoing challenges in the company’s financial performance and valuation concerns, which have weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a8a965fee1521d59bed9b2827de691a9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Azad Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-azad-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3808547</link><description>On 28-Jan, Azad Engineering Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 3.88% to ₹1,500.40 by 9:17 PM, reflecting a combination of robust quarterly performance and positive sector trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3a384e483eefe131b438410948d78668</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GHCL Textiles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ghcl-textiles-ltd-fallingrising-3808546</link><description>On 28-Jan, GHCL Textiles Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 5.59% to ₹77.21 by 9:15 PM. This upward movement comes despite a backdrop of mixed fundamental indicators and a challenging one-year performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1904f3f99dfd97b6e38e07d00505fc62</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Fusion Finance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-fusion-finance-ltd-fallingrising-3808545</link><description>As of 28-Jan, Fusion Finance Ltd’s stock price has surged by 3.58% to ₹185.05, continuing a recent upward trend that contrasts sharply with its underlying financial challenges. This article examines the factors driving the stock’s rise amid a backdrop of weak fundamentals and sector dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>224cb025e140e66c5195b7701b28a19f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Alivus Life Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-alivus-life-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3808544</link><description>On 28-Jan, Alivus Life Sciences Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹935.00 with a gain of ₹47.3 or 5.33%. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust quarterly financial performance and sustained market outperformance relative to benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b545a423e48078d84e9fdb08f68a5fd1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinyas-innovative-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3808543</link><description>On 28-Jan, Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.14% to close at ₹1,042.70. This downward movement reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by technical indicators signalling weakness.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3d0c747313b963f8c46e7b032928104f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Goldkart Jewels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-goldkart-jewels-ltd-fallingrising-3808542</link><description>As of 28-Jan, Goldkart Jewels Ltd has witnessed an extraordinary surge in its stock price, rising by 300.28% to ₹285.00, marking a new 52-week and all-time high. This remarkable performance significantly outpaces the broader market and sector benchmarks, reflecting heightened investor interest and robust trading dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6c7fbc5887f815d733cb3e2aae251a86</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GCM Securities Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gcm-securities-ltd-fallingrising-3808541</link><description>On 28-Jan, GCM Securities Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 5.63% to close at ₹0.75. This increase reflects a short-term positive momentum in the stock, outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e5500ce848ca2e21f3140eb7993cb720</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is United Van Der Horst Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-united-van-der-horst-ltd-fallingrising-3808540</link><description>On 28-Jan, United Van Der Horst Ltd experienced a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.99% to close at ₹48.55. This drop comes amid a three-day losing streak, despite the company’s impressive long-term performance and robust financial results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1862d7748f7d56f42a018683a556980d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-garden-reach-shipbuilders-engineers-ltd-fallingrising-3808539</link><description>On 28-Jan, Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, closing at ₹2,521.60, up by ₹135.50 or 5.68%. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust long-term fundamentals, positive quarterly results, and favourable sector dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>890232cb65c5460df47c22c141435b14</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ircon International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ircon-international-ltd-fallingrising-3808538</link><description>On 28-Jan, Ircon International Ltd’s stock price surged by 5.57% to close at ₹163.85, marking a notable rebound despite the company’s challenging financial backdrop and recent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d539fe1d2160a72e394039c033fd5901</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bandhan Bank Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bandhan-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3808537</link><description>On 28-Jan, Bandhan Bank Ltd. witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.65% to close at ₹152.90. This upward movement comes despite a backdrop of mixed financial performance and cautious investor sentiment, reflecting a complex interplay of factors influencing the stock’s trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d0e3875b6544448539729f3e2253cb35</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Moksh Ornaments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-moksh-ornaments-ltd-fallingrising-3808536</link><description>As of 28-Jan, Moksh Ornaments Ltd has experienced a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.46% to ₹13.87. This downturn reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by subdued investor participation and disappointing financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>855d64ddb5558acd47b6a2b3516ab790</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omfurn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omfurn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3808535</link><description>On 28-Jan, Omfurn India Ltd's stock price rose by 1.48% to ₹64.95, reflecting a notable short-term rebound despite a challenging longer-term performance. This movement is underpinned by increased investor participation and a relative outperformance compared to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c7f45fb2d7bf3723ba54337dd1df7a7c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Overseas (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-overseas-india-ltd-fallingrising-3808534</link><description>On 28-Jan, Shanti Overseas (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹7.32, down by 3.05%. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s prolonged underperformance, driven by weak financial results, deteriorating fundamentals, and diminishing promoter confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>081813aaa499dd90d7d234e8435521b4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Polo Queen Industrial and Fintech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-polo-queen-industrial-and-fintech-ltd-fallingrising-3808533</link><description>On 28-Jan, Polo Queen Industrial and Fintech Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹25.12, down ₹0.65 or 2.52% from the previous session. This drop coincided with the stock hitting a new 52-week low and continuing a three-day losing streak, reflecting mounting investor concerns over the company’s deteriorating financial performance and valuation challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>288bb3189c21ab6d078085354de6bf80</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Archidply Decor Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-archidply-decor-ltd-fallingrising-3808532</link><description>On 28-Jan, Archidply Decor Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 6.58%, closing at ₹75.00, reflecting a significant rebound amid a backdrop of prolonged underperformance and fundamental weaknesses.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5c150a5b17ffdef6534ccfd59b887390</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Advik Capital Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-advik-capital-ltd-fallingrising-3808531</link><description>On 28-Jan, Advik Capital Ltd's stock price surged by 11.36% to ₹1.47, marking a notable rebound after three consecutive days of decline. This rise comes despite the company’s ongoing operational challenges and weak long-term fundamentals, highlighting a complex interplay between short-term market dynamics and underlying financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b953dbae4f5999dcfd15c88f584dbb33</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Apar Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-apar-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3808530</link><description>On 28-Jan, Apar Industries Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 2.97%, closing at ₹7,425.00. This rise comes despite a complex backdrop of recent underperformance and fluctuating investor participation, reflecting a nuanced market response to the stock’s technical and sectoral dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>908dc25be7cbd794d9de275103ee51b6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>