<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>When is the next results date for Indrayani Biotech Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-indrayani-biotech-ltd-3854406</link><description>The next results date for Indrayani Biotech Ltd is 26 February 2026.
Time: Feb 24 2026 11:16 PM IST</description><guid>024e4ce852ad711f7e74ca5371fc88d1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Vesuvius India Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-vesuvius-india-ltd-3854405</link><description>The next results date for Vesuvius India Ltd is 26 February 2026.
Time: Feb 24 2026 11:16 PM IST</description><guid>90ca97d08425842f6ebda1597000cc42</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-nova-iron-steel-ltd-3854404</link><description>The next results date for Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd is 26 February 2026.
Time: Feb 24 2026 11:16 PM IST</description><guid>74ba6ce226a64ff593c17449778b53e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Fractal Analyt.?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-fractal-analyt-3854403</link><description>Fractal Analyt. will announce its results on March 5, 2026.
Time: Feb 24 2026 11:16 PM IST</description><guid>ea2837aeeba12e411f352e181027c345</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3854390</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 4,085 companies declared results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability and sales growth. While the overall proportion of companies reporting positive results rose slightly to 46.0%, sectoral and market capitalisation segments displayed divergent trends, underscoring the varied pace of recovery and operational performance across industries and company sizes.
Time: Feb 24 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>608d2d6ea6f1d568d99bb0d171fdb967</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Latent View Analytics Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/latent-view-analytics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3853460</link><description>Latent View Analytics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: Feb 24 2026 06:45 PM IST</description><guid>a7d93271a34e3943f2696d6baa0cb7e4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sellwin Traders Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sellwin-traders-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3853458</link><description>Sellwin Traders Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: Feb 24 2026 06:45 PM IST</description><guid>9ba074b0e119aad987aee26975293e6d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/authum-investment-infrastructure-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3853462</link><description>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: Feb 24 2026 06:45 PM IST</description><guid>2827e11b0d3a9f150542f40710062f84</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Regency Ceramics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/regency-ceramics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3853461</link><description>Regency Ceramics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: Feb 24 2026 06:45 PM IST</description><guid>2e2ea2a73c745a1c6892b70f27b69acc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Triveni Engineering and Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/triveni-engineering-and-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3853459</link><description>Triveni Engineering and Industries Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the sugar sector company, which has seen mixed performance against the broader market over the past year.
Time: Feb 24 2026 06:45 PM IST</description><guid>58b620672ca9056fb693f695661c66a6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3853422</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded with 4,082 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced picture of corporate performance across market capitalisations. While the proportion of companies delivering positive results has inched up slightly to 46.0%, sectoral and size-based disparities remain evident, underscoring the varied pace of recovery and growth across the Indian equity landscape.
Time: Feb 24 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>e49c0341b3d5c8a43487677746d2f7ce</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 1082</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-1082-3853367</link><description>Network People Services Technologies Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, closing at Rs.1082, marking a significant decline amid broader sectoral and market pressures. The stock’s recent performance reflects a combination of valuation concerns and subdued profit trends over the past year.
Time: Feb 24 2026 04:06 PM IST</description><guid>3fec07f77512c5fc89ba21830f18b6e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>