<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Standard Glass Lining Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-glass-lining-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3783823</link><description>On 06-Jan, Standard Glass Lining Technology Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹142.20, down ₹2.45 or 1.69% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum amid broader market and sector challenges.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>37a9bb75e0587ae0e21c47746fcc709c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Chamunda Electrical Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-chamunda-electrical-ltd-fallingrising-3783822</link><description>As of 06-Jan, Chamunda Electrical Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 3.33% to ₹49.30, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor participation.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>60e02df4b660b985298b770183580aa0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sahasra-electronic-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3783821</link><description>On 06-Jan, Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.86% to close at ₹281.80. This downward movement reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and weakening investor participation.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b2a628fbfe4561c8681f566ad8d4ec33</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gajanand International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gajanand-international-ltd-fallingrising-3783820</link><description>On 06-Jan, Gajanand International Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 15.69%, closing at ₹11.80. This sharp rise reflects a notable shift in investor sentiment and short-term trading dynamics, as the stock outperformed both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>8229afee6adb5fc08d7ea3e8ca09b062</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3783819</link><description>On 06-Jan, Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 7.55%, closing at ₹1,194.10, reflecting renewed investor confidence driven by robust quarterly results and attractive valuation metrics.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>cd950c1a4eb1ee0f43098c1197d3ffa0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Harshdeep Hortico Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-harshdeep-hortico-ltd-fallingrising-3783818</link><description>On 06-Jan, Harshdeep Hortico Ltd's stock price rose by 2.04% to close at ₹100.00, reflecting robust investor interest and significant outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a2a15184d77262fb2519ca517f516ad6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Australian Premium Solar (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-australian-premium-solar-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783817</link><description>As of 06-Jan, Australian Premium Solar (India) Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 2.03% to ₹352.80, continuing a downward trend that reflects a complex interplay of strong financial growth overshadowed by disappointing market performance and investor sentiment.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>68bf8d3e337c3fca9cb12d6cd6d445f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kalyani Cast-Tech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kalyani-cast-tech-ltd-fallingrising-3783816</link><description>On 06-Jan, Kalyani Cast-Tech Ltd’s stock price fell sharply, closing at ₹451.10, down ₹13.55 or 2.92%, reflecting a continuation of recent negative momentum and underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e8c8c5bc076eb56a6a82ee8cd77912f0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is C P S Shapers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-c-p-s-shapers-ltd-fallingrising-3783815</link><description>On 06-Jan, C P S Shapers Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, reaching a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹1,306.45. This surge reflects robust investor confidence and notable outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>5551099b3c6538907104536c957794f7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Piramal Pharma Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-piramal-pharma-ltd-fallingrising-3783814</link><description>On 06-Jan, Piramal Pharma Ltd's share price rose by 0.64% to ₹180.05, continuing a recent upward trend despite underlying financial challenges and a history of underperformance relative to the broader market.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b7c46dc669cff7f5a6d84c91f28c54fb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-divgi-torqtransfer-systems-ltd-fallingrising-3783813</link><description>On 06-Jan, Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd recorded a modest rise in its share price, closing at ₹618.00, up by ₹1.95 or 0.32%. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust quarterly financial results and relative outperformance against broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f81f6acd0bdcc3d2344ddfd3da59895f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Fusion Finance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-fusion-finance-ltd-fallingrising-3783812</link><description>On 06-Jan, Fusion Finance Ltd's stock price rose sharply by 5.22% to ₹177.30, continuing a strong upward trend despite underlying fundamental weaknesses and volatile trading patterns.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f86bad3a5c1411a7b1a330f4067eea6c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Greenchef Appliances Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-greenchef-appliances-ltd-fallingrising-3783811</link><description>On 06-Jan, Greenchef Appliances Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 1.37% to ₹59.30, outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks despite some underlying challenges in investor participation.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>ea09e30c3afc6f15a167a9499d606264</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-upsurge-seeds-of-agriculture-ltd-fallingrising-3783810</link><description>On 06-Jan, Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.24% to close at ₹140.00. This downturn contrasts sharply with the broader market's modest gains, highlighting sector-specific challenges and persistent underperformance over multiple time horizons.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>fb85e522620dd5f7da546ba448cd2d8c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pace E-Commerce Ventures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pace-e-commerce-ventures-ltd-fallingrising-3783809</link><description>On 06-Jan, Pace E-Commerce Ventures Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.13% to close at ₹18.80. This drop comes after a brief two-day rally and reflects broader challenges faced by the stock over recent periods.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>2936b3d94b4f4f4d01ba85967d3e1deb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Home First Finance Company India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783808</link><description>On 06-Jan, Home First Finance Company India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.02% to close at ₹1,071.50. This drop reflects a short-term underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market, despite the company’s robust long-term financial performance and positive quarterly results.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>1858a8c47cb94c2e17fe41c65f1629d9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Euro Panel Products Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-euro-panel-products-ltd-fallingrising-3783807</link><description>On 06-Jan, Euro Panel Products Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.81% to close at ₹169.30. This downturn reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by subdued investor participation and technical weaknesses.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>7aa0d07a3b2de397706aadbc7fdd38a3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Debock Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-debock-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3783806</link><description>On 06-Jan, Debock Industries Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹1.66, down 2.92% from the previous session. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including sustained operating losses and significant underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>c27f3a12c793a2f3c47a41cb3b60a443</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Hardwyn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hardwyn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783805</link><description>On 06-Jan, Hardwyn India Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 10.65%, closing at ₹19.22, driven by robust short-term performance and a fresh 52-week high, outpacing both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f37c5e2be49a01f9c3691a42b573f5a8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-fallingrising-3783804</link><description>On 06-Jan, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 9.15% to close at ₹48.15. This sharp drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d6ac7f3c65f855127ae625118fcc42c4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>