<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865644</link><description>Swiggy Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development reflects a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>0d3af085faceae4d0e43cdd0c31226f5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ACME Solar Holdings Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/acme-solar-holdings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865645</link><description>ACME Solar Holdings Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum, raising concerns among investors about potential further downside.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>20aa089c6bfc0e1be5e52e9edd3c7f7e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/waaree-energies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865642</link><description>Waaree Energies Ltd, a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>499751fe7bd723e7b7cbcdb5b7e5fde7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyundai Motor India Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hyundai-motor-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865641</link><description>Hyundai Motor India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors and market participants should carefully analyse this event in the context of the company’s recent performance and broader market conditions.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>e4aac0ae510149387fc16c30f00412ce</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diffusion Engineers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/diffusion-engineers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865643</link><description>Diffusion Engineers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development reflects a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already subdued fundamentals and weak price performance.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>ebe1dd12c7d9a3bb1bb59e66ed99e7f6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manba Finance Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manba-finance-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865639</link><description>Manba Finance Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>4e5233cd9a09d8e1ca71f8688bd22eb6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Western Carriers (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/western-carriers-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3865640</link><description>Western Carriers (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength within the Transport Services sector.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>0235b9f3bbfa9e339cb6a49197e1e033</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/p-n-gadgil-jewellers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865634</link><description>P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>35acdcd6a91dfba49355af5b20563098</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tolins Tyres Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tolins-tyres-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865635</link><description>Tolins Tyres Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average, forming a Death Cross. This event is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>bfdc1f7745c916b0d54819972aed40a5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/raymond-lifestyle-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865638</link><description>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already challenging fundamentals and sector headwinds.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>81d338b5896e7ce823303ebf45559b98</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Interarch Building Solutions Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/interarch-building-solutions-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3865632</link><description>Interarch Building Solutions Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness in the construction sector stock.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>7c8eca047ffd62ceaa86b5792ffd7211</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allied-blenders-distillers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3865633</link><description>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>5d8fc0f9e30b89d03eea4d0686011318</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G K P Printing &amp; Packaging Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-k-p-printing-packaging-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3865637</link><description>G K P Printing &amp; Packaging Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>8ca0474c1bbd6d7f182bdf41c30d1a63</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tembo Global Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tembo-global-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3865630</link><description>Tembo Global Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s short-term momentum relative to its long-term trend, raising concerns about sustained weakness in the coming months.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>15de19f1ab8a0a5389f689dd08a8efb4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greenlam Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/greenlam-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3865629</link><description>Greenlam Industries Ltd has recently experienced a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average has crossed below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>85bb272729b1e32df213e3c2eea2771a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Captain Polyplast Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/captain-polyplast-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3865631</link><description>Captain Polyplast Ltd (Stock ID: 301332), a player in the Plastic Products - Industrial sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>e32e8c449fe8e52c902c4f41ee7993f0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kross Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kross-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3865636</link><description>Kross Ltd, a player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that investors may want to reassess the stock’s prospects amid improving technical and fundamental indicators.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>a3ff5e5a1d3a36c3e9754875cabcf72e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.98</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-instrumentation-gujarat-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs98-3865578</link><description>Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd’s stock touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.98 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market pressures and sectoral headwinds. This new low reflects a continued downward trend over the past year, with the stock underperforming its peers and key indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>89c79f7e8a29b88b487f41ecca5d1aa7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zodiac Energy Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zodiac-energy-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-market-downturn-3865577</link><description>Zodiac Energy Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.220.05 on 2 March 2026, reflecting ongoing pressures in the construction sector and broader market weakness. The stock’s recent performance highlights a significant correction, with the price now substantially below key moving averages and its previous year’s high of Rs.560.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>245e099ca8667e50cc12c9d8336f1256</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D.P. Abhushan Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 1056.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dp-abhushan-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-105605-3865576</link><description>D.P. Abhushan Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.1056.05 on 2 Mar 2026, marking a significant drop amid broader sector weakness and subdued market sentiment. The stock’s recent performance reflects a continuation of downward pressure, with a notable gap down opening and underperformance relative to its sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>30d547c681e43f86708eedf31549c4b1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>