<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Synoptics Technologies Ltd Falls 6.10%: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/synoptics-technologies-ltd-falls-610-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3849114</link><description>Synoptics Technologies Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 16 to 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.60.00, down 6.10% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.63.90. This decline sharply contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period, reflecting intense selling pressure and volatility in the micro-cap stock amid mixed investor sentiment and limited liquidity.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>e8d506c78fd8b4e9d16b5738e12f1c91</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd Declines 1.99% Amid Bearish Momentum and Technical Downgrades</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-declines-199-amid-bearish-momentum-and-technical-downgrades-3849113</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd closed the week down 1.99% at Rs.258.60, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock faced persistent bearish momentum amid rising open interest in derivatives, technical downgrades, and mixed market signals, reflecting cautious investor sentiment in a challenging NBFC sector environment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>d49bddfc32775769542ed1b435fadc58</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Gains 3.18%: Volume Surge and Mixed Technical Signals Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/utkarsh-small-finance-bank-gains-318-volume-surge-and-mixed-technical-signals-shape-week-3849109</link><description>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd recorded a 3.18% gain over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock showed resilience amid mixed technical signals and a notable surge in trading volume, reflecting a complex interplay of cautious accumulation and persistent bearish sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>78167043777a27c62021566d4961deba</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Netweb Technologies India Ltd Gains 17.42%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/netweb-technologies-india-ltd-gains-1742-6-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3849107</link><description>Netweb Technologies India Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance from 16 to 20 February 2026, surging 17.42% compared to a modest 0.39% rise in the Sensex. The stock demonstrated strong intraday rallies, robust trading volumes, and sustained institutional interest, outperforming both its sector and the broader market amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>faa3df68c09a18f748c35e10dbf29f52</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VL E-Governance Surges 28.82% Amid Volatility and Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vl-e-governance-surges-2882-amid-volatility-and-strong-buying-pressure-3849106</link><description>VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd experienced a highly volatile week from 16 to 20 February 2026, closing with a remarkable 28.82% gain despite early lows and persistent fundamental challenges. The stock’s recovery sharply contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise, driven by a series of dramatic price swings, including multiple new 52-week and all-time lows followed by consecutive upper circuit hits on the final two trading days.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>2eaad1224850b794b8e071b530fa3f3f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd Falls 6.80%: Mixed Signals Amid Technical Upgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-ltd-falls-680-mixed-signals-amid-technical-upgrade-3849110</link><description>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 6.80% from Rs.131.29 to Rs.122.36, contrasting with a modest 0.39% gain in the Sensex over the same period. Despite this underperformance, the stock saw a technical upgrade to a 'Hold' rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting a nuanced improvement in technical and financial indicators amid mixed market signals.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>02e94a266e8b0c7c55a6b3c27616d20a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concord Biotech Declines 7.10% Amid Mixed Fundamentals and Technical Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/concord-biotech-declines-710-amid-mixed-fundamentals-and-technical-weakness-3849108</link><description>Concord Biotech Ltd’s stock closed the week down 7.10%, falling from Rs.1,183.25 on 13 February to Rs.1,099.25 on 20 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical momentum shift, an investment rating upgrade to Sell, and a fresh 52-week low, reflecting a complex interplay of cautious optimism and persistent bearish pressures.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>4c5c4d59999d15c0d65763f7af66072d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Basilic Fly Studio Ltd Falls 15.90%: Key Technical and Earnings Factors Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/basilic-fly-studio-ltd-falls-1590-key-technical-and-earnings-factors-weigh-3849104</link><description>Basilic Fly Studio Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 20 Feb 2026, with its share price tumbling 15.90% from Rs.281.45 to Rs.236.70, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The steep decline was driven primarily by disappointing Q3 FY26 results marked by margin compression and a consequential technical downgrade that intensified bearish momentum. Despite some short-term oversold signals, the stock remains under pressure amid weak volume and negative technical indicators.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>91e4dfbcd6ed2d26817c9eb5435df247</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aeroflex Industries Ltd Gains 19.39%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aeroflex-industries-ltd-gains-1939-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3849103</link><description>Aeroflex Industries Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance from 16 to 20 February 2026, surging 19.39% from Rs.186.70 to Rs.222.90, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by multiple new 52-week highs, strong institutional interest, and sustained technical strength, underscoring a robust momentum within the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector despite mixed broader market conditions.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>bc578110e233bbcd2eb5d3471ed4fc5d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EMS Ltd Falls 6.92% This Week: 6 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ems-ltd-falls-692-this-week-6-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3849105</link><description>EMS Ltd’s shares declined by 6.92% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.307.45 from Rs.330.30 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain, reflecting persistent company-specific challenges amid volatile trading and mixed technical signals.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>eed69066aba69e5903afdf687c6bf586</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd Drops 18.06%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zaggle-prepaid-ocean-services-ltd-drops-1806-6-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3849102</link><description>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd endured a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its share price plunging 18.06% from Rs.286.25 to Rs.234.55, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid sustained selling pressure, technical weakness, and reduced institutional participation, despite the company reporting robust financial results and attractive valuation metrics. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped Zaggle Prepaid’s turbulent week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>6ac6275d94ef1fca586cb78b5e1044b2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd’s 0.58% Weekly Decline: Bearish Technicals and Derivatives Activity Shape Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvama-wealth-management-ltds-058-weekly-decline-bearish-technicals-and-derivatives-activity-shape-outlook-3849100</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd closed the week ending 20 Feb 2026 with a marginal decline of 0.58%, settling at Rs.1,291.65, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of bearish technical developments, including a notable Death Cross formation and a downgrade in the company’s Mojo Grade to Sell, signalling increased caution among investors amid subdued price momentum and heightened derivatives activity.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>cec88544562b1690236ded763d164d1b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karnika Industries Gains 5.60%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karnika-industries-gains-560-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3849099</link><description>Karnika Industries Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 5.60%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise during 16–20 February 2026. The stock exhibited strong momentum early in the week, driven by robust quarterly results and a surge to the upper circuit on 18 February, before succumbing to heavy selling pressure and hitting the lower circuit on the final trading day. This week’s price action reflects a volatile interplay of positive fundamentals and valuation concerns, culminating in a sharp reversal that investors should carefully analyse.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>2ce9f6311ab7baeeaadd3ac9a8ff77fb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRM Energy Ltd Declines 3.40%: Bearish Momentum and Valuation Shift Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/irm-energy-ltd-declines-340-bearish-momentum-and-valuation-shift-mark-the-week-3849101</link><description>IRM Energy Ltd closed the week down 3.40%, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock faced intensified bearish momentum amid technical downgrades and sectoral headwinds, despite a brief valuation improvement signalling fairer price levels. Persistent selling pressure and negative technical indicators dominated the week’s trading, reflecting ongoing challenges in the gas sector and subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>87fd1109dc9acba9d7fb288adf268dbb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd Drops 10.57%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-jet-healthcare-ltd-drops-1057-4-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3849097</link><description>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 10.57% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.355.45 from Rs.397.45 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, reflecting company-specific challenges amid a difficult earnings backdrop and sustained technical weakness.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>afe48399cb7fb543c729d3a9976b8791</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cello World Ltd Falls 12.77%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cello-world-ltd-falls-1277-5-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3849098</link><description>Cello World Ltd experienced a sharp decline of 12.77% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.442.85 compared to Rs.507.70 the previous Friday. This significant underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% during the same period, highlighting persistent challenges for the company amid a broadly resilient market. The stock repeatedly hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows, reflecting deteriorating financial results, technical weakness, and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>0d5de8cbbfe912528d3c5bd929d3b277</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gandhar Oil Refinery Falls 1.91%: Technical Shift and Mixed Financials Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gandhar-oil-refinery-falls-191-technical-shift-and-mixed-financials-shape-week-3849096</link><description>Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 20 February 2026, with its stock price declining 1.91% to close at Rs.143.70, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Sell rating amid mixed financial results and a shift to a mildly bearish technical trend, contributing to increased selling pressure and volatility.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>66b13a540760b1e700eae8a21b6b2234</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox India Ltd Falls 3.11%: Mixed Signals and Downgrade Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-india-ltd-falls-311-mixed-signals-and-downgrade-shape-weekly-performance-3849094</link><description>Inox India Ltd closed the week at Rs.1,132.85, down 3.11% from Rs.1,169.20 last Friday, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock experienced a shift from technical momentum improvement early in the week to a downgrade by MarketsMOJO and a mildly bearish technical stance by week’s end, reflecting a complex interplay of strong quarterly results, valuation concerns, and mixed market signals.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>c0b378753ad06fe9fea0fa1979aaa09e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin Ltd Falls 4.05%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/muthoot-microfin-ltd-falls-405-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3849093</link><description>Muthoot Microfin Ltd’s shares declined by 4.05% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.182.50 from Rs.190.20, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% during the same period. The week was marked by a cautious upgrade in the company’s rating to 'Hold' amid mixed fundamentals and bullish technicals, followed by the stock hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.210 before a minor pullback in the final sessions.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>a39be74aaaf236da680517154d311df4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Forgings Ltd Gains 3.91%: Key Milestones and Market Outperformance This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/happy-forgings-ltd-gains-391-key-milestones-and-market-outperformance-this-week-3849090</link><description>Happy Forgings Ltd closed the week with a solid gain of 3.91%, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock demonstrated resilience despite early-week declines, culminating in a new 52-week and all-time high on 20 Feb 2026. This week’s price action was marked by strong technical momentum and notable volume surges, reflecting renewed investor interest and sector leadership.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>5a8fb3a735440c3465c09c1d81b26827</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>