<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Show Mixed Trends as Metal Sector Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-edges-higher-as-metal-sector-leads-gains-mixed-breadth-reflects-cautious-sentiment-3772781</link><description>The Indian equity markets exhibited a cautious stance on 29 December 2025, with the Sensex and Nifty indices trading near flat levels amid mixed sectoral performances. While the metal sector emerged as the top gainer, utilities lagged, reflecting a divergence in investor sentiment. Market breadth indicated more declines than advances, and foreign institutional investors (FIIs) alongside domestic institutional investors (DIIs) activity remained key factors influencing market dynamics.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>2487cb796e9642cd990962a6726c61fa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amidst-mixed-performance-3772779</link><description>Jio Financial Services, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, continues to attract attention as a constituent of the Nifty 50 index. Despite recent market fluctuations and sector-wide challenges, the company’s position within this benchmark index underscores its growing significance in India’s financial landscape.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>676e6c84505074d82c6b1375a4283edf</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute: Navigating Market Dynamics Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-faces-downgrade-amidst-mixed-market-performance-and-nifty-50-membership-3772778</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute, a prominent player in the hospital sector and a constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to attract investor attention as it navigates a complex market environment. Despite recent fluctuations in its share price and valuation metrics, the company’s position within the benchmark index underscores its significance in India’s healthcare landscape and the broader equity market.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>126894aaaaf7a67dc9f436b51d865712</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance Company: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3772777</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in India’s insurance sector. Despite recent trading pressures and a series of short-term declines, the company’s market capitalisation and long-term performance metrics underscore its significance as a large-cap stock and a benchmark constituent.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>bb615f5879ace4dadee43594e3acaee8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3772776</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading player in India’s insurance sector. The company’s market capitalisation of over ₹2 lakh crore and its performance relative to benchmark indices underscore its significance for institutional investors and market participants alike.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>f86f2576d1e7cfe0d1847d3020c37c66</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Key Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-autos-nifty-50-membership-reinforces-market-standing-amid-mixed-performance-3772780</link><description>Bajaj Auto continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in the Indian automobile sector. Recent market data reveals nuanced shifts in its performance and institutional holdings, underscoring the stock’s ongoing influence on benchmark movements and investor sentiment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>fc22b5e23cd56a0423c1976ae88f12fe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India: Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Holding Insights</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-sustained-outperformance-reinforces-nifty-50-benchmark-status-3772774</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading player in the Indian automobile sector. Recent market data highlights the company’s performance relative to benchmarks and sector peers, underscoring its significance for investors and institutional stakeholders alike.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>27f93bdb397a80ede93223da4831a4bd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance: Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Holding Insights</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3772775</link><description>Bajaj Finance continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading non-banking financial company (NBFC) in India. Recent market data highlights the stock’s performance relative to sector benchmarks and the broader Sensex, underscoring its significance for institutional investors and index-linked portfolios.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>77c3d60c018f55d601e5cd548f7c54e1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles: Nifty 50 Membership and Market Performance Analysis</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-navigating-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3772773</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to attract attention amid evolving market dynamics. Despite recent fluctuations in its stock price and performance metrics, its role within the benchmark index underscores its significance in the Indian automobile sector and broader equity markets.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>c13ed999ba348139315302221575fd02</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-performance-3772772</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, a prominent player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to attract significant attention amid evolving market conditions. Its status within the benchmark index underscores its influence on sectoral and broader market movements, while recent trading patterns and valuation metrics offer insights into its current market positioning.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>daab4fd0854c5e8d7b9a8fb79be11320</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel's Market Position Strengthened by Nifty 50 Inclusion and Institutional Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steels-nifty-50-membership-reinforces-market-standing-amid-mixed-sector-performance-3772771</link><description>JSW Steel continues to assert its significance within the Indian equity landscape, buoyed by its status as a Nifty 50 constituent and evolving institutional shareholding patterns. The company’s performance metrics and benchmark relevance underscore its pivotal role in the ferrous metals sector and broader market indices.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>0e26001560d6d3184f973847ed1a1e84</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra's Market Position Strengthened by Nifty 50 Inclusion and Institutional Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindras-market-momentum-strengthened-by-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-confidence-3772768</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra continues to consolidate its stature as a key player in the Indian automobile sector, buoyed by its status as a Nifty 50 constituent and notable institutional holding patterns. The company’s market capitalisation and performance metrics underscore its significance within the benchmark index, reflecting a nuanced interplay between sector dynamics and broader market trends.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>fa17a1c887f372a5cd9d4d8196e0b8ac</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Key Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubros-strategic-position-strengthened-by-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-confidence-3772767</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T), a cornerstone of the Indian construction sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market conditions. With a market capitalisation exceeding ₹5.57 lakh crores and a price-to-earnings ratio below the industry average, the stock's recent performance reflects nuanced shifts in institutional holdings and benchmark status impact, underscoring its significance in India’s equity landscape.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>f29c115534ffe377ed6586228a258903</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv’s Market Position and Institutional Holding Dynamics Amidst Nifty 50 Benchmark Status</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finservs-nifty-50-membership-reinforces-market-standing-amid-mixed-performance-3772770</link><description>Bajaj Finserv, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention in India’s financial markets. Despite recent short-term price movements, the company’s long-term performance and its role within the benchmark index underscore its importance to investors and institutional stakeholders alike.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>a946c3cc4034fb4c7092ca8dccaa3891</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Faces Market Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-faces-heightened-pressure-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3772769</link><description>Adani Enterprises, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to navigate a complex market environment marked by subdued price performance and valuation disparities relative to its sector and benchmark indices. Despite its significant market capitalisation and diversified business model, the stock's recent trading patterns and comparative returns highlight the challenges faced by large-cap stocks within the diversified sector.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>5269ee2452d97de05097adcf5fd07dc2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra's Market Position and Institutional Holding Dynamics Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindras-nifty-50-membership-highlights-institutional-shifts-and-market-position-3772766</link><description>Tech Mahindra continues to hold a significant position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector. Recent market data reveals nuanced shifts in its performance and institutional holdings, underscoring the company's evolving role as a benchmark constituent and its impact on investor sentiment.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>fa42b8ccf82ff6c89e9c92f60ffd538b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr Reddys Laboratories: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dr-reddys-laboratories-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3772765</link><description>Dr Reddys Laboratories continues to hold its position as a significant constituent of the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. Recent market data reveals nuanced shifts in its performance relative to benchmarks and sector peers, underscoring the complexities faced by large-cap pharmaceutical companies in the current economic environment.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>ea71437354d9c0471e1941b49ca5a3ef</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-ports-special-economic-zone-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3772764</link><description>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in India's transport infrastructure sector. Recent market activity and institutional holding patterns underscore the stock’s evolving role amid broader benchmark movements and sectoral trends.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>88f7108e5df18623e408a024efcbc348</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grasim Industries: Cement Sector Stalwart Maintains Steady Course Amid Market Fluctuations</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grasim-industries-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-mixed-cement-sector-trends-3772763</link><description>Grasim Industries, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index and a prominent player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, continues to demonstrate resilience amid recent market movements. With a market capitalisation of approximately ₹1,91,737 crores, the company’s performance remains a focal point for investors tracking large-cap stocks within the benchmark index.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>a88487c11757576632fdd903d44085b5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-3772762</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC), a key player in India’s oil sector and a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to attract attention amid evolving market conditions. As a large-cap stock with a market capitalisation of approximately ₹2,94,630 crore, ONGC’s performance and institutional holding patterns offer valuable insights into its role within the benchmark index and the broader oil exploration and refinery sector.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>dede027fbd6ba907c6176b06d1b12d36</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>