<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>SMS Pharmaceuticals Ltd Hits Intraday High with 9.32% Surge on 12 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sms-pharmaceuticals-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-932-surge-on-12-feb-2026-3835186</link><description>SMS Pharmaceuticals Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 12 Feb 2026, surging by 9.32% to touch a day’s high of ₹343.50, marking a significant rebound after two days of declines and outperforming its sector by 8.11%.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>153b8e5db0cf8459b3b6b4cf2c3e6177</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.124.15</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-renewable-energy-development-agency-ltd-hits-52-week-low-at-rs12415-3835180</link><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd (IREDA) has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.124.15 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific factors.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>01399e09a9f23121e98447bb42db2905</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vl-e-governance-it-solutions-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3835179</link><description>VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd has reached a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.13.27, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader sector and market pressures. The stock’s performance over the past year has been notably weak, reflecting ongoing financial difficulties and subdued business metrics.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>b0c2f54b6dc9fad2f668f8aee6890e6a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Landmark Cars Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 12 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/landmark-cars-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-12-feb-2026-3835174</link><description>Shares of Landmark Cars Ltd declined sharply on 12 Feb 2026, hitting an intraday low of Rs 426.8, reflecting significant price pressure amid a broadly cautious market environment. The stock underperformed its sector and the benchmark Sensex, reversing gains from the previous three sessions.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>8f02186dfe4eb13c3f4f0322a06d4fa0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 12 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-oil-corporation-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-12-feb-2026-3835175</link><description>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd (IOC) experienced a notable intraday decline on 12 Feb 2026, with the stock touching a low of Rs 176.55, reflecting a 2.62% drop from its previous close. This downturn comes after three consecutive days of gains, signalling a temporary reversal in momentum amid broader market pressures and sector underperformance.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>fbcf4450b1262a7a0e3f1010bc14f92b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hexaware Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hexaware-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3835173</link><description>Hexaware Technologies Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 12 Feb 2026, touching a new 52-week low of Rs 540.25 as the stock faced sustained selling pressure, underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>51230648ad168f64743d210bdc48021e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-weak-price-action-3835172</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, rising by 14.13% to 34,809 contracts, even as the stock price hit a fresh 52-week low of ₹898.1 on 12 Feb 2026. This divergence between rising open interest and declining price signals a complex market positioning, with investors possibly taking fresh directional bets amid subdued sectoral and broader market conditions.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>ea3b0f09d09ecd27af726bc57d468e75</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LTI Mindtree Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lti-mindtree-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-decline-3835169</link><description>LTI Mindtree Ltd (LTIM) has witnessed a significant 23.18% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, rising from 30,611 to 37,707 contracts. This surge comes amid a notable price decline, with the stock falling 4.94% on 12 Feb 2026, underperforming its sector and broader market indices. The sudden spike in open interest alongside heavy volume near the day’s low suggests a shift in market positioning, raising questions about directional bets and investor sentiment in this large-cap software and consulting firm.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>6b95478c127718d03975652fa760da4d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesh Infraworld Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganesh-infraworld-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3835168</link><description>Shares of Ganesh Infraworld Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 12 Feb 2026, closing at ₹103.75, down 4.99% on the day. The sharp decline reflects intense selling pressure and panic among investors, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>548fc803c86b99b09bacdbdccb7b95f8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-market-downturn-3835171</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd. has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent price decline, the stock’s derivatives market shows increased participation, reflecting complex directional bets amid broader sector weakness.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>b855a636e391028121927341c3548655</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oracle Financial Services Software Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oracle-financial-services-software-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3835170</link><description>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd (OFSS) has witnessed a notable 12.85% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low of ₹6,854 on 12 Feb 2026. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and volume patterns, suggests a shift in market positioning with potential bearish directional bets gaining traction.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>7c52dd954345c42ca29cc12164825ca3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Engineering Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-engineering-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3835162</link><description>Shares of Supreme Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 12 Feb 2026, closing at ₹1.08, down 4.42% on the day. The stock witnessed intense selling pressure, with panic-driven trades and unfilled supply dominating the session, signalling deep investor concerns amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>a7d45b67f1c4b00dceeb9d9b347e7ee6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3835156</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across market capitalisations and sectors, as 2,547 companies declared results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings outcomes improved modestly to 47.0%, mid-cap stocks outperformed with a 53.0% positivity rate, signalling a shift in profit momentum away from large caps. This report analyses the key trends, sectoral highlights and standout performers shaping the current earnings landscape.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>57306a61372bf2de553e511ba818e5d3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arshiya Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arshiya-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3835167</link><description>Shares of Arshiya Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Transport Services sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 12 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and widespread panic among investors. The stock’s maximum daily loss triggered automatic trading halts, underscoring the fragile sentiment surrounding the company amid deteriorating fundamentals and weak market interest.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>0fc7a69b93a051e6302bf9c53ca2c80d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wipro Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wipro-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-and-market-volatility-3835166</link><description>Wipro Ltd. has witnessed a notable 11.46% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low of ₹218.6. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and falling delivery volumes, suggests a complex interplay of investor positioning and potential directional bets in the IT software sector.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>9a1552448af8b15ad075f8995e781dd8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Ltd Sees Sharp Value Turnover Amid Declining Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-ltd-sees-sharp-value-turnover-amid-declining-momentum-3835163</link><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd (HINDUNILVR), a heavyweight in the FMCG sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 12 Feb 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹58,432.8 lakhs. Despite this high-value turnover, the stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a shift in investor sentiment and institutional interest amid a notable price correction.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>44b57c34ee3defa4d305e2876fd4bbce</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coforge-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-performance-3835164</link><description>Coforge Ltd, a mid-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment despite recent price weakness. The stock’s open interest jumped by 11.88% to 79,205 contracts, signalling increased market participation and potential shifts in investor positioning amid a broader sectoral and market decline.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>760dea296ff25a4f975733e3519ac69b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Ltd Sees Surge in Call Option Activity Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eicher-motors-ltd-sees-surge-in-call-option-activity-amid-bullish-momentum-3835165</link><description>Eicher Motors Ltd (EICHERMOT) has emerged as the most actively traded stock in the call options segment, signalling strong bullish sentiment among investors. With the underlying stock hitting a fresh 52-week high and sustained gains over the past week, market participants are positioning aggressively for further upside ahead of the 24 February 2026 expiry.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>6ba1d7fbd208fda129a39ab849ff1367</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Surges 2.5% Amid Mixed Breadth and Sectoral Divergence</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-surges-25-amid-mixed-breadth-and-sectoral-divergence-3835159</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index has demonstrated notable resilience in recent trading sessions, advancing 2.52% on the day and gaining 1.95% over the past five days. Despite a challenging breadth with a higher number of declining stocks, the segment remains the best performer across market capitalisation categories, buoyed by select high-return stocks and recent technical upgrades.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>713bec3820152085433c5ad5c676ae8c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Sees Mixed Performance as BSE 100 Declines 0.57%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-sees-mixed-performance-as-bse-100-declines-057-3835158</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, experienced a modest decline of 0.57% on 12 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious market mood as investors weighed defensive resilience against cyclical pressures. While select heavyweight stocks demonstrated bullish momentum, the broader index was weighed down by notable underperformers, signalling a nuanced market landscape ahead of key earnings announcements.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>a5fb4236bb2978b48cb7a9df4bb546d8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>