<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Callista Industries Ltd Stock Hits Record High of Rs.118 on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/callista-industries-ltd-stock-hits-record-high-of-rs118-on-2-jan-2026-3779060</link><description>Callista Industries Ltd reached a new all-time high of Rs.118 today, underscoring a remarkable phase of sustained gains and robust market performance. This milestone reflects the company’s strong momentum over recent months, highlighted by significant returns and consistent upward movement across key technical indicators.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>24d14c794786197f7c4251bc84ecba05</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.203.6</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs2036-3779061</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd has reached an all-time high of Rs.203.6, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and underscoring the company’s strong performance within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector. This milestone caps a sustained period of gains, with the stock outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>2e769d1f8f0bb6a117e61c0405704a2d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance Company Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.17% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cholamandalam-investment-finance-company-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-317-surge-3779052</link><description>Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance Company Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, touching a high of ₹1,779.9, marking a 3.28% increase from its previous close. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, continuing its upward momentum with a fifth consecutive day of gains.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>2de7c1f614d745f17cbadecf2df95a14</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindalco Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.13% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindalco-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-313-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3779053</link><description>Hindalco Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, touching a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs 923.85, marking a 3.22% gain during the trading session. The stock’s strong momentum aligns with sectoral gains and broader market strength, reflecting sustained buying interest and technical strength.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>8da2225470b9fe5c98467bb808b02da9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trent Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 3.03% Surge on 2 January 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trent-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-303-surge-on-2-january-2026-3779051</link><description>Trent Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 4,436.7, marking a 3.23% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum within the garments and apparels industry.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>1c41eeccc335abfac1aff312565d4bf7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.3886.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-pharmaceuticals-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs388605-3779050</link><description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.3886.05, reflecting sustained momentum and robust market performance within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>0a826cc0ac340f0041dbc9a0eff118e2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thinkink Picturez Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thinkink-picturez-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-decline-3779045</link><description>Shares of Thinkink Picturez Ltd have fallen to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained downward trajectory over recent years. The stock’s latest close places it just 4.35% above its 52-week low of ₹0.22, underscoring the severity of its market position within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>3d13bde82cec95c5bcffd39358fa2660</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.04% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-power-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-504-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3779042</link><description>Torrent Power Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 2 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 1397.4, marking a 5.27% increase from its previous close. This performance outpaced the broader Power sector and the Sensex, reflecting heightened trading activity and positive momentum within the stock.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>d734029bd93320d5126c63376c4ce49d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Advances 0.55% Led by Midcaps; Coal India Tops Large Cap Gainers</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-advances-055-led-by-midcaps-coal-india-tops-large-cap-gainers-3779041</link><description>Indian equity markets advanced on 2 January 2026, with the Sensex rising 470.70 points or 0.55% to close at 85,659.30, driven by robust midcap performance and broad sectoral participation. The Nifty50 mirrored this optimism, supported by strong gains in public sector undertakings and energy stocks, while FMCG lagged. Market breadth was healthy, with advances outnumbering declines by more than twofold across the BSE500, signalling broad-based buying interest amid mixed global cues.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>955d6a066a07307448dabb12a43fd902</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tourism-finance-corporation-of-india-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3779040</link><description>Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 2 Jan 2026, hitting a low of Rs 65.01, down 5.67% from its previous close. The stock underperformed sharply against the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued sentiment within the finance sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8d1744336094b6ae83ae7e5648e8d2d3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.9604.65</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs960465-3779039</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd. has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.9604.65, marking a notable phase of momentum in the automobile sector. This achievement reflects a sustained upward trend over recent sessions, underscoring the stock’s resilience amid broader market movements.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>199955cc1753d35ccdaf851d34f5c42c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cupid-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-2-jan-2026-3779038</link><description>Cupid Ltd experienced a sharp intraday decline on 2 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 419.95, down 19.99% from its previous close. This marked a notable reversal after a 15-day consecutive gain streak, with the stock underperforming its FMCG sector peers and broader market indices amid prevailing price pressures and shifting market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a12ea0d4126f5226fd78e5ffced083d9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maral Overseas Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maral-overseas-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3779037</link><description>Maral Overseas Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has reached a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures on its stock price. The share closed at its lowest level in a year, marking a significant milestone in its recent performance trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5bf84a35138c93856c1aa39a61d9995e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NLC India Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.32% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nlc-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-532-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3779034</link><description>NLC India Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 2 Jan 2026, surging 5.32% to touch a day’s high of Rs 272, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its sector peers in the power industry.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5dd33ce3b405f9501798d939b49534e8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. Stock Hits All-Time High on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-pharmaceuticals-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-on-2-jan-2026-3779035</link><description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has reached an all-time high in its stock price, underscoring the company’s robust performance and sustained growth within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. This milestone reflects a combination of strong financial metrics, consistent returns, and favourable market positioning.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>22cbaf0cdecf071f5b21e0b789566c6b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Covance Softsol Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.101.24</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/covance-softsol-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs10124-3779031</link><description>Covance Softsol Ltd, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.101.24. This achievement marks a notable moment in the stock’s recent performance, reflecting strong momentum and positive market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>aefcab8b7c0e12b34aae3efd64c8a750</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aether Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.954.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aether-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs9545-3779030</link><description>Aether Industries Ltd, a key player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs.954.5 today, reflecting robust momentum and sustained gains over recent sessions. The stock’s performance outpaced its sector peers and demonstrated resilience amid a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c1e245ede76890fc6e257cb7f44b26d4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Bank Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1008</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/au-small-finance-bank-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs1008-3779029</link><description>AU Small Finance Bank Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.1008, marking a strong rally in the stock price amid a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c45a7e6e6e5adc21507d587c52ce1046</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3779025</link><description>Swiggy Ltd witnessed a significant 20.96% rise in open interest in its derivatives segment on 1 Jan 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting cautious sentiment amid bearish technical indicators and a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>39284a442cf3cb1533c7cbaaa279ae25</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>