<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Landmark Cars Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.08% Surge on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/landmark-cars-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-808-surge-on-1-feb-2026-3814563</link><description>Landmark Cars Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 1 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 422.1, marking an 8.99% increase from its previous close. This sharp uptick outpaced the broader sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum in the automobile stock.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>3c538b2668e07369c4c6c7cd769a3b44</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-dynamics-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814564</link><description>Shares of Bharat Dynamics Ltd declined sharply on 1 Feb 2026, hitting an intraday low of Rs 1,467.6 as the stock faced significant price pressure, underperforming its sector and the broader market amid subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>7fa961b4a76dd6a4af86afd1ec65b203</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCB Bank Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcb-bank-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814561</link><description>Shares of DCB Bank Ltd. declined sharply on 1 Feb 2026, touching an intraday low of Rs 188.9, reflecting significant price pressure amid broader market softness and sector underperformance.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>baa02eda11ac9bf307386b9c023bfe85</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of Baroda Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-baroda-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814562</link><description>Bank Of Baroda’s shares declined sharply on 1 Feb 2026, touching an intraday low of Rs 288.85, reflecting sustained price pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance. The stock fell by 4.98% on the day, underperforming the Sensex and its own sector, as investors reacted to immediate selling pressures and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>da74a9e13c288f45ae5c33e54cd03a11</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punjab National Bank Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/punjab-national-bank-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814560</link><description>Punjab National Bank (PNB) experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 122.1, reflecting a 2.48% drop from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid subdued market sentiment and immediate price pressures.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>116829fdff8796a3f1b0eda3bb953447</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of India Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-india-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814566</link><description>Bank Of India’s shares declined sharply today, touching an intraday low of Rs 155.65, reflecting a 5.09% drop as the stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid subdued market sentiment and immediate selling pressure.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>e746e70694e2fdbfc1bdb1ee9042b3fa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ACC Ltd Falls 1.97% Amid Profit Pressures: 3 Key Factors Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/acc-ltd-falls-197-amid-profit-pressures-3-key-factors-shaping-the-week-3814537</link><description>ACC Ltd’s share price declined by 1.97% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.1,637.50 compared to Rs.1,670.35 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain during the same period, reflecting investor concerns following a sharp quarterly profit contraction and the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low. Despite record revenue growth, margin pressures and operational challenges weighed heavily on the company’s financials and market sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>cbb7275a53595f7bdf03aac8c7d8024e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd Gains 5.75%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaghani-techno-build-ltd-gains-575-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3814538</link><description>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 5.75% from Rs.228.85 to Rs.242.00 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, supported by sustained technical momentum and consistent buying interest despite a cautious broader market environment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>f008c85836e43fbd08208363b69061d9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Declines 1.85% Amid Rising Open Interest and Put Option Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/persistent-systems-declines-185-amid-rising-open-interest-and-put-option-activity-3814536</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its share price falling 1.85% from Rs.6,147.50 to Rs.6,033.80, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.62% over the same period. Despite robust fundamentals and a strong mojo score, the stock faced short-term pressure driven by increased open interest in derivatives and heavy put option activity signalling cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>9827e0b8d0b402cf5c578fe7194ccd00</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balaji Amines Ltd’s Volatile Week: -1.08% Amid Mixed Technical Signals and Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balaji-amines-ltds-volatile-week--108-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-sector-headwinds-3814535</link><description>Balaji Amines Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 30 January 2026, with its share price declining 1.08% to close at Rs.1,117.75, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The stock showed sharp intraday swings, including a strong rally on 28 January followed by steep declines on 29 and 30 January, reflecting mixed technical signals and ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>dabfe21137584daa7cd44069205de253</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ion Exchange Gains 1.49%: Key Events and Market Pressures Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ion-exchange-gains-149-key-events-and-market-pressures-shape-weekly-performance-3814534</link><description>Ion Exchange (India) Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a modest gain of 1.49%, rising from Rs.349.45 to Rs.354.65. This performance, however, lagged slightly behind the Sensex’s 1.62% advance over the same period. The week was marked by a mix of positive rating upgrades and sharp price declines, culminating in a volatile finish with the stock hitting a new 52-week low amid significant selling pressure.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>07f4d26ebe6e3ea325ca8167ef0c4aaf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indus Towers Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indus-towers-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814565</link><description>Indus Towers Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 1 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 428, reflecting a 3.59% drop from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid subdued market sentiment and immediate selling pressures.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>babdc2e481ff6f16a341615d56630bb0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Foodbrands Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/united-foodbrands-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3814567</link><description>United Foodbrands Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Leisure Services sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 1 Feb 2026, propelled by intense buying interest and a remarkable 20.00% gain in a single trading session. This sharp rally outpaced both its sector and the broader market, signalling renewed investor enthusiasm despite the company’s challenging fundamentals and a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>691475a90f19cd5a23d3ebc3caf16c3f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Osia Hyper Retail Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/osia-hyper-retail-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3814559</link><description>Osia Hyper Retail Ltd surged to its upper circuit limit on 1 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.88% as robust buying interest propelled the stock to ₹14.82. The micro-cap retailing company outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting heightened investor enthusiasm despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>13439a4be6c069953f48add5399bf2bf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bartronics India Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bartronics-india-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3814558</link><description>Bartronics India Ltd witnessed a robust rally on 1 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 3.55% gain, driven by intense buying interest and a surge in investor participation. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, signalling renewed optimism despite lingering challenges in its technical indicators and fundamental outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>33847e9e0bf5b2914ddcba119df33611</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mazagon-dock-shipbuilders-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-strong-price-momentum-3814554</link><description>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Ltd (MAZDOCK) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and shifting investor sentiment. The stock has outperformed its sector peers recently, supported by rising volumes and sustained price gains, prompting a reassessment of its market positioning and future prospects.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>a64b6719c2643895db78cd2bc6da3ce2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sejal Glass Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sejal-glass-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3814557</link><description>Sejal Glass Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Products sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 1 Feb 2026, closing at ₹736.05, marking a maximum daily gain of 5.0%. This sharp rally was driven by strong buying interest, limited supply, and positive market sentiment, positioning the stock as a notable outperformer within its sector and the broader market.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>08efeb48cf671992a838019670277109</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-dynamics-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3814555</link><description>Bharat Dynamics Ltd (BDL), a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defence sector, witnessed a notable 10.2% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader benchmarks, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and technical factors.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>07e3cdc74a3981f3af25773a0259d6a0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biofil Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/biofil-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-pressure-3814556</link><description>Biofil Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd witnessed a remarkable surge on 1 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit of 20% to close at ₹35.11. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, resulting in the stock outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid a backdrop of subdued investor participation and regulatory trading restrictions.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>3eb2264cc1733a0c65563f839716be3d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BF Utilities Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bf-utilities-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-pressure-3814550</link><description>BF Utilities Ltd, a small-cap player in the Transport Infrastructure sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 1 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a maximum daily gain of 5.0%. The stock’s performance outpaced both its sector and the broader market, signalling renewed investor confidence despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>89505e3fad72e47f0181f769b06ef385</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>