<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:13:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Shaily Engineer and Orissa Minerals Highlight Market Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-notable-sector-performers-3764677</link><description>As the curtain falls on the September 2025 quarter results, a comprehensive analysis of nearly 4,000 stocks reveals nuanced trends across market capitalisations and sectors. Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Shaily Engineer and Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd emerge as notable performers, reflecting diverse sectoral dynamics and financial outcomes in a complex market environment.
Time: Dec 20 2025 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>cdbd1534453c82b7c22b973856480f79</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Orissa Minerals latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-orissa-minerals-latest-results-good-or-bad-3764667</link><description>Orissa Minerals' latest results show a mixed picture: while there was a year-on-year sales growth of 7.44% and a return to profitability with a net profit of ₹3.14 crores in Q2 FY26, the company faces significant challenges, including negative equity and substantial accumulated losses, raising concerns about its long-term financial health.
Time: Dec 20 2025 07:10 PM IST</description><guid>511896f370b88858f531cf6b2fc9b890</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Shaily Engineer and Orissa Minerals Lead Market Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-select-sectoral-strength-3764649</link><description>As the Sep-2025 quarter earnings season concludes with 3,990 companies reporting, the market reveals a nuanced picture of corporate performance across sectors and market capitalisations. Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Shaily Engineer and Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd. stand out among the top performers, reflecting varied sectoral dynamics and financial outcomes.
Time: Dec 20 2025 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>0ff349c2c054961ce8d937fd3ae5cb62</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Shaily Engineer and Orissa Minerals Lead Market Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-notable-sectoral-performances-3764619</link><description>As the Sep-2025 quarter earnings season concludes with 3,990 companies reporting, the market reveals a nuanced picture of corporate performance across sectors and market capitalisations. Positive results were recorded by 43.0% of companies, marking a slight rise from 40.0% in the previous quarter, reflecting a cautious but steady trend in earnings growth. Large caps, mid caps and small caps displayed varied outcomes, with mid caps showing the highest proportion of positive results at 50.0%.
Time: Dec 20 2025 03:00 PM IST</description><guid>0254842dc149305037c7ed20bd38179d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>