<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Inox Green Energy Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-green-energy-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3846080</link><description>Inox Green Energy Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>b5fc9f87e59617d8f054e7c13f62b7ca</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indigo Paints Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indigo-paints-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846081</link><description>Indigo Paints Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>51619af0d93d17f3ecb0f5d7236518df</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moksh Ornaments Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/moksh-ornaments-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3846079</link><description>Moksh Ornaments Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>fe5677081db722272b119d4a3d426e33</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yash Chemex Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yash-chemex-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846076</link><description>Yash Chemex Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>bc53557ce80b028998dba2ab3bc99fbf</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/narayana-hrudayalaya-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846075</link><description>Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s short- to medium-term momentum and raising concerns about long-term weakness despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>88442ac51752483b40eece0f4e18ed10</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carysil Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/carysil-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846078</link><description>Carysil Ltd, a prominent player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock’s near-term momentum and long-term strength despite its impressive historical performance.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>f2d798affa2faf5f9bfc3518022552f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Haria Apparels Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/haria-apparels-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846073</link><description>Haria Apparels Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend. Investors should carefully consider this shift amid mixed fundamental and technical indicators.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>79468739cba2524d0b017677a04b4523</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3846072</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout, signalling a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the heavy electrical equipment company.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>2f4a89f0ae7512c56a9aef30c75e7def</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vivid Mercantile Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vivid-mercantile-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3846077</link><description>Vivid Mercantile Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that investors may want to reassess the stock’s outlook amid improving technical conditions.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>dd07b4097c5e6b6eb6cc8734b2811ca4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starlineps Enterprises Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/starlineps-enterprises-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3846071</link><description>Starlineps Enterprises Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>b426880dc0fb958a23fadf85a6fa342f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varun Beverages Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varun-beverages-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3846074</link><description>Varun Beverages Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>b5838af298b4ada57af3bf49c56c0a51</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Auro Laboratories Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/auro-laboratories-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3846070</link><description>Auro Laboratories Ltd, a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift, suggesting renewed investor confidence and a possible trend reversal in the stock’s trajectory.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>0997f1780416b0c3754999157d055667</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Mixed Results as 46% of Stocks Report Positive Growth in Dec-2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-as-46-of-stocks-report-positive-growth-in-dec-2025-3846069</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture, as 4,080 companies reported results reflecting a modest improvement in positive outcomes compared to previous quarters. While mid-cap firms continue to outperform with a 52.0% positive result rate, large caps lag behind at 43.0%, underscoring sectoral and size-based disparities in earnings momentum.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>b3e1062af5dee728f866c7a21f374ea4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.26.7</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs267-3846006</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.26.7 on 18 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop amid continued underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b7b71238723a52b03738cb72bcca5d93</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matrimony.com Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/matrimonycom-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3846003</link><description>Shares of Matrimony.com Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing at Rs 448.6 on 18 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid a series of negative quarterly results and sustained underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1fd107d092a26c2f1119da469959bc0f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dharan Infra-EPC Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.0.19</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dharan-infra-epc-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs019-3846005</link><description>Dharan Infra-EPC Ltd, a player in the Realty sector, has recorded a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.0.19 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price. This drop comes amid a backdrop of deteriorating financial metrics and subdued market performance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>75fa650c4812235e1c6aa7bb810f3645</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orissa-minerals-development-company-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3846004</link><description>Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near Rs 4,200.9, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market gains and sectoral outperformance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c78511ca323504ffba1e7e875d0afe0e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baazar Style Retail Ltd Reports Robust Quarterly Growth Amid Sector Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baazar-style-retail-ltd-reports-robust-quarterly-growth-amid-sector-challenges-3846002</link><description>Baazar Style Retail Ltd has delivered a strong quarterly performance for the December 2025 quarter, showcasing significant revenue growth and margin expansion that marks a positive shift in its financial trend. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell, the company’s operational metrics reveal a compelling turnaround compared to its historical averages, signalling renewed investor interest in the garments and apparels sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>db467d31c25913a3311e49d5008db921</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Edges Higher as Select Stocks Show Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-edges-higher-as-select-stocks-show-bullish-momentum-3846000</link><description>The BSE Midcap index edged higher by 0.45% on 18 February 2026, demonstrating resilience amid a mixed market backdrop. With 84 stocks advancing against 60 decliners, the segment’s breadth remained positive at a 1.4x advance-decline ratio, underscoring selective buying interest across sectors. Key technical upgrades and sectoral performances contributed to the modest gains, while investors await upcoming quarterly results for further directional cues.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6084b58a97e52a59a07f1e59eec7999a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Shows Resilience with 0.41% Gain Amid Selective Upgrades</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-shows-resilience-with-041-gain-amid-selective-upgrades-3846001</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, has demonstrated steady resilience with a modest gain of 0.41% on the day and a 0.12% rise over the past five sessions. This performance underscores a cautious but positive market sentiment, driven by selective strength among heavyweight stocks and a nuanced interplay between defensive and cyclical sectors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3ded8fe79410217717bbb0de59a740db</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>