<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Mixed Trends Across Market Caps with Tata Steel and FSN E-Commerce Leading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-amid-sectoral-divergence-and-moderate-profit-growth-3765998</link><description>As the curtain falls on the September 2025 quarter results, a comprehensive analysis of nearly 4,000 companies reveals a nuanced earnings landscape. Positive results were recorded by 43.0% of companies, marking a slight rise from the previous quarter’s 40.0%. Market capitalisation segments displayed varied performance, with mid caps showing the highest proportion of positive outcomes. Leading the pack in their respective categories, Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, and Shaily Engineer. exemplify sectoral strengths amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>37b44f940fb1183634b4830ce3a12713</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orissa Minerals Joins Hidden Turnarounds List Amid Strong Quarterly Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/orissa-minerals-joins-hidden-turnarounds-list-on-strong-financial-upswing-3765995</link><description>Orissa Minerals, a small-cap player in the Minerals &amp; Mining sector, has been added to the Hidden Turnarounds list as of 22 December 2025, reflecting its recent positive financial trajectory and potential for sustained growth. The company’s latest quarterly results reveal notable improvements in profitability and operational efficiency, positioning it as a compelling candidate for investors seeking emerging turnaround opportunities.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>1092403d1fdd4f191ba00e72214d68ec</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are G V Films latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-g-v-films-latest-results-good-or-bad-3765980</link><description>G V Films' latest results are concerning, showing a 62.5% decline in net sales to ₹0.30 crores and a net loss of ₹0.05 crores, indicating ongoing operational and financial challenges, with significant accumulated losses and a lack of investor confidence.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>3517bba63297dc7431a4df891c4ad5ba</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/medi-assist-healthcare-services-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3765968</link><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services, a small-cap player in the insurance sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ef3a9f3c31c1ad90e2d83ee30e0da71a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWL Agri Business Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/awl-agri-business-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765969</link><description>AWL Agri Business, a mid-cap player in the edible oil sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>10c7688af33f36560717a83d7f571c99</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MMP Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mmp-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765967</link><description>MMP Industries, a micro-cap player in the Non - Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>8118f2784c896e92f886e9015da5bc32</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brand Concepts Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brand-concepts-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765965</link><description>Brand Concepts, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3bae30b16e9d221358dd942140b6cec0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Felix Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/felix-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765964</link><description>Felix Industries, a micro-cap player in the miscellaneous sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a possible shift towards a weakening trend and long-term challenges for the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>202e0d37d0c615a4dc012c7199e7bdbc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archit Organosys Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/archit-organosys-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765966</link><description>Archit Organosys, a micro-cap player in the Commodity Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5cc6b679c03820f1b904f6d25796772b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765961</link><description>Adani Enterprises has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the medium to long term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>704b8c3aa7dd7a0ec33f343ce28b418b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sindhu Trade Links Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sindhu-trade-links-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765963</link><description>Sindhu Trade Links has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price movement over the medium to long term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>750d70593fb1812725e880c5176ccadc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axita Cotton Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axita-cotton-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3765962</link><description>Axita Cotton, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed above the 200-day moving average, forming what is commonly known as a Golden Cross. This event is widely regarded by market analysts as a bullish signal, indicating a possible shift in long-term momentum and a potential trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>07da74bd96808f45efeb316b78740e56</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>