<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Artson Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/artson-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862970</link><description>Artson Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the company’s current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>b7ea7444f51d5c008aa6292b4fb8fae1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mankind-pharma-ltd-is-rated-sell-3862968</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>11cdea041ecafb2ffdb2bd992d3b33bd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premco Global Ltd. is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/premco-global-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862969</link><description>Premco Global Ltd. is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>af92cfcf5a87c016f8c7849ba43f7a30</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonal Mercantile Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sonal-mercantile-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862966</link><description>Sonal Mercantile Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a0520545b79ebba7871a96a23641bcf6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/krn-heat-exchanger-and-refrigeration-ltd-is-rated-sell-3862964</link><description>KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 04 December 2025, reflecting a change from the previous 'Hold' status. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 01 March 2026, providing an up-to-date view of the stock's position in the market.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>aec760c587208930937865558360fd4c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Polson Ltd. is Rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/polson-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-by-marketsmojo-3862965</link><description>Polson Ltd. is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>9cc1abbb53ed8f7cdfe409895c84fdc2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swadeshi Industries &amp; Leasing Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/swadeshi-industries-leasing-ltd-is-rated-sell-3862967</link><description>Swadeshi Industries &amp; Leasing Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>8174414f5c4a497d7e22672015f7f1d7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baazar Style Retail Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/baazar-style-retail-ltd-is-rated-sell-3862962</link><description>Baazar Style Retail Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>d004159f7a733743f0f16014d663cae6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tamboli Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tamboli-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862963</link><description>Tamboli Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 08 January 2026, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below are based on the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>ad35be3a8b909bf8a48e74d12904adc8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rudrabhishek Enterprises Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rudrabhishek-enterprises-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862961</link><description>Rudrabhishek Enterprises Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>5d70148d1e851e22e512378eed0d55d4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BGR Energy Systems Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bgr-energy-systems-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862958</link><description>BGR Energy Systems Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>7b1b214d93090012a27aa5690dec29d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVV Infra Ltd is Rated Buy by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pvv-infra-ltd-is-rated-buy-by-marketsmojo-3862959</link><description>PVV Infra Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>476a218d790aec5c653a2e3d23453f9d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vaghani-techno-build-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3862960</link><description>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>06a10678ee32dcb42cc8ab48d064e1e4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Intrux Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gujarat-intrux-ltd-is-rated-sell-3862954</link><description>Gujarat Intrux Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest comprehensive analysis.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>302686eb833ce784fd5f060924dc5de8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D &amp; H India Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/d-h-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3862956</link><description>D &amp; H India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>cca5bf50136f59238da717e6fb7fd2ac</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dai-ichi Karkaria Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dai-ichi-karkaria-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862955</link><description>Dai-ichi Karkaria Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 26 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a893d70f6e69d77ddd4ce2a4c26d2634</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hawkins Cookers Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/hawkins-cookers-ltd-is-rated-sell-3862957</link><description>Hawkins Cookers Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>e30fdd7d1cb664cda860568de44c2997</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NILE Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nile-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3862952</link><description>NILE Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>504f381cef42d1aca906c5bbd21f94e6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/siyaram-silk-mills-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3862950</link><description>Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>d41f251e9937b96628f775dd3c10e410</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everest Kanto Cylinder Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/everest-kanto-cylinder-ltd-is-rated-sell-3862953</link><description>Everest Kanto Cylinder Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 February 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 March 2026, providing investors with the latest comprehensive analysis.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>f4040a2fe87d85547f1982b2073aba5a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>