<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kirloskar-pneumatic-company-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780515</link><description>Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>53000aa618b13c25ab36a9f6d459cf65</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Ltd. is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ashok-leyland-ltd-is-rated-hold-3780514</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd. is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>4c888d3637478d4e11e65d22cae288a7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ABM Knowledgeware Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/abm-knowledgeware-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780512</link><description>ABM Knowledgeware Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a5738769469b8658364e050f66f11199</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bannari Amman Spinning Mills Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bannari-amman-spinning-mills-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780507</link><description>Bannari Amman Spinning Mills Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 February 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>05fbaffcdadfac008fd502c826ec9013</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jainam Ferro Alloys (I) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jainam-ferro-alloys-i-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780513</link><description>Jainam Ferro Alloys (I) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>3e6e7db7427326a4bd1dd799eade4bc4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashapura Minechem Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ashapura-minechem-ltd-is-rated-hold-3780510</link><description>Ashapura Minechem Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>c3eb1bf02c2bdf868d6d4eff06e36513</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>V-Guard Industries Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/v-guard-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-3780511</link><description>V-Guard Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>55cd64058c0dbcbab3413b5fde961e9f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brooks Laboratories Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/brooks-laboratories-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780508</link><description>Brooks Laboratories Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b6282f813483f8634fd16e3faca3249a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indian-toners-developers-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780506</link><description>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the most recent and relevant data to assess the company’s outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b9cebba6ebac6293372f76db306c82be</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peria Karamalai Tea &amp; Produce Company Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/peria-karamalai-tea-produce-company-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780505</link><description>Peria Karamalai Tea &amp; Produce Company Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 29 December 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position in the market.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f66e8e4c75bb56d21341ae6a486a906f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genus Paper &amp; Boards Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/genus-paper-boards-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780509</link><description>Genus Paper &amp; Boards Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f35703a8bb4dc5e08afbd2c9947477ae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multibase India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/multibase-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780504</link><description>Multibase India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on its performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>0d41522061b545f91209d145d7eb6497</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Felix Industries Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/felix-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-3780502</link><description>Felix Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e0c73ade8a1a55a0beb4588d4443d802</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mazagon-dock-shipbuilders-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780503</link><description>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>67f5d05bf0c0aac5ddab138f783d9579</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aveer Foods Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aveer-foods-ltd-is-rated-hold-3780500</link><description>Aveer Foods Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 January 2026. While the rating change occurred at the start of the year, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b8c3486febc6aed6422c4ec6f618b2a5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jasch-gauging-technologies-ltd-is-rated-buy-3780501</link><description>Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b45e290a32bcf81a3265ebaef15d9c16</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bafna Pharmaceuticals Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bafna-pharmaceuticals-ltd-is-rated-sell-3780496</link><description>Bafna Pharmaceuticals Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>5420ed85da135a0d892e58de9c51cff9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abbott India Ltd. is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/abbott-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3780499</link><description>Abbott India Ltd. is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 04 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>da1d8b76c6e698115637a5be188f48a1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>