<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Bank Of Baroda Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-baroda-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3855863</link><description>Bank Of Baroda has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high, reflecting a sustained period of strong performance and market confidence. The stock’s recent surge underscores the company’s robust fundamentals and its prominent position within the public sector banking industry.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>b6376a969f84e6a19d654b24e15cc6ff</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Saw Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.23% Surge on 25 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-saw-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-723-surge-on-25-feb-2026-3855861</link><description>Jindal Saw Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 25 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 188.85, marking a significant 7.45% increase. This sharp rise outpaced the broader Iron &amp; Steel Products sector and reversed a two-day downward trend, reflecting notable trading momentum in the stock.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>b195765ea3c22f47cd2ed600adf2c6e8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Angel One Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/angel-one-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3855860</link><description>Angel One Ltd, a key player in the capital markets sector, witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest price gain, the stock remains under pressure from broader technical indicators and a recent downgrade in its mojo grade, raising questions about the sustainability of this momentum.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>a5505c691c2419ed6fa39ef3c87f2d75</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-momentum-3855858</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a major player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has witnessed a notable 11.01% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s ongoing bearish momentum. This development comes as the stock continues to underperform its sector and broader indices, raising questions about evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>60349b7f0106b81cccc8f899258be7ad</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ind-Agiv Commerce Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ind-agiv-commerce-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3855862</link><description>Ind-Agiv Commerce Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.62.5 today, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on its valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>e942cae762f6720bb0f168baa0e4abc9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Polycab India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/polycab-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3855859</link><description>Polycab India Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock, which recently hit a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs 8,407.5, continues to attract investor attention amid robust volume and improving fundamentals.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>204ddc778e276dd0059f1b4d1928f92c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dalmia-bharat-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3855857</link><description>Dalmia Bharat Ltd (DALBHARAT) has witnessed a significant 25.24% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, raising questions about the directional bets underpinning this surge and the implications for investors in the cement sector.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>8fe7d7b3e5b84e5d3870173c967fe3a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amber-enterprises-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3855856</link><description>Amber Enterprises India Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling a notable shift in market positioning. The stock’s recent outperformance against its sector and sustained gains over the past three sessions have attracted increased attention from traders, reflecting evolving directional bets amid a backdrop of mixed investor participation.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>fafb7815f91b856c54da2c472e4c950f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dixon Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Prolonged Price Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dixon-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-prolonged-price-decline-3855855</link><description>Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd has witnessed a significant 17.6% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s ongoing downward trend. This spike in open interest, coupled with falling prices and subdued delivery volumes, suggests a complex interplay of investor positioning and potential directional bets in the electronics and appliances sector.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>3e4dc90fb02d1ea2f70afaf33f8456e3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Capital Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-capital-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3855854</link><description>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd (ABCAPITAL) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased investor participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price momentum, coupled with rising volumes and improving technical indicators, suggests a growing bullish sentiment among market participants.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>2c9e98541e8be0da763b7b8e5cf82c8e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Union Bank of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/union-bank-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3855850</link><description>Union Bank of India has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market activity and shifting positioning among traders. Despite a slight dip in the stock price, the underlying volume and open interest data suggest evolving directional bets that merit close attention from investors and market analysts alike.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>717f29c6acbff55a115091c362cf040f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd. Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3855849</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd. has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock hit a fresh 52-week high of ₹10,160 on 25 Feb 2026, supported by robust volume and positive sectoral momentum, reflecting growing investor confidence in the automobile giant’s near-term prospects.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>634211b5de9a3e9bbc67823248756b84</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3855853</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd (MARUTI) has witnessed a notable 11.5% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.64% gain in the stock price, the surge in OI alongside volume patterns and moving average trends suggests a complex interplay of bullish and cautious sentiment among traders.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>d5faa4a6de213a342c756fbe7a387cf5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3855846</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd., a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a significant 14.7% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite trading close to its 52-week low, the stock’s recent uptick in volume and open interest suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and market sentiment.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>441713dc02b43e41b3add0073399ef60</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Steady Price Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-zinc-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-steady-price-gains-3855852</link><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd (HINDZINC) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s recent price gains, coupled with a 17.97% increase in open interest, suggest growing bullish sentiment among traders, even as delivery volumes show signs of moderation.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>31d4dbf9021fbf66c61f896491e12126</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Authority Of India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-authority-of-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3855851</link><description>Steel Authority Of India Ltd. (SAIL) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market participation and potential directional bets. The stock recently hit a new 52-week high of Rs. 167.2, supported by robust volume and positive price action, reflecting growing investor confidence in the ferrous metals sector.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>bc50871b848c6b535f65b16396253940</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedanta-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3855845</link><description>Vedanta Ltd., a leading player in the non-ferrous metals sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock has outperformed its sector peers, supported by robust volume and positive price action, prompting a reassessment of its near-term outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>f83ab8701d8171191c6acd872f54be25</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prestige Estates Sees Sharp Open Interest Rise Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prestige-estates-sees-sharp-open-interest-rise-amid-bearish-momentum-3855848</link><description>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd (PRESTIGE) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, rising by 10.82% to 13,303 contracts from 12,004 previously. This increase accompanies a continued bearish trend in the stock, which has declined by 4.62% over the past two days, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among investors in the realty sector.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>33a4ff342b62a340da97539e1b66df89</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Finance Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-finance-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3855844</link><description>L&amp;T Finance Ltd (LTF), a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market sentiment and positioning. The stock outperformed its sector peers on 25 Feb 2026, buoyed by increased volumes and a strong uptick in futures and options activity, suggesting investors are placing directional bets on further upside potential.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>e8fa3956f78dcf682cb4e83059a1d6f2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-holdings-investment-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3855847</link><description>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd (BAJAJHLDNG) has witnessed a notable 16.6% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and technical factors.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>e4e7ba0a08a149e2d10a67c27e33034b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>