<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prime Securities Ltd Falls 3.89%: Technical Shifts and Earnings Impact Weekly</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prime-securities-ltd-falls-389-technical-shifts-and-earnings-impact-weekly-3803409</link><description>Prime Securities Ltd’s shares declined by 3.89% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at ₹264.30 from ₹275.00 the previous Friday. This underperformance slightly exceeded the Sensex’s 3.31% fall during the same period, reflecting a challenging week marked by technical momentum shifts, mixed signals, and a sharp profit decline reported in Q3 FY26.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>0743fb127276871e1eacd259e6c53275</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shekhawati Industries Ltd Drops 22.63% Amidst Steep Declines and Sudden Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shekhawati-industries-ltd-drops-2263-amidst-steep-declines-and-sudden-rally-3803410</link><description>Shekhawati Industries Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price plummeting 22.63% from Rs.17.81 to Rs.13.78, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The week was marked by a series of fresh 52-week lows, deteriorating financial results, and a late-session surge that capped the week with a sharp rebound. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s volatile performance.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>e63c1f0fceefb331c12f800dece51d07</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Petrochem Falls 7.09% Amid Earnings Pressure and Quality Downgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-petrochem-falls-709-amid-earnings-pressure-and-quality-downgrade-3803408</link><description>Supreme Petrochem Ltd’s stock declined by 7.09% over the week ending 23 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The stock hit fresh 52-week lows amid continued earnings pressure, margin compression, and a downgrade in its quality grade, reflecting a challenging environment for the petrochemical company despite some long-term fundamental strengths.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>b38ee63698d03fc0e707b2f4cfcac769</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hubtown Ltd Falls 10.87%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hubtown-ltd-falls-1087-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803405</link><description>Hubtown Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 10.87% to close at Rs.202.55, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall. The stock’s volatile trading was marked by a sharp rebound on 22 January, followed by renewed selling pressure amid bearish technical signals and sectoral headwinds.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>bfff9bd6a36d76ec125cdd03378d617f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Black Box Ltd Falls 5.31%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/black-box-ltd-falls-531-6-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803407</link><description>Black Box Ltd’s stock declined by 5.31% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at ₹480.95 from ₹507.90, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The week was marked by volatile price swings, technical momentum shifts, and a downgrade in the company’s Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell, reflecting growing caution amid mixed signals from technical indicators and flat financial performance.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>c8b8d3b9af3919631203683e03a7bfc2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frontier Springs Ltd Declines 2.52% Despite Technical Strength: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/frontier-springs-ltd-declines-252-despite-technical-strength-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3803406</link><description>Frontier Springs Ltd experienced a volatile week from 19 to 23 January 2026, ending with a 2.52% decline to close at Rs.4,344.90, while the Sensex fell 3.31%. The stock showed strong intraday rallies early in the week, including an 8.23% surge on 19 January and an 8.71% jump on 22 January, but faced sharp reversals and selling pressure midweek. Despite the weekly loss, Frontier Springs outperformed the Sensex by 0.79 percentage points, reflecting resilience amid broader market weakness and sector-specific headwinds.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>a4cb650dc91f002f8a2f6a01ab41b180</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Falls 4.61%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-falls-461-7-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803404</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 4.61% to close at Rs.535.55, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. Despite robust trading volumes and sustained institutional interest, the stock faced pressure amid mixed sectoral trends and short-term profit-taking, reflecting a complex interplay of technical and fundamental factors.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>74f19e8da21f6cc38b9509add6faf634</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J K Cements Ltd Falls 6.03%: Key Downgrades and Volatility Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/j-k-cements-ltd-falls-603-key-downgrades-and-volatility-shape-weekly-performance-3803403</link><description>J K Cements Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining 6.03% from Rs.5,892.45 to Rs.5,537.00, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. Despite a strong intraday surge on 20 January, the week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating and a quality grade reduction, reflecting growing concerns over profitability and leverage amid volatile market conditions.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>4f5c566952a6ef99d4b7993e699c1468</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gravita India Ltd Declines 2.75% Amid Mixed Technical Signals and Death Cross Formation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gravita-india-ltd-declines-275-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-death-cross-formation-3803402</link><description>Gravita India Ltd’s stock closed the week down 2.75% at Rs.1,549.25, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The week was marked by a series of mixed technical signals, a notable death cross formation, and quarterly results that revealed profit growth amid margin pressures. Despite short-term volatility and bearish technical developments, the stock’s long-term performance remains robust, reflecting a complex investment landscape for market participants.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>8068d5cd3e6b701380f5b5e64df64708</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Triveni Enterprises Ltd Falls 3.10%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/triveni-enterprises-ltd-falls-310-4-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3803401</link><description>Triveni Enterprises Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.1.25, down 3.10% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1.29, marginally outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant drop to an all-time low of Rs.1.01 on 21 January 2026, reflecting ongoing financial and operational challenges amid a broadly weak market environment.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>40cb0bd59c8ad36680d2421374e632e0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd Falls 4.64%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/l-g-balakrishnan-bros-ltd-falls-464-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803400</link><description>L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.1,731.45 on 23 January 2026, down 4.64% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,815.75. Despite this decline, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant technical downgrade, a sharp intraday rebound, and mixed momentum signals that shaped investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>7d2faaf1a60daa32e3bd2b347a71e672</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intense Technologies Ltd Falls 7.47%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/intense-technologies-ltd-falls-747-3-key-factors-driving-the-volatile-week-3803399</link><description>Intense Technologies Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, closing down 7.47% to Rs.105.95, despite the broader Sensex falling 3.31%. The stock’s volatility was driven by a downgrade to Strong Sell, a sharp plunge to the lower circuit on heavy selling, and a late-week surge to the upper circuit, reflecting a week of mixed investor sentiment and significant price swings.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>71bc4d7631a5391396c24b312fa7f661</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Themis Biosyn Ltd Falls 11.60%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-themis-biosyn-ltd-falls-1160-7-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803398</link><description>Gujarat Themis Biosyn Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 11.60% to close at Rs.315.65, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. The stock’s volatile price action was marked by sharp intraday swings, rating downgrades, and mixed technical signals, reflecting investor caution amid broader market weakness and sector-specific pressures.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>be9f1ea60b282e4cc1302dc59a146375</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge Declines 2.11% Amid Mixed Technical Signals and Rising Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-declines-211-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-rising-derivatives-activity-3803395</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd closed the week ending 23 January 2026 at ₹1,301.40, down 2.11% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹1,329.40. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell 3.31% over the same period, indicating relative resilience despite a challenging market environment. The week was marked by mixed technical momentum, significant surges in derivatives open interest, and fluctuating investor sentiment amid sector headwinds.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>06ab1e4d076f29eb1c7fb0abdda80c99</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navneet Education Ltd Declines 1.36% Amid Strong Sell Downgrade and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/navneet-education-ltd-declines-136-amid-strong-sell-downgrade-and-bearish-technicals-3803396</link><description>Navneet Education Ltd closed the week at Rs.140.95, down 1.95% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.143.75, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock showed a mixed performance during the week, with a notable rebound on 22 January before retreating again on the final trading day. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating technical and financial trends, which weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>560fcd642c94b3a53f30ebad24e20b01</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ISGEC Heavy Engineering Ltd Falls 4.60% Amid 52-Week Lows and Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/isgec-heavy-engineering-ltd-falls-460-amid-52-week-lows-and-bearish-momentum-3803397</link><description>ISGEC Heavy Engineering Ltd’s stock declined by 4.60% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.736.40 compared to Rs.771.90 the previous Friday. This underperformance, though sharper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall, reflects a week marked by fresh 52-week lows, bearish technical signals, and subdued financial results amid broader market weakness.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>fe3c2bf533c8c05fc9f4e76a24d2632a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veljan Denison Ltd Falls 2.69%: Downgrade and Technical Shift Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veljan-denison-ltd-falls-269-downgrade-and-technical-shift-shape-weekly-trend-3803394</link><description>Veljan Denison Ltd’s stock declined by 2.69% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.1,180.75 compared to Rs.1,213.35 the previous Friday. This underperformance was slightly better than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall, reflecting a mixed week marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating and a notable shift in technical momentum. The stock’s price action and market sentiment were influenced by subdued financial results, operational challenges, and a complex technical landscape.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>be0e177d58e0aa3c5c6467c6bf058493</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Rama Synthetics Falls 4.06%: 2 Key Technical Signals Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-rama-synthetics-falls-406-2-key-technical-signals-drive-weekly-decline-3803393</link><description>Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 4.06% from Rs.42.66 to Rs.40.93, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by significant technical developments, including the formation of a Death Cross and a subsequent downgrade from Buy to Hold, signalling increased bearish momentum amid broader market weakness.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>a28a3e1ac1ba9763317ec07573c39426</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Falls 2.34% Despite Upper Circuit Surge: 4 Key Factors This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/housing-development-infrastructure-ltd-falls-234-despite-upper-circuit-surge-4-key-factors-this-week-3803389</link><description>Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd (HDIL) experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 2.34% from Rs.2.14 to Rs.2.09, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by multiple new 52-week lows, persistent underperformance relative to the broader market, and a late-week surge to the upper circuit, reflecting a volatile trading environment amid weak fundamentals and sector headwinds.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>40eb815de317f938342005d5fbb90e00</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Hume Pipe Falls 4.04%: Technical Shifts and Mixed Financial Signals Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-hume-pipe-falls-404-technical-shifts-and-mixed-financial-signals-shape-weekly-performance-3803390</link><description>Indian Hume Pipe Company Ltd’s shares declined by 4.04% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.374.90 from Rs.390.70 the previous Friday. This underperformance was marginally worse than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall during the same period. The week was marked by mixed technical signals and a cautious upgrade in the stock’s rating, reflecting a complex interplay of improving momentum and fundamental concerns.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>3aaab9e2c1ad37e444b41837c5b0ad95</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>