<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ddev-plastiks-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776697</link><description>DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd, a small-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock’s near-term momentum and long-term strength.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2ef7462661e8295af689cf05cd8c3a6a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manorama Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manorama-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776695</link><description>Manorama Industries Ltd, a prominent player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term strength despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4ddcf1919be3011cb29c63bd2147eb34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elitecon International Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/elitecon-international-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776696</link><description>Elitecon International Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a4a765c12239b1d909992d24741a97be</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/advanced-enzyme-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3776693</link><description>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b08a5e17ddd14d73f337c1eeb4520295</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olectra Greentech Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/olectra-greentech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776692</link><description>Olectra Greentech Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9d49e4038b0f863cc90c363a35b98f2d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sikozy Realtors Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sikozy-realtors-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3776689</link><description>Sikozy Realtors Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a significant bearish trend and potential long-term weakness for the stock. This technical development, coupled with deteriorating fundamentals and weak price performance, underscores growing investor caution.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>82e8c14ae9481b2d88478eabae08eaec</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B2B Software Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b2b-software-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3776690</link><description>B2B Software Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a sustained bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bf3f4859c0dbc6bb272c8e114e5e5c45</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nalwa Sons Investments Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nalwa-sons-investments-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3776686</link><description>Nalwa Sons Investments Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s short- to medium-term momentum, raising concerns about sustained weakness in the coming months.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c05021c90c884f583252d3722e414365</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One Point One Solutions Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/one-point-one-solutions-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3776691</link><description>One Point One Solutions Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, suggesting a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the stock within the Commercial Services &amp; Supplies sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>51c2b9e6a151c38fe5aaee8abeecea24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ludlow Jute &amp; Specialities Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ludlow-jute-specialities-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3776685</link><description>Ludlow Jute &amp; Specialities Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s short- to medium-term momentum and raising concerns about its near-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>706ff1d3560550101083390c5a249cb7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Road Network Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-road-network-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3776694</link><description>Bharat Road Network Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that the stock could be poised for an upward trend reversal despite its challenging recent performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>87e88e7077a081b4ca8d232e72818324</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NILE Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nile-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776687</link><description>NILE Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Minerals &amp; Mining sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ad7ae28d89f80e73c348551d06dc079a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TCI Finance Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tci-finance-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3776688</link><description>TCI Finance Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting renewed investor interest despite the company’s current Sell mojo grade.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>59daa0e1f6d8083f0e3d6c1a30895b16</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Worth Peripherals Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/worth-peripherals-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-mixed-financial-signals-3776618</link><description>Worth Peripherals Ltd has declined to its 52-week low, reflecting a significant downturn in its stock price despite positive quarterly earnings and a stable debt profile. The stock’s current price marks a notable contrast to its previous highs and broader market trends.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d5e0fbe053d9842174f987ea615a2cfc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedant Fashions Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedant-fashions-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3776619</link><description>Vedant Fashions Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 574.6, marking a significant downturn in the garment and apparel sector. This new low comes amid a year of sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks and peers, reflecting a challenging period for the company’s stock.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>ba8c8c945f1cb7eb53ecba01259fb693</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shankara Building Products Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shankara-building-products-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3776621</link><description>Shankara Building Products Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near ₹100.3, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a backdrop of subdued financial performance and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>a672997cc47bdb472d0c736e292da7c9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tijaria-polypipes-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3776620</link><description>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures within the plastic products industrial sector. The stock's latest low price marks a significant decline over the past year, underscoring persistent challenges faced by the company amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>c8280db78788d712e0899f4d0fb88c94</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Rally as Oil &amp; Gas Sector Leads; Small Caps Outperform</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-rally-as-oil-gas-sector-leads-small-caps-outperform-3776617</link><description>Indian equity markets closed higher on 31 Dec 2025, with the Nifty gaining 0.74% to settle at 26,129.60 and the Sensex advancing 0.64% to 85,220.60. Broad-based sectoral strength, led by the Oil &amp; Gas segment, and robust market breadth underpinned the rally as investors positioned ahead of key corporate earnings and global cues.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f5f5854dbe5e48ae4931187574c40c83</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>