<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Zen Technologies Q3 FY26: Growth Momentum Stalls Amid Execution Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/zen-technologies-q3-fy26-growth-momentum-stalls-amid-execution-challenges-3813405</link><description>Zen Technologies Ltd., a leading defence simulator manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹12,482 crores, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹54.77 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a sequential decline of 7.79% from the previous quarter. The results reveal a concerning deceleration in the company's growth trajectory, with revenue growth moderating to just 2.45% quarter-on-quarter, whilst year-on-year consolidated profit growth of 37.89% masked underlying execution challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ea5a12e1a4e3e9be7c57b7a03c212f41</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GAIL (India) Q3 FY26: Profit Plunges 57% as Margin Pressures Intensify</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/gail-india-q3-fy26-profit-plunges-57-as-margin-pressures-intensify-3813403</link><description>GAIL (India) Ltd., the nation's largest state-owned natural gas processing and distribution company, reported a sharp 56.97% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit for Q3 FY26, with earnings falling to ₹1,756.17 crores from ₹4,081.56 crores in the corresponding quarter last year. The results, announced for the quarter ending December 2025, reveal mounting operational pressures as the company grapples with contracting margins and subdued revenue growth despite its commanding ₹109,015 crore market capitalisation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5d4f1deef2f69c60052623de53b8814e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Incap Ltd Q2 FY26: Revenue Plunge and Margin Pressure Trigger Sharp Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/incap-ltd-q2-fy26-revenue-plunge-and-margin-pressure-trigger-sharp-concerns-3813402</link><description>Incap Limited, a Vijayawada-based manufacturer of aluminium electrolytic capacitors, reported deeply concerning results for Q2 FY26, with net profit declining 26.67% quarter-on-quarter to ₹0.22 crores from ₹0.30 crores in Q1 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the micro-cap company witnessed a steeper 51.11% decline from ₹0.45 crores in Q2 FY25. The stock, currently trading at ₹75.00 with a market capitalisation of ₹36.00 crores, surged 6.99% in the trading session following the results announcement, though this appears to be a technical bounce rather than fundamental optimism.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0d5f27a4ba46f4b64a2666b8b3ff80cb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishnu Chemicals Q3 FY26: Modest Growth Amid Rising Interest Costs</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/vishnu-chemicals-q3-fy26-modest-growth-amid-rising-interest-costs-3813401</link><description>Vishnu Chemicals Limited, a Hyderabad-based specialty chromium chemicals manufacturer, reported a marginal decline in net profit for Q3 FY26, with earnings of ₹33.76 crores compared to ₹34.40 crores in Q3 FY25, representing a year-on-year decline of 1.86%. However, on a sequential basis, the company posted a modest improvement of 2.68% from Q2 FY26's ₹32.88 crores. The stock traded at ₹522.45 on January 30, 2026, up 1.20% from the previous close, giving the company a market capitalisation of ₹3,453 crores.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>66f295c58fbcd8cc9cd2c53514cb64d4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Northern ARC Capital Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-northern-arc-capital-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813400</link><description>Northern ARC Capital Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with record revenue of ₹721.14 crores and a net profit of ₹100.76 crores, both showing significant growth. However, the company faces challenges with margin compression and a high debt-to-equity ratio, indicating mixed financial performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b064111063f5925c34b950b488be37df</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-odigma-consultancy-solutions-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813399</link><description>Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd's latest results are poor, showing a 23.95% decline in net sales and a net loss of ₹1.44 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and a deteriorating financial position. The company is struggling with declining profitability and a loss of institutional investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>032239af484d5fba4a9551d7d6fca312</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are ESAF Small Finance Bank Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-esaf-small-finance-bank-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813398</link><description>ESAF Small Finance Bank Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹115.81 crores for Q3 FY26, declining revenues, and rising non-performing assets, indicating significant operational challenges and a negative return on equity. The bank faces a tough road to recovery, requiring improvements in asset quality and profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3949331609be81f1114ae3a22d6c5ed9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Doms Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-doms-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813397</link><description>Doms Industries Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth with net sales of ₹592.19 crores, but profit growth is slowing, raising concerns about sustainability. While the company maintains a solid return on equity, its high P/E ratio suggests investors should carefully assess its valuation amid margin pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2979f0225483fa70e188a38dc9052c74</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aadhar-housing-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813396</link><description>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong operational performance with a net profit of ₹281.21 crores and a robust operating margin of 77.35%. However, concerns about elevated valuations relative to earnings may pose risks for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>91dd1725a1ea64e6e4d7ca9e258afea2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are TransIndia Real Estate Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-transindia-real-estate-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813395</link><description>TransIndia Real Estate Ltd's latest results show a net profit increase of 23.30% to ₹10.85 crores, but revenue declined by 8.55% year-on-year, raising concerns about sustainability and capital efficiency despite a debt-free balance sheet. Overall, the results reflect profit growth overshadowed by ongoing operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e6c7f6fd9c873ef49bafa209a73f2be7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Jupiter Life Line Hospitals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jupiter-life-line-hospitals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813394</link><description>Jupiter Life Line Hospitals Ltd's latest results show strong operational performance with a net profit of ₹57.35 crores and revenue growth in Q2 FY26, but a decline in net sales and profit in the following quarter raises concerns about sustainability. Investors should consider these mixed signals when evaluating the company's future prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bf2b8fe44df17915567d552dda18a8f6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Meghmani Organics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-meghmani-organics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813393</link><description>Meghmani Organics Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing an 11.87% decline in revenue and a net loss of ₹3.53 crores, indicating ongoing operational challenges and pressure in the agrochemicals sector. The company's profitability has been negatively impacted by high costs and reliance on other income, reflecting a period of instability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ac07a59a66689a0acfca3b6ba5e40690</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Delhivery Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-delhivery-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813391</link><description>Delhivery Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 11.57% quarter-on-quarter, but the company reported a net loss of ₹50.38 crores, raising concerns about profitability and operational efficiency. While revenue gains indicate market share growth, significant losses and declining margins suggest critical challenges ahead for the company's sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6db278e723b387176d99179413ef8acd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Epigral Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-epigral-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813390</link><description>Epigral Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 7.46% year-on-year decline in net sales and a 62.26% drop in net profit after tax, alongside significant margin compression and rising costs, indicating operational challenges and reduced investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8e23a54d4edf53ed3f1951d5e21ee9cf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Clean Science &amp; Technology Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-clean-science-technology-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813389</link><description>Clean Science &amp; Technology Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 30.10% year-on-year decline in net profit and an 8.78% drop in revenue, alongside significant margin compression, indicating ongoing operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ed520ee025e652835131c1e808acd381</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Medplus Health Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-medplus-health-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813388</link><description>MedPlus Health Services Ltd reported strong Q3 FY26 results with record net sales of ₹1,806.12 crores, reflecting solid growth. However, margin compression and a slight decline in operating margin raise concerns about profitability sustainability, despite a year-on-year increase in net profit.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b2d23719ca287237e884052562cdff21</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-motherson-sumi-wiring-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813387</link><description>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 25.57% year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure, as operating margins declined and net profit fell 9.63% sequentially. Overall, while revenue generation is robust, the company faces challenges in maintaining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>97a90dad74f10e8fb51b956454ca1256</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are United Foodbrands Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-united-foodbrands-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813386</link><description>United Foodbrands Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 14.50% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹7.10 crores, marking its fourth consecutive quarter of losses and raising concerns about profitability and financial stability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>74b07259ab309001d9d9fc2431b555e9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Antony Waste Handling Cell Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-antony-waste-handling-cell-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813385</link><description>Antony Waste Handling Cell Ltd's latest results show revenue growth of 8.12% year-on-year, but profitability has declined significantly, with net profit down 27.03% and operating margins at their lowest. This indicates ongoing operational challenges and rising costs that could impact future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>70070c8704fcbd14149138aecf66c5ae</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nila Spaces Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nila-spaces-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3813384</link><description>Nila Spaces Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit of ₹8.04 crores and net sales of ₹52.20 crores, showing significant year-on-year growth. However, challenges like low return on equity and rising interest costs suggest caution regarding long-term sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1cf2b7cd2676551141b12b022d96aa49</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>