<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>MTAR Technologies Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs 2915</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mtar-technologies-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs-2915-3810858</link><description>MTAR Technologies Ltd, a prominent player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has reached a new all-time high of Rs.2915, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and underscoring the company’s robust performance over recent periods.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>1d4f294a7eab47df22be82a62a440dc4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gautam Gems Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gautam-gems-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-underperformance-3810860</link><description>Shares of Gautam Gems Ltd have plunged to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance and financial strain within the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector. The stock’s recent 14.00% decline in a single day marks a significant milestone in its downward trajectory, underscoring ongoing challenges faced by the company.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>9f0f5d40d780d260e352e88642b239dc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Bank Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-bank-stock-hits-all-time-high-amid-robust-performance-3810859</link><description>Indian Bank has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high, reflecting a sustained period of strong financial performance and market confidence. The stock’s recent surge underscores the bank’s robust fundamentals and consistent growth trajectory within the public sector banking space.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>017f27f8d155ee7310bf9ba7a6cd7bc6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avalon Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.89% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avalon-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-789-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3810857</link><description>Avalon Technologies Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 853.7, marking a 6.11% increase during the session and closing with a notable 7.89% gain. This strong upward movement outpaced both its sector and the broader market indices, reflecting significant trading momentum.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>ce726a063eaa404faefd42fdd3ddffc5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Ltd Surges to Intraday High with 11.34% Gain on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cupid-ltd-surges-to-intraday-high-with-1134-gain-on-30-jan-2026-3810852</link><description>Cupid Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging 11.34% to touch an intraday high of Rs 430.5, significantly outperforming its FMCG sector peers and the broader market indices.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>5315c2d365868cba75911a56dfb6b218</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balu Forge Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.89% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balu-forge-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-789-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3810854</link><description>Balu Forge Industries Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 424.8, marking an 8.46% increase from the previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum amid a generally subdued market environment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>9ce276ff2f21353fa9ef53925da6f3ac</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gabriel India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.53% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gabriel-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-753-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3810856</link><description>Gabriel India Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 30 Jan 2026, surging 7.53% to touch a day’s high of Rs 932.35, significantly outperforming its sector and the broader market amid a subdued Sensex session.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>5cc31df8a68b02a778c152630867f978</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>REC Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rec-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-30-jan-2026-3810855</link><description>REC Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 363.55 as the stock faced significant price pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance. The stock closed with a day change of -3.05%, underperforming its finance sector peers and the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>785a502083c47327e4dcdcf7de6a5407</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Media Matrix Worldwide Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/media-matrix-worldwide-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3810853</link><description>Media Matrix Worldwide Ltd commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price 5.13% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market concerns following overnight developments. The stock’s weak start underscores ongoing pressures within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, as investors digest recent performance trends and technical indicators.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>e6c83626aa38bb51d8685927e5d1a09e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sri Adhikari Brothers Television Network Ltd Opens with Weak Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sri-adhikari-brothers-television-network-ltd-opens-with-weak-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3810851</link><description>Sri Adhikari Brothers Television Network Ltd commenced trading today with a significant gap down, opening at Rs 1,655.9, reflecting a 5.0% decline from the previous close. This sharp drop underscores prevailing market concerns and marks the continuation of a downward trend for the media and entertainment company.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>498eadffdcbb870107a1302daa2abaee</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-builders-engineers-india-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-decline-3810850</link><description>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.89.85, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock’s recent performance reflects sustained pressure amid a challenging market environment, with key financial indicators underscoring the severity of the situation.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>758468243bb7a4e66c94925e17169ed4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-housing-finance-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3810849</link><description>Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.87.3, marking a significant milestone in its recent market trajectory. Despite a slight positive movement today, the stock continues to reflect extended periods of underperformance relative to key benchmarks and its sector peers.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>4097f95158211af33160a9abbc913e0d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akme-fintrade-india-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3810848</link><description>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), recorded a new all-time low share price of Rs.4.8 on 30 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. Despite a modest uptick of 0.82% on the day, the stock remains substantially below key moving averages and continues to underperform both its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>d6f9c64eb1e364b5651db7701e7eca3c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jana-small-finance-bank-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3810844</link><description>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd’s stock plunged to a new all-time low of Rs.351.85 on 30 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices over multiple timeframes, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial performance and market valuation.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>b6a7cccbf79714e692b77b9e8b617170</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sai-silks-kalamandir-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3810843</link><description>Shares of Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd have declined to a new all-time low of Rs.106.7, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The garment and apparel company’s stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices over multiple time frames, reflecting persistent pressures on its valuation and market sentiment.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>ba6b6753f03ac8445513d1ab683e750e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sula Vineyards Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sula-vineyards-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3810847</link><description>Sula Vineyards Ltd, a key player in the Indian beverages sector, recorded a new all-time low of ₹180.15 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind market benchmarks, reflecting a challenging period for the company amid subdued financial results and diminished institutional interest.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7c31c72406eceae7c8c83f05763d1e28</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sigachi Industries Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sigachi-industries-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3810842</link><description>Sigachi Industries Ltd, a player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.19.3 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag notably behind market benchmarks, reflecting a challenging period for the company.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>d9fd179177863b72c7a2bd6d6a3a74fb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishwaraj Sugar Industries Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vishwaraj-sugar-industries-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3810846</link><description>Shares of Vishwaraj Sugar Industries Ltd have fallen to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance and financial strain. The stock’s recent decline underscores significant challenges faced by the company within the sugar sector, as it continues to lag behind market benchmarks and peers.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>350617be5bb453592dcf165717c3248d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.147.6</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lotus-eye-hospital-institute-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs1476-3810841</link><description>Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd has reached a significant milestone, hitting an all-time high of Rs.147.6 on 30 Jan 2026, marking a remarkable phase in the company’s market performance and reflecting sustained investor confidence in the hospital sector.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>fc510c38f76a8ec3b6523e87adb163ce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murae Organisor Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/murae-organisor-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3810845</link><description>Shares of Murae Organisor Ltd, a player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, have declined to an all-time low of Rs.0.2, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s extended downward trajectory despite recent positive earnings reports.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>1e5c5ba828736b93a84fe1bb2ba8becc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>