<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Le Travenues Technology Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.13% Surge on 27 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/le-travenues-technology-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-713-surge-on-27-jan-2026-3806211</link><description>Le Travenues Technology Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 27 Jan 2026, surging 7.13% to touch a day’s high of Rs 216.2, significantly outperforming its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c95cf2d16ae60f7564a06df3b830d594</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DLF Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 3.09% Surge on 27 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dlf-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-309-surge-on-27-jan-2026-3806210</link><description>DLF Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 27 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of ₹604.45, marking a 2.69% rise during the trading session. The stock closed with a notable gain of 3.09%, outperforming the Sensex and its sector peers amid a broader market recovery.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>df6bc8ec433bb53f16d8e41283de8ad8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raymond Ltd Q3 FY26: Operational Gains Overshadowed by Exceptional Items and Structural Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/raymond-ltd-q3-fy26-operational-gains-overshadowed-by-exceptional-items-and-structural-challenges-3806213</link><description>Raymond Ltd., the integrated textile and realty conglomerate with a market capitalisation of ₹2,582.40 crores, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹3.58 crores for Q3 FY26 ended December 2025, marking a dramatic 95.04% year-on-year decline from ₹72.13 crores in the corresponding quarter last year. The quarter-on-quarter performance was equally concerning, with consolidated net profit plunging 68.54% from ₹11.38 crores in Q2 FY26. The stock closed at ₹387.90 on January 27, 2026, up 4.95% on the day but down 50.40% from its 52-week high of ₹782.00, reflecting investor concerns about the company's deteriorating profitability despite operational improvements.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>b8ac8cb533b39e3c34ab9a5f8150c7d6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nila Infrastructures Q3 FY26: Growth Momentum Masks Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/nila-infrastructures-q3-fy26-growth-momentum-masks-profitability-concerns-3806212</link><description>Nila Infrastructures Ltd., an Ahmedabad-based real estate developer with a market capitalisation of ₹352.00 crores, reported consolidated net profit of ₹4.65 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a concerning 23.52% sequential decline from ₹6.08 crores in Q2 FY26, despite posting robust revenue growth. The stock, currently trading at ₹8.82, has declined 21.95% over the past year, significantly underperforming the Sensex's 8.28% gain during the same period.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>2040e59fd69ea929e7704a1f35ac9807</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Updater Services Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/updater-services-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-decline-3806207</link><description>Updater Services Ltd, a player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.151.6, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind key market indices and sector averages, reflecting a challenging period for the company.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>f25841eb4bf969f5c9c40d4b13667821</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Paints Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 27 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asian-paints-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-27-jan-2026-3806209</link><description>Asian Paints Ltd. experienced notable intraday weakness on 27 Jan 2026, with its share price touching a low of Rs 2,545.8, marking a decline of 5.79% from previous levels. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid subdued market sentiment and immediate price pressures.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>ffd0e69221ca137a4635186eaa652083</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Finserve Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 27 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sg-finserve-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-27-jan-2026-3806208</link><description>SG Finserve Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 27 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 349.55, down 7.05% from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment within the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) space.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>0f73f0c9c421602d46baf71e0b5ac042</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Add-Shop E-Retail Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/add-shop-e-retail-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3806205</link><description>Add-Shop E-Retail Ltd has reached an all-time low, continuing its extended period of underperformance within the E-Retail sector. The stock’s latest decline of 4.31% on 27 Jan 2026 marks a significant milestone in its downward trajectory, reflecting persistent challenges in financial metrics and market valuation compared to benchmarks and peers.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>22ab53f802e64118c1937fb6a85af97b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3806198</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd (POLICYBZR) has witnessed a significant 16.8% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and volume patterns, suggests a complex repositioning by investors that may hint at directional bets in the near term.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>c9eeac095046158eac35aa0f36b2a54b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-technicals-3806197</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd has witnessed a notable 13.36% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock trades below all major moving averages, reflecting a cautious sentiment amid mixed volume and price action.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>e9c934e7d2afaa729c75ab11c3e403b9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3806196</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd, the parent company of Nykaa, has witnessed a notable 11.3% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent price softness. This surge in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and shifting investor positioning, offers critical insights into potential directional bets and market sentiment for this mid-cap e-commerce player.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>b6f19ae068a0edda18e418e646e0dcd5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Green Energy Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-green-energy-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3806194</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.78% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite trading near its 52-week low, the stock outperformed its sector with a 2.32% gain on 27 Jan 2026, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish bets among traders.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>ac34f7c654119e80b0a39ff30fe9c023</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amber-enterprises-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3806193</link><description>Amber Enterprises India Ltd has witnessed a significant 14.03% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock continues to trade near its 52-week low, reflecting persistent bearish sentiment amid a six-day losing streak and underperformance relative to its sector.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>c5b2ca2358fe39d568ace4d886f72c80</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bandhan-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3806195</link><description>Bandhan Bank Ltd. has witnessed a notable 12.4% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>99627ebf2d5aeb2693040b671af8399e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Mixed Moving Average Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-mixed-moving-average-signals-3806192</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (LT), a heavyweight in the construction sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This development comes alongside the stock’s outperformance relative to its sector and the broader Sensex, reflecting renewed investor interest and potential directional bets in the near term.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>faf22aee40f1a4016908f810ab13c7d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3806188</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd has witnessed a notable 14.6% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and subdued investor participation, suggests a complex interplay of positioning and directional bets among traders.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>1038a8843dc09b4b90e8ac1efb71c397</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Power Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-power-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-momentum-3806189</link><description>Tata Power Company Ltd has witnessed a notable 12.2% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent downward trend. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and moving average indicators, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among investors.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>ee0c5398c86cc553e32c83a213e898c3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/glenmark-pharmaceuticals-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3806190</link><description>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and a potential shift in investor sentiment towards a bullish stance. The stock outperformed its sector peers and the broader Sensex, supported by increased volumes and rising delivery-based investor activity, signalling renewed confidence in the mid-cap pharmaceutical player.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>5e912bbec352d05ba496b8c387a34526</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ambuja Cements Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ambuja-cements-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3806191</link><description>Ambuja Cements Ltd (AMBUJACEM) has witnessed a notable 11.5% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among traders. Despite this surge, the stock remains below key moving averages, reflecting a complex technical backdrop as investors weigh directional bets amid rising volumes and delivery participation.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>52c35c204c2813aed0962e8a41b51e75</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GAIL (India) Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gail-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3806187</link><description>GAIL (India) Ltd has witnessed a significant 16.0% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock continues to trade below all major moving averages, reflecting persistent bearish sentiment amid falling investor participation and a recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>dd6d2e6e67399a291d439825b4ee814e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>