<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Airan Ltd Gains 30.47%: 2 Key Events Driving Volatility This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/airan-ltd-gains-3047-2-key-events-driving-volatility-this-week-3839389</link><description>Airan Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 30.47% from Rs.14.67 to Rs.19.14 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by extreme volatility, with the stock hitting an upper circuit on 11 February before plunging to a lower circuit on 13 February amid heavy trading volumes and sharp price swings.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>7fb532ce83c3f958e4f8cb5b266eb3ad</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sarthak Metals Gains 17.81%: Margin Improvements and Profit Surge Drive Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sarthak-metals-gains-1781-margin-improvements-and-profit-surge-drive-volatility-3839385</link><description>Sarthak Metals Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, gaining 17.81% from Rs.73.00 on 9 Feb to Rs.86.00 on 13 Feb, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s sharp rise early in the week was driven by reports of flat quarterly results accompanied by margin improvements, followed by volatility in the latter sessions amid broader market weakness.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>88cb625ffacba6eaa8b203b691c213f2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maximus International Gains 0.92%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maximus-international-gains-092-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3839388</link><description>Maximus International Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.92%, rising from Rs.9.80 to Rs.9.89, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp earnings update revealing a 29% profit decline and a subsequent valuation upgrade signalling renewed price attractiveness despite ongoing margin pressures.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>00ef62a1bcf74b42352d088b1f15516b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shankara Building Products Falls 8.51%: Quarterly Setbacks and 52-Week Low Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shankara-building-products-falls-851-quarterly-setbacks-and-52-week-low-mark-the-week-3839387</link><description>Shankara Building Products Ltd experienced a sharp decline of 8.51% over the week ending 13 February 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell by just 0.54%. The stock opened at Rs.110.45 on 9 February and closed at Rs.101.05 on 13 February, pressured by a steep quarterly revenue drop and a fresh 52-week low. Despite some relative resilience on the final trading day, the week was marked by sustained selling and deteriorating fundamentals.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>13271225a2e504132528f94873afaca3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Newtech Ltd Falls 6.53%: Technical Weakness and Market Underperformance Drive Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/creative-newtech-ltd-falls-653-technical-weakness-and-market-underperformance-drive-sell-off-3839386</link><description>Creative Newtech Ltd experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 6.53% to close at Rs.649.65, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell by only 0.54%. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid deteriorating technical indicators and persistent market underperformance despite strong financial results. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped the stock’s trajectory over the week.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>d0a1d8ac8b4fbc99545d6dc3f955e8bb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd Falls 4.73%: Valuation and Quality Shifts Mark a Tumultuous Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/focus-lighting-fixtures-ltd-falls-473-valuation-and-quality-shifts-mark-a-tumultuous-week-3839384</link><description>Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 4.73% from ₹69.62 to ₹66.33, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp profit plunge announcement, a valuation recalibration, and a quality grading upgrade, all influencing investor sentiment and price movements amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>f56fc78178a7fc04650cb571f0caa057</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls 10.32%: Key Financial and Valuation Challenges Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-1032-key-financial-and-valuation-challenges-weigh-3839380</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd experienced a sharp decline of 10.32% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.28.06 from Rs.31.29 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall, highlighting significant company-specific pressures amid deteriorating financials, valuation concerns, and negative market sentiment.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>b20c4e1a8ce39d1ff5c846d5e89d2f94</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Escorp Asset Management Ltd Declines 2.40%: Quarterly Results and Market Volatility Impact</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/escorp-asset-management-ltd-declines-240-quarterly-results-and-market-volatility-impact-3839382</link><description>Escorp Asset Management Ltd’s stock declined by 2.40% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.114.10 compared to Rs.116.90 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s smaller 0.54% fall, reflecting investor caution amid a sharp deterioration in the company’s quarterly financial results and operational challenges within the NBFC sector.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>24dd6a5fc623f00d9435f88ac461c236</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panache Digilife Ltd Falls 3.73%: 5 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/panache-digilife-ltd-falls-373-5-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-volatility-3839383</link><description>Panache Digilife Ltd experienced a volatile week from 9 to 13 February 2026, ending with a 3.73% decline to close at Rs.323.60, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54%. The stock saw sharp intraday rallies midweek, including two upper circuit hits, before succumbing to heavy selling pressure on the final trading day. This review analyses the key events driving price swings and the implications for investors amid mixed fundamental signals and technical developments.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>8c9d7db0cbcac86cd6b954d213fc691c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starlineps Enterprises Gains 10.01%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/starlineps-enterprises-gains-1001-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3839381</link><description>Starlineps Enterprises Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 10.01% from Rs.8.49 to Rs.9.34 between 09 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock marked new 52-week highs on five consecutive trading days, reflecting sustained momentum amid mixed broader market conditions and a cautious sector backdrop.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>2cd847a3a06a4d93e26363ec95655d78</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meera Industries Falls 4.82%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/meera-industries-falls-482-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3839375</link><description>Meera Industries Ltd’s stock declined by 4.82% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.72.24 from Rs.75.90 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall, highlighting the stock’s relative weakness amid mixed technical signals and disappointing quarterly results.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>31c4199084aa01a5cfc193d973036ac9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Variman Global Enterprises Ltd Gains 21.53%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/variman-global-enterprises-ltd-gains-2153-2-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3839374</link><description>Variman Global Enterprises Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 21.53%, closing at Rs.5.25 on 13 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s steady ascent was supported by a series of positive developments, including a strong quarterly profit report and a notable upgrade in valuation attractiveness, despite some operational concerns. This review analyses the key events that shaped the stock’s performance during the week and places them in the context of broader market movements.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>4ec6cd9b0e66d095e4c7c020d5450b71</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ERIS Lifesciences Dips 1.22%: Mixed Technical Signals and Hold Upgrade Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eris-lifesciences-dips-122-mixed-technical-signals-and-hold-upgrade-shape-the-week-3839377</link><description>ERIS Lifesciences Ltd experienced a turbulent trading week from 9 to 13 February 2026, closing with a modest decline of 1.22% to Rs.1,414.65, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54%. The week was marked by a significant upgrade in the company’s Mojo Grade from Sell to Hold, reflecting improving technical and financial fundamentals, though the stock faced sharp volatility on the final trading day amid mixed momentum signals.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>600747685c6b8dd9fc87b3396863b946</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Bank Gains 0.45%: 4 Key Technical and Fundamental Shifts This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/au-small-finance-bank-gains-045-4-key-technical-and-fundamental-shifts-this-week-3839378</link><description>AU Small Finance Bank Ltd closed the week ending 13 Feb 2026 with a modest gain of 0.45%, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54%. The stock exhibited mixed price action throughout the week, influenced by a significant upgrade to a Buy rating, shifts in technical momentum, and fluctuating volume levels. Despite some short-term consolidation, the bank’s strong fundamentals and improving technical indicators underpinned its relative resilience in a volatile market.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>7023e1d0cad7595acc88e4d32b01a139</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Univastu India Gains 13.44%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/univastu-india-gains-1344-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-surge-3839376</link><description>Univastu India Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 13.44% from Rs.61.29 to Rs.69.53 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s rally was underpinned by a marked improvement in valuation metrics early in the week and strong Q3 FY26 profit growth reported on the final trading day, despite broader market volatility and sector headwinds.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>c4eda314b910c1c1aa61155ef92d1fc7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrenik Ltd Gains 10.26%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shrenik-ltd-gains-1026-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-surge-3839373</link><description>Shrenik Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 10.26% from ₹0.39 to ₹0.43 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock repeatedly hit upper circuit limits on four trading days, reflecting intense buying pressure despite its micro-cap status and a prevailing Strong Sell analyst rating. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped Shrenik Ltd’s volatile week.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>2e4cf12889b162d618ded91621947788</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G G Engineering Ltd Falls 3.85%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-g-engineering-ltd-falls-385-3-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3839370</link><description>G G Engineering Ltd’s shares declined by 3.85% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.0.50 compared to Rs.0.52 at the start. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall, reflecting company-specific challenges amid a broadly resilient market. The stock hit a fresh 52-week and all-time low during the week, driven by weak financial results, deteriorating technical indicators, and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>b5cbd3f492c67be018095ace4769bfff</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Globalspace Technologies Gains 9.73%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/globalspace-technologies-gains-973-2-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3839379</link><description>Globalspace Technologies Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 9.73% from Rs.18.70 to Rs.20.52 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s surge was driven by a new 52-week high and a mixed quarterly earnings report, reflecting strong investor interest amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>ad6cb4bd358de1b37497bd65cb710937</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apex Frozen Foods Surges 24.82%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apex-frozen-foods-surges-2482-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3839371</link><description>Apex Frozen Foods Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 24.82%, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s strong momentum was fuelled by robust quarterly results, multiple new 52-week highs, and sustained buying interest, culminating in an upper circuit hit on 13 February 2026. Despite some valuation concerns, the company’s operational improvements and technical strength have captured investor attention in a mixed market environment.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>3e35247fd81f9fd7f1a557664ed992d0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lexus Granito Surges 27.07% in Volatile Week: Key Drivers Behind the Rally and Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lexus-granito-surges-2707-in-volatile-week-key-drivers-behind-the-rally-and-sell-off-3839372</link><description>Lexus Granito (India) Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance from 9 to 13 February 2026, surging 27.07% from Rs.26.97 to Rs.34.27, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by extreme volatility, with the stock hitting both upper and lower circuit limits amid strong buying and selling pressures, reflecting a turbulent investor sentiment despite the company’s Strong Sell Mojo Grade.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>6344ab06b38faa4f2296c3e2347a61ca</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>