<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Bharat Gears Drops 9.30%: 2 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-gears-drops-930-2-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-slide-3841118</link><description>Bharat Gears Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 9.30% from Rs.120.40 to Rs.109.20, significantly underperforming the Sensex, which fell by a modest 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp drop on 10 February following the quarterly results announcement, and a subsequent mixed recovery attempt overshadowed by market volatility and profit-taking pressures.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>9b1e97e1e00757139c59cdfa045b8e13</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd. Declines 1.78% Despite Intraday Strength: Mixed Technical Signals Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-declines-178-despite-intraday-strength-mixed-technical-signals-shape-week-3841119</link><description>Bosch Ltd. closed the week ending 13 February 2026 at Rs.35,715.00, down 1.78% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.36,361.10. The stock underperformed the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a volatile price action, with a sharp intraday recovery on 11 February followed by renewed selling pressure. Mixed technical signals and a recent upgrade in analyst rating contributed to a complex trading environment.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>2a1f8eb882b8ced4765057d7f3b980aa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Covidh Technologies Ltd Gains 10.30%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/covidh-technologies-ltd-gains-1030-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3841117</link><description>Covidh Technologies Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 10.30% from Rs.28.26 to Rs.31.17 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex, which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock marked new 52-week highs on each trading day, reflecting sustained momentum amid mixed broader market conditions.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>8f2329d2150b8a31a25b7fb4da43d378</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Omnitex Industries Gains 8.46%: Technical Signals Drive Mixed Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/omnitex-industries-gains-846-technical-signals-drive-mixed-weekly-performance-3841115</link><description>Omnitex Industries (India) Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 8.46%, closing at Rs.550.00 on 13 Feb 2026, despite the broader Sensex declining by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s performance was driven by a mix of technical improvements and persistent fundamental challenges, with key events including a sharp revenue collapse and a cautious upgrade in investment rating. This review analyses the week’s price movements in relation to news flow and market context.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>701d53d6988c058fefe8b12ced3c91c7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JM Financial Ltd Gains 11.87%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jm-financial-ltd-gains-1187-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-surge-3841116</link><description>JM Financial Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance from 9 to 13 February 2026, rising 11.87% from Rs.122.15 to Rs.136.65, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s gains were driven by robust intraday rallies on 9 and 10 February, supported by shifting technical momentum and active trading volumes amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>c409a9b58f56a74e94614f275ccaca7b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Batliboi Ltd Falls 2.18%: Margin Pressures and Interest Costs Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/batliboi-ltd-falls-218-margin-pressures-and-interest-costs-weigh-on-stock-3841113</link><description>Batliboi Ltd’s stock declined by 2.18% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.96.55 compared to Rs.98.70 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall, reflecting investor caution amid mounting margin pressures and rising interest expenses despite strong revenue growth reported midweek.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>990f14edc4a8c0dbb108221d23730d45</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd Falls 5.43%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mep-infrastructure-developers-ltd-falls-543-6-key-factors-driving-the-downtrend-3841114</link><description>MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, declining 5.43% to close at Rs.1.22, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall. The micro-cap transport infrastructure player faced persistent selling pressure, hitting multiple lower circuit limits and new 52-week lows amid deteriorating fundamentals and subdued liquidity.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>58d6345dc3d0c9b55077c423057d8f32</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kilitch Drugs Declines 7.40%: Mixed Technicals and Financial Pressures Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kilitch-drugs-declines-740-mixed-technicals-and-financial-pressures-shape-the-week-3841111</link><description>Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its share price declining 7.40% to close at ₹329.60, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s volatile price action was influenced by mixed technical signals, deteriorating quarterly financial results, rising debt concerns, and a shift in valuation metrics, culminating in a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. This review analyses the key events and market reactions shaping Kilitch Drugs’ performance this week.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>aabae0975672f7bab36a4aaf6008d4bf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd Surges 20.49%: Key Financial Turnaround and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/centenial-surgical-suture-ltd-surges-2049-key-financial-turnaround-and-technical-shifts-3841112</link><description>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 20.49% from Rs.86.50 to Rs.104.22 between 09 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. This strong rally was driven by a combination of positive quarterly financial results, technical upgrades, and renewed investor interest despite lingering fundamental challenges.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>22d90846e47aed31712e6cbd04dac9a9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Declines 3.06%: Valuation Shift and Option Activity Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hero-motocorp-declines-306-valuation-shift-and-option-activity-shape-week-3841110</link><description>Hero MotoCorp Ltd. experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 3.06% from ₹5,755.70 on 9 February to ₹5,579.65 on 13 February 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell by a more modest 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by heightened call option activity signalling bullish sentiment ahead of the February expiry, alongside a notable shift in the company’s valuation metrics to a very attractive level amid ongoing market volatility.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>030e2cb75d9e4ce21797b70a4ce8a252</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Austin Engineering Falls 2.28%: 2 Key Factors Driving Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/austin-engineering-falls-228-2-key-factors-driving-volatility-3841108</link><description>Austin Engineering Company Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 9 to 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.118.05, down 2.28% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.120.80. This decline contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell a more modest 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s price movements were marked by sharp intraday swings, notably a 7.21% surge on 12 February following Q3 FY26 results, before a steep 7.74% drop the next day amid valuation reassessments. These fluctuations reflect a week of mixed signals for investors amid margin pressures and shifting valuation metrics.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>5835962dc1f8548b8ffc5b92fd89a642</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transcorp International Ltd Gains 1.11%: Valuation and Technical Upgrades Drive Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/transcorp-international-ltd-gains-111-valuation-and-technical-upgrades-drive-momentum-3841106</link><description>Transcorp International Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.11%, closing at Rs.28.30 on 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant upgrade in the company’s investment rating to Hold, driven by improved financial metrics and attractive valuation shifts, although the final trading day saw a notable price correction amid broader market weakness.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>c65245490c3f21ae155752cea7abada7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge Ltd Falls 11.85%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coforge-ltd-falls-1185-5-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3841109</link><description>Coforge Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 11.85% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.1,362.55 from Rs.1,545.80 the previous Friday. This underperformance was stark compared to the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall, reflecting a week marked by deteriorating technical signals, elevated volatility, and sectoral headwinds that weighed heavily on the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>c844d3a2f61276ae1b249ca9b215cd99</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rapicut Carbides Surges 22.06%: 4 Key Drivers Behind the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rapicut-carbides-surges-2206-4-key-drivers-behind-the-rally-3841107</link><description>Rapicut Carbides Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 22.06% from Rs.126.00 to Rs.153.80 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by consecutive daily gains, new 52-week highs, and a notable upgrade in its valuation profile, reflecting strong investor confidence amid a mixed broader market environment.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>f0d21870882970a8c8d5039a50dc7736</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sakthi Sugars Declines 1.83% Amid Steep Losses and Negative Financial Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sakthi-sugars-declines-183-amid-steep-losses-and-negative-financial-trend-3841105</link><description>Sakthi Sugars Ltd closed the week ending 13 Feb 2026 at Rs.17.15, down 1.83% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.17.47, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock showed early strength midweek but succumbed to mounting pressure following the release of disappointing quarterly results and a sharp deterioration in financial trends, reflecting operational challenges and sector headwinds.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>9c32d37589162337e4fdf8529d50303c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat State Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd. Declines 1.61%: Technical Weakness and Quality Downgrade Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-state-fertilizers-chemicals-ltd-declines-161-technical-weakness-and-quality-downgrade-shape-week-3841104</link><description>Gujarat State Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd. (GSFC) closed the week ending 13 February 2026 at Rs.174.10, down 1.61% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.176.95. This decline contrasted with the BSE Sensex’s smaller fall of 0.54% over the same period, indicating relative underperformance amid a backdrop of technical deterioration and a downgrade in the company’s quality grade. The week was marked by mixed financial results, bearish momentum shifts, and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>ce1d1f404ab63c96cd90df340d6e6ee1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mihika Industries Ltd’s 0.55% Weekly Gain Masks Underlying Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mihika-industries-ltds-055-weekly-gain-masks-underlying-weakness-3841103</link><description>Mihika Industries Ltd’s shares ended the week with a modest gain of 0.55%, closing at Rs.12.81 on 13 February 2026, despite a turbulent trading week marked by a new 52-week and all-time low on 12 February. The stock outperformed the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period, reflecting a mixed week influenced by company-specific challenges and broader market volatility.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>c910a42c2d6647c6806f262733fb58d6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MIC Electronics Gains 5.19%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mic-electronics-gains-519-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3841102</link><description>MIC Electronics Ltd recorded a notable weekly gain of 5.19%, closing at ₹42.17 on 13 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by a strong start with an upper circuit hit on 09 Feb, followed by mixed technical momentum shifts amid fluctuating market conditions. Despite short-term volatility, the stock demonstrated resilience relative to the broader market, reflecting a complex interplay of speculative buying and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>da9578ed32350460748ba5494fd8215b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biocon Ltd Gains 3.45%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/biocon-ltd-gains-345-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3841101</link><description>Biocon Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 3.45% from Rs.365.20 to Rs.377.80 between 9 and 13 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s resilience amid a mixed market backdrop was supported by a significant surge in derivatives open interest and a remarkable 473% profit jump in its Q3 FY26 results, signalling renewed investor interest and evolving market positioning.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>fd16c55b773909055c6bacdcd5cb690f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kernex Microsystems Falls 2.05%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kernex-microsystems-falls-205-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3841100</link><description>Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 2.05% from Rs.1,193.05 on 6 February to Rs.1,168.55 on 13 February 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of significant developments including a mixed quarterly financial report, a downgrade in valuation metrics, and a shift in market sentiment, all contributing to the stock's volatility and downward pressure.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>471d465055e37104386c1e4d1653fa93</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>