<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Mixed Earnings Momentum as 887 Companies Report Dec-2025 Quarterly Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mixed-earnings-momentum-as-887-companies-report-dec-2025-quarterly-results-3812713</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has delivered a mixed bag of results across market capitalisations and sectors, with 887 companies declaring their financials. While the overall proportion of companies reporting positive results has improved to 50.0%, this marks a modest recovery from the previous quarter’s 43.0%, reflecting cautious optimism amid ongoing macroeconomic challenges.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>e2c14c43ace272c66ba43afa3694eff2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Gains 4.53%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suryoday-small-finance-bank-gains-453-5-key-factors-driving-the-week-3812707</link><description>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a 4.53% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. Despite a challenging start marked by a 1.77% decline on 27 January, the stock rebounded strongly in the following sessions, supported by mixed but evolving technical momentum and key fundamental developments. The week was characterised by a shift from bearish to more neutral technical signals, a downgrade in analyst ratings, and notable volume spikes, reflecting a complex market sentiment around this micro-cap banking stock.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>bedf53e2c99a2229cc64e97c06e80e02</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Foodbrands Ltd’s 1.37% Weekly Gain Masks Underlying Weakness and Technical Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/united-foodbrands-ltds-137-weekly-gain-masks-underlying-weakness-and-technical-downtrend-3812706</link><description>United Foodbrands Ltd’s stock recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.37% closing at Rs.180.75 on 30 January 2026, slightly underperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The week was marked by significant price swings, technical weakness, and deepening losses reported in the company’s Q3 FY26 results, reflecting ongoing operational challenges amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>1ea9ceb54b4951a222b930ab874dab13</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd Declines 1.57%: 2 Key Events Mark a Challenging Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suvidhaa-infoserve-ltd-declines-157-2-key-events-mark-a-challenging-week-3812704</link><description>Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.3.13, down 1.57% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.3.18, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp decline to a 52-week low and an all-time low on 29 January 2026, reflecting ongoing financial challenges and negative market sentiment despite intermittent intraday recoveries.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>461c7525f98bac7dc102d80a7ba368eb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Gains 7.90%: 4 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lodha-developers-gains-790-4-key-events-shaping-the-week-3812705</link><description>Lodha Developers Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.90% from Rs.899.85 to Rs.970.95 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock rebounded from a fresh 52-week low on 27 January to close near its weekly high on 30 January, supported by robust quarterly results and notable intraday price rallies amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>e6df344f8a2ecfe183925bcecf49490f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep Industries Ltd Gains 8.31%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deep-industries-ltd-gains-831-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3812702</link><description>Deep Industries Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.31% from Rs.343.55 to Rs.372.10 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s rebound followed a challenging start marked by a 52-week low, but was supported by a shift to fair valuation and a robust intraday surge midweek. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s trajectory and their impact on price movements.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>f418ada74366602a2137d33c4b1beb43</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Gains 8.23%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sona-blw-precision-forgings-gains-823-5-key-factors-driving-the-week-3812701</link><description>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.23% from Rs.457.85 to Rs.495.55 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a technical momentum shift, intraday highs, and a rating upgrade, reflecting a complex interplay of financial results, valuation concerns, and market sentiment.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>89ac7ec14e50ed196af87c2d8e70536d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shyam Metalics Surges 10.29% in a Week: Mixed Signals Shape Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shyam-metalics-surges-1029-in-a-week-mixed-signals-shape-outlook-3812703</link><description>Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 10.29% from Rs.778.60 to Rs.858.70 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s momentum was driven by a combination of technical shifts and a cautious upgrade in its investment rating, reflecting mixed but improving fundamentals amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>ada54537b41b86bbe893cda621942b3a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G R Infraprojects Ltd Gains 4.67%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-r-infraprojects-ltd-gains-467-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3812700</link><description>G R Infraprojects Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a notable gain of 4.67%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by a sharp drop to a 52-week and all-time low on 27 January, followed by a steady recovery culminating in a strong 9.11% intraday surge on the final trading day. This week’s price action reflects a mix of persistent challenges and renewed buying interest amid a subdued broader market environment.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>610e69d47422d92c6b761bc6ea9066d0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Gains 5.82%: 4 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-gains-582-4-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3812698</link><description>Eternal Ltd delivered a solid weekly gain of 5.82%, closing at Rs.273.70 on 30 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The stock showed notable resilience with strong volume surges and intraday highs, despite lingering technical headwinds and a recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. This review analyses the key events shaping Eternal Ltd’s price action and market sentiment during the week.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>926efc8efa7dbd84b37e8f3c679584b6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Ltd Falls 6.50% Amid Downgrade and 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-falls-650-amid-downgrade-and-52-week-low-3812697</link><description>Network People Services Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock declining 6.50% from Rs.1,295.70 to Rs.1,211.50, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The stock hit a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1,220 on 28 January 2026, coinciding with a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO amid deteriorating financials and stretched valuation metrics.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>48217af050d316db198cefa98a3825af</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meghmani Organics Gains 7.67%: Key Market and Financial Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/meghmani-organics-gains-767-key-market-and-financial-factors-driving-the-week-3812696</link><description>Meghmani Organics Ltd rebounded strongly this week, gaining 7.67% from Rs.55.80 to Rs.60.08, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. After hitting a 52-week and all-time low of Rs.55 on 27 January, the stock staged a recovery driven by improving financial results and positive market sentiment, despite lingering concerns over its long-term fundamentals and sector challenges.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>49c5adcc31f2c15b839b01f575c7cd45</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epigral Ltd Falls 2.54% Amidst 52-Week Lows and Earnings Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/epigral-ltd-falls-254-amidst-52-week-lows-and-earnings-pressure-3812693</link><description>Epigral Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.1,038.70, down 2.54% from Rs.1,065.75 the previous Friday, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a persistent downtrend with the stock hitting successive 52-week lows amid subdued financial results and rising interest expenses, contrasting sharply with the broader market’s positive momentum.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>28fd07224d72a618b49ffc35aecd2e78</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cartrade Tech Gains 8.27%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cartrade-tech-gains-827-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3812695</link><description>Cartrade Tech Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.27% from Rs.2,448.30 to Rs.2,650.80 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The week was marked by notable intraday volatility, a sharp profit surge in Q3 FY26 results, and a robust rally on the final trading day, underscoring a mixed but ultimately bullish sentiment for the stock amid broader market fluctuations.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>146c397b964674570824340ba3110577</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Acutaas Chemicals Surges 15.65% in a Week: 6 Key Drivers Behind the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/acutaas-chemicals-surges-1565-in-a-week-6-key-drivers-behind-the-rally-3812694</link><description>Acutaas Chemicals Ltd delivered a strong performance in the week ending 30 January 2026, rising 15.65% from Rs.1,651.40 to Rs.1,909.80, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was fuelled by a series of positive developments including record quarterly results, new 52-week and all-time highs, and a notable upgrade in its technical and fundamental ratings. Despite a minor pullback on the final trading day, the week was marked by robust momentum and investor confidence in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector leader.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>e3465006b38f4cfdf1520393383c8397</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd Falls 3.94%: 2 Key Technical Signals Drive the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vijaya-diagnostic-centre-ltd-falls-394-2-key-technical-signals-drive-the-week-3812692</link><description>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.956.90 on 30 Jan 2026, down 3.94% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.996.20. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid bearish technical developments and weakening momentum signals.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>c916619220322e5e9c3e75b56b20d650</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paras Defence Surges 14.25% in a Week: Key Technical Shifts and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paras-defence-surges-1425-in-a-week-key-technical-shifts-and-market-dynamics-3812691</link><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 14.25% from Rs.623.70 to Rs.712.60 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by notable intraday highs and a shift in technical momentum, reflecting a complex but predominantly positive trading environment amid broader market gains.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>80f7e4d4d45c1b6b5370d626fbd30574</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jainam Ferro Alloys Gains 2.93%: 2 Key Circuit Hits Define Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jainam-ferro-alloys-gains-293-2-key-circuit-hits-define-volatile-week-3812690</link><description>Jainam Ferro Alloys (I) Ltd experienced a volatile week from 27 to 30 January 2026, marked by sharp swings between upper and lower circuit limits. The stock gained 2.93% over the week, closing at Rs.235.55, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. Intense buying pressure on 27 January propelled the stock to its upper circuit at Rs.240.25, followed by a steep decline hitting the lower circuit at Rs.228.25 on 28 January amid heavy selling. The subsequent sessions saw the stock stabilise, closing flat at Rs.235.55, reflecting a week of mixed sentiment and heightened volatility.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>d1a496f82d1ae9e5eaaea2965d85f846</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank Gains 1.97%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fino-payments-bank-gains-197-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-moves-3812689</link><description>Fino Payments Bank Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.97%, closing at Rs.217.20 on 30 January 2026, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp intraday rally on 28 January, followed by a cautious retreat amid mixed market signals and a quarterly earnings report that highlighted profitability pressures. This review analyses the key events driving the stock’s performance and places them in the context of broader market trends.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>94f3e2ec33fc2e90531de0cb2c74d13f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Declines 1.51% Amid Rising Open Interest and Sell Rating</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-declines-151-amid-rising-open-interest-and-sell-rating-3812688</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 at Rs.1,652.80, down 1.51% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,678.15. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period, reflecting a challenging week marked by rising derivatives activity amid falling prices and a significant downgrade by MarketsMOJO. The stock’s price movements were influenced by a sharp surge in open interest on 27 January and a subsequent rating downgrade on 28 January, both of which contributed to heightened volatility and cautious sentiment among investors.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>819ca2af1b21ca538043024218cab68e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>