<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Gujarat Alkalies &amp; Chemicals Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gujarat-alkalies-chemicals-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814024</link><description>Gujarat Alkalies &amp; Chemicals Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c202d8f86a2ea034680fa98e1f2c0419</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grauer &amp; Weil (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/grauer-weil-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814023</link><description>Grauer &amp; Weil (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>6820d199b917e2deee13eefe8e01cafe</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indiqube Spaces Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indiqube-spaces-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814022</link><description>Indiqube Spaces Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>dd6ff400fe40d0fcfa06495f4c1ee0bd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GRM Overseas Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/grm-overseas-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3814018</link><description>GRM Overseas Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>55c58d9294d049db61f3039020ed8fd4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Timex Group India Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/timex-group-india-ltd-is-rated-buy-3814020</link><description>Timex Group India Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>484894e0ba1ce006877c5a43ffa1a5cc</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tourism-finance-corporation-of-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814021</link><description>Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 27 October 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>de2ad1594c9ab4a89262477fb5ae40c7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NDR INVIT Trust is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ndr-invit-trust-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3814019</link><description>NDR INVIT Trust is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>422c561ce140a863c7d8b3ea64e53f80</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GE Power India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ge-power-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814017</link><description>GE Power India Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date analysis.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>e5fc354d88f25ccbf238614b688b7333</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lloyds Metals &amp; Energy Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/lloyds-metals-energy-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814012</link><description>Lloyds Metals &amp; Energy Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>b50ef51374750e07448ec82de483c9df</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PTC Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ptc-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814015</link><description>PTC Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c26f2920fa751a2d337e7e644425e3fc</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delta Corp Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/delta-corp-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814016</link><description>Delta Corp Ltd. is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>0420cd88e1b2466b07e05a54590b47c2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Westlife Foodworld Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/westlife-foodworld-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3814014</link><description>Westlife Foodworld Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 22 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>e210707bf25c811b4f05d7ee298adbc0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parag Milk Foods Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/parag-milk-foods-ltd-is-rated-hold-3814013</link><description>Parag Milk Foods Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 October 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>fb8e21ca93f891c9260ed4b65b9dfda3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mastek Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mastek-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3814011</link><description>Mastek Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>56832f45db14572f661e604e34e23c3b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SIS Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sis-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814010</link><description>SIS Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>023c00bfcff439ee851b617423aa89fa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rallis India Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rallis-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3814009</link><description>Rallis India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Oct 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>7f97ea369d61bd0d6a9b9c69e2c07b60</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahamaya Steel Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mahamaya-steel-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3814007</link><description>Mahamaya Steel Industries Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 20 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest comprehensive analysis.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>28dbf7577b41535eef9380eabf5102cd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marine Electricals (India) Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/marine-electricals-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3814008</link><description>Marine Electricals (India) Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>44022596414c76370182825f37da8bab</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Petrochem Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/panama-petrochem-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3814006</link><description>Panama Petrochem Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on its performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>cf6856ff40a7f9e08f457b406bdaf9b6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/paisalo-digital-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3814005</link><description>Paisalo Digital Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 01 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c6873bdc31b51bf7cf8f488271dbaa6d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>