<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sector Performance; Small Caps Show Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-equity-markets-slip-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-small-caps-show-resilience-3769978</link><description>The Indian equity markets closed the day with modest declines as the Sensex and Nifty edged lower, reflecting a cautious investor sentiment amid mixed sectoral trends and subdued breadth. While large caps faced pressure, small caps demonstrated relative strength, supported by select sectoral gains and global cues.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>95422ebec7ec43cd831873326171e27e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AG Ventures Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ag-ventures-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769595</link><description>AG Ventures Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 13 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are based on the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest comprehensive analysis.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>abfcaf05e1b6bda61380c880c554682f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integrated Proteins Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/integrated-proteins-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769594</link><description>Integrated Proteins Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c77b1a927bbde126388c18722f49bac1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>International Combustion (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/international-combustion-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769592</link><description>International Combustion (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 Nov 2025. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date analysis of the company’s standing.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b0c09724abb49eaf8ad4b4ec5a27217f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elegant Marbles and Grani Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/elegant-marbles-and-grani-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769593</link><description>Elegant Marbles and Grani Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 11 February 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>f26c39f103523e50920a3fb018c891f3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Metroglobal Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/metroglobal-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769591</link><description>Metroglobal Ltd. is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>4afd6f5f0463982931a058d9500eb6d1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Par Drugs &amp; Chemicals Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/par-drugs-chemicals-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769590</link><description>Par Drugs &amp; Chemicals Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c7c5c3404c033d9f9c7f4d8c9bedef7b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cenlub Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cenlub-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769588</link><description>Cenlub Industries Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>f4e66868aeab762f5104e6daa7722702</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Denis Chem Lab Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/denis-chem-lab-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769589</link><description>Denis Chem Lab Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Mar 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>51fd21934c6184dc2e9560d8aa96f937</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Facility Management Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/supreme-facility-management-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769587</link><description>Supreme Facility Management Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 June 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>854ecb91e27bfd905e6c1e65e3b88a55</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Odyssey Technologies Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/odyssey-technologies-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769586</link><description>Odyssey Technologies Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 31 October 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5b1cb3a95d0ed9af6db44f20c493d6ef</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gowra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gowra-leasing-finance-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769585</link><description>Gowra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the stock’s performance and outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>359fc7a37aaf1959f189a5c8e1a0c9e8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajnish Retail Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rajnish-retail-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769584</link><description>Rajnish Retail Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 26 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the most recent insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5fa31a0475d2785bc855457eaa216401</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SPA Capital Services Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/spa-capital-services-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769582</link><description>SPA Capital Services Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 18 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position in the market.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>09db554cb2f3456f942dc47e87fb5ae3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pee Cee Cosma Sope Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pee-cee-cosma-sope-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769583</link><description>Pee Cee Cosma Sope Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c2505975940743d7c9dc8d3fb508352b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kreon Finnancial Services Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kreon-finnancial-services-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769581</link><description>Kreon Finnancial Services Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>aa98b0694cd470b1b321f354a1a4dc1b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>