<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Wonderla Holidays Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.470</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wonderla-holidays-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs470-3860334</link><description>Wonderla Holidays Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.470 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and market sentiment.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>1cb03b193f21c7d43c2010e25d25597c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dish TV India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.2.86 Amid Continued Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dish-tv-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs286-amid-continued-weakness-3860332</link><description>Dish TV India Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.2.86 on 27 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent pressures on the company’s financial performance and market valuation within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>ea8ebf443cd2ea7d24744e0f4359511d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Impex Ferro Tech Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/impex-ferro-tech-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-weakness-3860335</link><description>Impex Ferro Tech Ltd’s stock has declined to a fresh 52-week low of ₹1.63, marking a significant downturn in its market performance. This new low reflects ongoing pressures within the ferrous metals sector and highlights the company’s continuing struggles with fundamental financial metrics.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>0b5bbdfaca7d786dd7570a8e33ec1f56</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonata Software Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.268.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sonata-software-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2688-3860337</link><description>Sonata Software Ltd., a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.268.8 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market pressures and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>d54ad612094aeaf2c4768331769baca7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KEI Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.5078.6</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kei-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs50786-3860333</link><description>KEI Industries Ltd, a prominent player in the Cables - Electricals sector, reached a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.5078.6 today, underscoring a sustained rally and robust market momentum. This milestone reflects the company’s strong performance over the past year and its continued outperformance relative to sector peers and broader indices.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>b3fc081b2ad95836e3d5af46b543ae28</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elcid Investments Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.108150 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/elcid-investments-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs108150-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3860331</link><description>Elcid Investments Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.108150 today, marking a significant decline amid an extended period of price weakness. The stock has been on a downward trajectory for eight consecutive trading sessions, cumulatively losing 4.25% over this span, reflecting ongoing pressures within the holding company sector.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>726b2c596bf447f77739abb58ae028b4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.9% Surge on 27 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sarda-energy-minerals-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-79-surge-on-27-feb-2026-3860327</link><description>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 27 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 559.45, marking a significant 7.91% increase. This strong upward movement outpaced the broader Sensex, which declined by 0.61% during the same session, underscoring the stock’s notable resilience amid a generally subdued market.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>22c6cfd5d6d1e7ac2d2ac9b221e8b094</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finolex Cables Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 7.42% Surge on 27 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/finolex-cables-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-742-surge-on-27-feb-2026-3860324</link><description>Finolex Cables Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 27 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 935, marking a 7.25% increase. This advance significantly outpaced the broader market, with the stock outperforming its sector by 7.06% amid a generally subdued Sensex environment.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>ea6c560d0876f66a94178b428bf51639</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motor &amp; General Finance Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motor-general-finance-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3860326</link><description>Motor &amp; General Finance Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures within the diversified commercial services sector. The stock closed at a new low price of ₹24.50, marking a significant drop from its 52-week high of ₹31.80 and underscoring a year-long trend of underperformance relative to the broader market.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>b3ded5c82f3f5cae4b8c585fc92438d7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ravikumar Distilleries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ravikumar-distilleries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3860325</link><description>Ravikumar Distilleries Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, closing just 4% above its lowest price of Rs 18.25. The stock has been on a downward trajectory, reflecting a series of financial and market pressures that have weighed on its performance over the past year.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>f6157e9c3eee3c2ca474b7f75cb3b559</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Angel One Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/angel-one-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-momentum-3860323</link><description>Angel One Ltd, a key player in the capital markets sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, even as its share price underperformed the broader sector and benchmark indices. This divergence between rising market positioning and declining price action signals a complex interplay of investor sentiment and potential directional bets.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>e2ddfd3d7e4bdb45920d7629b62bd807</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Computer Age Management Services Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/computer-age-management-services-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3860322</link><description>Computer Age Management Services Ltd (CAMS) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting a significant shift in market positioning amid a backdrop of declining stock prices and subdued investor participation. This development warrants a closer examination of volume patterns, directional bets, and the broader implications for investors navigating the capital markets sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6362e74e232daf6cd2d59f30deec2305</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Ltd Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/360-one-wam-ltd-sees-notable-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-price-weakness-3860321</link><description>360 ONE WAM Ltd (360ONE), a mid-cap player in the Capital Markets sector, has witnessed a notable 10.5% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, raising questions about the directional bets underpinning this spike in OI.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>32312b67dacf265034d284b8526df020</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd Surges 20% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vl-e-governance-it-solutions-ltd-surges-20-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3860319</link><description>VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd witnessed a remarkable rally on 27 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit of 20% to close at ₹15.60. This surge was driven by robust buying interest, resulting in a maximum permissible daily gain and triggering a regulatory freeze on further trading. The stock’s performance notably outpaced its sector and the broader market, signalling renewed investor confidence after a brief period of decline.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>d885615dcaec24d137a84ed45a2414ee</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Capital Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-capital-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3860320</link><description>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd (ABCAPITAL) has witnessed a notable 11.45% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a 3.29% decline in the stock price on 27 Feb 2026, the spike in OI alongside volume patterns suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and hedging strategies within the mid-cap Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>22af1c41bd7e44d63d3d3f4a2cf3aeee</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avro India Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avro-india-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3860317</link><description>Avro India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the diversified consumer products sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 27 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a significant intraday rally. The stock closed at ₹139.35, marking a 5.0% gain on the day, outperforming both its sector and the broader Sensex indices.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>8dc42b6032589ef34fe5019b2d3d7375</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3860307</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded with 4,089 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced landscape of corporate performance marked by modest profit growth and varying sectoral outcomes. While the overall proportion of companies reporting positive results edged up to 46.0%, the distribution across market capitalisations and sectors highlights divergent trends that investors should carefully consider.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>8bedb52b664e86e5ab9d7639da1aed00</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Finance Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-finance-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3860318</link><description>L&amp;T Finance Ltd (LTF), a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent price decline, the sharp increase in OI and trading volumes suggests evolving directional bets and potential volatility ahead for this mid-cap stock.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>b02add4b6067857f309b8e1a805c354a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jaiprakash-power-ventures-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3860312</link><description>Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd (JPPOWER) emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 27 Feb 2026, registering a remarkable volume surge that outpaced sector and benchmark indices. Despite a positive intraday price movement, the stock’s technical and fundamental indicators present a nuanced picture, reflecting both investor interest and caution in the power sector’s small-cap segment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>8e0ad0df03ed9e286fdcfc9f5dd5be7b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lotus-eye-hospital-institute-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3860315</link><description>Shares of Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 27 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a significant intraday gain. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting renewed investor confidence despite subdued delivery volumes and a micro-cap market capitalisation of ₹225 crores.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6dd6de7190eabade796823294e2b6ee2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>