<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Pavna Industries Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.23.92 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pavna-industries-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3765932</link><description>Pavna Industries, a player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.23.92, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e717b585f33a03f5c3a0606ec0d70355</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Advance as Small Caps Lead Market Rally; IT Sector Tops Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-advance-as-small-caps-lead-market-rally-it-sector-tops-gains-3765931</link><description>The Indian equity markets witnessed a broad-based rally on 22 December 2025, with the Sensex and Nifty indices registering gains amid positive global cues and robust domestic buying. Small caps outperformed other segments, while the IT sector emerged as the top sectoral gainer. Market breadth remained healthy, supported by strong foreign institutional investor (FII) and domestic institutional investor (DII) activity.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>461e0e1d52eeac735a0fe30dfe06ff85</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Synthetics Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.16.15 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-synthetics-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3765908</link><description>Garware Synthetics has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.16.15 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a broader market environment where the Sensex continues to show strength. The stock has experienced a sustained downward trend over the past week, reflecting ongoing challenges within the company’s trading and distribution sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>764e2c09cbc9f3ed9eaf25e23cbb968e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan India Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1345.55</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anupam-rasayan-india-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs134555-on-22-dec-2025-3765898</link><description>Anupam Rasayan India, a key player in the specialty chemicals sector, reached a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1345.55 today, marking a significant milestone in its market performance. This achievement reflects sustained momentum supported by robust financial results and favourable market conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4bca827d51c2bf36d0edb3e86cfdc315</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Franklin Industries Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.63</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/franklin-industries-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs063-3765902</link><description>Franklin Industries, a player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has reached a new 52-week low, with its stock price touching Rs.0.63 today. This marks a significant decline from its 52-week high of Rs.2.30, reflecting a challenging period for the company amid broader market movements.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>71ebe2cb47e7c67a1366134300ef9257</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mega Nirman &amp; Industries Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.36.71</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mega-nirman-industries-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs3671-3765899</link><description>Mega Nirman &amp; Industries, a key player in the realty sector, reached a significant milestone today by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.36.71. This achievement marks a notable phase in the stock’s recent performance, reflecting sustained momentum amid a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c4a8a766067699899104a13586a0fb11</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Logistics Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.10.74</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allcargo-logistics-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3765901</link><description>Shares of Allcargo Logistics touched a fresh 52-week low today, closing at Rs.10.74, marking a significant decline amid broader market gains. The stock's performance contrasts sharply with the upward trajectory of the Sensex and sector peers, reflecting ongoing pressures within the company’s financials and market positioning.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f1f7adf14ab70caf7f49116f917a9eb2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.16,696.1</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs166961-3765900</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India has reached a significant milestone by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.16,696.1, marking a notable moment in the stock's performance within the automobile sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ed11aeeea04bd8132b0c5a2a38bf5dec</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galaxy Bearings Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.525 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/galaxy-bearings-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs525-amid-continued-downtrend-3765906</link><description>Galaxy Bearings has reached a fresh 52-week low of Rs.525 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects a continuation of downward momentum amid broader market gains, with the industrial products company underperforming its sector and key benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9119f7f966c1eb717eb00e31ad473970</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suryaamba Spinning Mills Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.114.1 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suryaamba-spinning-mills-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3765904</link><description>Suryaamba Spinning Mills touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.114.1 today, marking a significant decline in its share price as it underperformed its sector and broader market indices. The stock's performance reflects ongoing pressures within the Garments &amp; Apparels industry and highlights the challenges faced by the company over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e9e04be6ec9efbb971ac932c6d837365</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palred Technologies Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.37.9 Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/palred-technologies-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs379-amidst-continued-underperformance-3765903</link><description>Palred Technologies touched a new 52-week low of Rs.37.9 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing challenges in its financial performance and market positioning within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>36fada863c32355f1f533fea1f80518b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Golden Tobacco Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/golden-tobacco-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3765905</link><description>Shares of Golden Tobacco have reached a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges within the company’s financial and market performance. The stock’s current price level marks a significant point in its year-long trajectory, contrasting sharply with broader market trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4940d38737d9372d8b5ccf97be558679</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infronics Systems Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.22.41 Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infronics-systems-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3765907</link><description>Infronics Systems, a player in the Software Products sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.22.41 today, marking a significant milestone in its recent market trajectory. This development comes despite a modest gain of 2.07% over the past two days, with the stock still trading below all key moving averages.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>faed59ccb9356cd0807fa9bf3c64cac2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kairosoft AI Solutions Hits Intraday High with Strong Trading Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kairosoft-ai-solutions-hits-intraday-high-with-974-surge-on-22-dec-2025-3765897</link><description>Kairosoft AI Solutions recorded a robust intraday performance on 22 Dec 2025, surging to an intraday high of Rs 45.58, reflecting a gain of 8.81% from the previous close. The stock demonstrated notable volatility and trading activity within the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, outperforming its peers and the broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>80a3498bec1524ec5748e02e7687aa6d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Stock Surges 391.5% in Six Months, Outperforming FMCG Sector Benchmarks</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/top-small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-3765895</link><description>Cupid has delivered an extraordinary return of 391.51% over the past six months, significantly outpacing the broader FMCG sector and market benchmarks. This remarkable performance highlights the stock’s strong momentum amid a challenging market environment, driven by a combination of bullish technical indicators and robust financial fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>63ff7a0acce19f033fc4bdb6c83d5f2e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Stock Surges Over 480% in One Year, Outperforming Market Benchmarks</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-stars-deliver-exceptional-returns-amid-varied-sectoral-strengths-3765896</link><description>Cupid has delivered an extraordinary return of 480.37% over the past year, significantly outpacing key market indices and peers within the FMCG sector. This remarkable performance highlights the stock’s strong momentum amid a challenging market environment, driven by a combination of robust financial health and positive technical indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e8301274db8b8601f8319e7657689dc8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3765894</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India has reached a significant milestone as its stock price touches an all-time high, reflecting a sustained period of strong performance across multiple timeframes and outperforming key market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e8686930b61fc09b203a66b51c95530d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan India Stock Hits All-Time High Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anupam-rasayan-india-stock-hits-all-time-high-on-22-dec-2025-3765889</link><description>Anupam Rasayan India, a key player in the specialty chemicals sector, has reached an all-time high in its stock price, underscoring a period of robust performance and sustained growth. This milestone reflects the company’s strong financial results and consistent market presence over recent quarters.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a6b7c0b1b78c7c882386ba0c0f5de53c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Explosives Hits Intraday High with Strong Intraday Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-explosives-surges-to-intraday-high-on-strong-703-gain-3765890</link><description>Premier Explosives demonstrated robust intraday momentum today, reaching a peak price of Rs 522, marking a 5.67% rise within the session. This surge outpaced the broader Chemicals sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading activity and positive market dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>72d7dd8b31ae746301b1b2609b62e25a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Hits Intraday High with Strong Trading Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajmera-realty-infra-india-hits-intraday-high-with-763-surge-on-22-dec-2025-3765892</link><description>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India demonstrated robust intraday performance today, reaching a peak price of Rs 992.5, reflecting a 7.9% rise during the trading session. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, supported by heightened volatility and sustained buying interest.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>966204d2cb5eca0cafd16424a3d34798</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>