<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends with Mid Caps Leading Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-with-mid-caps-leading-growth-3803762</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has unfolded with a notable improvement in positive results, particularly driven by mid-cap companies. With 420 stocks having declared results, the proportion of companies reporting profit growth has risen to 54.0%, marking a significant uptick compared to previous quarters. This article analyses the key trends, sectoral performances, and standout performers shaping the current earnings landscape.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>b0c181079c45d0db3285433e97ab403c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AXISCADES Technologies Ltd Falls 10.26%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axiscades-technologies-ltd-falls-1026-5-key-factors-behind-the-volatile-week-3803760</link><description>AXISCADES Technologies Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 10.26% to close at ₹1,152.80, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock endured a prolonged downtrend marked by multiple lower circuit hits before a sharp rebound on the final trading day, reflecting a volatile investor sentiment amid sectoral headwinds and technical shifts.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>b93b34860e9656fce6ff0ca0a05a17e8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winsome Yarns Ltd Falls 0.56% Despite Sector Gains: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/winsome-yarns-ltd-falls-056-despite-sector-gains-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3803758</link><description>Winsome Yarns Ltd closed the week marginally lower by 0.56% at ₹1.79, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock faced intense selling pressure midweek, hitting lower circuit limits on three consecutive days before a late surge to the upper circuit on 23 Jan 2026. This volatile price action was driven by a combination of a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, weak fundamentals, and thin liquidity in the micro-cap garment sector stock.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>663d4d9c6f5954f2ff577c747bc90e84</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arihant Superstructures Falls 13.26%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arihant-superstructures-falls-1326-4-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3803757</link><description>Arihant Superstructures Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 13.26% to close at Rs.269.55, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid persistent financial pressures, sectoral weakness, and deteriorating technical indicators, reflecting a broad-based bearish sentiment.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>c52a8d213c1afabd9bf9d82206742330</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd’s Volatile Week: -5.57% Amid Sharp Swings and Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/transworld-shipping-lines-ltds-volatile-week--557-amid-sharp-swings-and-strong-buying-pressure-3803759</link><description>Transworld Shipping Lines Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, closing down 5.57% at Rs.157.80 despite a remarkable 19.96% surge on 22 January. The stock underperformed the Sensex, which declined 3.31% over the same period, reflecting persistent financial challenges and volatile investor sentiment amid mixed market signals.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>0d17060dd74db469df36342257e03fd9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanla Platforms Gains 4.03%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanla-platforms-gains-403-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3803756</link><description>Tanla Platforms Ltd closed the week ending 23 January 2026 with a 4.03% gain, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid a broadly negative market backdrop, driven by strong intraday rallies, heightened institutional interest, and continued revenue momentum despite margin pressures. This review analyses the key events shaping Tanla’s price action and market sentiment during the week.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>4a6655b8b58ef1ec9c01f4d11571822e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Gains 2.48%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-gains-248-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3803755</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NACL) recorded a resilient week, closing at Rs.370.45 on 23 Jan 2026, up 2.48% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.361.50. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 3.31% over the same period, underscoring NACL’s relative strength amid broader market weakness. The week was marked by a new 52-week high and robust trading activity, reflecting strong institutional interest and sustained investor confidence.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>47111e0cf239dece3e86f6d63166656e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd Falls 2.98%: Technical Weakness and Valuation Concerns Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uni-abex-alloy-products-ltd-falls-298-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-shape-the-week-3803754</link><description>Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd closed the week at ₹2,988.30, down 2.98% from ₹3,080.15 the previous Friday, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by a shift from sideways to mildly bearish technical momentum, a downgrade to a Sell rating, and mixed price movements influenced by technical and valuation concerns.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>269e7c6a10b1d00b1fd6ad85065b4c7b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>APL Apollo Tubes Gains 3.15%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apl-apollo-tubes-gains-315-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3803753</link><description>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd closed the week with a 3.15% gain, rising from Rs.1,939.80 on 16 Jan 2026 to Rs.2,001.00 on 23 Jan 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by a sharp rebound midweek, a new 52-week and all-time high, and robust derivatives market activity signalling strong investor interest amid mixed broader market conditions.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>26c4034a8b60ed421ad6a2e4511c5a86</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Electronics Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.06% Price Change Amid Derivatives Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-electronics-ltds-mixed-week--006-price-change-amid-derivatives-surge-3803752</link><description>Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) experienced a largely sideways week ending 23 January 2026, with its share price marginally declining by 0.06% to close at Rs.409.90, outperforming the broader Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock showed resilience amid volatile market conditions, buoyed by strong derivatives activity and sectoral rallies, though short-term price fluctuations reflected cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>59e97764f276d9afd5a505a0cca7231f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nirlon Ltd Falls 2.40% This Week: Mixed Technicals and Financials Shape Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nirlon-ltd-falls-240-this-week-mixed-technicals-and-financials-shape-outlook-3803749</link><description>Nirlon Ltd’s share price declined by 2.40% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.489.60 from Rs.501.65 the previous Friday. This underperformance occurred despite the broader Sensex falling more sharply by 3.31%, indicating a relative resilience in Nirlon’s stock amid mixed technical signals and a recent upgrade to a Hold rating by MarketsMOJO. The week was marked by a nuanced shift in technical momentum and a reassessment of the company’s financial and valuation metrics, which together shaped investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>ef37688af8ac70ec5b38f67b3f6bf82f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genesys International Falls 9.76% in Volatile Week: Key Price Lows and Rebounds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/genesys-international-falls-976-in-volatile-week-key-price-lows-and-rebounds-3803751</link><description>Genesys International Corporation Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining 9.76% to close at Rs.308.95, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall. The week was marked by a persistent downtrend, punctuated by a sharp intraday rebound on 22 January, but overall the stock remained below key moving averages amid weak quarterly results and elevated interest expenses.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>e35ea5fb74f3d6736a7f842055d5bbce</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd Falls 4.36%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vintage-coffee-beverages-ltd-falls-436-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803748</link><description>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining 4.36% to close at Rs.147.90, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock showed notable volatility, including a sharp rebound midweek, but was weighed down by a downgrade to a Hold rating, mixed technical signals, and ongoing concerns about management efficiency and leverage. Despite the short-term weakness, the company’s valuation metrics improved, signalling renewed price attractiveness amid broader market volatility.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>91bc4d5f52ec84cb302e3c1d36f4a1cf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Renewables Declines 6.83%: 6 Key Technical and Valuation Factors This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-renewables-declines-683-6-key-technical-and-valuation-factors-this-week-3803750</link><description>Borosil Renewables Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.505.55 on 23 January 2026, down 6.83% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.542.60. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a combination of technical setbacks, valuation concerns, and mixed market sentiment amid volatile trading sessions.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>e899754726936c73d647a3192ae4246d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oberoi Realty Declines 12.65%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Drop</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oberoi-realty-declines-1265-5-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-drop-3803746</link><description>Oberoi Realty Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price falling sharply by 12.65% to close at Rs.1,453.75, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure amid bearish technical signals, heavy put option activity, and a downgrade to a Sell rating, reflecting cautious investor sentiment in a difficult real estate market environment.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>f25215573d2c7b0f88db9c7b6ce1eade</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Setubandhan Infrastructure Ltd Falls 11.11%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/setubandhan-infrastructure-ltd-falls-1111-6-key-factors-driving-the-volatile-week-3803747</link><description>Setubandhan Infrastructure Ltd’s stock experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.0.40, down 11.11% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.0.45. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting heightened volatility amid mixed trading sessions, multiple circuit hits, and persistent fundamental challenges.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>5d5de4aa540f964158dd679c6333724d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd Drops 13.41%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-fashion-retail-ltd-drops-1341-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3803745</link><description>Aditya Birla Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd’s shares fell sharply by 13.41% over the week ending 23 January 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows amid sustained selling pressure, heavy volumes, and deteriorating financial fundamentals, reflecting a challenging environment for the company and its sector.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>2de8ac181e2e87339cc9272d02ebc700</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jay Bharat Maruti Ltd Falls 11.28%: Mixed Technical Signals and Downgrade Shape Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jay-bharat-maruti-ltd-falls-1128-mixed-technical-signals-and-downgrade-shape-volatile-week-3803744</link><description>Jay Bharat Maruti Ltd experienced a challenging week on the BSE, closing at Rs.82.99 on 23 January 2026, down 11.28% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.93.54. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a combination of technical momentum shifts, a recent downgrade to Hold, and mixed financial signals that weighed on investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>d1081c2926e005b8b1edc451d444c15d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMD Industries Ltd Gains 0.30%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amd-industries-ltd-gains-030-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-volatility-3803742</link><description>AMD Industries Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.30%, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock exhibited significant volatility, surging nearly 20% on Monday before retreating steadily through the week amid mixed market sentiment and valuation concerns. Key events including a sharp upper circuit rally and a notable shift in valuation metrics shaped the stock’s trajectory in a challenging broader market environment.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>4e02cdaa85751b07e88cd13cdfb48145</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Havells India Declines 9.81%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Drop</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/havells-india-declines-981-5-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-drop-3803743</link><description>Havells India Ltd. experienced a challenging week ending 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 9.81% from Rs.1,424.90 to Rs.1,285.15. This underperformance was notably sharper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting intensified selling pressure amid deteriorating technical indicators, sectoral headwinds, and subdued financial results. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows during the week, signalling sustained downward momentum despite a brief technical upgrade midweek.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>72a78d854a019932f678fe3db517b592</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>