<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indian-renewable-energy-development-agency-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788593</link><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd's latest results are strong, with a record net profit of ₹585.16 crores and a 37.56% year-on-year growth. However, the stock faces selling pressure and trades below key moving averages, indicating market concerns despite solid operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d25a90a2f3701821d36f09fd0896fd52</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tejas Networks Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tejas-networks-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788592</link><description>Tejas Networks Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, with net sales plummeting 88.39% year-on-year to ₹306.79 crores and a net loss of ₹196.55 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and a deteriorating financial position. Despite a slight sequential improvement in sales, the overall outlook remains negative due to ongoing losses and rising debt.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ed2e93933521015b6a3364e440e5e3a8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gretex Corporate Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gretex-corporate-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788591</link><description>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd's latest results show a strong quarter-on-quarter recovery with net sales up 261.97% and net profit up 1,387.01%. However, concerns about year-on-year revenue decline, negative cash flow, and earnings volatility suggest caution regarding long-term sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e7869d0b13895662f7c4645b42b8de83</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Hawa Engineers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-hawa-engineers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788590</link><description>Hawa Engineers Ltd's latest results show some sequential improvement in net profit and revenue, but significant year-on-year declines and compressed margins indicate ongoing operational challenges and a difficult environment ahead. Overall, the financial performance is concerning, reflecting struggles in the industrial valve segment and issues with debt management.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b201139f2c12be971b9caf1259d6f595</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gretex Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gretex-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788589</link><description>Gretex Industries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 62.71% year-on-year, but limited profitability improvement with a net profit increase of only 8.41%. While the company is debt-free, concerns about its low operating margins and declining return on equity suggest challenges in sustaining growth and justifying its high valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>024e0b9aaa81c33496860a9f75573672</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are G G Engineering Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-g-g-engineering-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788588</link><description>G G Engineering Ltd's latest results show a significant net profit increase of 394.89% to ₹4.04 crores, despite a 16.35% decline in revenue to ₹28.35 crores, raising concerns about sustainability and capital efficiency, as indicated by low return metrics and minimal promoter holding. Overall, the results are mixed, highlighting operational challenges despite the profit surge.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2ad3d10c5e78195e11c720ecdb74d969</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sanginita Chemicals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sanginita-chemicals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788587</link><description>Sanginita Chemicals Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹2.78 crores and a 29.36% decline in revenue year-on-year, marking the lowest quarterly revenue in seven quarters. The company faces significant operational challenges, with negative margins and a deteriorating financial outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4e1aeadfb97a81160592c2f399d18908</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanginita Chemicals Q3 FY26: Losses Deepen as Revenue Decline Continues</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sanginita-chemicals-q3-fy26-losses-deepen-as-revenue-decline-continues-3788580</link><description>Sanginita Chemicals Ltd., a micro-cap chemicals manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹28.00 crores, reported a sharp deterioration in Q3 FY26 results, posting a net loss of ₹2.78 crores compared to a profit of ₹0.14 crores in the year-ago quarter. The stock, trading at ₹11.51, has declined 22.07% over the past year, significantly underperforming both the broader market and the chemicals sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d219150a4849c60ff5e56b280092de5a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winsome Yarns Ltd Falls 4.15%: 3 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/winsome-yarns-ltd-falls-415-3-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-volatility-3788572</link><description>Winsome Yarns Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.1.85, down 4.15% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1.93. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting heightened volatility and mixed investor sentiment amid circuit limit hits and fluctuating trading volumes.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>4b2a1c2f433ae2c9bc04e485df64fccf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries Ltd Falls 4.83%: Bearish Momentum and Price Pressure Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-drilling-industries-ltd-falls-483-bearish-momentum-and-price-pressure-mark-the-week-3788570</link><description>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, closing at Rs.543.75 on 9 January 2026, down 4.83% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.571.35. This decline outpaced the broader Sensex’s fall of 2.62% over the same period, reflecting company-specific pressures amid a volatile market backdrop. The week was marked by sharp intraday price drops and a technical downgrade that intensified bearish momentum, despite some short-term rebounds midweek.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>f5d0801c7969c410d867a8b0287375b8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Gains 5.37%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-gains-537-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788571</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NACL) delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 5.37% from Rs.330.25 to Rs.348.00 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, supported by robust volume, strong derivatives activity, and positive fundamental upgrades, despite a midweek price correction amid sectoral weakness.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>93f58854efd32d7eb12d7a8b1ee37185</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ADC India Communications Falls 13.62%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adc-india-communications-falls-1362-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788569</link><description>ADC India Communications Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 13.62% to close at ₹1,313.20, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a shift from mild bullishness to bearish momentum, culminating in a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating technical indicators and weakening financial results.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>3d8be347fa7fa99619b1960956ea515c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Electronics Ltd Gains 3.91%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-electronics-ltd-gains-391-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788568</link><description>Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 3.91% from Rs.403.10 to Rs.418.85 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market signals, buoyed by strong institutional interest, active options market positioning, and sustained technical momentum, despite a recent downgrade in its mojo rating to 'Hold'.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>fcad3df4db2ed5e0fe7d61df0a139d72</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Overseas Bank Falls 5.91%: Downgrade and Mixed Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-overseas-bank-falls-591-downgrade-and-mixed-signals-shape-the-week-3788567</link><description>Indian Overseas Bank (IOB) endured a challenging week, with its share price declining 5.91% from ₹37.25 to ₹35.05, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The week was marked by a notable downgrade of the bank’s quality grade and investment rating to 'Sell' amid mixed financial signals and valuation concerns, which weighed heavily on investor sentiment and contributed to sustained selling pressure.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>211a3b2e844ddb7da1696b607c9fe0d3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd Gains 2.96%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vintage-coffee-beverages-ltd-gains-296-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788566</link><description>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd delivered a solid weekly gain of 2.96%, closing at Rs.165.25 on 9 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock showed notable volatility and strength midweek, hitting new 52-week and all-time highs before retreating slightly in the final sessions amid broader market weakness. This review analyses the key events and financial metrics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>2dfff6d12cdf987a69368f395af10d93</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Renewables Declines 9.16%: Technical and Valuation Concerns Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-renewables-declines-916-technical-and-valuation-concerns-weigh-3788565</link><description>Borosil Renewables Ltd endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price falling sharply by 9.16% to close at Rs.499.15, significantly underperforming the BSE Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The steep weekly decline was driven by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid mixed financials and deteriorating technical indicators, signalling increased caution among investors.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>53adc367c4f5346c58dfba41c83ee9dc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan Company Ltd Gains 3.78%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/titan-company-ltd-gains-378-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3788564</link><description>Titan Company Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 3.78% from Rs.4,050.00 to Rs.4,203.00 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs early in the week, supported by strong financial results and sustained sector momentum, before closing slightly lower on the final two trading days amid broader market weakness.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>823c05a22e379e5727f227b2f8fb500c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>