<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Physicswallah Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 10 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/physicswallah-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-10-feb-2026-3831284</link><description>Physicswallah Ltd experienced a notable decline today, hitting an intraday low of ₹108.8 as the stock faced significant price pressure. The share price fell by 5.23% intraday, extending a losing streak that has seen the stock drop over 10% in the past four sessions, underperforming its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>9053b3e8935b9060a0a11c02b5958b50</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs 1337.65</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mobavenue-ai-tech-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs-133765-3831283</link><description>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd, a player in the Other Consumer Services sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1337.65. This achievement marks a continuation of the stock’s robust upward momentum, reflecting strong market performance over recent sessions.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>f2a45588103589ec73c632abb67564ca</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastal Corporation Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.54.64</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coastal-corporation-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs5464-3831285</link><description>Coastal Corporation Ltd, a key player in the FMCG sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs 54.64. This marks a notable surge in the stock’s momentum, reflecting strong market performance and sustained gains over recent sessions.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>65c366c79b0a9dd7b1945056a6bb1cdd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.580</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/investment-precision-castings-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs580-3831286</link><description>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs.580, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. This new peak reflects robust momentum in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, with the stock outperforming its peers and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and sustained buying interest.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>1cca9bb9777e58ee24916775ee222818</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Ltd Hits All-Time High Amid Strong Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/investment-precision-castings-ltd-hits-all-time-high-amid-strong-market-performance-3831275</link><description>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high, reflecting its robust performance and resilience within the Castings &amp; Forgings sector. The stock’s recent surge underscores a remarkable journey marked by sustained gains and notable outperformance against key benchmarks.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>f83440a2a57c66437b232734d555563d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Specialty Solutions Ltd Hits Day Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/welspun-specialty-solutions-ltd-hits-day-low-amid-price-pressure-3831272</link><description>Welspun Specialty Solutions Ltd experienced a notable decline today, hitting its intraday low as selling pressure intensified. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices despite a generally positive market environment, reflecting immediate pressures weighing on its price.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>ed3eb3db155fb068de67ad0127b969c0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Breweries Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.74% Surge on 10 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/united-breweries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-574-surge-on-10-feb-2026-3831271</link><description>United Breweries Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 10 Feb 2026, surging 5.74% to touch a day’s high of Rs 1,616, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex which gained 0.28% during the session.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>d680fe3da7d1b87b4cdbebed0bc2c198</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-mixed-market-signals-3831270</link><description>Swiggy Ltd has witnessed a notable 14.9% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a strong intraday performance and outperformance against its sector, the company’s overall mojo grade has deteriorated to a Strong Sell, reflecting cautious sentiment amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>2c885f807851ac21406c06576e4b25dd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3831269</link><description>Premier Energies Ltd (symbol: PREMIERENE), a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a significant uptick in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This surge accompanies a sustained price rally, reflecting growing bullish sentiment despite some cautionary signals from delivery volumes and moving average trends.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>feca501f904622421fd5956cf504fe57</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3831267</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd (POLICYBZR) has witnessed a notable 12.1% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a cautious or bearish stance among traders amid declining delivery volumes and price pressures.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>26482862469f4719e57fcf7575227994</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/360-one-wam-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3831268</link><description>Shares of 360 ONE WAM Ltd, a prominent player in the capital markets sector, witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in the derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting growing investor confidence amid evolving volume and price dynamics.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>4c302892cbd4888ca93f24a4bae10450</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rail-vikas-nigam-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3831265</link><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL), a mid-cap player in the construction sector, has witnessed a notable 12.6% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this uptick, the stock’s price action and volume patterns present a nuanced picture, reflecting cautious sentiment amid broader sectoral and market dynamics.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>b5182eb230ed4d853f8b36427098965c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Industries Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-industries-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3831260</link><description>Supreme Industries Ltd, a key player in the Plastic Products - Industrial sector, has witnessed a notable 16.14% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>8436507cdedf759f2053a6b6127b4aa1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samvardhana Motherson International Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samvardhana-motherson-international-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3831266</link><description>Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd (MOTHERSON) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock recently hit a new 52-week high of Rs 131.89, supported by robust volume and positive price action, reflecting growing investor confidence in the auto components sector.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>bfeae4ec71dab8d319bb42cbd42daec2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Ltd. Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Signalling Market Positioning Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lupin-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-signalling-market-positioning-shift-3831264</link><description>Lupin Ltd., a prominent player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price action, combined with rising volumes and a strong mojo score, suggests evolving investor sentiment and positioning ahead of key sectoral developments.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>cf5becbcb96cd36a11118e3bf1f98d26</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eicher-motors-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3831261</link><description>Eicher Motors Ltd (EICHERMOT) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, with a 12.35% increase to 61,270 contracts from 54,535 previously. This rise, coupled with robust volume and price momentum near its 52-week high, suggests a strengthening bullish sentiment among market participants, reflecting increased directional bets on the stock’s upside potential.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>60732d80bfb9841e24ef99f310a2656e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Star Ltd. Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-star-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3831263</link><description>Blue Star Ltd. (BLUESTARCO) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock has outperformed its sector recently, supported by rising volumes and sustained investor interest, prompting a reassessment of its market positioning and outlook.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>1272c6f6c7115293c55c6320aa3ed3f5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zydus-lifesciences-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3831262</link><description>Zydus Lifesciences Ltd has witnessed a significant 33.1% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, raising questions about the directional bets underpinning this surge.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>8ec0eab6baba387868a2f310401b4e5a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pavna Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pavna-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3831258</link><description>Pavna Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 10 Feb 2026, registering a remarkable 19.96% gain in a single trading session. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, significant unfilled demand, and heightened investor participation, marking a notable outperformance against its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>6a02d6e793b1d1351b421710c6269d1d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surge in Open Interest Signals Renewed Investor Confidence in Torrent Power Ltd.</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/surge-in-open-interest-signals-renewed-investor-confidence-in-torrent-power-ltd-3831254</link><description>Torrent Power Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and shifting investor sentiment. The stock outperformed its sector peers with a 3.97% gain on 10 Feb 2026, supported by robust volume and rising delivery volumes, signalling renewed confidence in the power sector mid-cap.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>c58633b1fc0bf75ad31f0cdedf780ec5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>