<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Afcons Infrastructure Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-afcons-infrastructure-ltd-fallingrising-3854495</link><description>On 24-Feb, Afcons Infrastructure Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹307.60, down ₹5.15 or 1.65%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid weak financial indicators and market pressures, with the stock hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹302.55 during the trading session.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2cdffe6549280252fb35e1e1ff4c6f9b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-fallingrising-3854494</link><description>On 24-Feb, Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.31% to close at ₹3,991.90. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by valuation concerns and disappointing returns over recent periods.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ea73b7d5333b5f9380def77e2311971a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sanstar Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanstar-ltd-fallingrising-3854493</link><description>On 24-Feb, Sanstar Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.5% to close at ₹86.83, reflecting a continuation of its underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>359898f8249b3cb39b1c68ec28caad22</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3854492</link><description>On 24-Feb, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.66% to close at ₹326.00. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ea4d5904af7d6035ad527378057b56a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is eMudhra Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-emudhra-ltd-fallingrising-3854491</link><description>On 24-Feb, eMudhra Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 4.47% to close at ₹443.60, marking a continuation of a downward trend that has seen the share lose over 8% in the past four days and hit a fresh 52-week low of ₹435.15. This decline reflects a combination of valuation pressures, underwhelming relative performance against benchmarks, and broader sector weakness.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2f718940c2f48be900aff1647e0efb13</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is NDR Auto Components Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ndr-auto-components-ltd-fallingrising-3854490</link><description>On 24-Feb, NDR Auto Components Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 4.31% to close at ₹755.45. This drop comes despite the company’s strong long-term growth metrics, reflecting a complex interplay of valuation pressures, subdued investor interest, and recent operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dda9f4ed74f52e917138c37b1696b990</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Artemis Electricals &amp; Projects Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-artemis-electricals-projects-ltd-fallingrising-3854489</link><description>On 24-Feb, Artemis Electricals &amp; Projects Ltd recorded a modest price increase of 0.16%, closing at ₹18.77. Despite this slight uptick, the stock continues to face downward pressure over multiple time horizons, underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f35a9dc0394743a533cc8e16c41fd8c3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Zota Health Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-zota-health-care-ltd-fallingrising-3854488</link><description>On 24-Feb, Zota Health Care Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.72% to ₹1,248.70, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share underperform both its sector and benchmark indices in recent weeks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a3d16d34b9faf5e5bef23643687efc12</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bandhan Bank Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bandhan-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3854487</link><description>On 24-Feb, Bandhan Bank Ltd. witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹180.45 with a gain of ₹6.85 or 3.95%. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong recent returns, favourable technical indicators, and solid financial metrics that have bolstered investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>77e34351f86a2aafce58149dcc9e9db5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-educational-initiatives-ltd-fallingrising-3854486</link><description>On 24-Feb, Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its stock price, climbing 7.68% to ₹191.50, reflecting robust investor interest driven by its impressive long-term growth and market outperformance despite recent challenges in profitability and management efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d0e5da9713d3377b9feeb4c855c0da79</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Polo Queen Industrial and Fintech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-polo-queen-industrial-and-fintech-ltd-fallingrising-3854485</link><description>On 24-Feb, Polo Queen Industrial and Fintech Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.32% to close at ₹21.50. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks, with the stock hitting a new 52-week low and underperforming both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1a59b69dedac835d4877dbbc44c3b9ca</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vishal Fabrics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vishal-fabrics-ltd-fallingrising-3854484</link><description>On 24-Feb, Vishal Fabrics Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹21.38, down ₹0.75 or 3.39% from the previous session. This drop continues a sustained period of underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6bd372b7e05893cd27686a25a00cb3d1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Beta Drugs Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-beta-drugs-ltd-fallingrising-3854483</link><description>On 24-Feb, Beta Drugs Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹1,046.50, down ₹16.8 or 1.58% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a broader downtrend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and benchmark indices over recent periods.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ba247e8357cd79af7231671775e5b420</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kranti Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kranti-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3854482</link><description>On 24-Feb, Kranti Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹65.00, down by ₹2.76 or 4.07%. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2ccb2f3865dd1b5d9f03d252fedb1f5c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aditya Vision Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aditya-vision-ltd-fallingrising-3854481</link><description>On 24-Feb, Aditya Vision Ltd’s stock price declined by 1.46% to close at ₹480.00, reflecting a short-term pullback despite the company’s robust long-term performance and solid fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2e400b58c3667c62a5a1b335128a0b62</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Trigyn Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-trigyn-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3854480</link><description>On 24-Feb, Trigyn Technologies Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹52.87, down ₹2.43 or 4.39% from the previous close. This drop continues a sustained downward trend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and benchmark indices over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d17e30198b985cf629968500923f1c4c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jet Freight Logistics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jet-freight-logistics-ltd-fallingrising-3854479</link><description>On 24-Feb, Jet Freight Logistics Ltd's stock price rose by 1.04% to ₹18.40, continuing a positive trend driven by robust trading volumes, sustained gains, and outperformance relative to benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>48dfecce6e14d91314f5d534b31339f2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nakoda Group of Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nakoda-group-of-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3854478</link><description>On 24-Feb, Nakoda Group of Industries Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 7.19% to close at ₹24.38. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, signalling challenges for the stock in recent trading sessions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>672a8128f4a1e7fdcbac1f2a30761580</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is SIS Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sis-ltd-fallingrising-3854477</link><description>On 24-Feb, SIS Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.05% to close at ₹293.80, marking a fresh 52-week and all-time low of ₹289.15 during intraday trading. This decline reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks and deteriorating profitability despite recent positive quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1302760998bdceeb5efe11a807c1b7dc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Samtex Fashions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-samtex-fashions-ltd-fallingrising-3854476</link><description>On 24-Feb, Samtex Fashions Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹1.55 with a drop of 2.52% from the previous session. This movement reflects a continuation of the stock’s recent underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4737072e903238c3adf47946e7443210</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>