<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sudal Industries Falls 15.80%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sudal-industries-falls-1580-2-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3804183</link><description>Sudal Industries Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price tumbling 15.80% from Rs.65.32 to Rs.55.00, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The week was marked by a critical technical development signalling a bearish trend, followed by a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid flat financial results and elevated promoter pledging, all contributing to sustained selling pressure and volatility.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>9de3cd43be507e99e1ef675d3f0a648c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Roto Pumps Ltd Falls 4.94%: Technical Shifts and Valuation Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/roto-pumps-ltd-falls-494-technical-shifts-and-valuation-drive-weekly-decline-3804181</link><description>Roto Pumps Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.94% to close at ₹57.57, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to Strong Sell, technical momentum shifts, and a subsequent cautious upgrade back to Sell, reflecting mixed signals amid ongoing financial pressures and valuation concerns.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>6609717d32aace78113c97fa71a98745</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PC Jeweller Ltd Gains 4.29%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Volume Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pc-jeweller-ltd-gains-429-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-volume-surge-3804182</link><description>PC Jeweller Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 4.29%, closing at Rs.10.70 on 23 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by exceptional trading volumes and mixed technical signals, reflecting a complex market sentiment amid sector headwinds and a recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>a8ae396185af00fc17680e94f59bc6d5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Rasayan Declines 26.98%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Steep Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-rasayan-declines-2698-6-key-factors-behind-the-steep-slide-3804178</link><description>Bharat Rasayan Ltd. endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price plunging 26.98% to close at Rs.1,566.10, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid sustained selling pressure, deteriorating financial results, and negative market sentiment, culminating in a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>31a47bf47fdc3ce6eddf6a8508545f30</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks Falls 6.67%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jubilant-foodworks-falls-667-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3804180</link><description>Jubilant Foodworks Ltd’s stock price declined by 6.67% over the week ending 23 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% during the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid sustained bearish momentum, despite the company’s solid financial fundamentals and strong market position within the Leisure Services sector. Heightened derivatives activity and a downgrade to a Sell rating further underscored the cautious market sentiment.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>d7f224cc918b22e2e14d0a0bad44f32a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Consumer Products Ltd Falls 3.00%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-consumer-products-ltd-falls-300-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3804179</link><description>Tata Consumer Products Ltd closed the week at Rs.1,153.25, down 3.00% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,188.90, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by technical momentum shifts, significant open interest surges in derivatives, and mixed indicator signals, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid broader market weakness.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>a018c240845ef43b31b83aee51e31a1a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solid Stone Company Ltd Falls 1.41% Amid Valuation Shifts and 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solid-stone-company-ltd-falls-141-amid-valuation-shifts-and-52-week-low-3804177</link><description>Solid Stone Company Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 1.41% to close at Rs.27.31, while the Sensex fell more sharply by 3.31%. Despite early gains driven by valuation reassessments, the stock succumbed to broader market weakness and company-specific headwinds, culminating in a 52-week low on 21 January. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s performance over the week.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>8e7bd74fde7f99f2c69633a1e8c7c8f8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piccadily Sugar Declines 1.38%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piccadily-sugar-declines-138-3-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-slide-3804176</link><description>Piccadily Sugar &amp; Allied Inds Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.36.40, down 1.38% from Rs.36.91 the previous Friday, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock faced renewed selling pressure after hitting fresh 52-week lows twice during the week, reflecting ongoing operational challenges and mixed quarterly results amid a broadly weak market environment.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>58e4fd8fafdcad6d11fa6222bd087dd5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eco Hotels and Resorts Ltd Falls 9.17%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eco-hotels-and-resorts-ltd-falls-917-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804175</link><description>Eco Hotels and Resorts Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 9.17% to close at Rs.11.89, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week lows amid deteriorating fundamentals, a strong sell rating downgrade, and persistent financial headwinds, reflecting mounting investor concerns.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>adb3176c1390c28851e59dd230cac89a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arman Financial Services Gains 8.34%: 5 Key Factors Driving This Week's Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arman-financial-services-gains-834-5-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3804174</link><description>Arman Financial Services Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.34% from ₹1,484.50 to ₹1,608.30 between 19 and 23 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by notable intraday highs, technical shifts, and a downgrade in rating, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish momentum and cautionary signals amid sector headwinds.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>a3d758eec84584a444872de06b79dc57</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Linde India Ltd Falls 4.00%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/linde-india-ltd-falls-400-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804173</link><description>Linde India Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.00% to close at Rs.5,860.90, slightly outperforming the broader Sensex which fell 3.31%. The week was marked by a series of rating changes and mixed technical signals that influenced investor sentiment amid valuation concerns and fluctuating momentum.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>609a78cadf971ea2b57892c4507a3cfb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B C C Fuba India Ltd Falls 8.53%: Valuation and Technical Concerns Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b-c-c-fuba-india-ltd-falls-853-valuation-and-technical-concerns-drive-weekly-decline-3804172</link><description>B C C Fuba India Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 8.53% from Rs.162.35 to Rs.148.50, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Sell rating amid concerns over valuation and technical indicators, alongside a shift in the company’s valuation grading from very expensive to expensive. Despite solid fundamentals and strong long-term returns, short-term price weakness and market pressures dominated investor sentiment.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>bc3544eab974ef8957d570d51c1d9355</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viji Finance Ltd Falls 14.58%: 5 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/viji-finance-ltd-falls-1458-5-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-volatility-3804171</link><description>Viji Finance Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price plunging 14.58% from Rs.2.95 to Rs.2.52, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The micro-cap NBFC stock saw sharp swings, hitting both upper and lower circuit limits multiple times amid heavy buying and selling pressures, reflecting heightened volatility and investor uncertainty.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>22c99efeee4815f22ad5b67e9bf9c568</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of Maharashtra’s 1.44% Weekly Decline Amid Strong Upgrade and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-maharashtras-144-weekly-decline-amid-strong-upgrade-and-market-volatility-3804170</link><description>Bank of Maharashtra’s stock closed the week at Rs.65.61, down 1.44% from Rs.66.57 last Friday, yet it outperformed the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant upgrade to a Strong Buy rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting robust financial performance and very attractive valuation metrics, even as the stock faced short-term volatility amid broader market weakness.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>3ef3d8df8259c1d722cf8fbc7c535d0d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balurghat Technologies Drops 14.67%: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balurghat-technologies-drops-1467-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3804169</link><description>Balurghat Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 14.67% to close at Rs.12.80, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by multiple fresh 52-week lows, a downgrade to Strong Sell, and volatile trading amid weak fundamentals and bearish technical signals.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>460ee9f7387fc418bfa54796b5a465c4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Ltd Falls 8.31%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vodafone-idea-ltd-falls-831-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804168</link><description>Vodafone Idea Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 8.31% to close at Rs.9.93, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. Despite sporadic volume surges and brief technical recoveries, the stock remained under pressure amid mixed market signals and ongoing sector headwinds.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>1de3ae9ba68f4892644853c74b52d505</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jet Freight Logistics Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jet-freight-logistics-ltd-is-rated-sell-3803977</link><description>Jet Freight Logistics Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 25 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b205b365e4cc092eaf67b7299082a791</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhanuka Agritech Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dhanuka-agritech-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3803975</link><description>Dhanuka Agritech Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 Jan 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>73767ad73c01df44ec67527cb08cca2f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/eclerx-services-ltd-is-rated-buy-3803976</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 January 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>69fa6827efba106c70c0a5f3efa3f416</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/patanjali-foods-ltd-is-rated-sell-3803973</link><description>Patanjali Foods Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>62ba01c81f06bce64d89e804c58b95b3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>