<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Orissa Minerals and Market Trends for Sep 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-select-sectoral-strength-3764606</link><description>As the Sep-2025 quarter earnings season concludes with 3,990 companies reporting, the market reveals a nuanced picture of corporate performance across sectors and market capitalisations. Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, and Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd stand out among the top performers, while overall positive result proportions show subtle shifts compared to previous quarters.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>41d89e3c0ede2b78f66f6d00764625ec</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanghvi Movers Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sanghvi-movers-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amidst-weak-financial-trends-3764451</link><description>Sanghvi Movers, a small-cap player in the automobile sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting a nuanced view of its recent financial and technical performance. This shift comes amid a backdrop of mixed operational results and fluctuating stock returns, prompting a reassessment of the company’s standing within its sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>9ff8807587cc141400391e8f0f88e312</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ugro Capital Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ugro-capital-upgraded-from-sell-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-on-19-dec-2025-3764452</link><description>Ugro Capital, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently undergone a revision in its market evaluation metrics. This shift reflects nuanced changes across several key analytical parameters, including quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook, providing investors with a refreshed perspective on the stock’s current standing.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f26c3311a952bbc7bc653d8133bb756b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS E-Services Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amid Positive Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bls-e-services-upgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-on-strong-fundamentals-3764453</link><description>BLS E-Services has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a more favourable analytical perspective driven by recent financial performance and market dynamics. This shift highlights the company’s evolving position within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector and offers investors a refreshed outlook on its prospects.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>9963fcf790b6a318abf196605a101483</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Trip Plann. Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amid Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/easy-trip-plann-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-technicals-3764450</link><description>Easy Trip Plann., a small-cap player in the Tour and Travel Related Services sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent financial and technical developments. This shift highlights ongoing challenges in the company’s operational performance and investor sentiment, underscoring the importance of closely monitoring fundamental and market indicators for informed investment decisions.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>bd1ff63badb24dc7581fb01f36978c33</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DDev Plastiks Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ddev-plastiks-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amidst-mixed-financial-signals-3764449</link><description>DDev Plastiks, a small-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation metrics, reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This change comes amid a backdrop of mixed performance indicators and sector-specific challenges, prompting investors to reassess the company’s position within the industry.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>0f1256b51b965ca7a5d3d3fe32bc7887</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wendt India’s Evaluation Revised Amidst Challenging Financial and Market Conditions</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/wendt-india-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-deteriorating-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3764448</link><description>Wendt India has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent financial results and market trends. The company’s assessment metrics have shifted due to changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook, signalling a cautious stance for investors amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>15713ef7eedc3b0f296f0bee861704c4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>West Coast Paper Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/west-coast-paper-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-deteriorating-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3764447</link><description>West Coast Paper's market evaluation has undergone a revision reflecting recent developments in its financial performance and market positioning. The changes in assessment metrics highlight shifts across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook, underscoring the challenges faced by this small-cap player in the Paper, Forest &amp; Jute Products sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d4964ab8580ee969fe4e58a1706677c9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Go Fashion (I) Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amidst Challenging Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/go-fashion-i-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-weak-financial-and-technical-trends-3764444</link><description>Go Fashion (I), a small-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent operational and market performance. This adjustment follows a period marked by subdued financial trends and technical indicators, alongside valuation metrics that continue to attract attention.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>bdb1f2289516c2702bdfd31146ade20e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Honda India’s Evaluation Revised Amidst Challenging Market Conditions</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/marketsmojo-downgrades-honda-india-from-hold-to-sell-amid-weak-performance-3764445</link><description>Honda India’s recent evaluation metrics have been revised downward, reflecting shifts in its fundamental and technical outlook amid a subdued market environment. The adjustment highlights evolving perspectives on the company’s quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators within the industrial manufacturing sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>9d46d91a8ad491cab147f119c9c49f03</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gateway Distri Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gateway-distri-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-weak-performance-3764446</link><description>Gateway Distri’s market evaluation has undergone a revision reflecting a more cautious outlook, influenced by a combination of financial trends, valuation appeal, and technical indicators within the transport services sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b1354def82f7564ec4d84ca6083d200f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishana Phosch. Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Parameter Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/krishana-phosch-upgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-on-strong-financial-and-technical-grounds-3764443</link><description>Krishana Phosch., a smallcap player in the fertiliser sector, has undergone a revision in its market evaluation reflecting nuanced changes across key analytical parameters. This shift highlights evolving perspectives on the company’s quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook amid a backdrop of strong year-to-date returns and sector dynamics.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>760a9e6050b574ac274b377f67b95b33</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Satin Creditcare Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/satin-creditcare-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-on-8-dec-2025-3764440</link><description>Satin Creditcare has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting nuanced changes across key financial and technical parameters. This shift comes amid a backdrop of subdued returns and evolving investor participation, offering a complex picture for stakeholders in the finance sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>cd023ee77a42a098c23882c9e51fec2f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Drilling Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Performance Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jindal-drilling-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-improving-fundamentals-3764439</link><description>Jindal Drilling’s market evaluation has been revised, reflecting a nuanced shift in its assessment metrics. This change comes amid a complex backdrop of strong financial growth, attractive valuation, and technical challenges, offering investors a detailed perspective on the company’s current standing within the oil sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>2fb0bc753b3e9cb7fed31ecb7a10e93e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhansali Engg. Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bhansali-engg-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-on-10-nov-2025-3764441</link><description>Bhansali Engg., a small-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting nuanced shifts across key analytical parameters. This adjustment comes amid persistent challenges in financial performance and market returns, underscoring the complex dynamics facing the company.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>c45dac834b4e976102179e0f50bce76f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advait Energy Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Performance Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/advait-energy-upgraded-from-sell-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-on-8-dec-2025-3764442</link><description>Advait Energy's market evaluation has undergone a revision reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of strong financial results contrasted by cautious technical signals and fair valuation metrics within the electrical cables sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e5e9dbad7fae63df320f21024a20580f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prabha Energy’s Evaluation Revised Amid Challenging Financial and Market Conditions</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/prabha-energy-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-risky-valuation-3764435</link><description>Prabha Energy has undergone a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting shifts in its financial health and market performance. This reassessment highlights the company’s ongoing operational challenges and the implications for investors within the oil sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d72433ee7a5367ecefe7441894c7e977</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Venky's (India) Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/venkys-india-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-valuation-concerns-3764437</link><description>Venky's (India), a smallcap player in the FMCG sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent shifts in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment follows a detailed reassessment of the company’s quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators, highlighting ongoing challenges in its operational and market performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>ae0d16e41af8311c7b963aa8d089fcaf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>