<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Multi Comm. Exc. Joins Reliable Performers List Following Stellar Quarterly Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/multi-comm-exc-joins-reliable-performers-list-following-stellar-quarterly-results-3810165</link><description>Multi Comm. Exc., a mid-cap player in the capital markets sector, has been added to the prestigious Reliable Performers list as of 29 January 2026, reflecting its robust financial performance and sustained growth trajectory. The stock’s recent quarterly results demonstrate exceptional operational efficiency and profitability, making it a compelling addition for investors seeking consistent fundamental strength combined with promising price momentum.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>df4f8f34fe1277d6493f58df4c1fbbad</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Swiggy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-swiggy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810145</link><description>Swiggy Ltd's Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 54.43% year-on-year, but the company reported a significant net loss of ₹1,092 crores, raising concerns about its long-term profitability and operational sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>08e13695f85842131d15ed1310ea2857</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Revathi Equipment India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-revathi-equipment-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810144</link><description>Revathi Equipment India Ltd's latest results are concerning, with a net loss of -₹1.40 crores and a significant decline in operating margins, despite a 41.17% increase in revenue quarter-on-quarter. The reliance on other income for profitability and below-average return on equity indicate ongoing operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>65649cc18082a739285715f7956a1bdd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Manba Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-manba-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810143</link><description>Manba Finance Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with a net profit of ₹11.40 crores, but profitability margins are under pressure and the company has high financial leverage, raising concerns about sustainability and institutional interest. Overall, the results present a mixed picture with both positive and negative aspects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>49c29cfc92ef95fabef52124fc352f9a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sagility Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sagility-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810142</link><description>Sagility Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with net sales of ₹1,971.15 crores reflecting an 18.85% sequential growth and 35.65% year-on-year increase. However, while revenue is robust, profitability margins have shown some compression, indicating a mixed performance overall.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2cd4beb32254cbb2f4aa6c18921577d8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Arkade Developers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-arkade-developers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810141</link><description>Arkade Developers Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a significant revenue decline of 25.38% and a net profit drop of 11.97%, despite improved profit margins. This suggests potential challenges in project completions and revenue recognition, warranting close monitoring in future quarters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5c7d7e691d24b1053018fc76db48e240</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-allied-blenders-distillers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810140</link><description>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Ltd's Q2 FY26 results are strong, with a 35.22% increase in net profit and a 14.11% rise in revenue, marking the highest quarterly sales to date. However, the stock's elevated valuation compared to historical norms raises some concerns despite improved operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0c1b32a36f22bc07e4c7c33ec4d8c073</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are ASK Automotive Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ask-automotive-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810139</link><description>ASK Automotive Ltd's latest results show stable revenue growth and strong capital efficiency, with a net profit increase of 21.29% year-on-year. However, rising interest expenses have led to a slight contraction in profit margins, and the stock is underperforming compared to market benchmarks, indicating potential challenges ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>abd16dec41491cc82cf68384646af7ab</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sudarshan-pharma-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810138</link><description>Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with a 45.26% increase year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure, as operating margins have contracted significantly due to rising costs and high leverage. Overall, while the company is growing, its financial health is challenged by declining margins and increased debt.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a972d7e00f512082473386f4797fb833</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-capital-small-finance-bank-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810137</link><description>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd's latest results show a mixed performance with a net profit of ₹34.89 crores, reflecting a modest year-on-year growth of 4.65%. While there are positive aspects like stable asset quality and growth in total income, concerns remain regarding reliance on non-operating income and a declining CASA ratio.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>59a94643aa6d7b5c118ce7ed017c2ca3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Suraj Estate Developers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-suraj-estate-developers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810136</link><description>Suraj Estate Developers Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 24.55%, but a significant decline in net profit by 24.02% raises concerns about profitability and operational challenges, leading to a cautious outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dd1333242dbb73e95894482bda156930</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sundaram Clayton Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sundaram-clayton-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810135</link><description>Sundaram Clayton Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹64.35 crores and a 12.06% year-on-year revenue decline, alongside negative return on equity and high debt levels, indicating ongoing operational challenges and a difficult outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>655e09568ae5cf3c9dc9219e423a1867</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are GHCL Textiles Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ghcl-textiles-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810134</link><description>GHCL Textiles Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth at ₹349.12 crores, up 22.50% year-on-year, but net profit declined by 17.68% quarter-on-quarter, indicating significant profitability challenges and margin pressures. Overall, while revenue is increasing, the company's financial health is concerning due to low return metrics and reduced institutional investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>089b7d93cd5d291fec929b966e6feb03</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Samhi Hotels Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-samhi-hotels-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810133</link><description>Samhi Hotels Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with a record ₹337.75 crores, but a significant profit decline of 57.15% raises concerns about sustainability and margin pressures. While the company is improving its balance sheet, investors should watch for consistent profitability amid operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8a4e4e1dcebcef7623d4aeb8cd7846cb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Go Fashion (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-go-fashion-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810132</link><description>Go Fashion (India) Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, with a 9.24% year-on-year revenue decline and a 70.52% drop in net profit, indicating significant operational challenges and margin compression. The company's reliance on non-operating income further raises sustainability concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fe46e45ac3ddfe97dcdae298e95e9fd5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Star Health &amp; Allied Insurance Company Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-star-health-allied-insurance-company-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810131</link><description>Star Health &amp; Allied Insurance Company Ltd's latest results show a net profit of ₹128.22 crores, a 133.55% increase sequentially but a 40.40% decline year-on-year, with premium growth not translating into improved profitability due to declining margins and rising claims ratios. Overall, the company faces challenges in maintaining its competitive position in the market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>302a19ec9ec4a4e399ea355ce04265c9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aeroflex Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aeroflex-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810130</link><description>Aeroflex Industries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong operational performance with a net profit of ₹16.49 crores and record revenue of ₹120.89 crores, but the stock has underperformed over the past year, raising concerns about translating operational gains into shareholder value. Despite a strong balance sheet, challenges in cash conversion and declining institutional holdings suggest potential risks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2aaa137917088427321fba1db8d48712</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Macfos Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-macfos-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810129</link><description>Macfos Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, showing a 15.20% revenue growth and a 103.62% increase in net profit year-on-year, despite slight margin compression and negative operating cash flow. Overall, the company demonstrates solid profitability and market expansion, though it faces challenges in maintaining margins and managing cash flow.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7536dda652c1525cffac62dd37a033a4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are JFL Life Sciences Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jfl-life-sciences-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810128</link><description>JFL Life Sciences Ltd's latest results show significant volatility, with a 158.07% sequential increase in net sales but a 24.30% year-over-year decline, and while net profit rose 162.67% from the previous quarter, it remains 35.86% lower than last year, indicating challenges in sustaining profitability and investor confidence. Overall, the company's performance raises concerns about its long-term growth potential.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9d7248347bd84cee0c8933ee3c76ccd0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rainbow-childrens-medicare-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3810127</link><description>Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd's latest results show a year-on-year profit growth of 5.59%, but a sequential decline in net profit and operating margins indicates operational challenges and concerns about sustainable revenue growth. While the company maintains a strong balance sheet, it faces pressures from rising costs and reduced working capital efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ca05cd8a7cf89bd7961cf87f631e1567</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>