<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Everest Organics Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/everest-organics-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-amid-robust-performance-3773598</link><description>Everest Organics Ltd, a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high in its stock price. This achievement reflects the company’s sustained strong performance and resilience in a competitive market environment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>0c851c119f4338f45fefb70eb7dbab07</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 29 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-zinc-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-29-dec-2025-3773592</link><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 29 Dec 2025, with the stock touching a low of Rs. 614.75, marking a 3.46% drop from its previous close. Despite opening with a gap-up and reaching a new 52-week high, the stock succumbed to selling pressure, underperforming its sector and the broader market amid cautious sentiment.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>0b55cddfc45f07a01bd13632da2918af</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kinetic Trust Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.39.46 on 29 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kinetic-trust-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs3946-on-29-dec-2025-3773589</link><description>Kinetic Trust Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has reached a new all-time high of Rs.39.46, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and underscoring the company’s robust performance over recent periods.
Time: 34 minutes ago</description><guid>d95fccc8c9f16df6f17af1b2397f2389</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prithvi Exchange (India) Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Financial Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prithvi-exchange-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-financial-pressures-3773586</link><description>Prithvi Exchange (India) Ltd’s stock declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.109 on 29 Dec 2025, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>f74c2b6e8ed7eed5335aa7c71fb28acb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RSD Finance Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Weak Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rsd-finance-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-weak-performance-3773587</link><description>RSD Finance Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.85 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid persistent downward momentum. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on the company’s financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>4379436b75da42c9b015a65043dfc2a6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amrapali Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.14</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amrapali-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs14-3773585</link><description>Amrapali Industries Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.14 today, marking a significant drop amid a broader market that showed mixed signals. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, with the company’s share price underperforming both its sector and benchmark indices over the past year.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>83c7e9a9de8bb388bf7a1802df0fd0ba</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalyan-jewellers-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3773581</link><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd has witnessed a notable 11.2% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume and price action, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>f832be563f940b67e85ef1e924f1585d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-momentum-3773579</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd (MAXHEALTH) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite recent price weakness. The stock’s open interest rose by 10.33% to 61,479 contracts, reflecting increased positioning by traders amid a backdrop of falling prices and subdued investor participation.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>7c08e30cb573c5845b67f47de6af3e6f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Asset Management Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-asset-management-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3773580</link><description>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd (HDFCAMC) has witnessed a notable 10.43% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.12% gain in the stock price, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests evolving directional bets amid a backdrop of mixed technical indicators and subdued investor participation.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>092930a2049e2bf680c384afcbc1fc06</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-lombard-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3773575</link><description>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd has witnessed a notable 11.5% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite a modest 0.55% decline in its share price. This surge in open interest, coupled with evolving volume patterns and shifting investor positioning, offers a nuanced view of market sentiment towards the insurance heavyweight as it navigates a period of consolidation within the broader sector.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>c3201dafda0636fce6915ed379e28d13</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varun Beverages Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Market Positioning Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varun-beverages-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-market-positioning-shift-3773577</link><description>Varun Beverages Ltd (VBL) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and evolving investor sentiment. The stock’s recent outperformance against its sector and the broader market, coupled with rising volumes and delivery volumes, suggests a potential shift in directional bets among traders and institutional investors.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>bae28494af48ebff4693506be7bc25ee</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-prudential-life-insurance-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3773578</link><description>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd has witnessed a notable 14.2% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest decline in share price, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests evolving directional bets among traders, warranting close attention from market participants.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>c33476810c3023228e9a7c8c5ffdf94f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alkem Laboratories Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alkem-laboratories-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3773576</link><description>Alkem Laboratories Ltd has witnessed a notable 15.7% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite a modest decline in its share price. This increase in open interest, coupled with evolving volume patterns and shifting investor positioning, offers valuable insights into the stock’s near-term directional bets within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>1b900e07293aec7afeb5caae247955cf</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-energy-solutions-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3773574</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd has witnessed a notable 11.1% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>d3573eaf9be02f783fdbe7b1d6ef23ab</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phoenix Mills Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/phoenix-mills-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3773582</link><description>Phoenix Mills Ltd., a prominent player in the realty sector, has witnessed a significant increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite a modest price decline over the past two sessions, the surge in OI and volume patterns suggest that traders are recalibrating their directional bets ahead of potential near-term catalysts.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>7f3ad3676c973dcf4257b0397d748d32</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3773573</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite a modest decline in the stock price, the increase in OI by over 11% suggests that traders are recalibrating their directional bets amid a backdrop of mixed technical and volume indicators.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>3d6eb617939eef05d188b5d848b371c1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3773572</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd has witnessed a notable 16.24% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest decline in share price and a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Hold, the surge in open interest alongside rising volumes suggests evolving directional bets and increased speculative interest in this large-cap holding company.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>e18b62a09c402941b94289988f7d6136</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Authority Of India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-authority-of-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3773568</link><description>Steel Authority Of India Ltd. (SAIL) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting a notable shift in market positioning. The 19.07% increase in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and price movements, suggests investors are recalibrating their directional bets amid evolving sector dynamics.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>fbc96c04259c9bf315ece5779be2581f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NMDC Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action and Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nmdc-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-and-market-positioning-3773565</link><description>NMDC Ltd, a key player in the Minerals &amp; Mining sector, has witnessed a notable 14.24% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among traders. Despite this, the stock underperformed its sector on 29 Dec 2025, reflecting a complex interplay between bullish bets and profit-taking pressures.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>c6eb4787b4b9617af3784c7b5b71ad28</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBCC (India) Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nbcc-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3773570</link><description>NBCC (India) Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened investor interest and potential directional bets. The construction sector stock’s open interest jumped by 17.3% to 32,479 contracts, accompanied by robust volume and improving technical indicators, suggesting a bullish market stance amid broader sector underperformance.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>ef1e5a3a1c945e19eeabe72014291aea</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>