<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:30:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>HBL Engineering Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/hbl-engineering-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771905</link><description>HBL Engineering Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>2ad7dfba3a39367cfd46ea0ff0095cc4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wheels India Ltd. is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/wheels-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3771903</link><description>Wheels India Ltd. is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>4b363cb628719e47d63506d0fb798bd7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aether Industries Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aether-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771904</link><description>Aether Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>df206cf54fdb5ddc37a32b846acd3cd9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jio-financial-services-ltd-is-rated-hold-3771900</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Dec 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>821d66b83551eb4b48f4c2230a12f7fa</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ratnaveer-precision-engineering-ltd-is-rated-buy-3771902</link><description>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 27 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>404f3134865aeb4e987bd7961f6e5b1a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>