<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Vikram Aroma Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vikram-aroma-ltd-fallingrising-3802775</link><description>On 23-Jan, Vikram Aroma Ltd’s stock price surged by 6.99% to close at ₹70.70, marking a notable rebound after a prolonged period of decline despite the company’s challenging financial backdrop.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5df63e112d62b9c2fc471b6c458088ee</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Royal Arc Electrodes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-royal-arc-electrodes-ltd-fallingrising-3802774</link><description>On 23-Jan, Royal Arc Electrodes Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 8.77% to close at ₹156.00. This sharp drop reflects a broader underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, signalling investor caution and subdued market sentiment towards the stock.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>6d8f9b7eb4217b5cbce5886b4d2bdd8b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Quest Laboratories Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-quest-laboratories-ltd-fallingrising-3802773</link><description>As of 23-Jan, Quest Laboratories Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 9.2% to ₹96.20. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and recent operational challenges despite the company’s strong underlying fundamentals.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>773544416fe7dc02c274cf51ea8c1089</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-unimech-aerospace-and-manufacturing-ltd-fallingrising-3802772</link><description>On 23-Jan, Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹848.00, down ₹24.8 or 2.84%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks, with the stock hitting a new 52-week and all-time low during the trading session.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3f75ba2f6ed4b0c98e49af8895ea8934</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-exicom-tele-systems-ltd-fallingrising-3802771</link><description>As of 23-Jan, Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd has experienced a notable decline in its share price, reflecting ongoing financial challenges and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9fc079d4ea5412a05325bf6163f4050c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Plada Infotech Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-plada-infotech-services-ltd-fallingrising-3802770</link><description>On 23-Jan, Plada Infotech Services Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹13.80. The stock fell by 4.83% during the trading session, underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>55d6608acd5e649ceafebf3f7415293e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Yudiz Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-yudiz-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3802769</link><description>On 23-Jan, Yudiz Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹25.55, down by ₹1.10 or 4.13%. This drop marks a fresh 52-week and all-time low for the stock, reflecting ongoing challenges faced by the company’s shares in the market.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>217a38f137393b4c221ade1b276f2e51</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Life Insurance Corporation of India falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-life-insurance-corporation-of-india-fallingrising-3802768</link><description>On 23-Jan, Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) shares fell by 2.07% to close at ₹802.75, reflecting a combination of recent underperformance, disappointing quarterly results, and technical indicators signalling weakness despite the company’s strong fundamentals.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>f86398fe3d8ef307ab64ff7b935d3cca</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Yasons Chemex Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-yasons-chemex-care-ltd-fallingrising-3802767</link><description>On 23-Jan, Yasons Chemex Care Ltd witnessed a significant intraday price increase of 11.11%, closing at ₹12.00, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices despite a challenging longer-term trend.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ccee2ce70490877ea802a4f9fe5aa804</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pearl-green-clubs-and-resorts-ltd-fallingrising-3802766</link><description>On 23-Jan, Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd recorded a 1.81% rise in its share price, closing at ₹106.90, marking a modest recovery after a sustained period of decline relative to the broader market.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>325b3d725681e1dea8ea82da86aa4bac</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is One 97 Communications Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-one-97-communications-ltd-fallingrising-3802765</link><description>On 23-Jan, One 97 Communications Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 9.53% to close at ₹1,140.75. This sharp drop comes amid heightened intraday volatility and a broad underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>1e473db27ba6d9e6d842ba19652821a2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Eternal Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-eternal-ltd-fallingrising-3802764</link><description>On 23-Jan, Eternal Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 6.29% to close at ₹258.65, continuing a recent downward trend driven by concerns over the company’s debt servicing ability and deteriorating profitability despite strong long-term sales growth.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>cf99fe8e8a1f56ad52364c5a34b16345</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Lodha Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-lodha-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3802763</link><description>On 23-Jan, Lodha Developers Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.03% to close at ₹899.85. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend over recent weeks, driven by valuation concerns and the stock's underperformance relative to broader market indices and its sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>fec3ba452ec4185fe57b7463ddc439de</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Home First Finance Company India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-fallingrising-3802762</link><description>On 23-Jan, Home First Finance Company India Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, closing at ₹1,112.40, up ₹62.65 or 5.97%. This surge reflects the company’s robust financial performance and positive investor sentiment despite a challenging sector environment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b900abe51dacdce1084e0b7233220a76</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-happiest-minds-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3802761</link><description>On 23-Jan, Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹405.25, down by ₹7.7 or 1.86%. This drop comes despite an initial gap-up opening and reflects broader concerns over the stock’s recent performance and market dynamics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>43372a3752ebe94257fbb59af5b085e8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mazagon-dock-shipbuilders-ltd-fallingrising-3802760</link><description>On 23-Jan, Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.86% to close at ₹2,301.45. This downward movement reflects a combination of disappointing recent earnings, expensive valuation metrics, and weakening investor participation despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>74d6e01f1a8b74c857c735aea915e1dc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Metropolis Healthcare Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-metropolis-healthcare-ltd-fallingrising-3802759</link><description>On 23-Jan, Metropolis Healthcare Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.85% to close at ₹1,793.00. This drop reflects a continuation of recent underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>08050ca2f5bf96f41cc28c9dfb1bb8fe</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hdfc-asset-management-company-ltd-fallingrising-3802758</link><description>On 23-Jan, HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.62% to close at ₹2,433.00. This drop reflects a broader short-term underperformance despite the company’s robust long-term fundamentals and consistent growth trajectory.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b17b391b2ed3dde3e9dddd39ede590b2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sharika Enterprises Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sharika-enterprises-ltd-fallingrising-3802757</link><description>On 23-Jan, Sharika Enterprises Ltd recorded a 2.64% rise in its share price to ₹13.20, marking a short-term rebound despite persistent long-term weaknesses and underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ef5b7017375a0723b19ba7d17f39cc41</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Heads UP Ventures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-heads-up-ventures-ltd-fallingrising-3802756</link><description>On 23-Jan, Heads UP Ventures Ltd recorded a notable intraday rise of 5.17%, closing at ₹8.54, despite a broader trend of underperformance against market benchmarks over the past year and beyond.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>fe235ca9eba47935028ad3f88ec6c1f0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>