<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sector Performance; Small Caps Show Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-equity-markets-slip-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-small-caps-show-resilience-3769457</link><description>The Indian equity markets closed the day with modest declines as the Sensex and Nifty indices edged lower, weighed down by sectoral weaknesses and a subdued market breadth. While large caps faced pressure, small caps demonstrated relative strength, supported by select stock performances and cautious investor sentiment ahead of global cues.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>0dee78ae4c27df679ba55885ec535d8f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sector Performance; Small Caps Show Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-markets-edge-lower-as-sensex-and-nifty-slip-amid-mixed-sector-performance-3768955</link><description>The Indian equity markets closed the day with modest declines as the Sensex and Nifty edged lower, weighed down by sectoral weaknesses and a broader market breadth tilted towards declines. While large caps faced pressure, small caps demonstrated relative strength, supported by select sectoral gains and positive momentum in key stocks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1761a1ec74c205aa9572cb565475587a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uno Minda Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/uno-minda-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3769082</link><description>Uno Minda Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred then, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a833d1cbddcef69a4f78b9dcfada61ba</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Talbros Engineering Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/talbros-engineering-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769079</link><description>Talbros Engineering Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 Dec 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ccadfaecd6e25e08c7a2dab2fc77a966</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bilcare Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bilcare-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769076</link><description>Bilcare Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ed023f06d4001bc140e10bef02b0110d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Plastic Technologies Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/national-plastic-technologies-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769075</link><description>National Plastic Technologies Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 Dec 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis below reflects the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, incorporating the latest fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7067184758f3e0f7052c0872a1e400d9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nirlon Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nirlon-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3769078</link><description>Nirlon Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2ba24641ad716d06e0acf3eeed213202</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanstar Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sanstar-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3769077</link><description>Sanstar Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>76ddfdfcd34464717eb7b68427fa3bd8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credent Global Finance Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/credent-global-finance-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769074</link><description>Credent Global Finance Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ccf836bd0a684c8814c196f8db45ef88</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>W H Brady &amp; Co Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/w-h-brady-co-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769073</link><description>W H Brady &amp; Co Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 14 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dffb136466647669efa2fabdceb389a7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Fittings Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/national-fittings-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769071</link><description>National Fittings Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred then, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d5afe49b1c9f8774d4bd4e62eff14b9b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge Ltd is Rated Strong Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/coforge-ltd-is-rated-strong-buy-3769070</link><description>Coforge Ltd is rated Strong Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ee51041ebc041c31cc1bc3e9b060f49</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ABB India Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/abb-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3769072</link><description>ABB India Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred then, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>03fd5889e22b490220bab4e6b92446f6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sandur Manganese &amp; Iron Ores Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sandur-manganese-iron-ores-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769068</link><description>Sandur Manganese &amp; Iron Ores Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 17 Nov 2025, reflecting a recalibration of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s performance and prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b7b4f3982c5ef5669928a086a26df44f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Enterprises Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/welspun-enterprises-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769069</link><description>Welspun Enterprises Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f28e6893224fc6387624291da27814f6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atishay Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/atishay-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3769067</link><description>Atishay Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f2027c8f34099c98ce71671651ef6858</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pidilite Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pidilite-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769066</link><description>Pidilite Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 05 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s performance and valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dae19ea08e43b487f3b4267ff32c2e26</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tilaknagar Industries Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tilaknagar-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769064</link><description>Tilaknagar Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Nov 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis below reflects the stock's current fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>83932bf835f6f8a4aaaf2456c96b279b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dabur India Ltd. is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dabur-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3769061</link><description>Dabur India Ltd. is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5ebc4c9f21e69ca9892047146a16e069</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silgo Retail Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/silgo-retail-ltd-is-rated-hold-3769063</link><description>Silgo Retail Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 Dec 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>705f98dd78d24ff9e498102d727c4093</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>