<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Lords Ishwar Hotels Ltd Falls 1.70%: Valuation Shifts Amid 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lords-ishwar-hotels-ltd-falls-170-valuation-shifts-amid-52-week-low-3839681</link><description>Lords Ishwar Hotels Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.14.49 on 13 Feb 2026, down 1.70% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.14.74. This decline contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell by 0.54% over the same period, indicating a relative underperformance. The week was marked by a notable valuation re-rating, a fresh 52-week low, and subdued quarterly results, all contributing to the stock’s cautious trading pattern.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>d8a54f9a4a6c9080644151db01cdebf0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minaxi Textiles Falls 7.19%: Downgrade and Valuation Shifts Shape Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/minaxi-textiles-falls-719-downgrade-and-valuation-shifts-shape-volatile-week-3839680</link><description>Minaxi Textiles Ltd experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its share price declining 7.19% to close at ₹1.55, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, renewed valuation attractiveness amid sector headwinds, and volatile price movements reflecting investor caution.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>e3145c4d098aea37aa72360db10091ef</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sylph Industries Ltd Declines 2.99%: Mixed Signals Amid Upgrade and Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sylph-industries-ltd-declines-299-mixed-signals-amid-upgrade-and-q3-results-3839679</link><description>Sylph Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week from 09 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 2.99% to close at Rs.0.65, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical upgrade to a Hold rating and mixed financial results that influenced investor sentiment and trading volumes.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>8a9221b4298cee72a4430f074f57bb31</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TIL Ltd Gains 3.89%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/til-ltd-gains-389-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3839678</link><description>TIL Ltd recorded a solid weekly gain of 3.89%, closing at Rs.258.85 on 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong intraday momentum early in the week, followed by a mixed technical outlook amid broader market volatility. This review analyses the key events shaping TIL Ltd’s price action and technical stance during the week.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>4c2997a0c8f1bf2cb71ee68166617678</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hi-Tech Gears Ltd Falls 4.13%: Profit Plunge and Bearish Momentum Weigh on Shares</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-hi-tech-gears-ltd-falls-413-profit-plunge-and-bearish-momentum-weigh-on-shares-3839673</link><description>The Hi-Tech Gears Ltd experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.13% to close at Rs.647.10, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell by just 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp 87% plunge in quarterly profit and a shift in technical momentum towards a mildly bearish stance, reflecting ongoing headwinds for the company amid sectoral pressures and market volatility.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>8f1fa10decd58ad17e744f7627b928ed</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sasken Technologies Ltd Declines 1.69%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sasken-technologies-ltd-declines-169-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-slide-3839677</link><description>Sasken Technologies Ltd closed the week ending 13 February 2026 at Rs.1,230.35, down 1.69% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,251.50. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall over the same period, reflecting a week marked by initial strength followed by mounting selling pressure amid mixed technical signals and broader market weakness.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>8ef84f94f6060186f422b5384620828e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ortel Communications Ltd Falls 9.64%: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ortel-communications-ltd-falls-964-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3839676</link><description>Ortel Communications Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 9 to 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.1.50, down 9.64% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1.66. This decline significantly underperformed the Sensex, which fell a modest 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s volatile swings included multiple circuit hits, reflecting intense buying and selling pressures amid subdued liquidity and a persistent strong sell rating.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>cd7d5f0d1e346e7cfdf9dbef58717ad5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filmcity Media Ltd Falls 9.64%: Technical Signals Clash with Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/filmcity-media-ltd-falls-964-technical-signals-clash-with-weak-fundamentals-3839675</link><description>Filmcity Media Ltd’s stock declined sharply by 9.64% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.2.53 from Rs.2.80 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% decline, highlighting the stock’s heightened volatility amid mixed technical signals and persistent fundamental challenges. Key events including disappointing quarterly results, a notable technical Golden Cross, and a cautious upgrade by MarketsMOJO shaped the week’s price action.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>722fe486f2fa0d3a1ecc291b59df4410</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Riba Textiles Declines 4.54%: Valuation Appeal Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/riba-textiles-declines-454-valuation-appeal-amid-mixed-financial-signals-3839674</link><description>Riba Textiles Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining 4.54% from Rs.75.94 to Rs.72.49, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. Despite the price weakness, the company’s valuation metrics improved markedly, reaching very attractive levels amid market pressure. A notable surge in profitability during Q2 FY26 contrasted with a revenue decline, adding complexity to the stock’s outlook as it closed the week near its recent lows.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>e9b8362b1e7c6f563fd8f1993b4ca947</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Finance Corporation Ltd Falls 4.39%: Mixed Technicals and Flat Financials Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-finance-corporation-ltd-falls-439-mixed-technicals-and-flat-financials-weigh-on-stock-3839672</link><description>Power Finance Corporation Ltd (PFC) experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.39% to close at Rs.400.80, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid mixed technical signals and flat financial performance, contributing to the downward pressure on the stock despite its relatively attractive valuation metrics.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>f893290dca341ca4ec25d90af366475d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AVT Natural Products Falls 4.41%: Margin Pressures and Valuation Shifts Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avt-natural-products-falls-441-margin-pressures-and-valuation-shifts-shape-week-3839671</link><description>AVT Natural Products Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its stock declining 4.41% from ₹69.00 to ₹65.96, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by mixed financial results, margin pressures, and a notable shift in valuation metrics that together influenced investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>fc04ca657e7a474a283cd869a2b70858</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WPIL Ltd Gains 4.66%: 3 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wpil-ltd-gains-466-3-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3839667</link><description>WPIL Ltd delivered a mixed yet ultimately positive week, closing at Rs.405.25 on 13 February 2026, up 4.66% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.387.20. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period, reflecting renewed investor interest amid shifting technical signals and sector dynamics.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>0384e141c4f7abbe28b13c64b9a5c1f6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anjani Foods Ltd Falls 4.06%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anjani-foods-ltd-falls-406-3-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3839666</link><description>Anjani Foods Ltd’s shares declined by 4.06% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.19.60 from Rs.20.43 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% fall, highlighting the stock’s continued weakness amid fresh 52-week lows and mixed quarterly results. The week was marked by significant volatility and bearish sentiment, reflecting ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and operational challenges.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>915e52b37dc71df4dfe292fa070dbe4c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karma Energy Ltd Gains 12.96%: 4 Key Events Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karma-energy-ltd-gains-1296-4-key-events-driving-the-weekly-rally-3839664</link><description>Karma Energy Ltd delivered a strong performance this week, gaining 12.96% from Rs.40.83 on 6 Feb to close at Rs.46.12 on 13 Feb 2026. This rally notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s surge was marked by multiple upper circuit hits, robust buying interest, and a spike in delivery volumes, despite the company’s recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. However, the final session saw a sharp correction amid broader market weakness, highlighting a mixed but predominantly bullish sentiment for the week.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>ab17054731a4a5c176333d3ebd078704</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods Ltd Ends Week Slightly Lower Despite Early Gains: 2 Key Factors Behind the Movement</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/patanjali-foods-ltd-ends-week-slightly-lower-despite-early-gains-2-key-factors-behind-the-movement-3839663</link><description>Patanjali Foods Ltd closed the week ending 13 February 2026 marginally lower by 0.34%, settling at Rs.522.30, slightly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by significant trading activity on 9 February amid a price correction, followed by mixed price movements and a Q3 earnings report revealing a tax credit windfall that masked underlying margin pressures.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>ce18f52ca38c3f20fc50eddc6ddf788b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SRF Ltd Declines 2.40% Despite Technical Upgrade: Key Factors Behind the Week’s Movement</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srf-ltd-declines-240-despite-technical-upgrade-key-factors-behind-the-weeks-movement-3839665</link><description>SRF Ltd. experienced a challenging week on the bourses, closing at ₹2,833.15 on 13 February 2026, down 2.40% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹2,902.80. This decline contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell by a more modest 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical upgrade to a Hold rating and a nuanced shift in momentum indicators, reflecting a complex interplay of positive financial fundamentals and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>4a697b0fb5aa9c3eb2c9f837b2c73698</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Scott India Ltd Edges Lower - 0.42% Weekly Dip Amid Technical Shift and Hold Upgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thomas-scott-india-ltd-edges-lower---042-weekly-dip-amid-technical-shift-and-hold-upgrade-3839661</link><description>Thomas Scott India Ltd experienced a volatile week, opening at Rs.320.35 and closing slightly lower at Rs.319.00, marking a marginal decline of 0.42%. Despite this, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was highlighted by a significant 6.48% surge on 9 February, driven by an upgrade to a Hold rating amid improving technicals and strong financial results. However, subsequent sessions saw profit-taking and mixed technical signals, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid sectoral challenges.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>3ed02c0660505058eb806ae37a4ba241</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gowra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd Falls 3.14%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gowra-leasing-finance-ltd-falls-314-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3839660</link><description>Gowra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.94.30, down 3.14% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.97.36, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by significant technical deterioration, a sharp intraday drop on 12 February, a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, and a notable shift in valuation metrics. Despite some positive quarterly financial results, the stock faced selling pressure amid waning promoter confidence and bearish technical signals.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>232f82dbc7aa78e55353b13b8ba0d0b8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>63 Moons Technologies Gains 8.16%: Key Drivers Behind This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/63-moons-technologies-gains-816-key-drivers-behind-this-weeks-volatility-3839662</link><description>63 Moons Technologies Ltd recorded a notable weekly gain of 8.16%, closing at Rs.686.50 on 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s performance was driven by a strong intraday rally on 9 February and followed by mixed reactions to its Q3 FY26 results, reflecting a volatile but resilient trading week.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>cc04dae6d9662bf1a5c9da5abb9d4402</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starteck Finance Ltd Gains 0.34%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/starteck-finance-ltd-gains-034-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3839658</link><description>Starteck Finance Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 0.34%, closing at Rs.278.00 on 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating technical and fundamental indicators, alongside a notable shift in valuation metrics signalling renewed price attractiveness despite ongoing market challenges.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>264e4b9058bbf1c1663e6e8c9a816efd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>