<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Unified Data- Tech Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-unified-data--tech-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3787801</link><description>On 09 January, Unified Data-Tech Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.58% to close at ₹337.00. This drop continues a sustained downward trend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over recent weeks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ae470cc6d606712143986566db948cb5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sai Life Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sai-life-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3787800</link><description>On 09-Jan, Sai Life Sciences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.1% to close at ₹920.85. This drop comes amid a three-day losing streak, despite the company’s robust financial performance and market-beating returns over the past year.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9e846b2e844213ac93b4bd5b0e5c7240</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-odigma-consultancy-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3787799</link><description>On 09-Jan, Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.73% to close at ₹29.41. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid disappointing financial results and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>cc9f2704df62c72a205d5e7f9e0d29d0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Transrail Lighting Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-transrail-lighting-ltd-fallingrising-3787798</link><description>On 09-Jan, Transrail Lighting Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 4.24% to ₹502.90, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share lose over 12% in the past week, significantly underperforming the broader Sensex index.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>76a7de307a65201e4e486501b3865164</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vilas Transcore Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vilas-transcore-ltd-fallingrising-3787797</link><description>On 09-Jan, Vilas Transcore Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.47% to close at ₹379.70. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>44b24a0eba0736e0a57fabc3d3f69e4f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Macobs Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-macobs-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3787796</link><description>On 09-Jan, Macobs Technologies Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.2% to close at ₹205.50. This movement reflects a combination of short-term market dynamics and investor behaviour, despite the company’s strong longer-term performance relative to the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7699ffabb4aaab55510cb1079cc929e0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Diensten Tech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-diensten-tech-ltd-fallingrising-3787795</link><description>On 09-Jan, Diensten Tech Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 6.25% to ₹131.25, continuing a trend of underperformance driven by weak fundamentals and disappointing returns relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2818c09b1bbf55ea5b898e3b340970ea</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Krystal Integrated Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-krystal-integrated-services-ltd-fallingrising-3787794</link><description>On 09-Jan, Krystal Integrated Services Ltd witnessed a significant price surge of 20.0%, closing at ₹638.20, driven by heightened investor participation and technical momentum despite mixed fundamental signals.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>96e24194d8bfc23945954568ab826d74</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-popular-vehicles-services-ltd-fallingrising-3787793</link><description>As of 09 January, Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd has witnessed a notable decline in its share price, reflecting ongoing challenges in its financial performance and investor sentiment. The stock closed at ₹113.00, down by ₹1.40 or 1.22%, continuing a downward trend that has persisted over recent sessions.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>86678851821421bf26d8b5efa940de05</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rashi Peripherals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rashi-peripherals-ltd-fallingrising-3787792</link><description>On 09-Jan, Rashi Peripherals Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.2% to close at ₹368.50. This drop comes despite the stock’s strong recent performance relative to the broader market, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term trading dynamics and longer-term valuation considerations.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>f6e9b342e42cf285f12d8030b049d935</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Australian Premium Solar (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-australian-premium-solar-india-ltd-fallingrising-3787791</link><description>On 09-Jan, Australian Premium Solar (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹335.10, down ₹14.05 or 4.02%. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers, despite the company’s robust profit growth and healthy financial metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9fb0aa388438e0c24c5791a5cea050d5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-apeejay-surrendra-park-hotels-ltd-fallingrising-3787790</link><description>On 09-Jan, Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹126.25, down by ₹4.80 or 3.66%. This drop marks a new 52-week and all-time low for the stock, reflecting ongoing challenges in both its financial performance and market sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>8a64fe9dfc65bfa45375e650d26040d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is S J Logistics (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-s-j-logistics-india-ltd-fallingrising-3787789</link><description>As of 09 Jan, S J Logistics (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.35% to ₹337.10. This downward movement reflects a combination of underwhelming recent performance and investor caution despite the company’s strong operational metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>92b9c43a6ccc414f1fb71c00680a8cf3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-india-shelter-finance-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3787788</link><description>As of 09 January, India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of technical pressures and concerns over promoter share pledging despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7ccb91abe9d93681ccc399b785699ae1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Amic Forging Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-amic-forging-ltd-fallingrising-3787787</link><description>On 09-Jan, Amic Forging Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.94% to close at ₹1,333.70. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor participation.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>660d4cff1384a573b4b7548379735203</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Protean eGov Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-protean-egov-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3787786</link><description>On 09-Jan, Protean eGov Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹717.20, down ₹21.65 or 2.93%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid disappointing returns and underwhelming financial performance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>1976d0358fd11e53c895896fec3aaa0e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Micropro Software Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-micropro-software-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3787785</link><description>On 09-Jan, Micropro Software Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 2.01% to close at ₹20.35. This positive movement reflects a combination of strong short-term performance and heightened investor participation despite the company’s longer-term challenges.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b022948003b4655ccd5243dd40add3de</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cellecor Gadgets Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cellecor-gadgets-ltd-fallingrising-3787784</link><description>On 09-Jan, Cellecor Gadgets Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹27.05, down ₹1.20 or 4.25% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s sustained underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and technical indicators.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3cad5b13d76b5696945a87ee17db3579</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shradha AI Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shradha-ai-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3787783</link><description>As of 09 January, Shradha AI Technologies Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹29.47, down by 1.8% on the day, continuing a downward trend that reflects a complex interplay of strong operational growth overshadowed by disappointing market performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>21d3b93598f37679084259a94081795a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sangani Hospitals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sangani-hospitals-ltd-fallingrising-3787782</link><description>On 09-Jan, Sangani Hospitals Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.97% to close at ₹48.75, edging perilously close to its 52-week low. This drop reflects a continuation of a sustained downward trajectory that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2696c3961973575bf3a60edf1c5b7efc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>