<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers: Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allied-blenders-distillers-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-signals-3770239</link><description>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers has experienced a nuanced shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of indicators across weekly, monthly, and daily timeframes. The stock’s recent price movements and technical signals suggest a transition from a previously bullish stance to a more cautiously optimistic outlook, with mixed signals from key momentum and volume indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>27b16342a5578cc5c001766a8958d15d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti CNC Automation Sees Shift in Technical Momentum Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-cnc-automation-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770238</link><description>Jyoti CNC Automation's stock price has exhibited a notable shift in momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of technical indicators that suggest a transition from a mildly bearish stance to a more sideways trend. This development comes amid a backdrop of mixed signals from key technical parameters such as MACD, RSI, moving averages, and volume-based indicators, underscoring the nuanced market assessment of this industrial manufacturing player.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>913dcccc391f202558ba610ceced6325</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jupiter Life Line Hospitals Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jupiter-life-line-hospitals-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downturn-3770237</link><description>Jupiter Life Line Hospitals has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with recent evaluation adjustments signalling a bearish trend across multiple timeframes. The stock’s price action, combined with key technical indicators such as MACD, RSI, and moving averages, suggests a cautious outlook for investors amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e8e069ac19d03dc3f897cbab56a2649a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aeroflex Industries Shows Shift in Price Momentum Amid Technical Indicator Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aeroflex-industries-technical-momentum-shifts-to-bullish-amid-market-volatility-3770235</link><description>Aeroflex Industries, a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has exhibited a notable shift in its price momentum, reflecting changes in several technical indicators. Recent market data reveals a transition towards a more bullish technical trend, supported by signals from MACD, Bollinger Bands, and moving averages, while momentum oscillators like RSI remain neutral. This evolving technical landscape offers investors a nuanced perspective on the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>68dfcc9d28f3f96f6efe4d4b0e4aad7d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHCL Textiles Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ghcl-textiles-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-bearish-market-sentiment-3770236</link><description>GHCL Textiles has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish and bullish signals across multiple timeframes. The stock’s recent price movements and technical indicators suggest a nuanced market assessment amid broader sector and benchmark comparisons.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3270b32f6df42c77e78957cfcc182318</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fusion Finance Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fusion-finance-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3770234</link><description>Fusion Finance has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish and bullish signals across multiple timeframes. The stock’s recent price movements and technical indicators suggest evolving market sentiment amid broader sector and benchmark comparisons.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f713561ce01bdb5f51cccb574fa2fa11</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electronics Mart India Faces Technical Momentum Shift Amid Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/electronics-mart-india-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downturn-3770233</link><description>Electronics Mart India is currently exhibiting a notable shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish and bullish signals across key indicators. The stock’s recent price movements and technical parameters suggest a cautious market stance amid broader sector and index trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ecd197e118708898fa187b5eb9d9759c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhampur Bio Organics Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dhampur-bio-organics-faces-intensified-downtrend-amid-technical-weakness-3770232</link><description>Dhampur Bio Organics, a key player in the sugar industry, is currently exhibiting a shift in price momentum as reflected by recent technical indicators. The stock’s performance over various time frames reveals a complex picture, with bearish trends dominating the short and medium term despite some mildly bullish signals on select weekly metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fa0b8262799c7512f826572f78ad828d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishival Foods Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishival-foods-faces-technical-setback-amid-sharp-price-decline-and-bearish-momentum-3770229</link><description>Krishival Foods has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a transition from a mildly bearish trend to a sideways movement. This change comes amid significant price fluctuations and evolving technical indicator signals, highlighting a complex market environment for the agricultural products company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>22dbb82bd4eb7a581591d3df427bf41f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cool Caps Industries Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cool-caps-industries-faces-intensified-downtrend-amid-bearish-technical-signals-3770231</link><description>Cool Caps Industries, a key player in the diversified consumer products sector, is currently exhibiting a shift in price momentum as reflected by recent technical indicators. The stock’s movement suggests a transition towards a more bearish outlook, with several technical parameters signalling caution for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb5ab997805427fc5560a5e114bef45a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medplus Health Services Exhibits Shift in Technical Momentum Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/medplus-health-services-sees-technical-momentum-shift-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770230</link><description>Medplus Health Services, a key player in the retailing sector, has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a sideways trend to a mildly bullish stance. This change comes amid a complex array of technical indicator signals, reflecting a nuanced market assessment as the stock navigates recent price fluctuations and broader sector dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b6653a803e8e1d369792ad13d172e551</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Latent View Analytics: Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/latent-view-analytics-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770228</link><description>Latent View Analytics has experienced a nuanced shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish indicators across multiple timeframes. The stock’s recent price movements and technical signals suggest a transition in market sentiment, warranting close attention from investors navigating the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>733dada27e8edc1dd6204b63de46d33d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paras Defence and Space Technologies: Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Indicators</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paras-defence-and-space-technologies-faces-mixed-technical-signals-amid-sideways-momentum-3770226</link><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with recent evaluation adjustments reflecting a transition from a mildly bullish trend to a sideways movement. This article analyses the latest technical indicators, price action, and comparative returns to provide a comprehensive view of the stock’s current market stance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bd05bd82113a580a04b79f2901eecde7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prevest Denpro Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prevest-denpro-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770224</link><description>Prevest Denpro, a micro-cap player in the Healthcare Services sector, has exhibited a nuanced shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish and mildly bullish indicators. Recent price movements and technical parameters suggest a cautious market stance as the stock navigates between resistance and support levels.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>93516e67cf6e8567b976f2a9faa98ac3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation: Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvoco-vistas-corporation-faces-technical-momentum-shift-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770227</link><description>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation's stock has exhibited a nuanced shift in technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish and bullish signals across multiple timeframes. Recent market data reveals a transition in the company’s technical trend from mildly bullish to mildly bearish, underscoring evolving investor sentiment within the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>deec7b8412cb53761ff9f1a79c5c5d44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Stock Analysis: Technical Momentum Shifts and Market Context</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-stock-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3770225</link><description>Eternal, a key player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bearish stance to a sideways trend. This article examines the recent changes in technical indicators such as MACD, RSI, moving averages, and other momentum measures, alongside the stock’s price performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b6b8b1de1e4b5b68f929547105e56820</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishna Institute of Medical Sciences Faces Mixed Technical Signals Amid Market Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishna-institute-of-medical-sciences-faces-technical-downshift-amid-mixed-momentum-signals-3770223</link><description>Krishna Institute of Medical Sciences has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a transition from a sideways trend to a mildly bearish stance. This change is underscored by a complex interplay of technical indicators, including MACD, RSI, and moving averages, which together paint a nuanced picture of the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>823d6d9fcc3fa8b6beda97b190a99894</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairchem Organics Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fairchem-organics-sees-technical-momentum-shift-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3770221</link><description>Fairchem Organics, a key player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has experienced notable shifts in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces. Recent evaluation adjustments reveal a transition in price trends and technical indicators, underscoring a nuanced outlook for investors amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dcdf060fe90b419b5cbd5f061b9dce6b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laxmi Goldorna House Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/laxmi-goldorna-house-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-bearish-signals-3770222</link><description>Laxmi Goldorna House, a key player in the realty sector, has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish and bullish signals across multiple timeframes. Recent price movements and technical indicators suggest a nuanced market assessment, with implications for investors monitoring the stock’s trajectory amid broader sector trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>737bb068553c35ec492154b1eafbd69d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Shows Bullish Momentum Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/360-one-wam-technical-momentum-shifts-signal-bullish-outlook-amid-mixed-market-returns-3770220</link><description>Shares of 360 ONE WAM, a key player in the capital markets sector, have exhibited a notable shift in price momentum, reflecting a transition from a mildly bullish to a more pronounced bullish technical trend. This movement is underscored by a combination of technical indicators, including MACD, RSI, Bollinger Bands, and moving averages, which collectively paint a nuanced picture of the stock’s current market stance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ffc8d143225fa0e6286e570b636bdd65</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>