<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>CWD Ltd Falls 11.06%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cwd-ltd-falls-1106-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-volatility-3788186</link><description>CWD Ltd’s stock experienced a volatile week from 5 to 9 January 2026, ending with a notable 11.06% decline to close at Rs.369.10, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week began with a fresh 52-week high of Rs.425, but was followed by sharp price corrections amid mixed technical signals and increased selling pressure, reflecting a complex market environment for the stock.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>74957ef7f475500245b359e25c471334</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd Falls 3.72%: Mixed Technical Signals Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-ltd-falls-372-mixed-technical-signals-shape-weekly-performance-3788184</link><description>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining 3.72% from ₹832.90 to ₹801.95, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s price movements were influenced by a series of technical momentum shifts and an upgrade to a Hold rating, reflecting a complex interplay of improving short-term indicators and cautionary longer-term signals amid broader market volatility.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>d24259d1f8d6ea11aaa555740c96fda8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd Falls 4.02%: Mixed Technical Signals and Valuation Concerns Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-ltd-falls-402-mixed-technical-signals-and-valuation-concerns-shape-the-week-3788185</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.254.10 on 9 January 2026, down 4.02% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.264.75. Despite this decline, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by mixed technical signals, a downgrade in analyst rating, and notable volatility amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>3467fb1bd60728b40de9d4ae94290935</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S J S Enterprises Ltd Falls 8.62%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/s-j-s-enterprises-ltd-falls-862-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788183</link><description>S J S Enterprises Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 8.62% to close at Rs.1,683.20, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1,888.9 on 5 January, the stock faced sustained selling pressure amid mixed technical signals and broader market weakness, culminating in a sharp drop on the final trading day.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>91d8ac862aa4e506d55a060ab4cfb0ec</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sapphire Foods India Ltd Falls 11.35%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sapphire-foods-india-ltd-falls-1135-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788182</link><description>Sapphire Foods India Ltd endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price declining by 11.35% to close at Rs.222.20, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure amid bearish technical signals, fresh 52-week lows, and ongoing financial struggles, despite some long-term operating profit growth. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s performance this week.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>88476f7ff9def9b87646a1df24d1a2e9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Go Fashion Declines 8.78%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Drop</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/go-fashion-declines-878-6-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-drop-3788180</link><description>Go Fashion (India) Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 8.78% over the week ending 09 Jan 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall. The stock hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows multiple times amid persistent bearish momentum, flat financial results, and deteriorating operational metrics, underscoring ongoing challenges for the apparel company in a broadly resilient market environment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>3bf7b69e053416552a99730e1362de29</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd Gains 2.37%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anand-rathi-wealth-ltd-gains-237-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788181</link><description>Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 2.37%, closing at Rs.3,145.20 on 9 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical downgrade to a Hold rating, mixed momentum signals, and a subsequent shift back towards bullish technical indicators amid broader market volatility. Despite some short-term caution, the stock maintained resilience supported by strong fundamentals and relative outperformance versus the benchmark index.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>4549a31135deb9e4c69f838e98bf1df1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Metro Brands Ltd Falls 6.04%: Downgrade and Bearish Momentum Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/metro-brands-ltd-falls-604-downgrade-and-bearish-momentum-drive-weekly-decline-3788178</link><description>Metro Brands Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 6.04% from Rs.1,177.55 on 2 January to Rs.1,106.40 on 9 January 2026. This underperformance was notably sharper than the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting growing concerns around the company’s financial health and technical outlook. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating and a pronounced shift towards bearish momentum, which weighed heavily on investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>0e1972a287cc0fd36f4d5771a49d3424</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HP Adhesives Ltd Falls 5.05% This Week: 2 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hp-adhesives-ltd-falls-505-this-week-2-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3788179</link><description>HP Adhesives Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing down 5.05% at Rs.40.64, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit a fresh 52-week and all-time low on 9 January, reflecting persistent downward momentum amid subdued financial results and waning institutional interest.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>99a47b1701c7da501a33554c63646dd5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AB Cotspin India Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.75% Price Change Amid Technical and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ab-cotspin-india-ltds-mixed-week--075-price-change-amid-technical-and-valuation-concerns-3788177</link><description>AB Cotspin India Ltd closed the week ending 9 January 2026 with a modest decline of 0.75%, closing at ₹409.90 from ₹413.00 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasts with the broader Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period, indicating relative resilience amid a challenging market backdrop. The week was marked by significant technical momentum shifts, a downgrade in the company’s Mojo Grade to Sell, and mixed financial signals that influenced investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>7415c42225ee33e3ab88d191272f1827</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CMS Info Systems Ltd Falls 5.70%: 2 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cms-info-systems-ltd-falls-570-2-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-decline-3788175</link><description>CMS Info Systems Ltd’s stock declined by 5.70% over the week ending 09 Jan 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The week was marked by a cautious upgrade to a Hold rating by MarketsMOJO amid mixed financial signals, followed by a sharp drop to a 52-week low on 09 Jan. These developments reflected ongoing challenges in profitability and technical momentum despite stable management efficiency and attractive valuation metrics.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>1d26d04f471621365c9fcbeef82558e4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedant Fashions Falls 6.52% This Week: 5 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedant-fashions-falls-652-this-week-5-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3788176</link><description>Vedant Fashions Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, declining 6.52% from Rs.578.00 to Rs.540.30, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows amid persistent underperformance, valuation concerns, and subdued financial results, reflecting ongoing headwinds in the garments and apparels sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>d4d509718e23b8bfc44263d734d20420</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gateway Distriparks Falls 4.71%: Technical Shifts and Valuation Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gateway-distriparks-falls-471-technical-shifts-and-valuation-drive-weekly-decline-3788174</link><description>Gateway Distriparks Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining 4.71% from ₹60.50 to ₹57.65, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite a recent upgrade to a Hold rating by MarketsMOJO reflecting improved technical and valuation metrics, the stock faced renewed bearish momentum amid mixed technical signals and weakening price trends.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>47c7246cb80e9f84966cf9fdd895a149</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GMR Power &amp; Urban Infra Ltd Falls 8.19%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gmr-power-urban-infra-ltd-falls-819-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788173</link><description>GMR Power &amp; Urban Infra Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 8.19% from ₹110.55 to ₹101.50, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of technical downgrades, deteriorating financial fundamentals, and mixed momentum indicators that collectively weighed on investor sentiment and pressured the stock lower.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>eeda44049f6d9af41b9da4068354b3b0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd Falls 4.03%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motherson-sumi-wiring-india-ltd-falls-403-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788170</link><description>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.03% to close at Rs.47.85, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite early strength marked by new 52-week highs on 5 and 6 January, the stock faced sustained selling pressure in the latter half of the week amid broader market weakness and technical consolidation.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>e3a7bcb843acc383a5b081d74c3bced1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Insurance Corporation of India Falls 3.82%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/life-insurance-corporation-of-india-falls-382-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788172</link><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) saw its stock price decline by 3.82% over the week ending 9 January 2026, closing at ₹828.35 from ₹861.25 the previous Friday. This underperformance slightly exceeded the Sensex’s 2.62% fall during the same period, reflecting a challenging week marked by bearish technical signals, a significant death cross formation, and a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. Despite some short-term bullish intraday moves, the overall momentum shifted decisively towards caution amid flat financial results and persistent underperformance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>be1628bbb4b754085ce92cf52ff5c5c4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eMudhra Ltd Falls 4.59%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/emudhra-ltd-falls-459-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-downtrend-3788171</link><description>eMudhra Ltd’s shares declined by 4.59% over the week ending 09 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The stock faced persistent selling pressure, hitting a fresh 52-week low amid bearish technical signals and continued downtrend, despite the company’s steady operational performance and a recent upgrade to a Hold rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>e3bfc08a85fe37cb5ab89e8d1837355f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aether Industries Gains 3.98%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aether-industries-gains-398-7-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788168</link><description>Aether Industries Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 3.98% from Rs.944.00 to Rs.981.55 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by multiple new 52-week highs, strong technical momentum, and a notable rating downgrade reflecting mixed signals on valuation and technical indicators.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>4238286e9da242170925061bb8eb0535</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd Gains 8.29%: Four Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-ltd-gains-829-four-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3788169</link><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.29% from Rs.525.60 to Rs.569.15 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week highs during the week, supported by robust financial results, bullish technical indicators, and an upgrade to a Buy rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting growing investor confidence amid a mixed broader market environment.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>09e14967a25fd042f6d6fcb3fa6f0161</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piramal Pharma Falls 5.55%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piramal-pharma-falls-555-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788167</link><description>Piramal Pharma Ltd’s shares declined by 5.55% over the week ending 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.168.60 from Rs.178.50 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 2.62% fall, signalling a sharper correction in the stock amid deteriorating fundamentals, bearish technical momentum, and heightened derivatives activity. The week was marked by a notable surge in open interest midweek, followed by a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating and a pronounced technical downturn towards the close.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>6e02cfee332ca842d55e77c927b026d1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>