<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:20:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Teamo Productions HQ Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-teamo-productions-hq-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792618</link><description>Teamo Productions HQ Ltd reported a record quarterly profit of ₹5.12 crores, but this is overshadowed by a 65.02% decline in net sales and a heavy reliance on non-operating income, raising concerns about its operational sustainability and future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6fca97f227e8eea38b9b7928a646fe6a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are International Travel House Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-international-travel-house-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792617</link><description>International Travel House Ltd's latest results show modest revenue growth but significant declines in net profit and profit margins, indicating ongoing operational challenges and profitability pressures. Overall, the company's performance raises concerns about its competitive positioning and efficiency in capital deployment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c451d5089633e50dee0b14277c07e37c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are BITS Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bits-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792616</link><description>BITS Ltd.'s latest Q2 FY26 results show strong growth in net profit and sales, with a consolidated net profit increase of 450% year-on-year. However, concerns remain about the company's small operational scale and low return on equity, indicating challenges in sustainability and market competitiveness.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bb3802d83bb7e7613262ee1dc5fc33d8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>