<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Q2 FY2026 Earnings Review: Mixed Results Amid Sectoral Divergence and Market Cap Variations</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-amid-sectoral-divergence-and-market-cap-variations-3775362</link><description>The September 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 4,044 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings outcomes remains subdued at 42.0%, mid-cap stocks continue to outperform, delivering a robust 50.0% positive result rate. Large caps lag slightly behind at 39.0%, reflecting ongoing sectoral challenges and selective earnings beats.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8d988d9430015272273317d6a4ec7107</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775345</link><description>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's long-term strength within the capital markets sector.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>a20793f9f50633c5a0b63e344e608a04</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishna Institute of Medical Sciences Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishna-institute-of-medical-sciences-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3775344</link><description>Krishna Institute of Medical Sciences Ltd (KIMS) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5676bbf67970b674a7bc227668efa817</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chalet Hotels Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chalet-hotels-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775343</link><description>Chalet Hotels Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors should carefully consider the implications of this event amid the company’s ongoing performance challenges and sector dynamics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>721752863edea26b327759af017bd629</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>E2E Networks Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/e2e-networks-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775342</link><description>E2E Networks Ltd, a player in the IT - Hardware sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>be5828fc695f07e7febaa4096118b15e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paushak Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paushak-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775341</link><description>Paushak Ltd, a specialty chemicals company, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>192eeb119c9e48cbaa59837ab0b042b7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kesar Petroproducts Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kesar-petroproducts-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3775339</link><description>Kesar Petroproducts Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>cf18f42bae67f1540d2dae82d0bb664e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>V-Mart Retail Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/v-mart-retail-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775336</link><description>V-Mart Retail Ltd., a key player in the diversified retail sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>23a53017a74ebdc4db8651b74e7f58c2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Power Company Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-power-company-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3775335</link><description>Tata Power Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e9c65944d6bf15801ebb2d1d758c94b2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nikhil Adhesives Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nikhil-adhesives-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3775338</link><description>Nikhil Adhesives Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ea499befcdaa3402b2a4304e910f5d06</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virinchi Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/virinchi-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775334</link><description>Virinchi Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Software Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>f56bab82207da632da1913c5b221f7eb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Schneider Electric Infrastructure Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/schneider-electric-infrastructure-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3775337</link><description>Schneider Electric Infrastructure Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>0f1790e8177b636130e81bb19b70b1e2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Permanent Magnets Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/permanent-magnets-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775333</link><description>Permanent Magnets Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>563a9a4a3e05827259b20c473d1c298c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Hardy Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-hardy-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775340</link><description>Hindustan Hardy Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>4620077aab344bb269b016d2e8826eb4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vijaya-diagnostic-centre-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3775328</link><description>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the healthcare services company, which has seen mixed performance against the broader market over the past year.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>f0457744fc5fd37a79c2ad9782e7dfcb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eiko Lifesciences Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eiko-lifesciences-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3775324</link><description>Eiko Lifesciences Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, suggesting a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the specialty chemicals company.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>61aeecdfa825b8e9b50450d848789d51</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rubfila International Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rubfila-international-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3775327</link><description>Rubfila International Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its near- to long-term performance prospects.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>972d069cd5472ac4591fe4ac1a29f22c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>