<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:15:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sector Performance; Small Caps Show Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-equity-markets-slip-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-small-caps-show-resilience-3769978</link><description>The Indian equity markets closed the day with modest declines as the Sensex and Nifty edged lower, reflecting a cautious investor sentiment amid mixed sectoral trends and subdued breadth. While large caps faced pressure, small caps demonstrated relative strength, supported by select sectoral gains and global cues.
Time: Dec 25 2025 04:00 PM IST</description><guid>95422ebec7ec43cd831873326171e27e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AG Ventures Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ag-ventures-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769595</link><description>AG Ventures Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 13 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are based on the company’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with the latest comprehensive analysis.
Time: Dec 25 2025 03:13 PM IST</description><guid>abfcaf05e1b6bda61380c880c554682f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integrated Proteins Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/integrated-proteins-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769594</link><description>Integrated Proteins Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: Dec 25 2025 03:13 PM IST</description><guid>c77b1a927bbde126388c18722f49bac1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>International Combustion (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/international-combustion-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3769592</link><description>International Combustion (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 Nov 2025. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date analysis of the company’s standing.
Time: Dec 25 2025 03:13 PM IST</description><guid>b0c09724abb49eaf8ad4b4ec5a27217f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elegant Marbles and Grani Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/elegant-marbles-and-grani-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3769593</link><description>Elegant Marbles and Grani Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 11 February 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 25 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: Dec 25 2025 03:13 PM IST</description><guid>f26c39f103523e50920a3fb018c891f3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>