<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Nova Agritech Declines 9.51%: 2 Key Events Mark a Challenging Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nova-agritech-declines-951-2-key-events-mark-a-challenging-week-3861898</link><description>Nova Agritech Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 9.51% over the week ending 27 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.29.59 compared to Rs.32.70 the previous Friday. This underperformance was stark against the Sensex’s modest 0.96% fall, reflecting ongoing financial pressures and a persistent downtrend culminating in fresh 52-week and all-time lows. Two significant events on 26 Feb marked the week’s nadir, underscoring the company’s challenges amid a difficult market backdrop.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>efc555dcd83032e0fb34ce6c0637dda3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd Falls 3.05%: Technical Nuances and Valuation Shifts Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jana-small-finance-bank-ltd-falls-305-technical-nuances-and-valuation-shifts-shape-the-week-3861897</link><description>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.370.80 on 27 February 2026, down 3.05% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.382.45. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s 0.96% fall over the same period, reflecting persistent financial headwinds despite some technical improvements and a more attractive valuation profile emerging late in the week.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>ffe3cfd3fcfca9e86078aacdd663f477</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Gains 2.61%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rashi-peripherals-gains-261-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-momentum-3861895</link><description>Rashi Peripherals Ltd closed the week with a 2.61% gain, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by a five-day decline followed by a sharp recovery on 26 February 2026, driven by strong technical signals and positive market sentiment. Despite early weakness, the stock’s resilience amid mixed technical indicators and a Mojo Score upgrade to 78.0 underpinned its relative strength in the IT hardware sector.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>608813e233fe14d64344dd5bad75594f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Signpost India Ltd Gains 4.28%: Technical Momentum and Financial Strength Drive Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/signpost-india-ltd-gains-428-technical-momentum-and-financial-strength-drive-weekly-rally-3861896</link><description>Signpost India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 4.28% from ₹241.70 to ₹252.05 between 23 and 27 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock’s gains were supported by an upgrade to a Hold rating following improved technical indicators and robust quarterly financial results, alongside a shift in technical momentum to mildly bullish amid market volatility.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>320198b865c79476a340a2aa74d06a51</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd Falls 4.14%: Valuation Shifts and Mixed Signals Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-falls-414-valuation-shifts-and-mixed-signals-shape-weekly-performance-3861894</link><description>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.1,036.15 on 27 February 2026, down 4.14% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,080.90. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s 0.96% fall over the same period, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid fluctuating valuation assessments and financial signals. The week was marked by an initial upgrade to a Hold rating, a valuation shift to very attractive, followed by a downgrade back to Sell, underscoring the complex dynamics influencing the stock’s performance.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>6e1c12285f04d03d27955633ca00d241</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vibhor Steel Tubes Ltd Declines 0.65%: Financial Pressures Drive New Lows</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vibhor-steel-tubes-ltd-declines-065-financial-pressures-drive-new-lows-3861890</link><description>Vibhor Steel Tubes Ltd’s shares declined by 0.65% over the week ending 27 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.115.15, marginally outperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96%. The stock hit a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.113.05 on 26 Feb, reflecting ongoing financial pressures and a prolonged downtrend despite intermittent intraday gains.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>92e7f4c5786d59789b52cb5488b46614</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GPT Healthcare Ltd Declines 0.40%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Week’s Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gpt-healthcare-ltd-declines-040-5-key-factors-behind-the-weeks-weakness-3861891</link><description>GPT Healthcare Ltd’s shares declined by 0.40% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.126.05, marginally outperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96%. The week was marked by a fresh 52-week and all-time low of Rs.123.05 on 24 February, reflecting ongoing financial pressures and subdued investor sentiment amid broader market volatility.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>86d9acfde516d81f7b9ecda921ee16a1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R K Swamy Ltd Falls 4.32% Amid All-Time Low and Persistent Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-k-swamy-ltd-falls-432-amid-all-time-low-and-persistent-downtrend-3861886</link><description>R K Swamy Ltd’s stock declined by 4.32% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.99.70 compared to Rs.104.20 the previous Friday. This underperformance was sharper than the Sensex’s 0.96% fall, reflecting continued bearish momentum amid fresh 52-week and all-time lows reached during the week. Despite some intraday recoveries, the stock remained below all key moving averages, signalling persistent challenges for the company within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>e25eca616cae76fce270000c15adca1c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gopal Snacks Ltd Falls 4.24%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gopal-snacks-ltd-falls-424-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3861892</link><description>Gopal Snacks Ltd closed the week at Rs.298.45, down 4.24% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.311.65, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by significant volatility and bearish technical signals, with the stock experiencing sharp intraday declines and sustained downward momentum amid broader market pressures.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>33ce81c6a2eb733cdc376eaf0fa7d481</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd Gains 4.57%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/popular-vehicles-services-ltd-gains-457-5-key-factors-driving-the-week-3861893</link><description>Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd experienced a volatile week, ultimately gaining 4.57% to close at Rs.95.00 on 27 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock’s journey was marked by a prolonged downtrend early in the week, hitting fresh 52-week and all-time lows before a sharp rebound in the final two trading sessions. This review analyses the key events and financial metrics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>afa2c015f909038185d60943168fcdaa</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indegene Ltd Gains 2.25%: 3 Key Technical and Fundamental Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indegene-ltd-gains-225-3-key-technical-and-fundamental-factors-driving-the-week-3861889</link><description>Indegene Ltd closed the week with a 2.25% gain, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. Despite a midweek downgrade to a Sell rating amid technical weakness and growth concerns, the stock showed resilience with notable rebounds on 25 and 26 February 2026. This review analyses the key events and technical developments that shaped Indegene’s price action during the week ending 27 February 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>cb196dd462802091247e5f12d40e84fd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd Gains 2.35%: Technical Momentum and Rating Upgrade Drive Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krystal-integrated-services-ltd-gains-235-technical-momentum-and-rating-upgrade-drive-weekly-performance-3861885</link><description>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd recorded a 2.35% gain over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.625.70 from Rs.611.35 the previous Friday. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 0.96% during the same period, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals, an upgrade in analyst rating, and renewed price momentum amid cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>bed9469b6206f4039b1db1d0c1cf3761</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd Falls 3.97%: Valuation Shift and Technical Momentum Define Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aadhar-housing-finance-ltd-falls-397-valuation-shift-and-technical-momentum-define-week-3861884</link><description>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd closed the week down 3.97% to Rs.460.35, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The stock faced a challenging week marked by a shift from fair valuation to bearish technical momentum, followed by a mild recovery amid mixed market signals. Key events including valuation reassessment, technical downturn, and momentum shift shaped the stock’s trajectory between 23 and 27 February 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>7947f5f84a40c30bc820437ee2b794bb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TBO Tek Ltd Falls 9.71%: Technical Weakness and Flat Financials Weigh on Shares</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tbo-tek-ltd-falls-971-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-weigh-on-shares-3861883</link><description>TBO Tek Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its stock price declining by 9.71% from ₹1,358.20 to ₹1,226.35, significantly underperforming the BSE Sensex which fell by 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid technical weakness and flat financials, coupled with a shift to a bearish technical outlook that weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>c52492a5b19e505e1f436094a3047a0a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd Falls 2.50%: Four-Day Slide Amidst Operational Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/awfis-space-solutions-ltd-falls-250-four-day-slide-amidst-operational-growth-3861882</link><description>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.292.50, down 2.50% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.300.00, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a sustained downtrend with the stock hitting fresh 52-week and all-time lows, despite the company reporting strong operational growth and positive quarterly results.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>c78fa213ebd44f3aba8cc6468d43f6b7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd Falls 0.75% This Week: 6-Day Downtrend and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-falls-075-this-week-6-day-downtrend-and-valuation-concerns-3861881</link><description>Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.119.10, down 0.75% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.120.00, marginally outperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a sustained downtrend with the stock hitting fresh 52-week and all-time lows amid mixed financial results and persistent valuation concerns.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>fa8d91c4f4d4e87056f1dada0391803b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Travenues Technology Ltd Falls 8.83%: Bearish Momentum and Price Pressure Dominate Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/le-travenues-technology-ltd-falls-883-bearish-momentum-and-price-pressure-dominate-week-3861877</link><description>Le Travenues Technology Ltd endured a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 8.83% from Rs.186.80 to Rs.170.30, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by sustained bearish momentum, technical downturns, and heightened price pressure, culminating in a series of losses despite brief intraday recoveries. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s performance from 23 to 27 February 2026.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>050fdc14bc7e71f2250119a803bff729</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adtech Systems Ltd Falls 8.19% Amidst New Lows and Weak Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adtech-systems-ltd-falls-819-amidst-new-lows-and-weak-financials-3861880</link><description>Adtech Systems Ltd’s stock declined sharply over the week ending 27 February 2026, falling 8.19% from Rs.56.54 to Rs.51.91, significantly underperforming the Sensex which dropped 0.96%. The week was marked by fresh 52-week and all-time lows, weak financial results, and persistent market pressures including high promoter share pledging. Despite a modest intraday recovery on the final trading day, the stock remains entrenched in a sustained downtrend below all key moving averages.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>c8846c7106d136999dd7530826968d80</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DEE Development Engineers Ltd Gains 27.52%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dee-development-engineers-ltd-gains-2752-5-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3861879</link><description>DEE Development Engineers Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 27.52% from Rs.231.50 to Rs.295.20 between 23 and 27 February 2026, vastly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong momentum with multiple intraday highs, a significant rating upgrade, and technical shifts signalling renewed investor interest amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>d1144c7b0ccc8211872c29b9e7241fd2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd Declines 6.56%: Financial Struggles and Technical Weakness Drive Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stanley-lifestyles-ltd-declines-656-financial-struggles-and-technical-weakness-drive-downtrend-3861878</link><description>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd’s stock declined by 6.56% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.161.80 compared to Rs.173.15 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasts with the Sensex’s modest 0.96% decline, highlighting company-specific challenges amid a sustained downtrend marked by multiple 52-week and all-time lows, deteriorating financial metrics, and bearish technical signals.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>6bae2315928302612030cdd1fe95eafc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>