<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/magnus-steel-infra-ltd-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3828918</link><description>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd, a key player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has reached an all-time high, underscoring a remarkable phase of sustained growth and market strength. This milestone reflects the company’s robust performance across multiple timeframes and its ability to outperform key benchmarks.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>469c3a6c1c8a16ef8b3c865cd38ac3df</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3828915</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 1009.15 as the stock faced significant price pressure. The hospital sector stock underperformed the broader market, continuing a recent downward trend amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>c34ffc956512315e1f61ff33409b28c4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.05% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indostar-capital-finance-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-805-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828923</link><description>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 9 February 2026, surging 8.05% to touch a day’s high of Rs 230, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its sector peers in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) space.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>1cd3dd84311476ea62c26522c52eeb60</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEPC Ltd Hits Day High with Strong Intraday Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sepc-ltd-hits-day-high-with-strong-intraday-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828920</link><description>SEPC Ltd witnessed a robust intraday rally on 9 Feb 2026, surging to its day high with a notable gain of 7.54%, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its construction sector peers.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>4fb40e60ce63905be32b1d962dbd931f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal-Mogul Goetze (India) Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.48% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/federal-mogul-goetze-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-848-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828919</link><description>Federal-Mogul Goetze (India) Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 459.7, marking a significant 7.66% rise during the session. The stock closed with an impressive 8.48% gain, outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid positive trading momentum.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>a2d20ed30285c733fe370fa977b0f226</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unitech Ltd Hits Day High with 11.33% Intraday Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/unitech-ltd-hits-day-high-with-1133-intraday-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828921</link><description>Unitech Ltd witnessed a robust intraday rally on 9 Feb 2026, surging to its day high with an impressive gain of 11.33%, significantly outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>481c03fe0b7796e4f876659adc09fd08</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Venkys (India) Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/venkys-india-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-9-feb-2026-3828922</link><description>Shares of Venkys (India) Ltd experienced notable intraday weakness on 09 Feb 2026, touching a day low of Rs 1,488.45, down 7.04% from the previous close, reflecting significant price pressure amid a volatile trading session.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>72df42b8a290eba27274adec87840faa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Websol Energy System Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.19% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/websol-energy-system-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-719-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828917</link><description>Websol Energy System Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 71.5, marking a 7.04% increase from its previous close. This sharp uptick reversed a three-day losing streak and outpaced the broader sector and market indices.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>37fe4319f78d2d74188d48ec259569a3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neuland Laboratories Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.29% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/neuland-laboratories-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-829-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828916</link><description>Neuland Laboratories Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 09 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 14,138.15, marking an 8.45% increase. This sharp rise outpaced the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and the broader market, reflecting notable trading momentum and a positive reversal after two days of declines.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>9b071ba25fae3d66d6ebf361598dfe56</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Valiant Communications Ltd Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/valiant-communications-ltd-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3828911</link><description>Valiant Communications Ltd, a prominent player in the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high price, reflecting a sustained period of strong performance and growth across multiple financial metrics.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>025cff1a84290121485c929f74b4c5ce</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.55% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/p-n-gadgil-jewellers-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-855-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828909</link><description>P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd witnessed a robust intraday rally on 9 Feb 2026, surging 8.55% to touch a day’s high of Rs 585.9, significantly outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>ea55b0ab29feca9375df73a163eb1bf7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epack Durable Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.48% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/epack-durable-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-748-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828908</link><description>Epack Durable Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 09 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 259.5, marking a 6.9% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum in the Electronics &amp; Appliances industry.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>4c492515b5b7f16a24c23a5ed237d30e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senco Gold Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.11% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/senco-gold-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-711-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828907</link><description>Senco Gold Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 359.1, marking a 7.81% increase. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, continuing its upward momentum for the fourth consecutive day.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>4c917fcf21213ea653e9d083f242e55e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemplast Sanmar Ltd Hits Intraday High with 9.03% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chemplast-sanmar-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-903-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828906</link><description>Chemplast Sanmar Ltd witnessed a robust intraday rally on 09 Feb 2026, surging 9.03% to touch a day’s high of Rs 282.2, significantly outperforming the broader market and its sector peers in commodity chemicals.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>faccf7639cac6ec55c6790bf3034a272</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patel Engineering Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.11% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/patel-engineering-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-711-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828900</link><description>Patel Engineering Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 30.72, marking a 7.11% gain. This sharp uptick outpaced the broader Sensex, which rose by 0.54%, signalling notable strength in the construction sector stock during the trading session.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>5d848a1618f67d91fdc8074927d5521e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>