<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Siti Networks Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure Despite Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siti-networks-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-despite-weak-fundamentals-3822089</link><description>Siti Networks Ltd (BZ series) surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 5 February 2026, reflecting intense buying interest despite a subdued market backdrop. The stock closed at ₹0.35, marking a maximum daily gain within its permitted price band, as investors responded to persistent demand and limited supply, triggering a regulatory freeze on further trades.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>702c985e0401a28142eaf1431593dfbb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tijaria-polypipes-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3822086</link><description>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Plastic Products - Industrial sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 5 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 19.88%. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, a significant gap-up opening, and a notable increase in delivery volumes, signalling strong investor confidence despite the company’s current strong sell rating.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>09d091a772d479b34e6a01ca111536c4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd Sees Heavy Trading Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ola-electric-mobility-ltd-sees-heavy-trading-amid-bearish-momentum-3822088</link><description>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd (symbol: OLAELEC) emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 5 February 2026, registering a total traded volume of 8,397,497 shares worth ₹26.74 crores. Despite this surge in trading activity, the stock closed lower by 1.87%, underperforming both its sector and the broader Sensex index, signalling a complex interplay of investor sentiment and market dynamics.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>2bd0b937ba88bb37d9263102ed8fcf0f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sigachi Industries Sees Exceptional Volume Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sigachi-industries-sees-exceptional-volume-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3822087</link><description>Sigachi Industries Ltd, a small-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, witnessed one of the highest trading volumes on 5 February 2026, with over 1.01 crore shares exchanging hands. Despite this surge in activity, the stock closed marginally lower, reflecting a complex interplay of investor sentiment and technical signals amid a broader market downturn.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>66f73556849cfed6396fff50bda36b02</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS International Services Ltd Sees Robust Trading Activity Amid Sector Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bls-international-services-ltd-sees-robust-trading-activity-amid-sector-outperformance-3822085</link><description>BLS International Services Ltd, a key player in the Tour and Travel Related Services sector, has emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 5 February 2026. Despite a cautious market backdrop, the stock demonstrated significant investor interest, registering a 4.60% gain and outperforming its sector and the broader Sensex index.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>7c7d0beec3c67272ad25b03e21042aa7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Devyani International Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amid Strong Sell Rating</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/devyani-international-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amid-strong-sell-rating-3822081</link><description>Devyani International Ltd, a key player in the Leisure Services sector, witnessed a remarkable surge in trading volume on 5 February 2026, accompanied by a robust price rally that outperformed its sector and the broader market. The stock’s exceptional liquidity and rising investor participation signal renewed interest despite its recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>9b4a1531df0922d496848c2c51b6ab2b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanwaria Consumer Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanwaria-consumer-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3822082</link><description>Sanwaria Consumer Ltd, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 5 Feb 2026, driven by robust buying interest and a sharp 3.33% gain in its share price. This notable price action comes despite the stock’s recent prolonged downtrend, signalling a potential shift in investor sentiment amid heightened demand and limited supply.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>dbb169707d69325166bfe5b933e9414e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS International Services Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amidst Mixed Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bls-international-services-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amidst-mixed-market-sentiment-3822078</link><description>BLS International Services Ltd, a key player in the Tour and Travel Related Services sector, witnessed a remarkable surge in trading volume on 5 February 2026, accompanied by a robust price appreciation. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, signalling heightened investor interest and potential accumulation despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>ad91bbe39247dc5a9aaec7ce7b21d400</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Sector Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-sector-downturn-3822083</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd (HINDCOPPER) emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 5 February 2026, despite a challenging day for the Non-Ferrous Metals sector. The stock recorded a total traded volume of 77.97 lakh shares, with a turnover exceeding ₹462.5 crores, underscoring significant institutional interest and large order flow amid a sector-wide decline.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f0fc8175b396a5ef7128f4cd42054651</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IL&amp;FS Engineering &amp; Construction Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ilfs-engineering-construction-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3822080</link><description>IL&amp;FS Engineering &amp; Construction Co Ltd (BZ series) surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 5 Feb 2026, closing at ₹24.65, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.98%. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest despite subdued liquidity and a regulatory freeze on further trades, reflecting a notable shift in investor sentiment within the construction sector.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>8aab0accbcfb254231231b890419bf04</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cool Caps Industries Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cool-caps-industries-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3822077</link><description>Shares of Cool Caps Industries Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 5 Feb 2026, closing at ₹31.6, marking a new 52-week low. The stock suffered a maximum daily loss of 4.96%, significantly underperforming its sector and the broader market amid intense selling pressure and unfilled supply, signalling heightened investor panic.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>3365f286c46ccbb50a9906610ffef4f5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yes Bank Ltd. Sees Exceptional Volume Amid Mixed Price Action and Sector Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yes-bank-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-amid-mixed-price-action-and-sector-trends-3822079</link><description>Yes Bank Ltd., a prominent player in the private sector banking space, witnessed one of the highest trading volumes on 5 February 2026, with over 1.45 crore shares exchanging hands. Despite a marginal decline in price, the surge in volume signals heightened investor interest and potential shifts in accumulation patterns amid a broadly cautious market environment.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>ae3b6103638c0c1896df951d2005c920</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Ltd Sees Sharp Value Turnover Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-zinc-ltd-sees-sharp-value-turnover-amid-market-downturn-3822075</link><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd, a leading player in the non-ferrous metals sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 5 February 2026, registering one of the highest value turnovers on the equity market. Despite this, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a cautious investor sentiment amid a broader market correction.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>4a83c49e813e86185e3996175d2b8baf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raj Rayon Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/raj-rayon-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3822076</link><description>Raj Rayon Industries Ltd, a small-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 5 February 2026, reflecting robust buying interest and a maximum daily gain of 2.00%. This notable price action comes despite subdued investor participation and a regulatory freeze on further trading, underscoring strong demand that remains unfilled at the current price level.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>962ef54d5caf7fdee06377ccb39c4a90</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Debock Industries Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/debock-industries-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3822072</link><description>Shares of Debock Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the industrial manufacturing sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 5 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and investor panic. The stock closed at ₹1.35, down 0.74% on the day, marking a maximum permissible daily loss and signalling heightened market concerns about the company’s near-term prospects.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f3000c6efcd8e995a551ffc8ac4b3744</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd Sees Surge in Put Option Activity Amid Bearish Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-aeronautics-ltd-sees-surge-in-put-option-activity-amid-bearish-sentiment-3822074</link><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL) has witnessed a significant increase in put option trading ahead of the 24 February 2026 expiry, signalling growing bearish positioning and hedging activity among investors. The aerospace and defence giant’s stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, prompting traders to seek downside protection through options at strike prices near and above the current market level.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>d652068c3f68486a181a7ab935034a66</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NMDC Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Amid Mixed Price Action and Strong Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nmdc-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-amid-mixed-price-action-and-strong-technical-signals-3822070</link><description>NMDC Ltd, a prominent player in the Minerals &amp; Mining sector, witnessed one of the highest trading volumes on 5 Feb 2026, with over 86 lakh shares exchanging hands. Despite a modest decline in price, the stock’s robust volume activity and strong technical indicators suggest significant investor interest and potential accumulation ahead.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>31cbba8765eb8840de261ead1a8e81fd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GVK Power &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gvk-power-infrastructure-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3822073</link><description>Shares of GVK Power &amp; Infrastructure Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit price limit on 5 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a notable increase in trading volumes. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting renewed investor confidence despite its current strong sell rating and micro-cap status.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>97f47f75cecfa94f62dc414d219ba1ca</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Sector Downturn and Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedanta-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-sector-downturn-and-institutional-interest-3822069</link><description>Vedanta Ltd., a heavyweight in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 5 February 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹2,845 crores. Despite a sharp intraday decline, the stock remains a focal point for institutional investors, reflecting its large-cap stature and strategic importance within the metals industry.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>5266fc52aed936fdb43569995d98bf76</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heavy Put Option Activity Signals Bearish Sentiment in Tube Investments of India Ltd</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/heavy-put-option-activity-signals-bearish-sentiment-in-tube-investments-of-india-ltd-3822071</link><description>Tube Investments of India Ltd (TIINDIA) witnessed significant put option activity ahead of the 24 February 2026 expiry, reflecting growing bearish positioning and hedging strategies among investors. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, with a sharp intraday decline and elevated volatility, signalling cautious sentiment in the auto components sector.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>d7311ebe85f4db5cd47e6959a26bd26a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>