<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Shree Tirupati Balajee Agro Trading Co. Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shree-tirupati-balajee-agro-trading-co-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3808993</link><description>Shree Tirupati Balajee Agro Trading Co. Ltd, a player in the packaging sector, has recorded a new all-time low in its stock price, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>c40ca42a450e7683b4f2bc2979fa0f6d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commercial Syn Bags Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/commercial-syn-bags-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-amid-robust-gains-3808992</link><description>Commercial Syn Bags Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high, reflecting robust gains and sustained momentum in the packaging sector. The stock’s recent surge underscores the company’s strong market positioning and consistent outperformance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d4605b2172db4c4b3ba65b20e151c90e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gala Global Products Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gala-global-products-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3808991</link><description>Gala Global Products Ltd has reached a new all-time low price of Rs.1.58, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag considerably behind market benchmarks, reflecting persistent financial and market pressures.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>ab9a981136b5b484a52e643014bc6bf4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GE Vernova T&amp;D India Ltd Opens with Strong Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ge-vernova-td-india-ltd-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3808994</link><description>GE Vernova T&amp;D India Ltd commenced trading today with a notable gap up, opening 4.85% higher than its previous close, reflecting a robust start and positive market sentiment within the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector. The stock outperformed both its sector and the broader market indices, signalling sustained momentum in early trading hours.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>484a57023d1df3180a13c0107786753f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Juniper Hotels Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/juniper-hotels-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3808990</link><description>Juniper Hotels Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.212.65, marking a significant decline amid sustained underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. The stock’s recent trajectory reflects a series of setbacks across multiple financial and market metrics, underscoring the severity of its current position.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>0b02b9c5773b6b324edb62b87b9bedc9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Acutaas Chemicals Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs 1,947.55</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/acutaas-chemicals-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs-194755-3808987</link><description>Acutaas Chemicals Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high of Rs.1947.55 on 29 Jan 2026, reflecting its robust performance in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. The stock’s sustained upward momentum underscores the company’s strong fundamentals and market leadership.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>ff01b16081da7a941680258e56350bc9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suvidhaa-infoserve-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3808989</link><description>Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd, a player in the Financial Technology sector, recorded a new all-time low of Rs.3.01 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind key market indices and sector benchmarks, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial health and market valuation.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>407d6151ca18c9b044bf3ef9169865e8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.141.1</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lotus-eye-hospital-institute-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs1411-3808988</link><description>Lotus Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new all-time high of Rs.141.1, marking a remarkable phase in its market journey. The stock’s strong performance over recent periods underscores the company’s sustained growth within the hospital sector.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>143c136990395b879448560f9a1d7285</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murae Organisor Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/murae-organisor-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3808985</link><description>Shares of Murae Organisor Ltd, a player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, plunged to a historic low of Rs.0.2 today, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s extended decline. Despite a modest rebound in the latest session, the stock remains deeply undervalued compared to its historical and sectoral benchmarks.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>748e199581bbed02085f96b7047a66aa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukat Pipes Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs 30.74 on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukat-pipes-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs-3074-on-29-jan-2026-3808984</link><description>Mukat Pipes Ltd, a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, reached a new all-time high of Rs.30.74 on 29 Jan 2026, reflecting a sustained upward trajectory that has captivated market attention. The stock’s performance over multiple time frames significantly outpaces the broader Sensex, underscoring its exceptional rally.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>cf6d22ac11226decef674266877f3f1a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.104.39</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs10439-3808983</link><description>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new all-time high of Rs.104.39, reflecting a strong performance trajectory and sustained investor confidence in the company’s prospects within the miscellaneous sector.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>5a006cdaa6efe9e0d919fc96012ede43</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thinkink Picturez Ltd Shares Plunge to All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thinkink-picturez-ltd-shares-plunge-to-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3808986</link><description>Shares of Thinkink Picturez Ltd, a company operating in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, have plummeted to an all-time low of Rs.0.2, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. This latest drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s extended underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>4e0b75d657fb59b028cfb58a4873f9aa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs 687.3, Marking a Milestone in Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs-6873-marking-a-milestone-in-market-performance-3808982</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high of Rs.687.3 on 29 Jan 2026, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and sustained strong performance across multiple timeframes.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>105e553b380eba522ae735eb669f235a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gland Pharma Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.6% Surge on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gland-pharma-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-76-surge-on-29-jan-2026-3808981</link><description>Gland Pharma Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 29 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 1849, marking a 9.49% rise from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting significant trading momentum and volatility throughout the session.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>68ce775de7c34d381daa749665ebf923</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Bank Stock Hits Record High of Rs.911.7 on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-bank-stock-hits-record-high-of-rs9117-on-29-jan-2026-3808980</link><description>Indian Bank’s shares surged to an all-time high of Rs.911.7 on 29 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in the public sector bank’s market journey. This peak reflects the company’s robust financial health and sustained growth, positioning it well above sector benchmarks and historical performance.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>c5a257e4b16454c84ce2108e5afb37bf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Hits Intraday High with 9.44% Surge on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-944-surge-on-29-jan-2026-3808978</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 29 Jan 2026, surging to a new 52-week high of Rs. 687.3, marking a significant 9.44% gain on the day. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and sustained buying momentum.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>5a991b9bed22b1a18b1687878b72d6e2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heritage Foods Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Significant Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/heritage-foods-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-significant-price-pressure-3808979</link><description>Heritage Foods Ltd experienced a sharp decline today, hitting an intraday low of Rs 355.85, marking a 10.37% drop from its previous close. The stock’s performance notably underperformed the FMCG sector and broader market indices, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>5efacc150e513539b69ae96840f0bf39</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Srestha Finvest Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Steep Declines</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srestha-finvest-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-steep-declines-3808976</link><description>Srestha Finvest Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has recorded a new all-time low in its stock price, reflecting a prolonged period of financial strain and deteriorating performance metrics. The company’s shares have fallen sharply over multiple time frames, underscoring significant challenges within its business operations and market positioning.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>3fc67e5e5230b5029de3289e75523cee</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Valor Estate Ltd Surges to Intraday High with 8.48% Gain on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/valor-estate-ltd-surges-to-intraday-high-with-848-gain-on-29-jan-2026-3808977</link><description>Valor Estate Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 29 Jan 2026, surging 8.48% to touch a day’s high of Rs 112, significantly outperforming its Realty sector peers and the broader market indices.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>b6bc0bc7b926b38ce6484464e01acb9e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindalco Industries Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs 1020, Marking a Milestone in Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindalco-industries-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs-1020-marking-a-milestone-in-market-performance-3808975</link><description>Hindalco Industries Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high of Rs.1020 on 29 Jan 2026, reflecting a robust performance across multiple financial and market parameters. This achievement underscores the company’s sustained growth and strong positioning within the non-ferrous metals sector.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>4b757e94ab1e28a68d1ad3803602e0c2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>