<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-virtual-galaxy-infotech-ltd-fallingrising-3797492</link><description>On 20-Jan, Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.74% to close at ₹129.85, marking a fresh 52-week and all-time low. This downturn reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e72bb5899a4bce1f9a1cb2ac089d5697</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vikram Aroma Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vikram-aroma-ltd-fallingrising-3797491</link><description>On 20-Jan, Vikram Aroma Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.51% to close at ₹67.90, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share price decline over the past week and year to date, underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e9c7092d70c9ed04cf6ca5045fea7ef2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solarium Green Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solarium-green-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3797490</link><description>On 20-Jan, Solarium Green Energy Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.98% to close at ₹205.00. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum, influenced by broader sector weakness and technical factors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f83477afb77dc49c79adac55c2e19a3b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is ITC Hotels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-itc-hotels-ltd-fallingrising-3797488</link><description>On 20-Jan, ITC Hotels Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.65% to close at ₹180.30. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum, influenced by broader sector weakness and technical factors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7f32315568d7874abc01486370599f9c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kabra Jewels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kabra-jewels-ltd-fallingrising-3797489</link><description>As of 20-Jan, Kabra Jewels Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹86.60 with a drop of ₹4.40 or 4.84%. This downturn reflects a combination of underperformance relative to benchmarks, proximity to a 52-week low, and waning investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>80c2456c0e62500c43366a0e23be313e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-international-gemmological-institute-india-ltd-fallingrising-3797487</link><description>On 20-Jan, International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 4.03% to close at ₹298.60. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum amid broader sector and market pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>49e6a25c1667f0c28d3b1a5b0c2a6a26</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sahasra-electronic-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3797486</link><description>On 20-Jan, Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.88% to close at ₹256.55. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>11413fe3f0b699d20a5450f026b08cf1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-akums-drugs-pharmaceuticals-ltd-fallingrising-3797485</link><description>As of 20-Jan, Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 3.5% to ₹422.00. This drop reflects a continuation of recent underperformance driven by weak financial metrics and subdued investor sentiment despite some positive profit growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e0242b70469b49582d5760a0a99293ee</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajputana Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajputana-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3797484</link><description>As of 20-Jan, Rajputana Industries Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c168f8d7fa7d34bffe30e04ba3ddc260</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Raymond Lifestyle Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-raymond-lifestyle-ltd-fallingrising-3797483</link><description>On 20-Jan, Raymond Lifestyle Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 5.02% to close at ₹889.00, continuing a downward trend amid weak financial performance and broader sectoral pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>889d68fc226066d9393b558135ed5be8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3797482</link><description>On 20-Jan, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, dropping by 8.33% to close at ₹341.00. This sharp fall reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>45414aee6c375d10c4dd3447da79c2d0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kataria Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kataria-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3797481</link><description>On 20-Jan, Kataria Industries Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.55% to close at ₹97.00. This drop reflects a continuation of a broader downward trend for the stock, which has underperformed both the benchmark Sensex and its sector peers over multiple timeframes.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d24ab78e8934acd567fa04b472bf397d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3797480</link><description>On 20-Jan, Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹123.00, down ₹5.65 or 4.39%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid disappointing returns and valuation pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f0c004f1aaaa8f7fa873f658a2c88098</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awfis-space-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3797479</link><description>On 20-Jan, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 5.82% to close at ₹412.45, marking a new 52-week low of ₹405 during intraday trading. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted for 12 consecutive trading sessions, resulting in a cumulative loss of 17.34% over this period.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>75332769beb8aa2f4d1b1a79a85d3c1f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vibhor Steel Tubes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vibhor-steel-tubes-ltd-fallingrising-3797478</link><description>On 20-Jan, Vibhor Steel Tubes Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 8.59% to ₹116.05, marking a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹114.15 during the trading session. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend driven by weak financial performance and deteriorating investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ce218665522ca2ded3dfbd4420b297bd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Digidrive Distributors Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-digidrive-distributors-ltd-fallingrising-3797477</link><description>As of 20-Jan, Digidrive Distributors Ltd has experienced a significant decline in its share price, hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹24.04. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market benchmarks, reflecting ongoing challenges in management efficiency and investor sentiment despite some positive operational growth metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ed01e83af94654a942327fb5e72f3ec5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jasch-gauging-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3797476</link><description>As of 20-Jan, Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd’s stock price has declined by 3.04% to ₹510, continuing a downward trend influenced by sectoral pressures and subdued investor participation despite the company’s solid fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5ad62008afd4a524b0192cb3090f162d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Max Estates Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-max-estates-ltd-fallingrising-3797475</link><description>On 20-Jan, Max Estates Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹386.55, down ₹12.25 or 3.07% as of 09:13 PM. This drop continues a recent downward trend amid broader sector weakness and persistent concerns over the company’s financial health and valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1372ad0605279111ee7f6322813224ca</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Samhi Hotels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-samhi-hotels-ltd-fallingrising-3797474</link><description>On 20-Jan, Samhi Hotels Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.78% to close at Rs 180.00. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum amid broader sector weakness and concerns over the company’s financial efficiency and debt servicing capabilities.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f2eb8033cfe6290cac7cc2fd3dd018c0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Azad Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-azad-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3797473</link><description>On 20-Jan, Azad Engineering Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.22% to close at ₹1,471.00. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's downward trend over recent weeks, driven by valuation pressures and underwhelming relative performance compared to broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d24fffcc04ed5c2c6a36cab24d178ba6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>