<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sector Performance; JBM Auto and Trent Lead Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-equity-markets-slip-amid-mixed-sector-performance-small-caps-show-resilience-3768935</link><description>The Indian equity markets closed lower on 25 December 2025, with the Sensex retreating by 116.14 points to 85,408.70 and the Nifty 50 index ending at 26,142.10, down 35.05 points. Market breadth remained weak as declines outnumbered advances across the BSE500, while sectoral trends showed a predominance of losses with only a handful of sectors managing gains.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>4db54676d39deb70504852b13aee954c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raymond Lifestyle's Market Assessment Reflects Mixed Signals Amidst Financial Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/raymond-lifestyle-stock-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technicals-and-weak-fundamentals-3768929</link><description>Raymond Lifestyle, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has experienced a shift in market evaluation driven by a combination of technical indicators, valuation considerations, financial trends, and quality metrics. Despite ongoing challenges in profitability and stock performance, recent changes in analytical perspectives highlight nuanced developments that investors should carefully consider.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>691730cc0e944459a709143a84f8dba4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Signpost India’s Market Assessment Reflects Mixed Signals Amidst Financial and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/signpost-india-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3768928</link><description>Signpost India, a key player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has recently undergone a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a complex interplay of financial performance, valuation metrics, and technical indicators. This article analyses the factors influencing the current market assessment of the stock, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its recent trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dd6e1f2d02353da22679011f5aed2ba1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robust Hotels Faces Mixed Signals Amidst Financial and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/robust-hotels-downgraded-to-sell-amid-weak-financial-metrics-and-bearish-technicals-3768927</link><description>Robust Hotels, a key player in the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector, is currently navigating a complex landscape marked by contrasting financial results and evolving technical indicators. Recent changes in market assessment reflect a nuanced view of the company’s valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook, underscoring the challenges and opportunities ahead for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fbf69d612264b54db0b2e409c4c66101</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One 97 Communications Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Technical and Fundamental Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/one-97-communications-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3768926</link><description>One 97 Communications, a prominent player in the Financial Technology sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting nuanced changes across technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and overall quality parameters. This article analyses the factors influencing the recent shift in the company's assessment, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its current standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a9e4768e81aadbb62b855e3541ad0afa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paras Defence and Space Technologies: Analytical Perspective Shift Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/paras-defence-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-financials-and-technical-weakness-3768923</link><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies has recently experienced a revision in its market assessment, reflecting nuanced changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article examines the factors influencing this shift, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the company’s current standing within the aerospace and defence sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>969ff4ca1d2bc7d40736dd0f4f3d88d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation: Analytical Revisions Reflect Mixed Signals in Cement Sector</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nuvoco-vistas-corporation-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-technical-and-fundamental-weaknesses-3768925</link><description>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation’s recent evaluation metrics have been adjusted following a comprehensive review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. The cement sector player’s current market position reflects a complex interplay of operational challenges and valuation opportunities amid fluctuating technical signals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>09fc35138c3c0b64434b301db792df99</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairchem Organics: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/fairchem-organics-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technicals-and-weak-financials-3768924</link><description>Fairchem Organics, a player in the specialty chemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed evaluation of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. Despite ongoing challenges in financial performance, recent technical signals and valuation metrics have prompted a nuanced reassessment of the company’s standing within its industry.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f74670d9b6f1df513375cf7fc47d0d76</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vineet Laboratories Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vineet-laboratories-stock-rating-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-weak-fundamentals-3768921</link><description>Vineet Laboratories, a player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a complex interplay of technical indicators and fundamental financial data. Despite ongoing challenges in profitability and sales, recent technical trends suggest a more optimistic market outlook, prompting a reassessment of the company’s investment profile.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>559f614f3ff04c69c2d5f3abe13af9b1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Technical and Financial Developments</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/360-one-wam-upgraded-to-buy-on-strong-technical-and-financial-performance-3768922</link><description>360 ONE WAM, a key player in the capital markets sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation following recent developments across technical indicators, financial performance, valuation metrics, and broader market trends. This article analyses the factors influencing the current market perspective on the stock, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its recent trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>486b59f67f1b1f0e567e3d92bc720942</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Empower India’s Market Assessment Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/empower-india-stock-rating-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technical-and-fundamental-signals-3768916</link><description>Empower India, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its financial performance, valuation metrics, technical indicators, and overall quality. This article explores the factors influencing the recent changes in the company’s evaluation, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the current market stance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9b68ebf3b78a3c6ede910a9d2d8e9362</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fundviser Capital (India) Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/fundviser-capital-india-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technicals-and-flat-financials-3768917</link><description>Fundviser Capital (India), a player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has experienced a notable shift in market assessment driven by a combination of technical indicators, valuation considerations, financial trends, and broader market context. This article analyses the factors influencing the recent revision in the company’s evaluation metrics, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the current landscape.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>82292712e4d1d78d5813e276b9ef3564</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gulf-oil-lubricants-india-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-3768918</link><description>Gulf Oil Lubricants India has experienced a revision in its market assessment reflecting a complex interplay of financial performance, valuation metrics, and technical indicators. While the company maintains strong management efficiency and a solid market position within the oil sector, recent technical trends and flat quarterly results have influenced the overall evaluation of the stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>412f6d2d2302efade4c0dfecaa124c9b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khaitan (India) Stock Evaluation Reflects Mixed Signals Amidst Market and Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/khaitan-india-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-financial-concerns-3768919</link><description>Khaitan (India), a player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has undergone a revision in its market assessment following a detailed analysis of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article explores the factors influencing the recent changes in the company’s evaluation metrics, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its current standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fe80b41160d9750f944f5756ddfa4543</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virat Industries: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/virat-industries-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-3768920</link><description>Virat Industries, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed evaluation of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This reassessment reflects a nuanced view of the company’s current position amid contrasting signals from its operational performance and market behaviour.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1db9078bf501c579c2510d7855dea541</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krypton Industries Faces Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/krypton-industries-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3768911</link><description>Krypton Industries, a diversified sector player, has experienced a notable shift in market assessment driven by evolving technical indicators and a complex financial backdrop. While the company posted positive quarterly results, its longer-term fundamentals and recent price trends have presented a challenging outlook for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>462331f17af0b5f46af95693603c9752</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intense Technologies: Analytical Revision Reflects Mixed Signals Across Key Investment Parameters</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/intense-technologies-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technicals-and-weak-financials-3768913</link><description>Intense Technologies, a player in the Software Products sector, has undergone a revision in its evaluation metrics reflecting a nuanced market assessment. The recent changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators highlight a complex investment landscape for this stock amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bd0d7793a123e20fea28e44667e0f4d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>South India Paper Mills Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/south-india-paper-mills-upgraded-to-hold-on-improved-technicals-and-financial-performance-3768914</link><description>South India Paper Mills has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a complex interplay of financial performance, valuation metrics, and technical indicators. Despite recent challenges in long-term returns, the company’s latest quarterly results and evolving technical trends have influenced a fresh perspective on its investment profile.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4c40b12a95f314193aeb61a9283328f7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sayaji Hotels: Analytical Review Highlights Mixed Signals Amidst Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sayaji-hotels-stock-rating-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technical-and-financial-signals-3768912</link><description>Sayaji Hotels, a key player in the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector, has experienced a shift in market assessment driven by a complex interplay of technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and quality considerations. This article explores the factors influencing the recent revision in the company’s evaluation, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its current standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fa15fa4dcec34336638f3914f082723c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quess Corp Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/quess-corp-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-mixed-financial-and-technical-signals-3768910</link><description>Quess Corp, a key player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting nuanced changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article analyses the factors influencing the recent shift in the company’s assessment, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its current standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ef875d4b404c66579b287e5b2c1bed24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>