<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Siemens Ltd Gains 2.48%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-gains-248-7-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3827479</link><description>Siemens Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 2.48% from Rs.3,100.20 to Rs.3,177.20 between 2 and 6 February 2026, outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock showed strong intraday rallies early in the week, supported by rising open interest and technical momentum, before facing profit-taking pressures on the final trading day amid mixed market signals and a recent fundamental downgrade.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>1ce9b7fef72a4c7089695fa5fefd6bea</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jocil Ltd Gains 4.51%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jocil-ltd-gains-451-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3827478</link><description>Jocil Ltd’s stock advanced by 4.51% over the week ending 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain. The week was marked by a rebound from early losses, positive quarterly financial trends, and a valuation reset that improved the stock’s attractiveness despite lingering margin pressures and liquidity concerns.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>96769870cbfa140b5aa35d0f58d44b34</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hikal Ltd Falls 6.94% Amidst Persistent Downtrend and Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hikal-ltd-falls-694-amidst-persistent-downtrend-and-volatile-week-3827477</link><description>Hikal Ltd’s shares declined by 6.94% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.179.55, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% during the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week lows twice this week amid continued financial pressures and weak earnings, despite a brief intraday recovery on 3 February. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics shaping Hikal’s performance over the past five trading sessions.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>69efe8891d32a9c8d3f3c4c80dbd7818</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaibhav Global Ltd Gains 1.56%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaibhav-global-ltd-gains-156-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3827476</link><description>Vaibhav Global Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a modest gain of 1.56%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock exhibited notable volatility midweek, driven by a remarkable surge on 3 February that saw it hit an intraday high of Rs.270.1, propelled by strong buying interest and technical momentum. Despite some profit-taking in the latter part of the week, Vaibhav Global maintained its position above key moving averages, reflecting sustained investor attention amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>b2bf157125f985e0773691c5eba6b1b6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GMM Pfaudler Gains 2.09%: Key Technical Shifts and Q3 Losses Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gmm-pfaudler-gains-209-key-technical-shifts-and-q3-losses-shape-the-week-3827471</link><description>GMM Pfaudler Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 2.09%, closing at Rs.994.45 on 6 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The week was marked by a volatile price trajectory, technical momentum shifts, and a disappointing quarterly earnings report that wiped out the year’s gains. Despite the mixed signals, the stock demonstrated resilience relative to the broader market benchmark.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>54f8e2ded9124bb106c24cfb07226cd1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Castrol India Gains 0.62%: Quality Upgrade and Mixed Technical Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/castrol-india-gains-062-quality-upgrade-and-mixed-technical-signals-shape-the-week-3827475</link><description>Castrol India Ltd. closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a modest gain of 0.62%, rising from Rs.184.05 to Rs.185.20. This performance trailed the broader Sensex, which advanced 1.51% over the same period, reflecting a mixed market environment. The week was marked by a notable upgrade in the company’s quality rating and a nuanced shift in technical momentum, alongside steady but pressured financial results.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>222b9eab3c323c0b749ee68b6cdc5c17</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yogi Infra Projects Ltd Falls 4.57%: Financial Struggles and 52-Week Low Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yogi-infra-projects-ltd-falls-457-financial-struggles-and-52-week-low-mark-the-week-3827470</link><description>Yogi Infra Projects Ltd’s stock declined by 4.57% over the week ending 06 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.5.85 against a 1.51% gain in the Sensex. The week was marked by mounting financial distress revealed in Q3 FY26 results and the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low, reflecting sustained bearish momentum amid broader market resilience.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>3a6293a8004e8a97a722789df26ca244</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti Structures Gains 3.83%: 4 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-structures-gains-383-4-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3827474</link><description>Jyoti Structures Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a 3.83% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock showed notable volatility, including a significant gap up on 3 February and an intraday surge on 4 February, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals and evolving valuation dynamics amid cautious market sentiment.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>a8dcb908768201fa7e4317332e46955b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shilchar Technologies Gains 12.82%: 4 Key Events Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shilchar-technologies-gains-1282-4-key-events-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3827473</link><description>Shilchar Technologies Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 12.82% from Rs.3,389.95 to Rs.3,824.60 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by robust intraday rallies, a notable gap up, and mixed technical signals, reflecting a complex but positive momentum shift amid cautious market conditions.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>1c915338d8f4420fd271be421b6370d0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vimta Labs Gains 3.33%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vimta-labs-gains-333-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-volatility-3827468</link><description>Vimta Labs Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 3.33%, closing at Rs.425.05 on 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a strong gap up on 2 February, followed by mixed price action amid valuation concerns and technical caution. Despite the positive start, the stock faced selling pressure later in the week, reflecting investor hesitation amid stretched multiples and bearish technical indicators.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>5de3b482d2fa6a78e2d93a73697c2d3f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Roofing Gains 5.79%: 2 Key Upgrades Drive Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bansal-roofing-gains-579-2-key-upgrades-drive-weekly-rally-3827472</link><description>Bansal Roofing Products Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 5.79% from ₹117.50 to ₹124.30, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a notable upgrade to a 'Buy' rating by MarketsMOJO, driven by strong fundamentals, improved valuation metrics, and emerging bullish technical signals. Despite some intraday volatility, the stock demonstrated resilience and ended the week on a strong note, supported by record quarterly results and positive market sentiment.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>04e4e1f619769b2c1cc59bacff883e38</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd Declines 0.51% Amid Mixed Signals and Rising Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-declines-051-amid-mixed-signals-and-rising-derivatives-activity-3827469</link><description>Bosch Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 at ₹36,361.10, down 0.51% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹36,546.80, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by significant volatility, with the stock experiencing a sharp rise in derivatives open interest amid mixed technical momentum and a notable downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>71584169a7e5935018257d47ece2b2a2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great Eastern Shipping Gains 5.96%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/great-eastern-shipping-gains-596-4-key-factors-driving-the-momentum-3827467</link><description>Great Eastern Shipping Company Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 5.96% from Rs.1,202.35 to Rs.1,273.95 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s steady ascent was supported by a series of positive technical shifts, new 52-week highs, and strong institutional confidence, underscoring its resilience amid mixed broader market conditions.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>2465456c7ea904e72615cf893f867208</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd Gains 5.26%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-strips-wheels-ltd-gains-526-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3827464</link><description>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 5.26% from ₹204.35 to ₹215.10 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a strong gap up on 3 February, a technical upgrade to Hold, and a shift to mildly bullish momentum amid mixed technical signals. Despite some intraday volatility and cautious volume trends, the company’s valuation appeal and management efficiency supported investor confidence in a challenging auto components sector.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>4202b99a208ce6a6eaed1c0d8f79b3ef</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kilitch Drugs Surges 14.45% in a Week: Valuation Pressure and Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kilitch-drugs-surges-1445-in-a-week-valuation-pressure-and-mixed-technical-signals-3827463</link><description>Kilitch Drugs (India) Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 14.45% from Rs.311.00 to Rs.355.95 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was supported by a combination of shifting technical momentum and evolving valuation dynamics, which together shaped investor sentiment and price action throughout the week.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>01cbcd7fccc5f162ef5d2df5f1ab0d04</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murudeshwar Ceramics Gains 4.21%: Valuation Shifts Amid Strong Sell Downgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/murudeshwar-ceramics-gains-421-valuation-shifts-amid-strong-sell-downgrade-3827461</link><description>Murudeshwar Ceramics Ltd recorded a 4.21% gain over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.34.37 compared to Rs.32.98 the previous Friday. This outperformance contrasted with the BSE Sensex’s 1.51% rise, reflecting a mixed market response amid a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating and improved valuation metrics. The week featured notable volatility in sentiment, with the stock’s price reacting to both fundamental reassessments and valuation shifts.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>aba4b8d0000ad332342887d3c3cc6bea</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd Falls 2.33%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alkyl-amines-chemicals-ltd-falls-233-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3827460</link><description>Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd ended the week down 2.33%, closing at Rs.1,532.25 on 6 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The stock experienced volatile trading amid disappointing quarterly results, a downgrade in financial trend, and mixed technical signals, reflecting investor caution in the face of margin pressures and subdued demand in the specialty chemicals sector.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>2cdbbdac4ffc66bebc9d877b5e1582bf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coromandel International Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.99% Price, 1.51% Sensex Gain Tell the Story</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coromandel-international-ltds-mixed-week--099-price-151-sensex-gain-tell-the-story-3827458</link><description>Coromandel International Ltd experienced a mixed week from 2 to 6 February 2026, closing marginally lower by 0.99% at Rs.2,269.15, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The stock’s price action was influenced by significant technical developments, including the formation of a Death Cross and a shift in technical momentum, signalling a cautious outlook amid mixed market signals.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>a04888888025b15be303d8bcca4f2c6c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Gains 3.99%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hero-motocorp-gains-399-7-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-momentum-3827466</link><description>Hero MotoCorp Ltd. delivered a 3.99% gain over the week ending 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock showed strong early-week rallies, reaching intraday highs near ₹5,857, before experiencing a mild pullback amid mixed technical signals and derivative market activity. This week’s price action was shaped by a combination of robust fundamentals, shifting technical momentum, and heightened options market interest, reflecting a nuanced investor sentiment.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>f2661bcff46004556daf0aa26d7461e9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transcorp International Ltd Gains 2.04%: Key Drivers Behind the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/transcorp-international-ltd-gains-204-key-drivers-behind-the-volatile-week-3827465</link><description>Transcorp International Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a modest gain of 2.04%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock exhibited notable volatility, reaching a new 52-week high midweek before retreating in the latter sessions. Key corporate developments and technical momentum shaped the stock’s trajectory amid a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>a100b9b90a75b5554eca60c5222271df</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>