<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prabha Energy Ltd Hits Intraday High with 9.01% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prabha-energy-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-901-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820821</link><description>Prabha Energy Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging 9.01% to touch a day’s high of Rs 168, significantly outperforming the Sensex and its sector peers in the oil industry.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>6e0c111d9ebf1699c955b8692d8a9ef9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments of India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 5.81% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tube-investments-of-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-581-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820820</link><description>Tube Investments of India Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 2,625.7, marking a 5.81% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum amid a recovering Sensex.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>a868824fa644b23b54e5023b92954c1f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SPML Infra Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.33% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spml-infra-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-733-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820819</link><description>SPML Infra Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 181, marking a 7.3% gain despite opening sharply lower. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum within the construction sector.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>148776f896e24237f9d4e19c87c62faa</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Man Infraconstruction Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.03% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/man-infraconstruction-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-703-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820825</link><description>Man Infraconstruction Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging 7.03% to touch a day’s high of Rs 118, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its sector peers in the construction industry.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>4aae61098699dbaeec91f4c472dbf06b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Trading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-trading-3820823</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd (MANKIND) witnessed a significant 27.8% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This spike comes amid a volatile trading session where the stock underperformed its sector and approached its 52-week low, raising questions about directional bets and future price momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ed2556751d6421fd1b915487f4ba017b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaynes Technology India Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaynes-technology-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3820822</link><description>Kaynes Technology India Ltd (KAYNES) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, supported by rising volumes and investor interest, despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>eded045fa2d1b842c7e7e8abca124b4f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Asset Management Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-asset-management-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3820824</link><description>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd (HDFCAMC) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock has outperformed its sector peers, supported by robust volume and rising investor participation, as it continues its upward trajectory over the past three sessions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>64aee69d6413da12fae3a3cd684809b0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Weak Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-weak-price-momentum-3820818</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd (POLICYBZR) has witnessed a significant 16.3% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s ongoing downward trend. This spike in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and deteriorating price performance, suggests a complex interplay of investor positioning and potential directional bets in the financial technology sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>49089321c0edd99ad1fa39c3d92d0d4b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LTI Mindtree Ltd Sees Sharp Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lti-mindtree-ltd-sees-sharp-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-price-pressure-3820814</link><description>LTI Mindtree Ltd (LTIM) experienced a significant 25.3% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the surge in open interest, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish sentiment and speculative bets in the software consulting space.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ec81596e25ceb6f873561b78b30c2267</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge (India) Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Trading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-trading-3820816</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock trading close to its 52-week low, the spike in OI alongside elevated volumes and volatility suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and hedging strategies among market participants.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>138a58c6a3c7cab6501d490776032a09</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Ltd. Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3820810</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd., a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a notable 11.05% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.19% gain on the day, the stock’s underlying dynamics reveal a complex interplay of bullish and cautious sentiment amid broader sector weakness.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>84dc4fbecae41461e052320cfd0f0acc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3820811</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd. (TECHM) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent price decline, the stock’s open interest rose by 14.58% to 53,172 contracts, reflecting increased speculative interest and potential directional bets amid broader sector weakness.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>204e535442bb379b7dc632c6fb31a43f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solar Industries India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solar-industries-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3820817</link><description>Solar Industries India Ltd (SOLARINDS), a prominent player in the Other Chemical products sector, witnessed a significant 17.08% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 4 February 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning despite a modest decline in its share price. This development comes amid a backdrop of mixed price action and evolving volume patterns, prompting a closer examination of the underlying market dynamics and potential directional bets.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>46907044374afc24ae5d9cbcfb5d0e8f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oracle Financial Services Software Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oracle-financial-services-software-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3820809</link><description>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd (OFSS) witnessed a significant 18.3% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning despite the stock’s bearish price movement. This development comes amid a broader sector decline, raising questions about directional bets and potential volatility ahead.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>aaaa8bd7c8a983bd116a2733d361bb68</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mphasis Ltd. Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mphasis-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3820808</link><description>Mphasis Ltd., a mid-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a significant 15% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s bearish price movement. This development, coupled with increased volume and shifting investor positioning, offers critical insights into the stock’s near-term outlook amid a challenging IT sector environment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>3bff38550c1ad8020c1c75ee26ac1fb2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Star Ltd. Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-star-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-bullish-market-momentum-3820812</link><description>Blue Star Ltd. (BLUESTARCO), a key player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, witnessed a notable 10.04% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This increase accompanies a 3.74% rise in the stock price, outperforming its sector peers and reflecting growing bullish sentiment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>c4111b469b2e89268fd29862216d08ec</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wipro Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Market Conditions</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wipro-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-market-conditions-3820815</link><description>Wipro Ltd. has witnessed a significant 23.9% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This increase comes amid a backdrop of price weakness and sectoral underperformance, raising questions about the directional bets being placed on the large-cap IT giant.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b90b89b3f9b3193243f63de66a2bc31a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3820813</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. (JINDALSTEL) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock has concurrently hit a new 52-week high of Rs 1180.5, supported by robust volume and positive price action, reflecting growing investor confidence in the ferrous metals sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>3d543d70c70261ba6a39abb9e7571d48</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HCL Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hcl-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-market-moves-3820802</link><description>HCL Technologies Ltd (HCLTECH) witnessed a significant 21.3% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a 4.3% decline in the stock price, the spike in open interest alongside robust volumes suggests complex directional bets amid a volatile IT sector backdrop.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>5d7ee42ec1e292e4b3d1c450f82f0f11</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/persistent-systems-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-market-moves-3820804</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd (PERSISTENT) witnessed a significant 30.5% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s 4.7% decline on the day. This divergence between price movement and open interest suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>eb0bece5a6ce78863ac93b47ccc50237</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>