<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Excel Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.01% Surge on 5 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/excel-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-701-surge-on-5-feb-2026-3822508</link><description>Excel Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 5 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 985, marking a 7.54% increase from the previous close. This strong upward movement outpaced the broader market and its sector peers, reflecting notable trading momentum throughout the session.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>6786ff28f5a4225e86832da2838f8ca1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palash Securities Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/palash-securities-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3822506</link><description>Palash Securities Ltd’s share price has declined to a fresh 52-week low, touching an intraday low of Rs 94.2 on 5 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory within the FMCG sector.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>bcaa38ff1fe417efc2d38920bedd05f4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heranba Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.49% Surge on 5 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/heranba-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-749-surge-on-5-feb-2026-3822499</link><description>Heranba Industries Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 5 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 243.2, marking a 7.83% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and sustained buying momentum.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>7513f5db7d6d03ae4952ca92e678858f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3822500</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd, the parent company of NYKAA, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock has outperformed its sector peers and is trading near its 52-week high, reflecting growing investor confidence amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>21d634c51e61cb5ef936456b760ed121</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaynes Technology India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaynes-technology-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3822495</link><description>Kaynes Technology India Ltd (KAYNES) has witnessed a notable 11.07% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This surge accompanies a significant price correction and increased trading volumes, reflecting a complex interplay of directional bets and market sentiment within the industrial manufacturing sector.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>2557a40ff81ecfd1f83e442498b0d6e4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Weak Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-dynamics-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-weak-price-momentum-3822494</link><description>Bharat Dynamics Ltd (BDL), a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has witnessed a notable 10.2% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock's ongoing bearish momentum. This surge in OI, coupled with declining prices and subdued investor participation, paints a complex picture of market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>303c109fcfface5590c620098173f334</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFB Agro Industries Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Intense Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ifb-agro-industries-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-intense-selling-pressure-3822497</link><description>IFB Agro Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the beverages sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 5 Feb 2026 as it hit its lower circuit limit, closing at ₹1,039.8, down 4.72% on the day. The stock’s persistent downward trajectory, marked by seven consecutive days of losses, reflects mounting selling pressure and investor apprehension amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>9b372d157b52a1bea6a4fe467b36f848</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eurotex Industries Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eurotex-industries-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3822493</link><description>Eurotex Industries and Exports Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 5 Feb 2026 as it hit its lower circuit limit, closing at ₹13.64, down 4.95% from the previous close. The stock’s plunge reflects intense selling pressure and panic among investors, marking a significant underperformance relative to its sector and the broader market.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>fe357616a098c7201ee4d6a791da5a04</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-holdings-investment-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3822498</link><description>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd (BAJAJHLDNG) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, with a near 30% increase signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a positive intraday price performance, the stock faces a cautious outlook as its Mojo Grade was downgraded to Sell from Hold recently, reflecting mixed signals for traders and investors alike.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>2c7ba04002e7760d132714a0efc4a03b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biofil Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/biofil-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3822496</link><description>Shares of Biofil Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, plunged sharply to hit the lower circuit limit on 5 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors. The stock closed at ₹37.54, down 10.0% on the day, marking its maximum permissible daily loss and underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>07f95f00d47c77a00140c2f244fc8eb6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eastern Silk Industries Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eastern-silk-industries-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3822490</link><description>Eastern Silk Industries Ltd witnessed a sharp decline on 5 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit price limit of ₹71.32, marking a maximum daily loss of 5.0%. The stock faced intense selling pressure, with panic selling dominating trade and leaving a significant unfilled supply on the order books, signalling deep investor concerns amid a prolonged downtrend.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>654ca5dff426e31da0756232e3ab2d4d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maheshwari Logistics Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maheshwari-logistics-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3822484</link><description>Maheshwari Logistics Ltd witnessed a remarkable surge on 5 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit amid strong buying momentum. The stock soared by 19.93% in a single trading session, significantly outperforming its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting heightened investor interest despite a cautious market backdrop.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>195df4fb506e40b67dd93abead03f0d4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vadivarhe Speciality Chemicals Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vadivarhe-speciality-chemicals-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3822483</link><description>Vadivarhe Speciality Chemicals Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Chemicals &amp; Petrochemicals sector, surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 5 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.92%. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, resulting in a price rise to ₹22.40, the highest and closing price of the day, signalling intense demand despite the stock’s strong sell rating and regulatory trading freeze.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>713c89e84c048bba23d2c7ad56bf4290</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3822482</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results across market capitalisations and sectors, reflecting a cautious yet improving corporate performance environment. With 1,285 companies reporting, the proportion of positive results has risen to 48.0%, marking a steady improvement from the previous three quarters and signalling tentative optimism among Indian corporates.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>476276c54405d14041896fc5118afb3d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Thai Securities Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-thai-securities-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3822489</link><description>Indo Thai Securities Ltd witnessed a significant surge on 5 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 4.99% gain to close at ₹269.41. The stock demonstrated strong buying momentum, outperforming its sector and broader market indices, signalling heightened investor interest despite a recent downgrade in its mojo grade.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>4a33a9548e011b2a67e5eb954864f49c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cummins India Ltd Sees Surge in Call Option Activity Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cummins-india-ltd-sees-surge-in-call-option-activity-amid-bullish-momentum-3822491</link><description>Cummins India Ltd. has emerged as the most actively traded stock in the call options segment, signalling heightened bullish sentiment among investors. With the underlying stock price hovering around Rs 4,367 and a significant volume of call contracts expiring on 24 February 2026, market participants appear confident in the company’s near-term upside potential despite recent volatility.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>72cd321e4b5ce035239ac5c27a61165d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Ltd. Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lupin-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3822487</link><description>Lupin Ltd., a leading player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock recently hit a new 52-week high of Rs 2,240, supported by robust volume and positive price momentum, reflecting growing investor confidence despite a backdrop of subdued sectoral and benchmark indices.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>6e4289e2303c50fc90a3c4a6110b2796</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cummins India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cummins-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-mixed-price-action-3822492</link><description>Cummins India Ltd. (CUMMINSIND) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a volatile intraday price movement, the stock has outperformed its sector and the broader market, prompting a closer examination of volume patterns, open interest changes, and potential directional bets shaping its near-term outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>b5478c2f16b712c86ad83c47e74294f2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Visa Steel Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/visa-steel-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3822488</link><description>Visa Steel Ltd, a micro-cap player in the ferrous metals sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 5 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit of Rs 37.94, marking a maximum daily loss of 4.98%. The stock’s plunge reflects intense selling pressure and panic among investors, with volumes concentrated near the day’s low and a notable drop in delivery volumes signalling waning investor confidence.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>bc3223086d98987b7112166179ff395c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-market-sentiment-3822486</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd (RELIANCE), a dominant player in the oil sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 5 February 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹52,866 lakhs. Despite this high turnover, the stock underperformed its sector and the broader Sensex, reflecting a cautious investor sentiment amid mixed technical signals and declining delivery volumes.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>19ced5c7ee72c6f6fbaef29c2e3b3af6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>