<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Paramount Communications Hits Intraday High with Strong 7.62% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paramount-communications-hits-intraday-high-with-762-surge-on-24-dec-2025-3768283</link><description>Paramount Communications recorded a robust intraday performance on 24 Dec 2025, touching a day’s high of ₹38.43, reflecting a 7.62% rise. This surge outpaced the broader sector and market indices, marking a notable trading session for the electrical cables company.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>c3473f6f09a6d4a6085445163f363fb3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sarthak Metals Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.84.02 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sarthak-metals-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs8402-amidst-continued-downtrend-3768281</link><description>Sarthak Metals, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.84.02, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a challenging period for the company’s shares.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>c957d0d039bc06d222c9e204e4e7c49c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Granito India Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.76.93</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asian-granito-india-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs7693-3768282</link><description>Asian Granito India has reached a significant milestone by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.76.93, reflecting notable momentum in the stock’s performance within the diversified consumer products sector.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>b447b335cb6907986d8b2139f1906432</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simplex Infrastructures Hits Intraday High with Strong Trading Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/simplex-infrastructures-hits-intraday-high-with-706-surge-on-24-dec-2025-3768280</link><description>Simplex Infrastructures recorded a robust intraday performance today, touching a high of Rs 284.15, reflecting a 9.35% rise during the session. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, demonstrating notable volatility and trading activity in the construction sector.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>d407111b98ca34b41901d80da64de523</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvama Wealth Management Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvama-wealth-management-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3768278</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd has registered a notable surge in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development coincides with the stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and broader indices, signalling increased participation and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>17d5f7da427d7d40741ad532186c774c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768276</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd has registered a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite a modest decline in its share price. The pharmaceutical giant's recent trading patterns reveal shifts in investor positioning and volume dynamics that merit close attention from market participants.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>a1494f13b12135b0abcbbdd1c7bc0b18</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lodha-developers-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768274</link><description>Lodha Developers Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This development comes as the stock trades close to its 52-week low, with volume and price patterns suggesting a cautious but active market stance in the realty sector.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>e5c67dc4423101ff1d06393da7800913</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768275</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has registered a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. This development comes alongside a modest price movement and evolving volume patterns, offering insights into potential directional bets and liquidity dynamics.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>210b7162cac020e752a8345b29bd77e1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalyan-jewellers-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768277</link><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite a slight decline in the stock price, the surge in open interest and volume patterns suggest a complex interplay of directional bets and market sentiment within the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>ca088f58838b65fe13c4e77355d2ef6b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-steady-price-gains-3768272</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning and investor interest. This development coincides with the stock trading near its 52-week high and maintaining momentum in a sector that has shown steady performance.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>b23ab070e8eea9077e56c65d3ec3c496</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Polycab India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Steady Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/polycab-india-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3768273</link><description>Polycab India has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning as the stock continues to trade near its 52-week high. This development, coupled with steady volume patterns and price action, offers insights into the evolving sentiment around the electrical cables sector.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>e58772dc4794268cf8f158ee24b8de13</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PNB Housing Finance Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pnb-housing-finance-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3768270</link><description>PNB Housing Finance has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and evolving positioning among traders. This development coincides with the stock outperforming its sector peers and trading above key moving averages, signalling a shift in investor sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>c8be6f8e3457251dda103400e308a793</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-lombard-sees-notable-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-mixed-price-action-3768271</link><description>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price movement and narrowing trading ranges, prompting a closer examination of volume patterns and potential directional bets in the stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>26511a732ba42ea639494feb4671572c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varun Beverages Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varun-beverages-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768269</link><description>Varun Beverages Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price performance and shifting volume dynamics, offering insights into potential directional bets and market sentiment within the beverages sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>44b99af55d23bd1bcbf06823442de470</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-prudential-life-insurance-sees-notable-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768268</link><description>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of mixed price performance and shifting volume patterns, offering insights into potential directional bets by market participants.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>a895a8196744ce6f5903726270fc5f1c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3768267</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries has registered a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning and investor sentiment. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price performance and shifting volume dynamics, offering insights into potential directional bets and trading strategies in the pharmaceutical sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>620ad4ad54a0494bda37092417f8dd11</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge (India) Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768266</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market engagement and evolving positioning among traders. This development coincides with a period of steady price movement and shifting volume patterns, offering insights into potential directional bets and investor sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>d10083baaa3e06741d9b576fdeb781e1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3768265</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price performance and shifting volume patterns, prompting closer scrutiny of potential directional bets in the stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>41557b3d4b4c70a931a9fffad81433a9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Sees Notable Surge in Open Interest Amidst Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedanta-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3768264</link><description>Vedanta Ltd., a key player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has experienced a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a sustained upward price trend. This development reflects evolving market positioning and investor interest, warranting a closer examination of volume patterns and potential directional bets shaping the stock’s near-term outlook.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>4f268620892b68f12ad0a52009e542e4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of India Sees Notable Surge in Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-india-sees-notable-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-mixed-price-action-3768263</link><description>Bank Of India has experienced a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning despite recent price softness. This development comes amid subdued investor participation and a backdrop of mixed technical signals, prompting closer scrutiny of potential directional bets and liquidity dynamics.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>14cc026e4e0c9588c5f1ec41de7ea9f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>