<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Ipca Labs Added to Mojo Stocks Amid Strong Financial Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/ipca-labs-added-to-mojo-stocks-amid-strong-financial-momentum-3792284</link><description>Ipca Labs, a mid-cap pharmaceutical company, has been added to the prestigious Mojo Stocks list as of 14 January 2026, reflecting its robust financial performance and bullish momentum. The stock’s recent surge in key metrics and operational efficiency positions it favourably within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, making it a compelling addition for investors seeking growth with solid fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4409e1dfe0a306b6f65805401f11c438</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Quicktouch Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-quicktouch-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792278</link><description>Quicktouch Technologies Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are poor, showing a net loss of ₹3.24 crores and a dramatic 99.96% drop in net sales, indicating severe operational challenges and a lack of revenue. The company's financial health is concerning, with negative operating margins and significant declines in stock performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0decaa92578b83f9ca3553022eb1be0b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Union Bank of India latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-union-bank-of-india-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792277</link><description>Union Bank of India's latest Q2 FY26 results show a net profit of ₹4,249 crore, up 3.25% quarter-on-quarter but down 9.97% year-on-year. While the bank has improved asset quality with reduced NPAs, it faces challenges with compressed net interest margins amid competitive pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>04f6155b921a06dd1a39319d739da10d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Raghav Productivity Enhancers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-raghav-productivity-enhancers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792276</link><description>Raghav Productivity Enhancers Ltd's latest results are positive, showing a 17.17% increase in net sales to ₹64.49 crores and a 43.93% rise in net profit to ₹14.12 crores for Q3 FY26, alongside strong margins and a solid financial position. Despite recent stock consolidation, the company demonstrates robust operational performance and growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c18b70c03c9ad8cdc9cee0ec0b80c2b3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-hdfc-asset-management-company-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792275</link><description>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd's latest results are strong, with a net profit of ₹769.42 crores, reflecting a 19.97% year-on-year growth, despite a recent stock decline of 8.67% due to market concerns. Overall, the company demonstrates robust operational performance and profitability, but investors should remain cautious about market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>607da34156a1d217624fdb38c9581930</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tata Elxsi Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tata-elxsi-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792274</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd.'s latest Q3 FY26 results show record revenue growth of 1.52% to ₹953.47 crore, but a significant net profit decline of 45.28% to ₹180.13 crore raises concerns about profitability and operational challenges. The company's underperformance relative to the market and high valuation metrics suggest caution for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>80a380fa1d64465848237abb884cf260</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Hathway Bhawani Cabletel &amp; Datacom Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-hathway-bhawani-cabletel-datacom-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792273</link><description>Hathway Bhawani Cabletel &amp; Datacom Ltd's latest results show declining revenues with net sales down 3.33% quarter-on-quarter, but a slight profit turnaround to ₹0.03 crores indicates improved cost management. Overall, the company faces ongoing challenges in the traditional cable market, suggesting cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>556e08ac1892f74c557416ff23730a3c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Plastiblends India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-plastiblends-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792272</link><description>Plastiblends India Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 3.54% decline in net sales and a 13.04% drop in net profit, alongside the lowest operating margins in eight quarters, indicating ongoing challenges in profitability and operational efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1e5b4a58685af43d1e7bdc37264411d3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tokyo Plast International Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tokyo-plast-international-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792271</link><description>Tokyo Plast International Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹0.13 crores compared to a profit last year, with revenues down 18.73% from the previous quarter and significant increases in interest expenses, indicating ongoing operational challenges and low profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>56612fb67debd1140020478a366f2f6c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indian Overseas Bank latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indian-overseas-bank-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792270</link><description>Indian Overseas Bank's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit of ₹1,226.42 crores (up 57.81% year-on-year) and improved asset quality, as evidenced by a gross NPA ratio of 1.83%. However, the stock has underperformed in the market, declining 33.32% over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2db5082dcf0b036e453ea4b20bb95548</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indosolar Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indosolar-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792269</link><description>Indosolar Ltd's latest results show a significant operational turnaround with a net profit of ₹46.34 crores, up 388.82% year-on-year, despite a sequential decline due to prior tax benefits. While revenue growth is strong at 620.82%, concerns about high valuation metrics suggest investors should watch for sustainable performance moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6ccdf15cad911e381f5eff61dd7a1b3e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Just Dial Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-just-dial-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792268</link><description>Just Dial Ltd.'s latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 13.23% to ₹305.69 crores and a record operating margin of 31.16%, but a significant 19.44% decline in net profit raises concerns about earnings sustainability. While the company has a strong balance sheet, its below-average return on equity and reliance on other income complicate the overall assessment of its financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6bd13cfd5e0a4eb6c944eb4de0c12bb1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indbank-merchant-banking-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792267</link><description>Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd's latest results show a net profit increase of 64.10% year-on-year to ₹1.92 crores, but revenue declined slightly by 0.48% sequentially, raising concerns about operating efficiency and competitive positioning despite a strong return on capital employed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8214d61b501023e25c8f64d28e4ed8f1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rama Phosphates Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rama-phosphates-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792266</link><description>Rama Phosphates Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a mixed performance, with a 3.12% sequential decline in net sales but a strong 32.50% year-on-year increase. While net profit fell 18.80% from the previous quarter due to higher costs, the company maintains a solid long-term growth outlook and operational efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>21dd4b9b4313b8088c81c5dbfa131ba6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Infosys Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-infosys-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3792265</link><description>Infosys Ltd's latest results show mixed performance: while net sales grew by 2.22% sequentially and 8.90% year-on-year, net profit declined by 9.64% sequentially due to margin pressures and rising costs. The company maintains strong capital efficiency and a solid balance sheet, but faces challenges in profitability management.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6709e22cc7601f16d455b620e424a6df</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BITS Ltd Q2 FY26: Profitability Surge Masks Deep Structural Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bits-ltd-q2-fy26-profitability-surge-masks-deep-structural-concerns-3792283</link><description>BITS Ltd., a micro-cap software products company with a market capitalisation of ₹111.00 crores, reported consolidated net profit of ₹0.11 crores for Q2 FY26, representing a remarkable 450.00% year-on-year surge from ₹0.02 crores in Q2 FY25. However, this impressive profitability growth belies deeper structural challenges, as the stock has plunged 49.60% over the past year, vastly underperforming the Sensex's 9.00% gain. Trading at ₹10.20 following a 4.94% single-day gain, the shares remain 52.11% below their 52-week high of ₹21.30, reflecting persistent investor scepticism about the company's long-term prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cb6e07165d165348071e05ba1ffc496c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>International Travel House Q2 FY26: Profit Plunges 14% Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/international-travel-house-q2-fy26-profit-plunges-14-despite-revenue-growth-3792282</link><description>International Travel House Limited, a part of the ITC Hotels Group, reported a disappointing second quarter for FY2026, with net profit declining 14.00% quarter-on-quarter to ₹6.39 crores despite modest revenue growth. The travel services company's shares closed at ₹378.55 on January 14, 2026, reflecting a 2.91% gain on the day but remaining under significant pressure with a 41.33% decline over the past year. With a modest market capitalisation of ₹301.00 crores, the company's results reveal persistent margin compression and operational challenges that have weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>221d40fe41e9dc0ec0d004f06bc3a115</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teamo Productions HQ Ltd: Micro-Cap Construction Stock Faces Severe Headwinds Despite Recent Quarterly Profit</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/teamo-productions-hq-ltd-micro-cap-construction-stock-faces-severe-headwinds-despite-recent-quarterly-profit-3792281</link><description>Teamo Productions HQ Ltd. (NSE: TPHQ), a micro-cap construction company with a market capitalisation of ₹70.00 crores, continues to struggle under the weight of deteriorating fundamentals and collapsing investor confidence. Trading at ₹0.62 as of January 14, 2026, the stock has plunged 72.32% over the past year, vastly underperforming both the Sensex's 9.00% gain and the construction sector's 22.87% decline. With a proprietary Mojo Score of just 23 out of 100 and a "STRONG SELL" rating, the company presents a cautionary tale of operational challenges, weak profitability metrics, and alarming technical deterioration that warrant immediate attention from existing shareholders.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ec223174339b43b8c102792f572a1ae1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal-Mogul Goetze Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/federal-mogul-goetze-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792257</link><description>Federal-Mogul Goetze (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors should carefully analyse the implications of this event amid the company’s current financial and market performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1b2ecd6a1be62ff6cb14155d45062394</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792247</link><description>Inox India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's long-term strength amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b9d3a9fb90683bf397ef7101da2627dc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>