<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3841219</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results across market capitalisation segments and sectors, as 3,956 companies declared their financials. While the proportion of companies reporting positive results has inched up slightly to 46.0%, the overall trend remains subdued compared to the previous quarter, reflecting ongoing challenges in the broader economy and sector-specific headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>38e59779025d9edbaabdef327bf3dfae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paragon Finance Ltd Gains 10.33%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paragon-finance-ltd-gains-1033-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3841217</link><description>Paragon Finance Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 10.33% from ₹45.32 to ₹50.00 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of valuation shifts, quarterly financial results, and an upgrade in analyst ratings, all contributing to the stock’s volatile yet upward trajectory amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>c99810e41e9f3452670daae938c5cc94</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Repro India Ltd Gains 15.74%: Key Technical Shifts and Q3 Profitability Spark Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/repro-india-ltd-gains-1574-key-technical-shifts-and-q3-profitability-spark-rally-3841216</link><description>Repro India Ltd. delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 15.74% from ₹412.30 to ₹477.20 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable technical momentum shift and a return to profitability in Q3 FY26, which together catalysed the sharp price appreciation despite broader market weakness.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>7147c195d0ba01e1f4a4f454efd69e88</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ircon International’s Mixed Week: -0.20% Price Change Amid Profit Concerns and Technical Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ircon-internationals-mixed-week--020-price-change-amid-profit-concerns-and-technical-headwinds-3841214</link><description>Ircon International Ltd’s stock closed the week marginally lower by 0.20% at Rs.152.95, slightly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp profit decline reported on 11 Feb and subsequent technical headwinds that weighed on investor sentiment, resulting in a volatile trading range and cautious market stance.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>162bbe59b6f0cbe9b9da11343b05c0ba</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Praj Industries Gains 8.38%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/praj-industries-gains-838-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3841215</link><description>Praj Industries Ltd delivered a volatile but ultimately positive week, closing at Rs.309.15 on 13 February 2026, up 8.38% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.285.25. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period, reflecting a week of sharp intraday swings, strong institutional interest, valuation concerns, and operational challenges that shaped investor sentiment.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>62897d759bdd955a6c1f440099a9ec27</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panth Infinity Ltd Edges Lower by 0.22%: 2 Key Factors Shaping This Week’s Movement</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/panth-infinity-ltd-edges-lower-by-022-2-key-factors-shaping-this-weeks-movement-3841213</link><description>Panth Infinity Ltd closed the week marginally lower by 0.22% at Rs.8.89, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54%. The week was marked by a significant upgrade to a Buy rating on 9 February, driven by strong financial results and improved technical indicators, followed by a mixed reaction to the company’s Q2 FY26 earnings report. Despite volatility, the stock demonstrated resilience with notable intraday gains and a sharp rebound midweek.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>689aa771db6b7fc7b3c6a2a296f845f2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Investments &amp; Commercials Ltd Gains 1.05%: Key Milestones and Market Dynamics This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/welspun-investments-commercials-ltd-gains-105-key-milestones-and-market-dynamics-this-week-3841204</link><description>Welspun Investments &amp; Commercials Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.05% from Rs.1,286.55 to Rs.1,300.00 between 9 and 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by a new 52-week and all-time high on 13 February, despite some volatility and a sharp intraday decline on the final trading day. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s trajectory during the week.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>ea905bf1f050a4e1c87f7f6c80b9d3d0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympia Industries Declines 1.80% Amid 52-Week Low and Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/olympia-industries-declines-180-amid-52-week-low-and-margin-pressures-3841206</link><description>Olympia Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 1.80% from Rs.31.11 to Rs.30.55, underperforming the Sensex which fell by 0.54%. Despite early gains on Monday and Tuesday, the stock faced selling pressure midweek, culminating in a steady downtrend amid fresh 52-week lows and mixed quarterly results.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>94d061053b3fb48fa2e2633f565ac6f4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ASM Technologies Ltd Gains 9.15%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asm-technologies-ltd-gains-915-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3841211</link><description>ASM Technologies Ltd recorded a robust weekly gain of 9.15%, closing at Rs.2,771.40 on 13 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s strong performance was driven by a combination of technical developments and valuation shifts that shaped investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>5a50f6c42b1f2bc2444ad3bda01fb103</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seasons Textiles Gains 1.41%: Valuation Shift and Mixed Weekly Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/seasons-textiles-gains-141-valuation-shift-and-mixed-weekly-signals-3841207</link><description>Seasons Textiles Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.41%, closing at Rs.18.00 on 13 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable valuation shift to very attractive levels amid persistent revenue pressures and cautious market sentiment, reflected in a strong sell mojo grade. Daily price movements showed initial strength followed by a late-week pullback, correlating with key corporate developments and market dynamics.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>da8973ca99329ac8f222dbabab12207a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Graphite India Gains 4.71%: Quarterly Turnaround and Market Resilience Highlight Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/graphite-india-gains-471-quarterly-turnaround-and-market-resilience-highlight-week-3841212</link><description>Graphite India Ltd. delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 4.71% from ₹619.20 to ₹648.35, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s gains were supported by a strong quarterly earnings report on 9 February and a subsequent upgrade in mojo grade, despite some operational challenges highlighted during the week.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>3f3f84b5c0337cf73736b8af0c84c0a0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVV Infra Ltd’s Subtle Decline of 0.58% Masks Strong Financial Upgrades</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pvv-infra-ltds-subtle-decline-of-058-masks-strong-financial-upgrades-3841210</link><description>PVV Infra Ltd experienced a mixed week from 9 to 13 February 2026, closing marginally lower by 0.58% at Rs.5.16, slightly underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54%. The week was marked by a strong quarterly earnings turnaround, an upgrade to a Strong Buy rating, and notable shifts in valuation and quality grades, reflecting both optimism and caution among investors.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>9d0cf261173b34a00941760423bed9b2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shree Ajit Pulp Gains 5.60%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shree-ajit-pulp-gains-560-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3841209</link><description>Shree Ajit Pulp and Paper Ltd delivered a robust performance this week, with its stock rising 5.60% from ₹232.15 to ₹245.15, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a stellar quarterly profit surge, an upgrade in valuation attractiveness, and a strong Mojo Score upgrade, all contributing to positive investor sentiment despite some late-week profit-taking.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>860f8231836c80fa97e6955aa5066656</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITL Industries Surges 18.07% Amid Quality Downgrade and Mixed Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/itl-industries-surges-1807-amid-quality-downgrade-and-mixed-fundamentals-3841208</link><description>ITL Industries Ltd surged 18.07% over the week ending 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% during the same period. The stock’s rally was fuelled by a strong Q3 result announcement, followed by a sharp downgrade in quality grade and rating to Strong Sell, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid fundamental concerns. Despite the price gains, underlying operational challenges and valuation questions remain key themes shaping the stock’s trajectory.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>3d68288bdd34548264071daea788c865</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Union Bank Declines 2.94%: Technical Shift and Valuation Concerns Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-union-bank-declines-294-technical-shift-and-valuation-concerns-shape-week-3841205</link><description>City Union Bank Ltd. experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its share price declining by 2.94% to close at ₹284.40, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Hold rating amid mixed technical signals and valuation concerns, which weighed on investor sentiment despite the bank’s strong financial fundamentals and long-term growth record.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>030a260b098bfa480c840691a33ec5f9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hemang Resources Ltd Falls 8.95%: Financial Struggles and Market Pressure Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hemang-resources-ltd-falls-895-financial-struggles-and-market-pressure-weigh-3841203</link><description>Hemang Resources Ltd’s stock declined sharply by 8.95% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.13.84 compared to Rs.15.20 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% decline, highlighting company-specific pressures amid broader market fluctuations. Key events including a zero revenue quarter and a fresh 52-week low weighed heavily on investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>b7ee481f54d19124ba15bcfe6d9a6331</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texmo Pipes Gains 6.61%: Technical Boost Counters Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/texmo-pipes-gains-661-technical-boost-counters-profitability-concerns-3841202</link><description>Texmo Pipes &amp; Products Ltd recorded a notable weekly gain of 6.61%, closing at Rs.49.82 on 13 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s rally was driven primarily by technical improvements and a strong quarterly result, despite ongoing fundamental concerns and mixed market sentiment.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>d56b5f206fec8802a49a299a9319c560</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd. Edges Down 0.47% Despite New Highs: 4 Key Developments This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karur-vysya-bank-ltd-edges-down-047-despite-new-highs-4-key-developments-this-week-3841201</link><description>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd. closed the week marginally lower by 0.47% at Rs.316.20, underperforming slightly against the Sensex which fell 0.54%. The week began with the stock hitting new 52-week and all-time highs, reflecting strong momentum and robust fundamentals. However, the latter half saw a gradual pullback amid broader market weakness and increased volatility, culminating in a cautious close for the week.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>93fe4f82171799c8af79073641cf8308</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Niyogin Fintech Ltd’s Volatile Week: -1.25% Amid Mixed Technical and Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/niyogin-fintech-ltds-volatile-week--125-amid-mixed-technical-and-financial-signals-3841200</link><description>Niyogin Fintech Ltd closed the week ending 13 February 2026 at Rs.44.95, down 1.25% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.45.52. This underperformance came despite the broader Sensex falling only 0.54% over the same period, highlighting a challenging week for the NBFC stock amid deteriorating financial results and shifting technical momentum.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>ed7e7fa6630b69e2ef83fad51602ad6d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Petrochem Ltd Declines 3.17%: Margin Pressures and 52-Week Low Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/panama-petrochem-ltd-declines-317-margin-pressures-and-52-week-low-mark-the-week-3841199</link><description>Panama Petrochem Ltd experienced a difficult week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its share price declining 3.17% to close at Rs.290.25, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp drop to a 52-week low, flat quarterly results amid margin pressures, and a downgrade to a Sell rating, reflecting growing concerns about profitability and capital efficiency in a challenging oil sector environment.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>7897d71cbeb837bf3b956fbb0411a2ae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>