<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/concord-enviro-systems-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3859698</link><description>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.307.45, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial health and market standing.
Time: 35 minutes ago</description><guid>e04b81380791bbdaf985f17964493ea8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dam Capital Advisors Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dam-capital-advisors-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3859694</link><description>Dam Capital Advisors Ltd has recorded a new all-time low price of Rs.149.35, marking a significant decline amid sustained underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers. The stock’s recent trajectory reflects a challenging period for the company within the capital markets sector, with multiple financial indicators signalling a cautious outlook.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>18731c6ab17955fd507cbb01f09599b1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/odigma-consultancy-solutions-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3859697</link><description>Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.25.51 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. Despite a modest 1.40% gain in the latest session, the stock remains deeply entrenched in a downward trajectory, reflecting persistent financial and market pressures.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>e18b187115d4d6c9e1b70792d4419627</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Enviro Infra Engineers Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/enviro-infra-engineers-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3859699</link><description>Enviro Infra Engineers Ltd has reached an all-time low in its stock price, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers. The stock closed just 0.54% above its 52-week low of ₹158, marking a significant milestone in its downward trajectory amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>28b852c951ad31a1839539e6aa97bf0d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/afcons-infrastructure-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3859696</link><description>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd’s shares plunged to a new all-time low of Rs. 292.75 on 27 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in a sustained period of decline. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices consistently, reflecting ongoing pressures within the construction industry and company-specific financial strains.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>d5cf8cdd9052a8244679a9d10cb9f3a2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stanley-lifestyles-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3859695</link><description>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd, a key player in the Furniture and Home Furnishing sector, has reached a new all-time low price of Rs.161, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind broader market indices and sector peers, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial health and market valuation.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>9171962b1476581d0900266f9f10adbe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adtech Systems Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adtech-systems-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3859688</link><description>Adtech Systems Ltd, a player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has reached a new all-time low price of Rs.51, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent difficulties in maintaining growth and profitability.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>783b680da5e82d41640d87c08a12062a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cello World Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cello-world-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3859686</link><description>Cello World Ltd, a key player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recorded a new all-time low share price of Rs.410.35, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing market decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects sustained pressures, with notable underperformance against benchmark indices and sector peers.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>3f9269b730421741d0a9a5ce93f75394</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plaza Wires Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/plaza-wires-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3859687</link><description>Plaza Wires Ltd, a player in the Cables - Electricals sector, has reached a new all-time low price of Rs.34, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. Despite some recent positive quarterly results, the stock continues to reflect a challenging market position with sustained underperformance relative to benchmarks and peers.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>8cb9e6da483c7dc81de5b46796bfb281</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Keystone Realtors Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/keystone-realtors-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3859691</link><description>Keystone Realtors Ltd has reached a new all-time low price of Rs.400.45, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance and financial strain.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>72bf695a1a70fba655d92dc8cd265b03</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedant Fashions Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedant-fashions-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-underperformance-3859685</link><description>Vedant Fashions Ltd has reached an all-time low, closing just 0.36% above its 52-week low of ₹398.3, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>ab633ff12e43a71c6a672690c44b48a1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Go Fashion (India) Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/go-fashion-india-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3859693</link><description>Shares of Go Fashion (India) Ltd plunged to a new all-time low of Rs.299 on 27 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s extended period of decline. The garment and apparel company’s stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices consistently, reflecting a challenging market environment and subdued financial performance.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>aafa86f9b0368f94e0b066871bf83732</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sula Vineyards Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sula-vineyards-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3859690</link><description>Sula Vineyards Ltd, a key player in the Indian beverages sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.170, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. Despite a slight uptick today, the stock remains under considerable pressure, reflecting persistent challenges in both its financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>2ebc35f59ed80187e88a0d38532d7b30</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreamfolks Services Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dreamfolks-services-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3859689</link><description>Dreamfolks Services Ltd, a key player in the Transport Infrastructure sector, has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.80.62, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting sustained pressures on the company’s financial metrics and market valuation.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>193a8a38c80ac9db70cf9f9b499dd8c7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs. 25,675.85</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs-2567585-3859692</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high of Rs.25,675.85 today, marking a remarkable phase in the company’s market journey. This achievement reflects the company’s robust performance across multiple financial metrics and sustained investor confidence over recent periods.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>99d8b3cf2854af6750050f5b5b84c22e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G G Engineering Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-g-engineering-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3859684</link><description>Shares of G G Engineering Ltd, a player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, have declined to a new all-time low of Rs.0.48, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s extended downward trajectory. This development reflects ongoing pressures on the company’s financial performance and market valuation amid a challenging industry backdrop.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>0d24cd68dab1c1d529a743f6659b76fe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.1025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pashupati-cotspin-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs1025-3859679</link><description>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd has reached an all-time high of Rs.1025 today, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and marking a key milestone in the company’s market journey. This achievement comes amid sustained gains and notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>613654f05cb5c3737da16c98aa257402</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agribio Spirits Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High on 27 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/agribio-spirits-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-on-27-feb-2026-3859674</link><description>Agribio Spirits Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high, reflecting a sustained period of robust performance and market confidence. The stock’s recent surge underscores its strong positioning within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, marking a notable achievement in its trading history.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>047e5ebfce283e8fce4fdf8d7f50f0fd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gala Global Products Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gala-global-products-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3859675</link><description>Gala Global Products Ltd has reached an all-time low, closing just 1.43% above its 52-week low of ₹1.38, reflecting a sustained decline that has seen the stock underperform its sector and benchmark indices significantly over multiple time frames.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>8eccc3b818f88de8d866e03855258abd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishal Mega Mart Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 27 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vishal-mega-mart-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-27-feb-2026-3859676</link><description>Shares of Vishal Mega Mart Ltd experienced significant intraday weakness on 27 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 117.8, reflecting a sharp price correction amid broader market pressures and heightened volatility in the diversified retail sector.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>a7ca16c7548dafd40db553d417f08741</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>