<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Ltd Hits Intraday High with 10.38% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sky-gold-diamonds-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1038-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828769</link><description>Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 09 Feb 2026, surging 10.38% to touch a day’s high of Rs 342, significantly outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>0fc7ec44d4a44b8f8c57700c88adcb45</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dynamic Cables Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.11% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dynamic-cables-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-711-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828766</link><description>Dynamic Cables Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging 7.11% to touch a day’s high of Rs 318.45. This marked a notable rebound after two consecutive days of decline, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its sector peers.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>1caef957d803c43559c546d86163c447</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carborundum Universal Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.25% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/carborundum-universal-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-725-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828768</link><description>Carborundum Universal Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance today, surging to a high of Rs 824, marking a 7.3% increase and outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>ea96d59ec27199b306243707c16a5575</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genesys International Corporation Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.08% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/genesys-international-corporation-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-708-surge-3828765</link><description>Genesys International Corporation Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 322.7, marking a 7.19% increase from its previous close. This sharp rise outpaced the broader Sensex gain of 0.55%, reflecting a notable rebound after two consecutive days of decline.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>2a4d845f513dbd4219ba99ea0909e0c6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.7% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shriram-finance-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-37-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828767</link><description>Shriram Finance Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 9 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of ₹1,036.8, marking a 3.43% rise and closing the day with a 3.7% gain. This performance notably outpaced the broader Sensex, which advanced by 0.55% during the session.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>782fd2a6c06ee940e816951d51a8ecd3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Ltd. Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3828762</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd., a prominent player in the Indian automobile sector, has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high stock price, reflecting a sustained period of strong performance and investor confidence. The stock closed just 0.29% shy of its 52-week high of ₹205.2, marking a new peak in its trading history.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>026e16df3489a3a64dc561ac51539c51</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motisons Jewellers Ltd Hits Intraday High with 10.93% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motisons-jewellers-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1093-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828759</link><description>Motisons Jewellers Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 09 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 14.81, marking a significant 10.93% increase. This sharp rise outpaced the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector by 6.99%, reflecting notable trading momentum and volatility in the stock.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>0a8b6b1f4a3f23b41d68f3c37b439a73</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishna Institute of Medical Sciences Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.81% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishna-institute-of-medical-sciences-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-781-surge-3828758</link><description>Krishna Institute of Medical Sciences Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 638, marking a 7.24% increase. This strong rebound follows three consecutive days of decline, signalling a notable shift in trading momentum within the hospital sector.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>f410d8114a37233d45b261bf7e2bf3e8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JFL Life Sciences Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jfl-life-sciences-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3828749</link><description>JFL Life Sciences Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 9 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.57%. This sharp price movement was driven by robust buying interest, resulting in a regulatory freeze on further trading and signalling strong unfilled demand for the stock.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>7e8a646d30ac6a7964618a6053ff6801</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mcleod Russel India Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mcleod-russel-india-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3828751</link><description>Mcleod Russel India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, surged sharply on 9 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a robust 9.47% gain. The stock’s strong buying momentum, coupled with a significant increase in traded volumes and a regulatory freeze on further trading, has drawn investor attention despite its current 'Strong Sell' rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>bbb7432e5ef6bc74dfae69900d03ba1d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tainwala Chemicals &amp; Plastics Surges to Upper Circuit on Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tainwala-chemicals-plastics-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-strong-buying-pressure-3828756</link><description>Tainwala Chemicals &amp; Plastics (India) Ltd witnessed a remarkable rally on 9 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with an 18.41% gain, driven by strong buying momentum and significant unfilled demand. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, signalling renewed investor interest despite its micro-cap status and recent negative analyst sentiment.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>7f943fce9d210baa8fbaca5a791c92ed</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tera Software Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tera-software-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3828748</link><description>Tera Software Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 9 February 2026, propelled by strong investor demand and sustained buying momentum. The stock closed at ₹448.90, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.99%, significantly outperforming both its sector and the broader Sensex indices.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>d6fa5a36299bf0948555b07480160b5e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Faze Three Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/faze-three-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3828757</link><description>Faze Three Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 09 Feb 2026, closing at ₹569.55 with a robust 9.99% gain. The stock’s sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, outpacing sector and benchmark indices, signalling renewed investor confidence despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>b3142f5ec89402b2ed31b4a46dba7993</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Engineering Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-engineering-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3828755</link><description>Supreme Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 9 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit price limit of ₹1.21. The stock plunged by 4.72% in a single session, underperforming its sector and the broader market amid intense selling pressure and panic among investors.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>4b5070db12c03eb35a3b0ffd279f1588</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel Sees Heavy Put Option Activity Amid Bearish Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharti-airtel-sees-heavy-put-option-activity-amid-bearish-sentiment-3828754</link><description>Bharti Airtel Ltd, a leading player in the Indian telecom sector, has witnessed a notable spike in put option trading ahead of the 24 February 2026 expiry, signalling increased bearish positioning and hedging activity among investors. Despite the stock’s underlying value hovering near ₹2,033, the surge in put contracts at the ₹2,000 strike price reflects growing caution in the market amid mixed technical signals and sector underperformance.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>439da29eba62e22b5c6452016ec7cda1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Venus Remedies Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/venus-remedies-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3828750</link><description>Venus Remedies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 9 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit and closing sharply down by 1.72% at ₹721.85. The stock’s seven-day losing streak extended further, reflecting mounting investor concerns amid a broader sector outperformance.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>f92c4c5cbad17c63bc021ad8136cac54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Ltd Sees Surge in Call Option Activity Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-steel-ltd-sees-surge-in-call-option-activity-amid-bullish-momentum-3828753</link><description>Tata Steel Ltd has witnessed a notable surge in call option trading, coinciding with the stock reaching a fresh 52-week high of ₹206.34 on 9 Feb 2026. The ferrous metals giant’s shares outperformed its sector and the broader Sensex, reflecting bullish investor sentiment ahead of the 24 Feb 2026 options expiry.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>89a2365ffd9f679f14881254a2c8719d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shree Cement Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shree-cement-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3828752</link><description>Shree Cement Ltd. has witnessed a significant 18.6% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s underperformance relative to its sector and the broader Sensex. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and price movements, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>00efe91c02de06e8c6c5a7c8780ff32a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S.A.L Steel Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sal-steel-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-amid-robust-performance-3828747</link><description>S.A.L Steel Ltd, a key player in the Ferrous Metals sector, has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high in its stock price, reflecting a sustained period of strong performance and market resilience.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>808f00c201d5608b18d7141dd91482ca</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Mart Ltd Hits Intraday High with 12.53% Surge on 9 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sg-mart-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1253-surge-on-9-feb-2026-3828743</link><description>SG Mart Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 9 Feb 2026, surging 12.53% to touch a day’s high of ₹397.95, significantly outperforming its construction sector peers and broader market indices.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>1f321418303af88c8563b79b171d6bef</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>