<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3833668</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture of corporate performance across India’s equity markets, with 2,432 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings surprises has improved modestly to 47.0%, sectoral and market-capitalisation distinctions highlight a complex landscape for investors to navigate.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>5616cdcce865b62bc6f52aeeb21a4741</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indiqube Spaces Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indiqube-spaces-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833641</link><description>Indiqube Spaces Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 45.56% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹17.07 crores, highlighting ongoing profitability challenges due to high interest and depreciation costs. While operational efficiency is improving, the persistent losses raise concerns about the sustainability of its business model.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e87a73be58f064f16519b96bb8b600b3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Prabha Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-prabha-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833640</link><description>Prabha Energy Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show significant revenue growth of 72.55% year-on-year, but the company faces ongoing operational challenges with a negative operating margin and reliance on non-operating income, raising concerns about its long-term viability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>48399cf32bcf66308e230fb6c992785d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Amanta Healthcare Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-amanta-healthcare-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833639</link><description>Amanta Healthcare Ltd's latest results show significant profit growth of 282.64% quarter-on-quarter, but declining operating margins and high debt levels indicate ongoing operational challenges. Overall, while profits have improved, the company faces difficulties in maintaining efficiency and managing costs.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0be46cc901ea44a8a9ea3ba6232061b3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indef Manufacturing Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indef-manufacturing-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833638</link><description>Indef Manufacturing Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show revenue growth with net sales up 13.19% year-on-year, but profitability has declined significantly, with net profit down 30.20% year-on-year and operating margins at their lowest in four quarters, raising concerns about operational efficiency and sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1f1967cb5f64c8b6b2f2333e73196f1a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Afcons Infrastructure Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-afcons-infrastructure-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833637</link><description>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd's latest results show a net profit decline of 34.77% year-on-year and a slight revenue drop, indicating challenges in consistent sales growth despite improved operational efficiency. Investors should watch for future revenue trends and project execution to gauge potential recovery.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8abf2791f5f36b08f38fe27b50628f5b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jyoti-cnc-automation-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833636</link><description>Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong net sales growth of 28.12% year-on-year, reaching ₹575.90 crores, and a net profit increase of 10.31%. However, rising interest expenses have raised concerns about future profitability, despite improvements in operational efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3b0f4c4354ac52b55a34a4762e50bcba</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-popular-vehicles-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833635</link><description>Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 30.83% year-on-year, but profitability remains a concern with a net profit margin of just 0.04%, indicating ongoing challenges in converting sales into meaningful profits.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2c069595e1bc9b7e219605585e3902d6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tvs-supply-chain-solutions-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833634</link><description>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd's latest results show modest revenue growth but significant profitability challenges, with a net profit decline of 77.77% from the previous quarter and thin profit margins, raising concerns about its financial sustainability. The company faces rising operational costs and competitive pressures in the logistics sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d886ed55d203734448b448ac0ad04e39</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Saj Hotels Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-saj-hotels-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833633</link><description>Saj Hotels Ltd's latest results show a 16.46% sequential increase in net sales but a 4.56% year-on-year decline, with net profit up 21.43% quarter-on-quarter but down 14.29% year-on-year, indicating mixed performance and ongoing operational challenges. Overall, while there are some positive trends, the company faces significant difficulties in maintaining profitability and market share.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a2c1b4c0b3b8a0ba8b39b785b53b63d5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Juniper Hotels Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-juniper-hotels-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833632</link><description>Juniper Hotels Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are strong, with net sales growing 28.14% to ₹295.13 crores and net profit increasing 289.17% to ₹65.42 crores, reflecting robust operational performance during peak travel season. However, ongoing evaluation of its financial health and sustainability will be crucial in the upcoming quarters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a2fa6a1a47512b5502f9e3cde0b5b839</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are RNFI Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rnfi-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833631</link><description>RNFI Services Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are positive, showing a 36.76% increase in net profit and a 17.04% rise in revenue, alongside improved operating margins. However, the company faces challenges in the broader NBFC market and concerns regarding market validation and liquidity.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4312006f261c280a7046f0e172a6791d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-manoj-vaibhav-gems-n-jewellers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833630</link><description>Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit increase of 36.63% year-on-year to ₹34.50 crore, but a sequential revenue decline of 9.40%. While operating margins improved and debt servicing capacity strengthened, the stock has underperformed in the market, indicating mixed overall performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>40d9f5312fcd841b6b9abf5df4840e27</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Motisons Jewellers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-motisons-jewellers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833629</link><description>Motisons Jewellers Ltd reported strong third-quarter results for FY26, with a 92.95% sequential revenue growth and a 69.56% year-on-year increase in net profit. However, challenges in operational efficiency and a significant stock price decline raise concerns about the sustainability of this growth, suggesting caution for potential investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a66c3e3845123e1f848889f6db2d3eda</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Concord Biotech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-concord-biotech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833628</link><description>Concord Biotech Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 33.59% decline in net profit and a 20.35% drop in revenue year-on-year, alongside reduced operating margins. While the company has a strong balance sheet, ongoing operational challenges raise concerns about future performance and profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7565e92312874a841990996daf2369f0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Allcargo Terminals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-allcargo-terminals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833627</link><description>Allcargo Terminals Ltd's latest results show strong net sales growth and improved profitability, but high debt levels and rising interest expenses raise concerns about financial sustainability. Overall, the performance is mixed, indicating operational momentum but ongoing challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>738df55005c112f6e3f1d9b8277f88a4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Robust Hotels Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-robust-hotels-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833626</link><description>Robust Hotels Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth and improved operating margins, but concerns about earnings quality and low returns on equity and capital employed indicate challenges in capital efficiency. Overall, the results present a mixed picture of operational improvement alongside financial vulnerabilities.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5f4b7c8042b9a69da7fbd979cc523337</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Krishival Foods Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-krishival-foods-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833625</link><description>Krishival Foods Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 128.32% and a net profit increase of 68.06%, but profitability is under pressure with declining operating and PAT margins. While cash flow has improved and debt levels are low, rising current liabilities raise concerns about working capital management.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dc1cb6f5c9ba40935eb0047c520fc642</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Dharmaj Crop Guard Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dharmaj-crop-guard-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3833624</link><description>Dharmaj Crop Guard Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, with a 95.61% decline in net profit and a 45.42% drop in revenue quarter-on-quarter, indicating significant operational challenges. While there is some year-on-year revenue growth of 8.61%, the company's reliance on non-operating income raises sustainability concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ad78c316ab469d146bf1c00cda15769a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>