<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3842876</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across market capitalisations, sectors, and individual companies. With over 4,000 stocks reporting, the aggregate data reveals a modest improvement in positive results, led by mid-cap companies, while large caps continue to face challenges amid a cautious economic backdrop.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>89615e924d99af0bfa83583f6615340a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Healthy Life Agritec Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-healthy-life-agritec-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842853</link><description>Healthy Life Agritec Ltd's latest results show a recovery with a 7.67% increase in net sales and a 68.35% rise in net profit compared to the previous quarter. However, ongoing challenges, including a significant stock price decline and low return on equity, raise concerns about long-term investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5fda4456240ffd57c20f67106a588596</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Athena Global Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-athena-global-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842852</link><description>Athena Global Technologies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net profit of ₹1.14 crores primarily due to a one-off income, while revenue declined by 47.26% year-on-year, indicating ongoing operational challenges and an unsustainable business model. The company faces significant financial strain with high employee costs and a deteriorating operating margin.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2a75f736a9d6281a7e98c7fd8ea7a3a1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Uma Exports Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-uma-exports-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842851</link><description>Uma Exports Ltd's latest results show strong sequential revenue growth of 38.31% to ₹560.44 crore, but a significant year-on-year net profit decline of 41.47% to ₹1.27 crore, indicating operational challenges and rising costs that may concern investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>60b44d56628759e9b04fb06d5a38a3e6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vishvprabha-ventures-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842850</link><description>Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹0.75 crore and an 80% revenue decline to ₹0.98 crore, alongside negative operating margins and deteriorating return on equity, indicating significant operational challenges and questions about its long-term viability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>697874ee5ddef76ef741d24fe59b38a7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Oricon Enterprises Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-oricon-enterprises-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842849</link><description>Oricon Enterprises Ltd's latest results show a net profit of ₹8.83 crores, up 175.94% year-on-year, but this is largely due to other income, while core operations reported a loss of ₹7.28 crores and a significant decline in sales. Overall, the financial health is concerning due to ongoing operational challenges despite a strong balance sheet and good stock performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5259325ff77f99828bf97b23657aa767</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are KMF Builders &amp; Developers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kmf-builders-developers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842848</link><description>KMF Builders &amp; Developers Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing zero revenue for the third consecutive quarter and widening losses, indicating significant operational challenges and questions about its business viability. Despite a stable balance sheet, the company's ongoing financial struggles and underperformance compared to peers raise investor skepticism.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>03bcb7eeb061dba6f7aebc03a0055b7e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Everest Organics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-everest-organics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842847</link><description>Everest Organics Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 16.49% decline in net sales and a 68.97% drop in net profit compared to the previous quarter, indicating significant operational challenges and rising cost pressures. Despite a year-on-year sales growth of 24.34% over nine months, profitability remains low, raising concerns about the company's financial stability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a03bb188c779b492f5e2d0f9c45d3f92</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Wardwizard Foods &amp; Beverages Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-wardwizard-foods-beverages-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842846</link><description>Wardwizard Foods &amp; Beverages Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 139.23% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹0.60 crores and declining operating margins, indicating ongoing profitability challenges that need to be addressed for sustainable growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f4b04795727dc74f28cebd6987b64122</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tarai Foods Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tarai-foods-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842845</link><description>Tarai Foods Ltd's latest results are poor, showing no sales revenue for over seven quarters and a net loss of ₹0.11 crores in Q3 FY26, leading to a negative net worth of ₹2.70 crores and significant financial distress. The company's stock has also dropped 22% over the past year, highlighting ongoing operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d8e76c783febde9566b4c82816ba4e9b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Communications Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-communications-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3842834</link><description>Tata Communications Ltd (NSE: 952728), a prominent player in the Telecom - Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b34d6c57ab767fd82f42da620662ad72</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sterlite Technologies Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sterlite-technologies-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3842833</link><description>Sterlite Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift for the telecom equipment company, despite its current Sell mojo grade and recent minor price pullback.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a6e8c4f173c00fa81da8837581efe1cf</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SRM Contractors Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srm-contractors-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842819</link><description>SRM Contractors Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—suggesting a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>6d5a2370ece3eda4a698bf7b51f9604e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Metropolis Healthcare Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/metropolis-healthcare-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842818</link><description>Metropolis Healthcare Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>36dcd8d8705fbde3e38714648877c16f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salasar Techno Engineering Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/salasar-techno-engineering-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3842817</link><description>Salasar Techno Engineering Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>91821330e83f9367045043956254ba5d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukand Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukand-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842811</link><description>Mukand Ltd, a player in the ferrous metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term price trajectory.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>6d94bb6eb2148c4a3492ef94323b9656</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precision Electronics Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/precision-electronics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3842816</link><description>Precision Electronics Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>cd5ebbbda52c57ae4f9cb3dc07416359</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3842814</link><description>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting renewed investor confidence and a possible trend reversal in the capital markets sector.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>3d126ff24592988d220bd04468461385</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orchid Pharma Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orchid-pharma-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842809</link><description>Orchid Pharma Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term prospects amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>18c9afb36285d5f82ba1d62e4bfcd579</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orosil Smiths India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orosil-smiths-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3842813</link><description>Orosil Smiths India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about its long-term price strength.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>bfbfecf051c6035b407fc3f1378dc8e3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>