<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-fallingrising-3859436</link><description>On 26-Feb, Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd witnessed a significant price surge of 14.36%, closing at ₹4,580.85, driven by robust quarterly performance and heightened investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89058a661d9f7bfd6044662cce35576f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gajanand International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gajanand-international-ltd-fallingrising-3859435</link><description>On 26-Feb, Gajanand International Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 9.04% to close at ₹8.55, marking a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹8.45 during the trading session. This decline reflects a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and sector benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6dd219f141465d056f20bbf5cb7abce2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3859434</link><description>On 26-Feb, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a significant uptick in its share price, rising by 7.44% to ₹369.05 as of 09:19 PM. This notable gain reflects a combination of strong short-term performance and heightened investor participation, setting the stock apart from broader market trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>00ae8421f00c475cf6cb913cae460521</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Go Digit General Insurance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-go-digit-general-insurance-ltd-fallingrising-3859433</link><description>On 26-Feb, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd's stock price rose by 0.9% to ₹343.10, continuing a four-day winning streak that has seen the share appreciate by 3.28%. This upward momentum is underpinned by the company's robust long-term fundamentals and its outperformance relative to both the sector and broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6a7f4a1ef12831173ea33d343e5aa737</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mankind Pharma Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mankind-pharma-ltd-fallingrising-3859432</link><description>On 26-Feb, Mankind Pharma Ltd’s stock price rose sharply by 5.8% to ₹2,280.05, reflecting robust short-term gains and increased investor interest despite some underlying concerns about its longer-term performance and valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>528fe9f34f31c6f39982a93e17160e94</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is HP Adhesives Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hp-adhesives-ltd-fallingrising-3859431</link><description>On 26-Feb, HP Adhesives Ltd’s stock price fell by 0.81% to close at ₹36.51, continuing a downward trend driven by disappointing financial results and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>278ca91f8ced26bd1f8190ab9543e885</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Fusion Finance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-fusion-finance-ltd-fallingrising-3859430</link><description>On 26-Feb, Fusion Finance Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 5.91%, closing at ₹202.40, driven by strong short-term performance and growing institutional participation despite underlying fundamental challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ce007d155f38b2aa495b786db916ddec</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bazel International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bazel-international-ltd-fallingrising-3859429</link><description>On 26-Feb, Bazel International Ltd experienced a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹24.29, down ₹1.29 or 5.04% from the previous close. This drop marks a continuation of a pronounced downtrend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>331e61c1b8bd4f8598c8dbae56303bdc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shri Venkatesh Refineries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shri-venkatesh-refineries-ltd-fallingrising-3859428</link><description>On 26-Feb, Shri Venkatesh Refineries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.48% to close at ₹250.95. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum, with the stock underperforming both its sector and key market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4b13abce2d8fc72a7ef9dd4fffae8d71</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-tirupati-balajee-fibc-ltd-fallingrising-3859427</link><description>On 26-Feb, Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 2.25%, closing at ₹552.00, reflecting a positive shift despite its challenging longer-term returns relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e303faede9fdf892d031ef7e32fdc82d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Interactive Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-interactive-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3859426</link><description>On 26-Feb, Interactive Financial Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 1.73% to close at ₹15.30. This drop reflects a continuation of recent underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f530d6555c66d69d82bdb8f36f1df257</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ascom-leasing-investments-ltd-fallingrising-3859425</link><description>On 26-Feb, Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd witnessed a significant price rise, hitting a new 52-week high of ₹199.50, reflecting a 5.0% increase or ₹9.50 by 09:03 PM. This surge underscores the stock’s robust performance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7c5b0213c863918dfecf7d88db663581</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pasupati Acrylon Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pasupati-acrylon-ltd-fallingrising-3859424</link><description>On 26 Feb, Pasupati Acrylon Ltd’s stock price surged by 5.2% to close at ₹53.25, marking a notable rebound after five consecutive days of decline and outperforming its sector peers significantly.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1f61a96c44105dd43a7cf8a91afda605</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is East West Freight Carriers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-east-west-freight-carriers-ltd-fallingrising-3859423</link><description>On 26-Feb, East West Freight Carriers Ltd recorded a modest rise in its share price, advancing by 1.53% to ₹3.32 as of 08:58 PM. This increase reflects a short-term positive momentum despite the company’s challenging longer-term performance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2f18d5937dee386a3546e96e279e9aad</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Samtex Fashions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-samtex-fashions-ltd-fallingrising-3859422</link><description>On 26-Feb, Samtex Fashions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 6.62% to close at ₹1.41. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by weak investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ea4f24cd518efa935f7ccf9e43fc1c65</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Paisalo Digital Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-paisalo-digital-ltd-fallingrising-3859421</link><description>On 26-Feb, Paisalo Digital Ltd's stock price rose by 2.86% to ₹36.27, continuing a six-day winning streak that has delivered a 9.02% return over this period. This upward momentum is underpinned by robust long-term financial performance, positive quarterly results, and increased promoter confidence, despite some signs of reduced investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>43e0e99f0011ab8e1055ce41417c714e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Central Depository Services (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-central-depository-services-india-ltd-fallingrising-3859420</link><description>As of 26-Feb, Central Depository Services (India) Ltd (CDSL) shares have declined by 2.34% to ₹1,295.80, reflecting investor caution driven by flat quarterly results and an expensive valuation despite strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>33e8309d30c6afa232dbf38bfd3fa70b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-jammu-kashmir-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3859419</link><description>On 26-Feb, The Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd. witnessed a significant rise in its stock price, closing at ₹121.25 with an increase of ₹8.90 or 7.92%. This upward momentum reflects a strong performance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3234632338bd5849134a19349a77f7e4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Geojit Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-geojit-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3859418</link><description>As of 26-Feb, Geojit Financial Services Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹63.65, down 1.79% on the day, continuing a downward trend driven by disappointing financial results and waning promoter confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dfc02223db73aac1ef2d9d715c3b8a19</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is TGV Sraac Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tgv-sraac-ltd-fallingrising-3859417</link><description>On 26-Feb, TGV Sraac Ltd's stock price fell by 0.85% to close at ₹86.50, continuing a trend of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>adf80f6c88f9eaa2959a309bf60ed5a9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>