<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Sai Life Sciences Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sai-life-sciences-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824975</link><description>Sai Life Sciences Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit of ₹100.38 crores (up 86.41% year-on-year) and revenue growth of 26.53%, alongside improved margins. However, concerns about its high valuation relative to industry averages may pose challenges for future growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e75fcae21f0c630e043d285eb21a3725</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Physicswallah Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-physicswallah-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824974</link><description>Physicswallah Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a strong recovery with a net profit of ₹100.52 crores, up from a loss last quarter, and a 30.07% year-on-year revenue increase. However, concerns about reliance on non-operating income and poor capital efficiency suggest challenges ahead for sustainable profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5afebe3bbb862839c124ec40c14f24b6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gala Precision Engineering Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gala-precision-engineering-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824973</link><description>Gala Precision Engineering Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with record sales of ₹85.25 crores, but profitability is under pressure due to a slight decline in net profit and operating margins, indicating potential challenges ahead. Investors should watch how the company manages these operational issues while maintaining growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>511ab04a96117b5b01c6687092873e65</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bharti Hexacom Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bharti-hexacom-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824972</link><description>Bharti Hexacom Ltd's latest results show strong profit growth of 81.56% year-on-year and improved operating margins, indicating solid operational performance. However, the company faces challenges with a recent stock price decline and market reassessment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4ffbfaef0041335af4eb4846de5024a1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sayaji Hotels (Pune) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sayaji-hotels-pune-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824971</link><description>Sayaji Hotels (Pune) Ltd reported strong quarterly results with net sales of ₹21.98 crores and a net profit of ₹5.86 crores, reflecting significant growth and improved margins. However, its long-term growth outlook is more modest, with a CAGR of 8.10% over the past five years.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>871db4015a59ced332d328c63a236095</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sanathan Textiles Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sanathan-textiles-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824970</link><description>Sanathan Textiles Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of ₹817.99 crores, but a concerning 50.23% decline in net profit to ₹20.12 crores due to soaring interest expenses, indicating significant operational challenges despite positive topline momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>da34a89b3c6a422e9d79387825bf5cc5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-suraksha-diagnostic-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824969</link><description>Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 17.95% year-on-year, but a concerning 13.06% decline in net profit and reduced operating margins indicate significant operational challenges. Investors should monitor future performance for improvements in profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3218ad0ccf61c6fe98964f2acd80ee35</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are National Peroxide Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-national-peroxide-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824968</link><description>National Peroxide Ltd's latest results show mixed signals: while net profit surged significantly to ₹1.83 crores and revenue increased 11.15% year-on-year, overall performance remains challenged with revenues trailing historical averages and stock underperformance, indicating ongoing structural issues.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>75f3d77d737d3af0d66dbc9789549563</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are BLS E-Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bls-e-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824967</link><description>BLS E-Services Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 249.60% year-on-year, but declining profitability with a significant drop in operating margins, raising concerns about the sustainability of its business model. Overall, the performance reflects a challenging balance between growth and profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1731aa831a3f2842e29998c3dc440c59</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824966</link><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 28.64% year-on-year, reaching ₹232.55 crores, but profitability has significantly declined, with net profit down 62.21% to ₹7.95 crores, raising concerns about operational efficiency and cost management. While the company has a solid return on equity and a healthy balance sheet, the drop in profit margins indicates challenges that need to be addressed for sustainable growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9bd8ceec333a19b1556ff78214ac4aad</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bajel Projects Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bajel-projects-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824965</link><description>Bajel Projects Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are mixed, showing a net loss of ₹0.42 crores due to high tax rates and interest costs, despite achieving the highest operating margin in seven quarters at 4.89%. While the company's financial structure is solid, the decline in net sales and low return on equity raise concerns about future profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>84ba0d79463742645e42db7d4f885e9a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Digidrive Distributors Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-digidrive-distributors-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824964</link><description>Digidrive Distributors Ltd's latest results show a decline in revenue with net sales down 22.57% sequentially, but a significant profit increase to ₹5.72 crores, driven by cost management rather than sustainable growth. Overall, while profitability has improved, ongoing revenue challenges and low capital efficiency raise concerns about the company's long-term viability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e0657846cf64b9a75ab65fffcc2c7143</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sayaji Hotels (Indore) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sayaji-hotels-indore-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824963</link><description>Sayaji Hotels (Indore) Ltd's latest results are concerning, with a net profit decline of 89.94% and an 11.36% drop in revenue for Q2 FY26, reflecting operational challenges and reduced profitability during the monsoon season. Investors should monitor future performance closely due to significant margin compression and ongoing operational difficulties.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>50421ea551404b8c89670d053d408ba3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Updater Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-updater-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824962</link><description>Updater Services Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 10.39% year-on-year, reaching ₹767.10 crores, but net profit plummeted by 70.34%, indicating significant operational challenges and declining profitability. Overall, while revenue is up, the sharp drop in profits raises concerns about the company's sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>362f29348e356fd2a147f1c82b4f6294</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vasa Denticity Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vasa-denticity-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824961</link><description>Vasa Denticity Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 22.82% year-on-year, but net profit declined by 11.17%, raising concerns about profitability and cost management. While the company has a debt-free balance sheet and effective asset utilization, operational challenges need to be addressed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b72988091c02cb0c461ed8893332100c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Yatharth Hospital &amp; Trauma Care Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-yatharth-hospital-trauma-care-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824960</link><description>Yatharth Hospital &amp; Trauma Care Services Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 46.23% year-on-year and a net profit increase of 48.74%, but margin compression due to rising employee costs raises concerns about sustainability. Overall, while the company is growing, investors should watch for ongoing margin pressures and operational efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6c89828353a46f22dfa98ed4dae7bdd3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rishabh Instruments Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rishabh-instruments-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824959</link><description>Rishabh Instruments Ltd's latest results show a strong operational turnaround with a significant increase in profitability, including a 436.32% rise in net profit year-on-year. However, recent declines in net sales and profit raise concerns about the sustainability of this growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>78015c1594943eaec78deec21ebf3a95</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Kaynes Technology India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kaynes-technology-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824958</link><description>Kaynes Technology India Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit increase of 101.64% and revenue growth of 58.40%. However, concerns about valuation, operational efficiency, and slower collection cycles suggest potential risks ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>26c7b24e934985714f7055bebeb52079</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tarsons Products Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tarsons-products-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824957</link><description>Tarsons Products Ltd's latest results show revenue growth with net sales up 12.76% year-on-year, but profitability remains a concern, as net profit declined 4.18% compared to last year, indicating operational inefficiencies and rising costs. Overall, while sales are improving, the company's ability to convert this into profit is under scrutiny.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a73782cbd527a89c82479009de2d6164</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Fusion Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-fusion-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3824956</link><description>Fusion Finance Ltd's latest results show a net loss of ₹22.14 crores for Q2 FY26, a significant improvement from the previous quarter but still indicative of ongoing challenges, including declining revenue and high debt. While there are some positive signs like improved operating margins, the company faces critical issues that raise concerns about its long-term viability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>949aa7fd6238e44afe04ee4a2e3d2dd8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>