<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Colinz Laboratories Q3 FY26: Marginal Revenue Growth Masks Deeper Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/colinz-laboratories-q3-fy26-marginal-revenue-growth-masks-deeper-profitability-concerns-3803825</link><description>Colinz Laboratories Ltd., a micro-cap pharmaceutical formulations manufacturer, reported a modest quarterly performance for Q3 FY26, with net profit declining 42.86% quarter-on-quarter to ₹0.08 crores from ₹0.14 crores in Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, net profit increased 60.00% from ₹0.05 crores in Q3 FY25, though this comparison benefits from an exceptionally weak base quarter. With a market capitalisation of just ₹13.00 crores, the Mumbai-based company continues to struggle with scale and profitability consistency, as reflected in its current stock price of ₹46.20, down 47.91% from its 52-week high of ₹88.70.
Time: Jan 24 2026 09:31 PM IST</description><guid>446e832e89d392bb3ca15bd0172a5ddd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nilachal Refractories Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Signal Deepening Crisis</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/nilachal-refractories-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-signal-deepening-crisis-3803824</link><description>Nilachal Refractories Ltd., a micro-cap player in the electrodes and refractories sector, reported a catastrophic quarterly loss of ₹3.53 crores in Q3 FY26, marking a severe deterioration from the ₹0.54 crore loss in Q2 FY26 and a staggering 740.48% increase in losses compared to the ₹0.42 crore loss in Q3 FY25. With a market capitalisation of just ₹73.00 crores and trading at ₹33.95 per share, the Bhubaneswar-based company faces mounting operational challenges that have pushed it into negative book value territory at ₹-13.72 per share.
Time: Jan 24 2026 09:31 PM IST</description><guid>3f7d170e777cc917f621615656073fe7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chennai Petroleum Q3 FY26: Refining Margins Power 4,720% Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/chennai-petroleum-q3-fy26-refining-margins-power-4720-profit-surge-3803823</link><description>Chennai Petroleum Corporation Ltd. (CPCL) has delivered a spectacular turnaround in Q3 FY26, posting a consolidated net profit of ₹1,001.59 crores compared to a modest ₹20.78 crores in the year-ago quarter—a staggering 4,719.97% year-on-year surge that marks one of the most dramatic profit recoveries in India's refining sector. The ₹12,494 crore market capitalisation company, majority-owned by Indian Oil Corporation, saw its stock trading at ₹843.50 on January 23, 2026, up 1.81% as investors digested the robust quarterly performance that underscores a remarkable revival in refining economics.
Time: Jan 24 2026 09:30 PM IST</description><guid>495f1f65f325a5632a479b54554aa86b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robust Quarterly Earnings Show Mixed Fortunes Across Market Caps in Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/robust-quarterly-earnings-show-mixed-fortunes-across-market-caps-in-dec-2025-3803816</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a notable improvement in positive results, particularly driven by mid-cap companies. With 422 stocks having declared results, the proportion of companies reporting profits has risen to 54.0%, marking a significant uptick from the previous quarter’s 43.0%. This quarter’s data reveals sectoral nuances and market cap-wise disparities that investors should carefully analyse as they position portfolios for the year ahead.
Time: Jan 24 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>9faf0e058e828f72a70cfebe838b315f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-shyam-metalics-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803807</link><description>Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 17.71% year-on-year, but a concerning 24.65% decline in net profit and reduced operating margins indicate significant challenges in profitability and operational efficiency. Overall, while revenues are up, the decline in profitability raises concerns about the company's financial health.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:14 PM IST</description><guid>896f34c909ed940ec518985c472473a3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gandhar-oil-refinery-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803806</link><description>Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 16.09% year-on-year, reaching ₹1,167.06 crores, but profitability has declined, with a net profit drop of 10.15% from the previous quarter and decreasing margins, indicating operational challenges despite the revenue increase.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:14 PM IST</description><guid>f056cd80920b73815fb2327697cc6426</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are SBFC Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sbfc-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803805</link><description>SBFC Finance Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show an 8.15% quarter-on-quarter net profit increase to ₹118.04 crores and a 27.51% year-on-year growth, but concerns about capital efficiency and rising interest expenses suggest potential challenges ahead. Investors should monitor these trends closely.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:14 PM IST</description><guid>4877babbe275e945979c665bbbd59d69</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Advik Capital Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-advik-capital-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803804</link><description>Advik Capital Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹20.87 crores and negative revenue of ₹-2.83 crores for the quarter ending December 2025, indicating severe operational and financial distress. The company's significant decline in sales and liquidity challenges suggest it is in a precarious position.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:14 PM IST</description><guid>89154f2c9fdc6465118be45a0a1900ce</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Cyber Media Research &amp; Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-cyber-media-research-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803803</link><description>Cyber Media Research &amp; Services Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 5.49% to ₹22.29 crores, but a concerning 33.73% drop in net profit to ₹0.55 crores, indicating challenges in profitability despite overall positive trends for the year. Investors should monitor future performance closely.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:14 PM IST</description><guid>85ccc291ae0fa34fc4d0b6b8965f8ed1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803802</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd's latest results show a slight decline in net profit and revenue, indicating a deceleration in growth momentum, although operating margins improved due to cost management. Overall, the company faces challenges in sustaining growth amid competitive pressures and market volatility.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:14 PM IST</description><guid>f3baed5e9c29b553bd1e118a143f64e0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are 20 Microns Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-20-microns-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803801</link><description>20 Microns Ltd's latest results show a mixed performance, with a year-over-year net profit increase of 16.06% but a sequential decline in both profit and revenue, indicating operational challenges despite some improvements in efficiency. Overall, the company is facing stagnant revenue growth and inflationary pressures, leading to concerns about capital efficiency.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>f5da824007ec70127ef88279b5a408ae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are JSW Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jsw-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803800</link><description>JSW Energy Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 59.91% to ₹5,177.42 crores, but net profit declined by 17.41% to ₹704.68 crores due to rising debt and interest expenses, raising concerns about financial stability and profitability. Investors should watch the company's ability to manage its debt and improve margins moving forward.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>192f9ec46517c594285d87edf44f2177</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ashish Polyplast Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ashish-polyplast-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803799</link><description>Ashish Polyplast Ltd's latest results show a return to profitability with a net profit of ₹0.15 crores, but revenue declined by 4.07% sequentially and 20.81% year-on-year, indicating ongoing operational challenges and negative returns on equity. Overall, the financial performance reflects mixed results with significant concerns about revenue generation and capital efficiency.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>610081528b361ef590868a78b55c919e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vakrangee Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vakrangee-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803798</link><description>Vakrangee Ltd's latest results show a significant net profit increase of 168.07% to ₹3.19 crores, but revenue declined by 11.46% to ₹60.10 crores, marking the lowest in seven quarters. While operating margins improved due to cost control, ongoing revenue challenges and low return on equity indicate potential long-term issues.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>81aa9084bf07084e63ae073fd0182a9d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Anka India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-anka-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803797</link><description>Anka India Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show impressive revenue growth of 419.44% year-on-year, but profitability has declined significantly, with a net profit of only ₹0.10 crores and concerns over operational efficiency and cost management. Overall, the company is experiencing strong sales but struggling to convert that growth into sustainable profits.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>58c5bd5c71883e8692bc90c44e24558d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bridge Securities Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bridge-securities-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803796</link><description>Bridge Securities Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 44% year-on-year decline in net sales and a 54.79% drop in net profit, alongside significant margin compression and structural balance sheet weaknesses. Overall, the company is facing considerable operational challenges and may be overvalued given its deteriorating fundamentals.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>e5dd4fa7dedd98b638c8d3f13eebf09f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Advani Hotels &amp; Resorts (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-advani-hotels-resorts-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803795</link><description>Advani Hotels &amp; Resorts (India) Ltd reported strong Q3 FY26 results with a net profit of ₹11.33 crores and record revenue of ₹36.09 crores, reflecting significant operational improvements and seasonal demand. However, despite this positive performance, the company's long-term stock results have been mixed, with a one-year return of -2.78%.
Time: Jan 24 2026 07:13 PM IST</description><guid>d68b70fcdae644361bf7f6272031c9c9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>