<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.42% Amid Mixed Sector Performance; Metal Sector Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-042-amid-mixed-sector-performance-metal-sector-leads-gains-3805083</link><description>The Indian equity markets closed lower on 27 Jan 2026, with the Sensex slipping 0.42% to 81,191.76 amid subdued investor sentiment and mixed sectoral trends. While the metal sector outperformed, auto stocks dragged the indices down, reflecting cautious trading ahead of key corporate earnings scheduled for later this week.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>77dafd10eefa9a66e9e1228adeaded6c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd Faces Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Inclusion and Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-faces-challenges-amid-nifty-50-inclusion-and-sector-headwinds-3805081</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, is navigating a challenging phase marked by a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade and subdued price performance. Despite its large-cap status and inclusion in India's premier benchmark, the stock has struggled to maintain momentum amid sector headwinds and shifting institutional holdings, raising questions about its near-term outlook.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>e0cdf7575a70ccc30a225cf51a386542</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd Faces Headwinds Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-faces-headwinds-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3805082</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently undergone a significant rating downgrade from Hold to Sell, reflecting mounting pressures in the hospital sector and shifting investor sentiment. Despite its large-cap status and historical outperformance over the medium term, the stock has struggled to keep pace with benchmark indices, raising questions about its near-term prospects and institutional holding patterns.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>3491cbc42edd0af974b39e67ce01ed6d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd: Navigating Challenges Amidst Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-company-ltd-navigating-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3805080</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention from institutional investors despite recent challenges in its valuation and price momentum. As a large-cap insurance sector heavyweight, its performance and market positioning remain critical for benchmark indices and portfolio managers alike.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>efbb76038d1762ebc1e5e4f77847f47a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3805079</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to command attention as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in India’s insurance sector. Despite recent short-term price pressures and a downgrade in its Mojo Grade, the company’s market capitalisation and institutional interest underscore its pivotal role in benchmark indices and investor portfolios.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>bb2259cf0ce145aed50db3c9cbf03da2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3805077</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd., a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market conditions. With a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Hold' from 'Sell' and sustained outperformance against the Sensex over multiple time horizons, the company’s position within the benchmark index remains pivotal for investors and institutional stakeholders alike.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>21e7f82def282a99f4e68808aa2a5d13</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd: Navigating Market Pressures Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-navigating-market-pressures-amid-nifty-50-membership-3805076</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd, a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently experienced notable shifts in its market performance and institutional holdings. Despite a challenging short-term price trajectory, the company’s long-term fundamentals and benchmark status continue to underscore its significance in India’s equity landscape.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>72b20db262a43487770eb6fbb8fe273a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-market-headwinds-3805073</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd, a stalwart in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, continues to command significant attention as a Nifty 50 constituent. Despite recent price softness, the company’s large-cap status, robust institutional holdings, and benchmark index membership underscore its pivotal role in India’s financial markets. This article analyses Bajaj Finance’s current market positioning, institutional investor behaviour, and the implications of its benchmark status for investors.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>f40a739773e211bd88d88a5d46bdbbce</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd Faces Pressure Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-faces-pressure-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-market-challenges-3805078</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, is currently navigating a challenging phase marked by a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell and a notable underperformance against benchmark indices. Despite its large-cap status and significant market presence, the stock has struggled to maintain momentum, reflecting broader sectoral pressures and shifting institutional investor sentiment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>0ba07c30a4de7feec15ee8c239dc81cc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3805075</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, continues to command attention as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index. Despite recent challenges reflected in its performance metrics and a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade, the company’s large-cap status and institutional interest underscore its enduring significance in India’s benchmark equity index.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>96542b48772df4efa16ca8273ee0750e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel Ltd. Strengthens Position Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steel-ltd-strengthens-position-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3805072</link><description>JSW Steel Ltd., a key player in the ferrous metals sector and a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has demonstrated notable resilience and outperformance in recent trading sessions. With a market capitalisation exceeding ₹2,85,959 crores and a strong track record against benchmark indices, the company’s evolving institutional holdings and sectoral dynamics underscore its critical role within India’s equity landscape.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>df5305d8112956b980cb1c4e460041e1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd: Navigating Market Pressures Amidst Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-navigating-market-pressures-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3805071</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently experienced notable market movements and institutional holding changes. Despite a challenging short-term price performance, the company’s long-term fundamentals and benchmark status continue to underscore its significance in India’s equity landscape.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>e88ab118744872be9a18c48d8a03e107</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd: Navigating Market Challenges Amidst Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-navigating-market-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3805074</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (L&amp;T), a cornerstone of India's construction sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, has recently experienced notable shifts in its market performance and institutional holdings. As the company grapples with short-term headwinds amid broader sectoral challenges, its status within the benchmark index continues to underscore its strategic importance to investors and market participants alike.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>f14a81b56dfa2df43c5c1dfb397b6de3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Institutional Shifts and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-institutional-shifts-and-market-dynamics-3805069</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a large-cap holding company with a market capitalisation exceeding ₹3,11,000 crores. Despite recent shifts in institutional holdings and a recalibration of its investment grade, the company’s long-term performance remains robust, underscoring its critical role in India’s financial sector and the broader benchmark landscape.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>ea58b0914a1beb3aac5b157fc646c3bd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Ltd Faces Heightened Scrutiny Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-ltd-faces-heightened-scrutiny-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3805070</link><description>Adani Enterprises Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to grapple with significant headwinds as it trades near its 52-week lows amid deteriorating fundamentals and subdued investor sentiment. Despite its large-cap status and benchmark inclusion, the stock’s performance remains underwhelming, reflecting broader challenges within the diversified sector and shifting institutional holdings.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>2f5d1de80fec69c454d49238ceac337d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd. Strengthens Position Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-strengthens-position-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-interest-3805068</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has demonstrated notable resilience and growth momentum in recent trading sessions, supported by increased institutional holdings and a favourable sectoral backdrop. The company’s upgraded rating and sustained outperformance relative to the benchmark Sensex underscore its growing appeal among investors in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>8bfeb2595913bef0b95a7f170383acb4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Ltd Faces Downgrade Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-ltd-faces-downgrade-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3805067</link><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd (HUL), a stalwart of India’s FMCG sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently seen a downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell, reflecting growing concerns over its near-term performance despite its large-cap status and benchmark significance.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>b980f6d70ee10ae84320d06138a66eb3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>