<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Bajaj Consumer Joins MomentumNow Stocks on Strong Financial Upswing</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/bajaj-consumer-joins-momentumnow-stocks-on-strong-financial-upswing-3800694</link><description>Bajaj Consumer, a small-cap FMCG company, has been added to the MomentumNow Stocks list as of 22 January 2026, following a remarkable quarter ending December 2025 that showcased robust financial growth and operational efficiency. This inclusion reflects the stock’s rising momentum and aligns with the strategy of capitalising on stocks demonstrating strong fundamental and technical performance in the current market cycle.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>5c179217efded68a83770aab3e7d2035</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Go Digit General Insurance Q3 FY26: Premium Growth Masks Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/go-digit-general-insurance-q3-fy26-premium-growth-masks-margin-pressure-3800698</link><description>Go Digit General Insurance Limited posted a net profit of ₹135.60 crores for Q2 FY26, marking a modest decline of 1.97% quarter-on-quarter but a robust 51.58% year-on-year surge. The Pune-based insurer, commanding a market capitalisation of ₹30,030 crores, demonstrated resilience in premium collection with net sales advancing 11.97% sequentially to ₹2,088.21 crores, yet the stock has struggled to maintain momentum, trading at ₹324.20 following a 1.20% uptick on January 22, 2026.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>459445ed52bba9af34323c27e5901060</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EKI Energy Services Q2 FY26: Carbon Credit Developer Plunges Into Loss Territory Amid Revenue Collapse</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/eki-energy-services-q2-fy26-carbon-credit-developer-plunges-into-loss-territory-amid-revenue-collapse-3800697</link><description>EKI Energy Services Ltd., the carbon credit developer and supplier, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹2.16 crores in Q2 FY26, marking a dramatic reversal from the ₹4.02 crores profit recorded in the same quarter last year. The company's stock has plummeted 60.69% over the past year, currently trading at ₹93.87 with a market capitalisation of ₹271.00 crores, reflecting severe investor concern over its deteriorating financial performance.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>e1bbbcd49cf0db5547592d7c794c7ed3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Q2 FY26: Asset Quality Concerns Eclipse Profitability Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/suryoday-small-finance-bank-q2-fy26-asset-quality-concerns-eclipse-profitability-gains-3800696</link><description>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Ltd. reported a net profit of ₹30.41 crores for Q2 FY26, declining 13.80% quarter-on-quarter from ₹35.28 crores in Q1 FY26 and plummeting 33.00% year-on-year from ₹45.39 crores in Q2 FY25. The Mumbai-based small finance bank, with a market capitalisation of ₹1,477 crores, faces mounting pressure from deteriorating asset quality metrics that overshadow modest operational improvements. The stock traded at ₹139.10 on January 22, 2026, reflecting a muted 1.46% single-day gain but remaining under pressure with a 7.91% decline over the past three months.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>ee315e5db96c6f5af039b1a5a90a6217</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Total Gas Q3 FY26: Margin Compression Overshadows Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/adani-total-gas-q3-fy26-margin-compression-overshadows-revenue-growth-3800695</link><description>Adani Total Gas Ltd., India's second-largest city gas distribution company, reported consolidated net profit of ₹163.49 crores for Q3 FY26, marking an 11.91% decline year-on-year despite posting healthy revenue growth of 19.09%. The ₹59,472 crore market capitalisation company witnessed its stock surge 3.85% to ₹548.40 following the results announcement, though the shares remain 31.23% below their 52-week high of ₹797.40, reflecting persistent investor concerns over margin compression and deteriorating profitability metrics.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>7512ac3aecf40d05c794587abed4a1c8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat State Petronet Q3 FY26: Margin Compression Weighs on Profitability Despite Stable Volumes</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/gujarat-state-petronet-q3-fy26-margin-compression-weighs-on-profitability-despite-stable-volumes-3800693</link><description>Gujarat State Petronet Ltd., the natural gas transmission infrastructure leader, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹256.75 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a marginal decline of 1.54% quarter-on-quarter but posting a 9.66% improvement year-on-year. The ₹17,067-crore market capitalisation company witnessed its stock trading at ₹302.85 as of January 22, 2026, reflecting a muted market response to results that revealed persistent margin pressures despite stable operational performance.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>6a887c9103d014eb0fdd48547c6c2af7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antelopus Selan Energy Q2 FY26: Profit Decline Amid Challenging Oil Market Conditions</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/antelopus-selan-energy-q2-fy26-profit-decline-amid-challenging-oil-market-conditions-3800692</link><description>Antelopus Selan Energy Ltd., a leading private sector oil and gas exploration and production company, reported a net profit of ₹11.81 crores for Q2 FY26, marking a decline of 41.36% year-on-year from ₹20.14 crores in Q2 FY25. The company's stock, trading at ₹438.50 with a market capitalisation of ₹1,540 crores, has struggled significantly over the past year, declining 43.35% against the Sensex's 7.73% gain. Whilst sequential growth showed modest improvement with profits rising 5.26% from Q1 FY26's ₹11.22 crores, the year-on-year performance reflects the challenging operating environment facing the oil exploration sector.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>67a7b178bdc8ef910d4abf543fc5deb5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DLF Q2 FY26: Revenue Decline and Margin Pressure Signal Challenging Quarter</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/dlf-q2-fy26-revenue-decline-and-margin-pressure-signal-challenging-quarter-3800691</link><description>DLF Ltd., India's largest real estate developer with a market capitalisation of ₹1,53,445 crores, reported a challenging second quarter for FY2026, with consolidated net profit declining 14.55% year-on-year to ₹1,180.09 crores despite a sequential improvement of 54.73% from Q1 FY26. The stock has been under sustained pressure, trading at ₹615.00 as of January 22, 2026, down 30.70% from its 52-week high of ₹887.50 and currently in a bearish technical trend since December 11, 2025.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>2401c1e3a2e1dd51746bc25b3009715b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BlueStone Jewellery Swings to Profit in Q3 FY26: A Festive Quarter Turnaround Amid Structural Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bluestone-jewellery-swings-to-profit-in-q3-fy26-a-festive-quarter-turnaround-amid-structural-concerns-3800686</link><description>BlueStone Jewellery &amp; Lifestyle Ltd. delivered a dramatic turnaround in Q3 FY26, swinging to a consolidated net profit of ₹69.08 crores from a loss of ₹51.75 crores in the previous quarter, marking a staggering sequential improvement of 233.49%. The omnichannel jewellery retailer, with a market capitalisation of ₹6,766 crores, posted net sales of ₹748.65 crores for the October-December quarter, representing robust growth of 45.76% quarter-on-quarter and 27.52% year-on-year. However, the stock remains under pressure, trading at ₹472.30 as of January 22, 2026, down 33.41% over the past three months despite an 11.38% surge in the latest trading session.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4c5c6d6aa6c1fe3883339fed0d1c6a7c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Travenues Technology Q3 FY26: Strong Revenue Growth Masks Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/le-travenues-technology-q3-fy26-strong-revenue-growth-masks-profitability-concerns-3800681</link><description>Le Travenues Technology Limited, the travel technology company operating the ixigo platform, delivered a mixed performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit surging to ₹24.26 crores—a remarkable recovery from the ₹3.18 crores loss in the previous quarter. However, the quarter-on-quarter growth figure of -862.89% reflects the volatility stemming from the prior quarter's anomaly. On a year-on-year basis, the company posted a healthier 56.31% profit growth, whilst revenue climbed 31.35% to ₹317.56 crores, marking the highest quarterly sales in the company's history.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a84f05e63bf8b014bd083aacfb24fece</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krystal Integrated Services Q2 FY26: Profitability Under Pressure Amid Revenue Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/krystal-integrated-services-q2-fy26-profitability-under-pressure-amid-revenue-volatility-3800678</link><description>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd., a micro-cap diversified commercial services provider with a market capitalisation of ₹849.00 crores, reported mixed quarterly results for Q2 FY26, with consolidated net profit declining 19.91% sequentially to ₹9.21 crores despite modest year-on-year revenue growth. The company's stock, trading at ₹601.05 on January 22, 2026, has declined 5.79% over the past year, significantly underperforming the Sensex's 7.73% gain during the same period.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b224304c184fe883029124784118e8bd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home First Finance Q3 FY26: Strong Profit Growth Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/home-first-finance-q3-fy26-strong-profit-growth-amid-valuation-concerns-3800677</link><description>Home First Finance Company India Limited, a small-cap housing finance company with a market capitalisation of ₹10,887 crores, reported robust financial performance for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), with net profit climbing to ₹140.20 crores—a sequential increase of 6.33% and an impressive year-on-year surge of 43.99%. The stock, currently trading at ₹1,049.60, has gained 0.86% following the results announcement, though it remains under pressure with a 16.26% decline over the past three months.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>027f898d20ab91c4d8a56942d812ddf7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Q3 FY26: Asset Quality Improves But Profitability Remains Under Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bandhan-bank-q3-fy26-asset-quality-improves-but-profitability-remains-under-pressure-3800676</link><description>Bandhan Bank Ltd., one of India's prominent microfinance-turned-universal banks, reported a net profit of ₹205.59 crores for Q3 FY26 (Oct-Dec'25), marking an 83.78% sequential recovery from the previous quarter's ₹111.87 crores. However, the year-on-year comparison reveals a more sobering reality, with profits plunging 51.79% from ₹426.49 crores in Q3 FY25. The Kolkata-headquartered lender, commanding a market capitalisation of ₹22,546 crores, continues to navigate challenging terrain as asset quality concerns and margin pressures weigh on its performance despite some green shoots emerging in the latest quarter.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d04435c725ca134445bf3822b879861c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nexome Capital Markets Q2 FY26: Profit Tumbles 21% as Revenue Halves Quarter-on-Quarter</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/nexome-capital-markets-q2-fy26-profit-tumbles-21-as-revenue-halves-quarter-on-quarter-3800675</link><description>Nexome Capital Markets Ltd., a micro-cap non-banking financial company with a market capitalisation of ₹50.00 crores, reported a challenging Q2 FY26 performance, with net profit declining 21.26% quarter-on-quarter to ₹1.00 crore despite a 300.00% year-on-year surge. The stock, currently trading at ₹83.50, has plunged 50.28% from its 52-week high of ₹167.95, reflecting investor concerns over the company's erratic operational performance and mounting pressure on core business profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>471c7827a3a621830e492f9bcc765a9e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mphasis Q3 FY26: Steady Growth Amid Margin Pressures and Promoter Stake Reduction</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mphasis-q3-fy26-steady-growth-amid-margin-pressures-and-promoter-stake-reduction-3800674</link><description>Mphasis Ltd., a mid-cap IT services provider specialising in cloud and cognitive solutions, reported consolidated net profit of ₹469.07 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sequential increase of 6.20% from Q2 FY26's ₹441.70 crores and a year-on-year growth of 10.80% compared to ₹423.33 crores in Q3 FY25. The Bengaluru-headquartered firm, with a market capitalisation of ₹54,673 crores, continues to demonstrate resilient top-line momentum whilst navigating margin headwinds and a significant shift in shareholding structure.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>577a9bb95cbb7fcd51f572fed95e9fff</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cyient Q2 FY26: Margin Pressures Mount Amid Revenue Stagnation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/cyient-q2-fy26-margin-pressures-mount-amid-revenue-stagnation-3800673</link><description>Cyient Ltd., the Hyderabad-based engineering and technology solutions provider with a market capitalisation of ₹12,556 crores, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹127.50 crores for Q2 FY26, marking a sharp decline of 17.10% quarter-on-quarter and 28.81% year-on-year. The results underscore mounting operational challenges as the company grapples with margin compression and tepid revenue growth in an increasingly competitive IT services landscape.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e2d04241bd1d60750ad9a2f65604d9e2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IndiGo Q3 FY26: Turbulence Hits India's Aviation Leader as Losses Mount</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/indigo-q3-fy26-turbulence-hits-indias-aviation-leader-as-losses-mount-3800672</link><description>InterGlobe Aviation Ltd., India's largest airline operating under the IndiGo brand, posted a consolidated net profit of ₹549.80 crores for Q3 FY26 (Oct-Dec'25), representing a dramatic reversal from the ₹2,581.70 crores loss recorded in the previous quarter. However, the year-on-year comparison reveals concerning weakness, with profits plunging 77.55% from ₹2,448.80 crores in Q3 FY25, raising questions about the sustainability of the carrier's profitability amidst rising operational pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>007ba295067f2578134101b1f2ffb102</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Forbes Precision Tools Q3 FY26: Profit Decline Signals Margin Pressures Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/forbes-precision-tools-q3-fy26-profit-decline-signals-margin-pressures-despite-revenue-growth-3800671</link><description>Forbes Precision Tools &amp; Machine Parts Ltd. reported a concerning 32.66% quarter-on-quarter decline in net profit for Q3 FY26, posting ₹5.59 crores compared to ₹8.30 crores in Q2 FY26, despite achieving modest revenue growth of 1.74%. The micro-cap industrial manufacturing company, with a market capitalisation of ₹700 crores, saw its stock price decline 2.17% year-to-date to ₹135.00, reflecting investor concerns about deteriorating profitability trends and margin compression that have overshadowed top-line expansion.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c083d59b73a196317449e6889511e5e1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Q3 FY26: Profit Growth Masks Mounting Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/adani-energy-solutions-q3-fy26-profit-growth-masks-mounting-valuation-concerns-3800670</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd., India's largest private transmission company, reported consolidated net profit of ₹533.97 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sequential improvement of 4.19% from Q2 FY26 but a concerning year-on-year decline of 20.89%. The stock, currently trading at ₹925.00 with a market capitalisation of ₹111,311 crores, faces mounting pressure from its stretched valuation despite operational resilience.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>955dcf98a3e09231f2d6eedd9f593857</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>