<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Afcons Infrastructure Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-afcons-infrastructure-ltd-fallingrising-3843039</link><description>As of 16-Feb, Afcons Infrastructure Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹325.05, down 2.08% on the day, reflecting a continuation of a downward trend driven by weak financial performance, subdued investor participation, and market concerns over debt servicing and promoter share pledging.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ca21ca96ec6cab17e4897c3e90b124f2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solarium Green Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solarium-green-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3843038</link><description>On 16-Feb, Solarium Green Energy Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 8.93% to close at ₹180.55, marking a continuation of a pronounced downtrend that has seen the share price hit new 52-week and all-time lows amid subdued investor participation and persistent selling pressure.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c8d6951dcd30b3657c90b8d59b93a808</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shipping-corporation-of-india-land-assets-ltd-fallingrising-3843037</link><description>As of 16-Feb, Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd has seen its share price fall by 2.03% to ₹45.40, continuing a downward trend driven by weak financial results, poor long-term growth, and underwhelming investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6136fcd0e0b1abd44da8a1861b11c95e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3843036</link><description>On 16-Feb, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.06% to close at ₹346.55. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f0b0559fd513ddfc318e73da113cbe50</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinyas-innovative-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3843035</link><description>On 16-Feb, Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.16% to close at ₹995.50. This drop reflects a broader short-term weakness in the stock’s performance despite its strong long-term gains.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>42dd609214e393e398ade9e83f581ebd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-venus-pipes-tubes-ltd-fallingrising-3843034</link><description>On 16-Feb, Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.69% to close at ₹1,125.10. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum amid broader market challenges and waning investor interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d9f24b93c9b41bc9b1e54fcec3aa2f37</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AGS Transact Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ags-transact-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3843033</link><description>On 16-Feb, AGS Transact Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹3.72, down by ₹0.12 or 3.12%. This drop reflects ongoing challenges for the stock, which has underperformed both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bcf6474275407817303fc493ceedb3c1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-upsurge-seeds-of-agriculture-ltd-fallingrising-3843032</link><description>As of 16-Feb, Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.99% to ₹125.65. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ef9cce5fc148341838a90bb5173aa14e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shri Venkatesh Refineries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shri-venkatesh-refineries-ltd-fallingrising-3843031</link><description>As of 16-Feb, Shri Venkatesh Refineries Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 7.7% to ₹251.05. This significant drop reflects mounting concerns over the company’s financial health, weak recent performance, and investor caution amid erratic trading patterns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9749060a1a0e2536caafd8d29b3e32c2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EKI Energy Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-eki-energy-services-ltd-fallingrising-3843030</link><description>On 16-Feb, EKI Energy Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹96.75, down by ₹1.92 or 1.95%. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including sustained negative financial results and underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>28bc2a4d2d573a468a9524084bec24a7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Artemis Electricals &amp; Projects Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-artemis-electricals-projects-ltd-fallingrising-3843029</link><description>On 16-Feb, Artemis Electricals &amp; Projects Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹19.71, down by 1.89% or ₹0.38. This drop reflects a continuation of underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market indices, driven primarily by disappointing quarterly financial results and subdued investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d0582aab10ec5dbcdd92392948d782bc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anuroop Packaging Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anuroop-packaging-ltd-fallingrising-3843028</link><description>On 16-Feb, Anuroop Packaging Ltd witnessed a significant price surge, rising by 19.94% to close at ₹12.57, reflecting robust short-term gains despite longer-term challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c2f728bd9c4b44523f6d597af95c7bc7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Anup Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-anup-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3843027</link><description>On 16-Feb, The Anup Engineering Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, falling by 5.64% to close at ₹1,871.10. This decline reflects a continuation of recent negative trends driven by disappointing quarterly earnings and valuation pressures, despite the company’s strong long-term growth fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d2f7018a8f860594e5c2df9cf54c54f4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is United Van Der Horst Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-united-van-der-horst-ltd-fallingrising-3843025</link><description>On 16-Feb, United Van Der Horst Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹46.66 with a 5.0% gain. This movement reflects a continuation of a strong upward trend that has significantly outperformed the broader market benchmarks over various time horizons.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cb743d51b4026e80033713f89f621d42</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sharanam Infraproject &amp; Trading Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sharanam-infraproject-trading-ltd-fallingrising-3843026</link><description>As of the latest available data, Sharanam Infraproject &amp; Trading Ltd has experienced a significant and sustained decline in its stock price, markedly underperforming the broader market benchmarks over multiple time horizons.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a6933f8bc668c15529208948abe19e5d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Halder Venture Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-halder-venture-ltd-fallingrising-3843024</link><description>On 16-Feb, Halder Venture Ltd experienced a slight downturn in its share price, falling by 1.12% to close at ₹265.00. This decline follows a two-day losing streak, reflecting a short-term correction despite the stock’s impressive long-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c4c667ceafa8bdc12fbdec337ddb3ad3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jubilant-ingrevia-ltd-fallingrising-3843023</link><description>As of 16-Feb, Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 2.1% to ₹628.25, continuing a downward trend over the past week and month, reflecting investor concerns over the company’s subdued sales growth and declining profitability despite some positive fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>26c48951136b20c9cfb77650ba2db94a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Beta Drugs Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-beta-drugs-ltd-fallingrising-3843022</link><description>On 16-Feb, Beta Drugs Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 17.74% to close at ₹1,129.90. This significant drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cdb1ca89df4f9c95a8dc58a57870dad4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ascom-leasing-investments-ltd-fallingrising-3843021</link><description>On 16-Feb, Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 5.0% to ₹179.55 by 9:04 PM, reflecting robust outperformance against both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>70fdbc66ab25c33f98116d5ff02cff4c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kranti Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kranti-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3843020</link><description>On 16-Feb, Kranti Industries Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 8.51% to close at ₹72.22. This sharp drop follows a brief period of gains and reflects a combination of profit-taking, reduced investor participation, and technical pressures despite the stock's strong longer-term performance relative to the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>208e2888cd3a15404b76415c2e0aa801</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>