<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Heritage Foods Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/heritage-foods-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3802351</link><description>Heritage Foods Ltd, a small-cap player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development, coupled with deteriorating price momentum and weak relative performance against the Sensex, raises concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>f7140e527545962e5e10b8bb1026d4a7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Marine Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-marine-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3802352</link><description>Garware Marine Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>2fa3c7823faa6e5c657b2add5a484a89</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sar Televenture Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sar-televenture-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3802349</link><description>Sar Televenture Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that the stock may be poised for an upward trend reversal despite recent underperformance relative to the broader market.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>0cb524491a13a5c5d6dd30b279317261</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Q4 2025 Earnings Review: Broad-Based Improvement with Mid-Caps Leading Profit Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q4-2025-earnings-review-broad-based-improvement-with-mid-caps-leading-profit-growth-3802348</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has unfolded with a notable improvement in positive results, particularly among mid and small cap stocks, signalling a cautious yet optimistic market environment. With 387 companies having declared results, the aggregate data reveals sectoral disparities and evolving profit trajectories that investors should carefully analyse.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>f479272bcd90085d4405fb090f71a2f3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BEML Land Assets Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Signal Deepening Distress</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/beml-land-assets-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-signal-deepening-distress-3802342</link><description>BEML Land Assets Ltd., the demerged non-core asset holding company of BEML Ltd., reported a net loss of ₹0.46 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a marginal improvement from the ₹0.53 crore loss in Q2 FY26 but representing a deterioration from the ₹0.44 crore loss in Q3 FY25. The micro-cap NBFC, with a market capitalisation of ₹842 crores, continues to struggle with operational viability as the stock declined 1.70% following the results, trading at ₹196.60 and reflecting mounting investor concerns about the company's ability to generate positive cash flows.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>18256493acbc6941e0d02972ea388395</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paras Defence Q3 FY26: Growth Momentum Intact Despite Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/paras-defence-q3-fy26-growth-momentum-intact-despite-margin-pressure-3802340</link><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd., a specialised aerospace and defence manufacturer, reported consolidated net profit of ₹18.21 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a decline of 11.77% quarter-on-quarter but a robust growth of 21.08% year-on-year. The ₹5,193 crore market capitalisation company continues to demonstrate strong top-line momentum with revenue expanding 23.99% YoY to ₹106.35 crores, though margin compression remains a concern for investors. The stock has declined 3.83% following the results announcement, trading at ₹623.70 and reflecting cautious market sentiment towards the premium-valued defence play.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6292e11262d0f0c3cf763232f5ba7864</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Green Energy Q3 FY26: Sharp Losses and Mounting Financial Pressures Test Investor Confidence</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/adani-green-energy-q3-fy26-sharp-losses-and-mounting-financial-pressures-test-investor-confidence-3802324</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd., one of India's largest renewable energy companies with a project portfolio of 21,953 MW, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹41.00 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a dramatic reversal from the ₹583.00 crores profit recorded in the previous quarter. The 107.03% quarter-on-quarter decline represents the company's first quarterly loss in recent years, sending shockwaves through the market and triggering a sharp 14.63% stock price decline to ₹772.10 on January 23, 2026.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f0aa2b935014ed01bf0587e97118ec16</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D.P. Abhushan Q3 FY26: Record Quarter Masks Valuation Concerns Amid Technical Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/dp-abhushan-q3-fy26-record-quarter-masks-valuation-concerns-amid-technical-weakness-3802323</link><description>D.P. Abhushan Ltd., the Madhya Pradesh-based jewellery retailer with a market capitalisation of ₹3,344 crores, delivered a stellar operational performance in Q3 FY26, posting record quarterly net profit of ₹73.35 crores. However, the stock has struggled to translate this fundamental strength into market performance, declining 5.21% on January 23, 2026, to close at ₹1,387.95, reflecting broader technical weakness and valuation concerns that have plagued the counter over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d9d5fc95d1ac4a4ffc28ddedc3c3dbb2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sampann Utpadan Q2 FY26: Strong Revenue Growth Masks Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sampann-utpadan-q2-fy26-strong-revenue-growth-masks-profitability-concerns-3802322</link><description>Sampann Utpadan India Ltd. (formerly S. E. Power Limited), a micro-cap industrial products manufacturer, reported Q2 FY26 net profit of ₹1.85 crores, representing marginal sequential growth of 1.09% from Q1 FY26's ₹1.83 crores. However, the year-on-year comparison reveals a stark reversal, with profits declining 263.72% from the previous year's loss of ₹1.13 crores. The company's stock has struggled significantly, trading at ₹30.70 as of January 23, 2026, down 21.16% over the past year whilst the market gained 6.56%, reflecting investor concerns about valuation and profitability sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7d482d408b29104d737aab970c35aa5a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Cements Q3 FY26: Turnaround Stumbles as Losses Return Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/india-cements-q3-fy26-turnaround-stumbles-as-losses-return-despite-revenue-growth-3802321</link><description>India Cements Limited, South India's largest cement producer, reported a disappointing Q3 FY26 performance with a consolidated net loss of ₹2.67 crores, reversing the previous quarter's profit of ₹8.81 crores. Despite achieving an 18.56% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹1,114.26 crores, the company's inability to sustain profitability has raised serious concerns about operational efficiency and cost management. The stock reacted sharply, plunging 5.75% to ₹432.00 following the results announcement, reflecting investor disappointment over the fragile recovery trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>90446997cbec9afe32185e278c19112c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Q3 FY26: Strong AUM Growth Drives 9% Profit Rise Despite Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/shriram-finance-q3-fy26-strong-aum-growth-drives-9-profit-rise-despite-margin-pressures-3802320</link><description>Shriram Finance Ltd., India's leading non-banking financial company specialising in commercial vehicle financing, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹2,529.65 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a robust 9.31% sequential growth and maintaining its position as the sector's second-largest player with a market capitalisation of ₹1,89,569 crores. The stock, trading at ₹1,003.45 as of January 23, 2026, has delivered an exceptional 89.28% return over the past year, significantly outperforming the broader market despite a modest 0.29% dip in the latest trading session.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>304e946802e7aca2eff1e8c99327df41</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kirloskar Pneumatic Q3 FY26: Modest Growth Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kirloskar-pneumatic-q3-fy26-modest-growth-amid-valuation-concerns-3802318</link><description>Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Ltd., a prominent player in India's compressors and industrial equipment sector with a market capitalisation of ₹7,208 crores, reported a modest performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit declining 2.99% quarter-on-quarter to ₹42.20 crores despite revenue growth of 5.31%. The stock has faced significant headwinds over the past year, declining 17.56% and trading at ₹1,060.45, down 31.50% from its 52-week high of ₹1,548.00, as investors grapple with premium valuations and muted near-term momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0981392f844d0301265ac2bee37c7126</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Finserve Q3 FY26: Robust Growth Momentum Masks Rising Leverage Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sg-finserve-q3-fy26-robust-growth-momentum-masks-rising-leverage-concerns-3802317</link><description>SG Finserve Ltd., a Delhi-based non-banking financial company specialising in supply chain financing solutions, reported its strongest quarterly performance in Q3 FY26 with net profit surging 14.33% quarter-on-quarter to ₹32.47 crores and an impressive 37.06% year-on-year growth. However, the stock has struggled to translate this operational momentum into market performance, declining 8.06% over the past month and trading 18.36% below its 52-week high of ₹460.60 at ₹376.05 as of January 23, 2026.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1bcb12cfb93a9f0cb4bcdb734abbd6c6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3802316</link><description>Shares of Dev Information Technology Ltd have declined to within 0.5% of their 52-week low, closing near Rs 30, marking a significant downturn amid broader market pressures and company-specific performance concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>22886e6b4e924d95b3018c61a1ae99f4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sundaram Clayton Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1150</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sundaram-clayton-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1150-3802313</link><description>Sundaram Clayton Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.1150 today, marking a significant decline amid persistent downward momentum. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures, with a notable underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>cfe8540766afcf846fca9b0379f331bf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Pipes Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.75 Amidst Broad Market Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hi-tech-pipes-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs75-amidst-broad-market-weakness-3802311</link><description>Hi-Tech Pipes Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.75 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market pressures and company-specific factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5a6d6220525843e2484b7c52334652ab</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airan Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.13.65 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/airan-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1365-amidst-continued-downtrend-3802312</link><description>Airan Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.13.65 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market pressures and company-specific performance issues.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>14a98e6368d7b81a116859abafa04656</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AVG Logistics Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.138 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avg-logistics-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs138-amidst-continued-downtrend-3802310</link><description>Shares of AVG Logistics Ltd, a player in the Transport Services sector, declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.138 on 23 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This fresh low reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>516525dd1dcb30681b7c821a7da54415</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diligent Media Corporation Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/diligent-media-corporation-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3802302</link><description>Diligent Media Corporation Ltd’s stock has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near ₹3.25, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock’s recent performance reflects persistent pressures within the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, with the share price now just 4.41% above its lowest point in the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>079cafd0c90ae1ee61588935e6ad063e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>