<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Tamboli Industri falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tamboli-industri-fallingrising-3758994</link><description>On 15 Dec, Tamboli Industries Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, continuing a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks and months, reflecting broader challenges faced by the stock relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 18 seconds ago</description><guid>4f9d12dbe0ab5fde8005ecadb4cdd3fc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Som Datt Finance falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-som-datt-finance-fallingrising-3758993</link><description>On 15-Dec, Som Datt Finance Corporation Ltd recorded a price increase of 1.08%, closing at ₹111.95, reflecting a continuation of recent positive momentum despite a challenging broader market context.
Time: 20 seconds ago</description><guid>5f4239e3560284d39cc0d8a5f1776897</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Seasons Textiles falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-seasons-textiles-fallingrising-3758992</link><description>On 15 Dec, Seasons Textiles Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, closing at ₹20.49, up ₹1.49 or 7.84% from the previous close. This upward movement reflects a strong short-term momentum supported by robust trading activity and technical indicators.
Time: 22 seconds ago</description><guid>ce7c8d4f99c0389f583aea319e3e45d0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rasandik Engg. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rasandik-engg-fallingrising-3758991</link><description>On 15-Dec, Rasandik Engineering Industries India Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at Rs 60.18, down by Rs 3.66 or 5.73% from the previous close. This drop marks a fresh 52-week low for the stock and reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 23 seconds ago</description><guid>4229db44d25ccccd3ecdceab5e0ac30c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sangal Papers falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sangal-papers-fallingrising-3758990</link><description>On 15 Dec, Sangal Papers Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 13.66%, closing at ₹215.95. This sharp rise reflects a combination of strong technical momentum and heightened investor participation, setting the stock apart from broader market trends.
Time: 23 seconds ago</description><guid>b50c4fdde93fee490a7df3f66ab7801e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Energy Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-energy-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3758948</link><description>JSW Energy, a prominent player in the power sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price over the longer term.
Time: Dec 15 2025 06:20 PM IST</description><guid>4b3dd8a1e0b938c3932760a36cf3587b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Pesticides Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-pesticides-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3758945</link><description>India Pesticides, a player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: Dec 15 2025 06:02 PM IST</description><guid>c1f0757ae8f4ece47bdc36bfbfd97843</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dodla Dairy Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dodla-dairy-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3758944</link><description>Dodla Dairy, a player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and may indicate a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: Dec 15 2025 06:02 PM IST</description><guid>5a0675a6d93f2b95f06b41ac24d9c078</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bodhi Tree Multimedia Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bodhi-tree-multimedia-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3758943</link><description>Bodhi Tree Multimedia, a player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price over the longer term.
Time: Dec 15 2025 06:02 PM IST</description><guid>e92be3bcec65bac76616a8e7cfb91b27</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indiamart Intermesh Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indiamart-intermesh-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3758940</link><description>Indiamart Intermesh, a key player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: Dec 15 2025 06:02 PM IST</description><guid>b9cacde869dc5595022cf2308fe69ae8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supra Pacific Management Consultancy Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supra-pacific-management-consultancy-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3758941</link><description>Supra Pacific Management Consultancy, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the medium to long term.
Time: Dec 15 2025 06:02 PM IST</description><guid>36312ea80cc47306534cf722b3b074bc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navkar Corporation Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/navkar-corporation-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3758942</link><description>Navkar Corporation, a player in the Transport Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: Dec 15 2025 06:02 PM IST</description><guid>9d759422d6f73b71be59831d26347de5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>