<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Raymond Lifestyle Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-raymond-lifestyle-ltd-fallingrising-3775549</link><description>As of 30-Dec, Raymond Lifestyle Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting persistent fundamental challenges and sustained investor caution despite some signs of promoter confidence.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>feb4bd059269f586cdeaa3a7ae7b5953</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ola Electric Mobility Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ola-electric-mobility-ltd-fallingrising-3775547</link><description>On 30-Dec, Ola Electric Mobility Ltd's stock price rose by 3.27% to close at ₹36.59, marking a notable intraday high of ₹36.78. Despite this short-term uptick, the company continues to face significant long-term financial headwinds, reflected in its sustained negative returns and weak fundamentals.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>5afcd843b5bac652854656ea23528b9d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kataria Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kataria-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3775546</link><description>On 30-Dec, Kataria Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹98.80, down ₹5.55 or 5.32% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s challenging performance over the past year, contrasting sharply with broader market gains.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>4df9f35865fd927e7905e795ae135d61</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shivalic Power Control Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shivalic-power-control-ltd-fallingrising-3775545</link><description>On 30-Dec, Shivalic Power Control Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 11.12%, closing at ₹90.90, reflecting a notable shift in market sentiment despite a challenging year-to-date performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>dfdcde4ce57eda31b7369211479aae06</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3775544</link><description>On 30-Dec, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.3% to close at ₹413.45. This drop comes despite the stock's strong year-to-date gains, reflecting a combination of technical pressures and relative underperformance against its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>10445dc6ebf11c4064b4f61c28733d89</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3775543</link><description>On 30-Dec, Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.53% to close at ₹135.00. This movement reflects a continuation of a broader downward trend that has persisted over recent months and years, with the stock significantly underperforming the benchmark Sensex and its sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>6de0328610f440ed2edecf29b459b165</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awfis-space-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3775542</link><description>On 30-Dec, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹476.45, down by ₹8.15 or 1.68%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid broader concerns over the company’s financial metrics and market performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>1b3922d6d311531d40921a56ffb487be</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Quest Laboratories Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-quest-laboratories-ltd-fallingrising-3775541</link><description>On 30-Dec, Quest Laboratories Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.65% to ₹104.65 by 09:22 PM, reflecting a strong market response despite a challenging year-to-date performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b235e6fdd7800b3fdc8191d04d5cc2ce</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-popular-vehicles-services-ltd-fallingrising-3775540</link><description>As of 30-Dec, Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd has experienced a notable decline in its share price, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial performance and market sentiment. The stock’s fall is underpinned by weak profitability, deteriorating operating metrics, and underwhelming returns compared to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>7b4b75b82cea61ea4d573c8739dcedb5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enser Communications Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enser-communications-ltd-fallingrising-3775539</link><description>On 30-Dec, Enser Communications Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 11.08% to ₹14.45 by 09:22 PM, reflecting a continuation of a prolonged downward trend that has significantly underperformed the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>5329d6982b65578b18622c1040a5c4fa</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nova Agritech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nova-agritech-ltd-fallingrising-3775538</link><description>On 30-Dec, Nova Agritech Ltd's stock price continued its downward trajectory, closing at ₹38.03, down 0.65% from the previous session. The stock hit a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹37.76 during the day, reflecting sustained selling pressure and underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>3df3992391ad4561510e3f99d281e6b4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree OSFM E-Mobility Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-osfm-e-mobility-ltd-fallingrising-3775537</link><description>On 30-Dec, Shree OSFM E-Mobility Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹73.20, down ₹2.05 or 2.72% from the previous session. This drop marks a fresh 52-week low for the stock, reflecting sustained downward pressure over recent periods.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>58da0ef8eede3eee597c89aaed9e3a5b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Tata Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tata-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3775536</link><description>As of 30-Dec, Tata Technologies Ltd has experienced a notable decline in its share price, falling by 1.85% to ₹639.10. This downward trend reflects a combination of disappointing recent financial results, sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks, and weakening investor interest.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>541601ba041e034e7774637e4b59b62e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Plada Infotech Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-plada-infotech-services-ltd-fallingrising-3775535</link><description>On 30-Dec, Plada Infotech Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.26% to close at ₹15.75. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and technical indicators, signalling challenges for the stock in the near term.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>520f529a252889beb64509fe5e511ffd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is C P S Shapers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-c-p-s-shapers-ltd-fallingrising-3775534</link><description>On 30-Dec, C P S Shapers Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, reaching a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹1,146.60, up by ₹54.6 or 5.0% as of 09:19 PM. This surge reflects robust performance over multiple timeframes, far outpacing benchmark indices and sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>424e848c4bb1bdf9d44720e9712edaa3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Crop Life Science Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-crop-life-science-ltd-fallingrising-3775533</link><description>On 30-Dec, Crop Life Science Ltd's stock price surged by 6.17%, closing at ₹49.90, reflecting a notable intraday gain despite a challenging broader market environment and mixed longer-term returns.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>ff9732430144f69ed357201eb3942725</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinsys IT Services India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinsys-it-services-india-ltd-fallingrising-3775532</link><description>On 30-Dec, Vinsys IT Services India Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹360.40, down ₹4.00 or 1.1% from the previous session. This drop reflects broader challenges faced by the stock over recent periods, marked by underperformance relative to key benchmarks and waning investor interest.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>0ea744d5ea38a5458e3fffaabdb9652e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Urban Enviro Waste Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-urban-enviro-waste-management-ltd-fallingrising-3775531</link><description>On 30-Dec, Urban Enviro Waste Management Ltd recorded a slight increase in its share price, rising by 0.52% to ₹154.00, reflecting a modest recovery despite a challenging year marked by significant declines relative to the broader market.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>4d0579f21e0841b80437d56ae735c3b8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is NMDC Steel Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nmdc-steel-ltd-fallingrising-3775530</link><description>As of 30-Dec, NMDC Steel Ltd’s stock price has risen by 3.54% to ₹43.24, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices despite underlying long-term fundamental challenges.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>136573a36680114d197c1503160ffc39</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is eMudhra Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-emudhra-ltd-fallingrising-3775529</link><description>On 30-Dec, eMudhra Ltd’s stock price fell to a new 52-week low of ₹580, declining by 2.47% during the trading session and continuing a recent downward trend that has seen the share price drop by 3.68% over the last two days.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>71187f8a3e68973da8521a927946da82</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>