<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Elecon Engineering Q3 FY26: Profit Plunge Raises Concerns Despite Revenue Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/elecon-engineering-q3-fy26-profit-plunge-raises-concerns-despite-revenue-resilience-3785868</link><description>Elecon Engineering Company Ltd., a leading manufacturer of material handling equipment and power transmission solutions, reported a concerning quarter-on-quarter decline in profitability for Q3 FY26, despite maintaining revenue stability. The company posted a consolidated net profit of ₹71.99 crores for the quarter ended December 2025, marking a sharp 17.93% decline from the previous quarter's ₹87.72 crores. More worryingly, on a year-on-year basis, net profit plummeted 33.06% from ₹107.54 crores in Q3 FY25, signalling deteriorating operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ee596aaee28e90a93e3e259e1b80af61</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-transformers-rectifiers-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3785866</link><description>Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd reported strong Q3 FY26 results with a net profit of ₹73.85 crores and record net sales of ₹736.76 crores, reflecting robust operational performance. However, the stock price declined amid market volatility, indicating mixed investor sentiment despite the positive financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d35ee0eda7e2224150bb38853da1526f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-yuranus-infrastructure-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3785865</link><description>Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a dramatic but misleading sales increase alongside persistent operating losses and a deteriorating financial position, with five consecutive quarters of losses totaling ₹1.25 crores. The company faces significant operational challenges and a declining return on equity and capital employed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a2b00f63f6a022e1b02c2186c7dc3801</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Eimco Elecon (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-eimco-elecon-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3785864</link><description>Eimco Elecon (India) Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit of ₹12.52 crores and a significant sales increase of 74.72%, indicating recovery; however, concerns remain due to a low return on equity of 4.92% and reliance on other income, suggesting ongoing operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>35f6db5837ff1486722765d4e18b5f9a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Madhya Bharat Agro Products Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-madhya-bharat-agro-products-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3785863</link><description>Madhya Bharat Agro Products Ltd's latest results are positive, showing a 115.84% increase in revenue and a 77.41% rise in net profit year-on-year. However, the operating margin has declined, indicating challenges in maintaining profitability amidst growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e9420783d5f3f27e17e4eb7eec9dadfc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aries Agro Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aries-agro-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785844</link><description>Aries Agro Ltd, a micro-cap player in the fertilisers sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development, coupled with deteriorating momentum indicators and a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell, raises concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bc6eaee9e86f4115993591cb080510c1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Estates Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-estates-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785841</link><description>Max Estates Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a3e4809f5eecfc1085af3723ec037756</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Terminals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allcargo-terminals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785840</link><description>Allcargo Terminals Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its long-term prospects amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>70792367ebc7dd39b9681628dcbad7e3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785842</link><description>Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>801b2dee7bba67d22467c5822bc474bc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We Win Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/we-win-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785839</link><description>We Win Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Commercial Services &amp; Supplies sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>95506a9e27ec9e6300d205a5ad00081a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nexome Capital Markets Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nexome-capital-markets-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785843</link><description>Nexome Capital Markets Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fabf832052722e0a01d49f4342f53042</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balkrishna-paper-mills-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785838</link><description>Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>781bb4a1f61540d2b0cfb15f1084c187</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kemistar Corporation Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kemistar-corporation-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785835</link><description>Kemistar Corporation Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>75e87904e04ce36fac830ee294114a20</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Bell Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orient-bell-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785834</link><description>Orient Bell Ltd., a micro-cap player in the diversified consumer products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ff0f216a09b6ad3efd524cef980ee6c1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zenith Steel Pipes &amp; Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zenith-steel-pipes-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3785833</link><description>Zenith Steel Pipes &amp; Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and suggests a bearish outlook for investors amid ongoing sectoral and company-specific challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>55c50883d6fbf8a701764a573a7bc4c9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kunststoffe Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kunststoffe-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3785832</link><description>Kunststoffe Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend and long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3dbde42e524b0a33962537db2f3a1e57</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Western India Plywoods Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/western-india-plywoods-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785836</link><description>Western India Plywoods Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term prospects.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>91a4c7a9b4442c95adeced9ba999cbbe</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utique Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/utique-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785831</link><description>Utique Enterprises Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non - Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a5dd8e135ba7bb9d2e24ac1e9a3fdfbc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Agrolife Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/best-agrolife-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3785837</link><description>Best Agrolife Ltd, a player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>682faae1272e68808979496a31ded5f8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MM Forgings Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mm-forgings-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3785828</link><description>MM Forgings Ltd., a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s trajectory amid mixed recent performances.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ab7c335d1ee5db66979dd758659dd294</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>