<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>RBZ Jewellers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rbz-jewellers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809992</link><description>RBZ Jewellers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development reflects a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>216e1b9e0de6527a4f69053132fc5d3e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delhivery Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/delhivery-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809991</link><description>Delhivery Ltd, a key player in the Transport Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>5920a09a61fd067f4986b2865e76872a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Patterns (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/data-patterns-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809988</link><description>Data Patterns (India) Ltd, a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>94befabcf7801d437865f65f0ab6ad0c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lemon-tree-hotels-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3809990</link><description>Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>d62e37faf7a18478f834e2a32060d1e3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Riba Textiles Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/riba-textiles-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809989</link><description>Riba Textiles Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200 DMA. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raising concerns about long-term weakness amid challenging market conditions.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>344ec77595c9dd7254f81a3a8a7705dc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JTEKT India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jtekt-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809986</link><description>JTEKT India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>1fbbe286ee1fb4dc282a8149bd3ca5e5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Nippon Electricals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-nippon-electricals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809985</link><description>India Nippon Electricals Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>eb3012cfdd752f83d9e508b652013320</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Endurance Technologies Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/endurance-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809987</link><description>Endurance Technologies Ltd., a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term strength.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>b6ab6e9abd978dc0940e40ba1f8c52d6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sobha Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sobha-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809983</link><description>Sobha Ltd., a prominent player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development, coupled with deteriorating momentum indicators and a downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Strong Sell, raises concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook amid broader market pressures.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f3609c011f21b25bb60896393bbd65ea</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DigiSpice Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/digispice-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3809982</link><description>DigiSpice Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>bdcde2a457906f2536be1578ff6383c3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVR Inox Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pvr-inox-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809979</link><description>PVR Inox Ltd, a key player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>b9bee245ae987e2e9f4ba38b3f2ca99e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OnMobile Global Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/onmobile-global-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3809984</link><description>OnMobile Global Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>d8ed02e203447393824994e1e0f9bcf6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Energy Development Company Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/energy-development-company-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3809980</link><description>Energy Development Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>6b4aca96a5f8f712f0d96567789cc9a4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pilani Investment &amp; Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pilani-investment-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-momentum-3809978</link><description>Pilani Investment &amp; Industries Corporation Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>729a10b8c40b181d99b70354bca49e1c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vipul Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vipul-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3809977</link><description>Vipul Ltd, a micro-cap player in the realty sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that investors may want to closely monitor the stock for possible trend reversals despite its recent underperformance.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>20b546419a7dff760a8f6d557aa0d72d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fermenta Biotech Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fermenta-biotech-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3809981</link><description>Fermenta Biotech Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that investors may want to reassess the stock’s outlook amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>c402eacb5a87872b3b373a3d0cecb0fe</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mixed Earnings Momentum as 650 Companies Report Dec-2025 Quarterly Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mixed-earnings-momentum-as-650-companies-report-dec-2025-quarterly-results-3809975</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has delivered a mixed bag of results with exactly half of the 650 companies declaring their numbers reporting positive outcomes. While mid and small caps continue to outperform large caps in terms of profitability, sectoral leaders and micro-cap performers have also emerged, signalling nuanced trends across the market.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>197dc76acf1862bb6727b87db76268b5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil India Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3809976</link><description>Oil India Ltd. has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the mid-cap oil company, which has outperformed the Sensex over multiple time frames.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>19f5c616e432be0c93e9a99618686aa3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summit Securities Q3 FY26: Profit Plunges 81% Despite Strong Nine-Month Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/summit-securities-q3-fy26-profit-plunges-81-despite-strong-nine-month-performance-3809995</link><description>Summit Securities Ltd., a non-banking financial company specialising in investments in shares and securities, reported a sharp sequential decline in its third-quarter results for FY2026, with net profit plummeting 81.23% quarter-on-quarter to ₹17.02 crores from ₹90.66 crores in Q2 FY26. The dramatic drop follows an exceptional second quarter that saw profits surge 349.03%. Despite the quarterly setback, the company's nine-month performance remains robust, with year-on-year growth metrics showing significant improvement. The stock, currently trading at ₹1,739.00 with a market capitalisation of ₹1,864 crores, has declined 10.60% year-to-date as investors digest the volatile quarterly performance.
Time: 43 minutes ago</description><guid>2dd43e5bce109fe972e9397bdbf3f871</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coromandel International Q3 FY26: Sequential Profit Decline Amid Volume Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/coromandel-international-q3-fy26-sequential-profit-decline-amid-volume-pressures-3809993</link><description>Coromandel International Ltd., India's largest fertiliser company by market capitalisation, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹505.88 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a marginal decline of 1.15% year-on-year and a sharp 37.18% drop quarter-on-quarter. The ₹66,530-crore company faced sequential headwinds despite posting robust revenue growth of 26.59% YoY to ₹8,779.45 crores, reflecting the cyclical nature of the fertiliser business and seasonal volume fluctuations.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>30b09a9d67b79590de4e3e3df313b32e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>