<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Dr Agarwals Eye Hospital Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dr-agarwals-eye-hospital-ltd-is-rated-sell-3852515</link><description>Dr Agarwals Eye Hospital Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>c11ef8d77da0f41479266b6683e0ce8f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanathan Textiles Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sanathan-textiles-ltd-is-rated-sell-3852514</link><description>Sanathan Textiles Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>2dbc5fab8a70fd69d48f46655760c1d6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashoka Buildcon Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ashoka-buildcon-ltd-is-rated-sell-3852513</link><description>Ashoka Buildcon Ltd. is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>bdccbe54d3549c71b98681da4f1b27f1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Alkalies &amp; Chemicals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gujarat-alkalies-chemicals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3852511</link><description>Gujarat Alkalies &amp; Chemicals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>3abb8dc168db7761f5ecb4bdb9ca73ce</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finolex Cables Ltd. is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/finolex-cables-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3852512</link><description>Finolex Cables Ltd. is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b357c26eac17f3f429ce0310584f1faa</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R Systems International Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/r-systems-international-ltd-is-rated-sell-3852508</link><description>R Systems International Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>7ee6e2bfc66f1c26aca4ac7331a51e0b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intellect Design Arena Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/intellect-design-arena-ltd-is-rated-sell-3852510</link><description>Intellect Design Arena Ltd. is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>a132d4484536c59125e508d8b0ecd288</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indus Infra Trust is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indus-infra-trust-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3852509</link><description>Indus Infra Trust is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>00c22597708d3d68bf9ba6bd84b652a5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thejo Engineering Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/thejo-engineering-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3852505</link><description>Thejo Engineering Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>c484d7d84dfeaaf0f784da37d148dd6c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mastek Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mastek-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3852507</link><description>Mastek Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>c10281a1cf4ccb650b3221e5fe7b8962</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gufic BioSciences Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gufic-biosciences-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3852506</link><description>Gufic BioSciences Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ba5522392174c3c9e98a8f5fb2ad7ff7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Somany Ceramics Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/somany-ceramics-ltd-is-rated-hold-3852503</link><description>Somany Ceramics Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6801d38d3fd8085ab4f02458e60d121e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quess Corp Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/quess-corp-ltd-is-rated-hold-3852504</link><description>Quess Corp Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 Feb 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>cc95308caaabdb31715530f9a1e9059b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vadilal Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vadilal-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3852500</link><description>Vadilal Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>4bc8e89771344d8626b83bfb546a82b8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Ltd. is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/idbi-bank-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3852501</link><description>IDBI Bank Ltd. is currently rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 January 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>bd74c37a386cf2f936d60ac5e0bc9d38</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>C.E. Info Systems Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ce-info-systems-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3852502</link><description>C.E. Info Systems Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>4dcb0503a106318bb42a0ffcd1ab1443</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finolex Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/finolex-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3852499</link><description>Finolex Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 31 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ce7bc2f52ef96b2421971e571c27fa71</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advait Energy Transitions Limited is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/advait-energy-transitions-limited-is-rated-hold-3852497</link><description>Advait Energy Transitions Limited is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>70ee5f89626358c0c59da92c221dddd2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/garuda-construction-and-engineering-ltd-is-rated-buy-3852496</link><description>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>9efd6d8398d3ae1e2b2f4e431c56fa90</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHV Infra Projects Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ghv-infra-projects-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3852498</link><description>GHV Infra Projects Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 February 2026, providing investors with the most recent insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>76dd251feba8fb3081d238db0c6e2959</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>