<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>L&amp;T Finance Ltd: A Multibagger Stock Delivering Exceptional Returns Amid Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-finance-ltd-a-multibagger-stock-delivering-exceptional-returns-amid-market-challenges-3858929</link><description>L&amp;T Finance Ltd has emerged as a standout performer in the Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, delivering multibagger returns of 125.82% over the past year, vastly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 10.25% gain. This remarkable surge has attracted significant investor attention, prompting a detailed analysis of the key drivers behind its stellar performance and the sustainability of its momentum going forward.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>089913f14865788a79918088caaf4fe9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tega Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tega-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3858858</link><description>Tega Industries Ltd, a key player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>618d51d97b9d4dab38d4987e967f55be</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishana Phoschem Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishana-phoschem-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3858856</link><description>Krishana Phoschem Ltd, a notable player in the Fertilizers sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average. This technical development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential long-term weakness and a deterioration in the stock’s momentum. Investors and market watchers should carefully analyse the implications of this event amid the company’s broader financial and market context.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>013b310652bde6b4eddb158d54f90b37</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Calcom Vision Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/calcom-vision-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3858855</link><description>Calcom Vision Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>8d37ffdd0b980066402ddb3b49727cd2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goyal Aluminiums Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goyal-aluminiums-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3858854</link><description>Goyal Aluminiums Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>42ec53b1ac92353b84e9a763ae025442</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fedders Holding Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fedders-holding-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3858859</link><description>Fedders Holding Ltd (Stock ID: 532434) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook within the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>a666497c46a5409de9385b6c141b2eac</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sukhjit Starch &amp; Chemicals Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sukhjit-starch-chemicals-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3858857</link><description>Sukhjit Starch &amp; Chemicals Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the micro-cap stock in the Other Agricultural Products sector.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>2a4b590cf25650a2b0fd90fc1e7bbca6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arvind Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arvind-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3858853</link><description>Arvind Ltd, a prominent player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential bullish breakout and a significant shift in long-term momentum for the stock.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>fce892714750b49ecb454ed798efd64c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIE Automotive India Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cie-automotive-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3858852</link><description>CIE Automotive India Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift for the auto components company, suggesting renewed investor confidence and a possible trend reversal in the stock’s trajectory.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>99c65eac0f9c380a3b26b56d4012384e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3858826</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 4,089 companies declared results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability and revenue growth. While mid-cap firms led the charge with a 53.0% positive results ratio, large caps lagged behind at 43.0%, signalling divergent sectoral and market cap dynamics amid a challenging macroeconomic backdrop.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>dd48659640663c6b1a9bc990d87f4a5f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D P Wires Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Earnings Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/d-p-wires-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-earnings-pressure-3858407</link><description>D P Wires Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, touched a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.152.35 today, marking a significant decline amid sustained negative financial performance and market pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fcbbe3cf42c433101474046ad77bbf9e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Equity Markets Show Mixed Trends as Nifty Edges Higher and Sensex Dips Slightly</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-equity-markets-show-mixed-trends-as-nifty-edges-higher-and-sensex-dips-slightly-3858401</link><description>The Indian equity markets closed the day with marginal gains as the Nifty 50 edged up by 0.06%, while the Sensex slipped slightly by 0.03%. Despite the subdued headline indices, sectoral performance was mixed with 29 sectors advancing against 9 decliners, led by strength in pharmaceuticals and weakness in media. Midcap and smallcap segments faced pressure, reflecting a cautious investor stance amid global uncertainties and domestic earnings anticipation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>39b1a27e5b3351f50ac88e0083a7b2fd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Breadth and Sectoral Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-breadth-and-sectoral-shifts-3858400</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index edged higher by 0.31% on 26 Feb 2026, maintaining its position as the best-performing segment across market capitalisations. Despite a nearly balanced advance-decline ratio, select stocks within the small-cap universe delivered notable returns, signalling pockets of strength amid broader market caution.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9fe6393c8635f7ffffac30a497933771</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Shows Resilient Gains Amid Mixed Stock Performances on 26 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-shows-resilient-gains-amid-mixed-stock-performances-on-26-feb-2026-3858399</link><description>The BSE Midcap index demonstrated steady resilience on 26 Feb 2026, advancing by 0.79% amid a mixed bag of stock performances. With 88 stocks advancing against 54 decliners, the segment maintained a healthy breadth ratio of 1.63x, underscoring broad-based participation despite pockets of weakness.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5da13182949f5978a243064ae77fe630</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Sector Trends on 26 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-sector-trends-on-26-feb-2026-3858398</link><description>The large-cap segment of the Indian equity market demonstrated a modest uptick on 26 Feb 2026, with the BSE 100 index advancing 0.14%. While the overall market breadth remained positive, a nuanced divergence emerged between defensive and cyclical stocks, reflecting investor caution amid evolving macroeconomic conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8a623ff1c174df88f3238b4a6ccee161</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicswallah Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.88.1</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/physicswallah-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs881-3858372</link><description>Physicswallah Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.88.1 on 26 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific concerns. The stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting ongoing challenges in financial metrics and market sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>59909a6c63a4f2a58b11cabccce0f1ec</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MRP Agro Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mrp-agro-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-market-underperformance-3858371</link><description>MRP Agro Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.84 on 26 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn for the retailing company amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific performance pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4fb249ede0c24a784b55bc4baca0aae9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bazel International Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bazel-international-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3858370</link><description>Bazel International Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.23.51 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend that has seen the stock lose over a third of its value in the past six trading sessions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1be36dbb544f226106972ef2277047c0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>