<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>ASK Automotive Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Flat Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ask-automotive-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-3785185</link><description>ASK Automotive Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 7 January 2026, reflecting a deterioration in technical indicators and flat financial performance. Despite strong management efficiency and attractive valuation metrics, the company faces near-term headwinds that have prompted a reassessment of its outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>04894b7843e75953a07a55c82c4ccd48</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Insurance Corporation of India Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical and Financial Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/life-insurance-corporation-of-india-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-and-financial-concerns-3785186</link><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has been downgraded from a Hold to a Sell rating, reflecting a combination of deteriorating technical indicators, flat recent financial performance, and consistent underperformance relative to benchmarks. Despite attractive valuation metrics, the overall outlook has weakened, prompting a reassessment of the stock’s investment appeal.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5ccb6da0952e1df6cea955b1e8342839</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Financial Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nuvoco-vistas-corporation-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-financial-concerns-3785187</link><description>Nuvoco Vistas Corporation Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Sell to Strong Sell, driven primarily by deteriorating technical indicators and persistent financial weaknesses. Despite a very attractive valuation, the company’s weak operational trends and bearish market signals have prompted a reassessment of its outlook within the cement sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8f639bb0606bf074f453a45791c0c8eb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Accuracy Shipping Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Weak Fundamentals and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/accuracy-shipping-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3785184</link><description>Accuracy Shipping Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Sell to Strong Sell as of 7 January 2026, reflecting deteriorating technical indicators and sustained financial weakness. The company’s transport services sector stock now carries a Mojo Score of 23.0, signalling heightened caution for investors amid challenging market conditions and operational setbacks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eca0868f9891cc2c529da52785620701</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Standard (India) Ltd Upgraded to Sell Amid Mixed Technical and Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/national-standard-india-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technical-and-financial-signals-3785183</link><description>National Standard (India) Ltd, a player in the Realty sector, has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 7 January 2026, driven primarily by a shift in technical indicators. Despite this upgrade, the company continues to face significant challenges in financial performance and valuation metrics, signalling caution for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>32c261cb03487c26a920d46b9cf04d19</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Richfield Financial Services Ltd Upgraded to Sell on Technical Improvements Despite Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/richfield-financial-services-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-on-technical-improvements-despite-weak-fundamentals-3785182</link><description>Richfield Financial Services Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 7 January 2026, driven primarily by a shift in technical indicators despite persistent fundamental challenges. This nuanced change reflects a mild bullishness in price action and technical momentum, contrasting with ongoing concerns over valuation and financial performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8daa6fba91a15d048b7e67982d766a4e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gopal Snacks Ltd Sees Mixed Technical Signals Amid Mild Momentum Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gopal-snacks-ltd-sees-mixed-technical-signals-amid-mild-momentum-shift-3785179</link><description>Gopal Snacks Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bearish to a mildly bearish trend. Despite a strong day gain of 4.29%, the company’s technical indicators present a complex picture, with some signals suggesting caution while others hint at potential stabilisation. This article analyses the recent price action, key technical indicators, and the broader market context to provide investors with a comprehensive view of Gopal Snacks’ current standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ea0436de7ec89e3de4f2a790fba846c3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukka Proteins Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Indicator Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukka-proteins-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-indicator-shifts-3785178</link><description>Mukka Proteins Ltd, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, has seen a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a bearish trend. Despite some mildly bullish signals on weekly MACD and KST, the overall technical landscape has deteriorated, reflected in a downgrade from Strong Sell to Sell by MarketsMOJO on 14 Nov 2025. The stock’s recent price action and technical parameters suggest caution for investors amid persistent downward pressure.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>92c5f39ffede5a65edf328a73e5661ad</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GPT Healthcare Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gpt-healthcare-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downturn-3785181</link><description>GPT Healthcare Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a bearish trend. The stock’s recent price action, combined with deteriorating technical parameters, suggests increasing downside pressure amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>12a3326d8f990aeb80ae7c91310ca933</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zodiac Energy Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/zodiac-energy-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-market-underperformance-3785180</link><description>Zodiac Energy Ltd, a key player in the construction sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 7 January 2026. This shift reflects a combination of deteriorating technical indicators, disappointing relative market returns, and a cautious outlook on valuation and financial trends despite some positive operational metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>469fa16aa1cb9db5140fe37369132898</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alpex Solar Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Indicator Deterioration</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alpex-solar-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-indicator-deterioration-3785177</link><description>Alpex Solar Ltd, a player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a bearish trend. Despite a modest day gain of 1.43%, the stock’s broader technical landscape reveals weakening momentum and a downgrade in its MarketsMOJO grade from Buy to Hold as of 6 January 2026.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e721330268bd557db6b35d14ac3b6e49</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd Sees Mixed Technical Signals Amid Mild Momentum Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jana-small-finance-bank-ltd-sees-mixed-technical-signals-amid-mild-momentum-shift-3785174</link><description>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd has experienced a subtle shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bearish to a mildly bearish trend, as reflected in recent price action and key technical indicators. Despite a modest day gain of 1.69%, the stock’s broader technical landscape presents a complex picture, with some indicators signalling caution while others hint at potential stabilisation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bd48ab81e78af18a24483ad092bed01c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd Faces Mixed Technical Signals Amid Price Momentum Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-cnc-automation-ltd-faces-mixed-technical-signals-amid-price-momentum-shift-3785176</link><description>Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with recent indicators signalling a transition from a mildly bearish trend to a sideways movement. Despite a day-on-day price decline of 2.12%, the stock’s technical landscape presents a complex picture, reflecting mixed signals across key metrics such as MACD, RSI, Bollinger Bands, and moving averages.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8bdb98ec875a0b47d5032d34d3ea2f0d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin Ltd Shows Bullish Momentum Amid Technical Upgrades</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/muthoot-microfin-ltd-shows-bullish-momentum-amid-technical-upgrades-3785175</link><description>Muthoot Microfin Ltd has demonstrated a notable shift in price momentum, supported by a series of bullish technical indicators that have upgraded its outlook from mildly bullish to bullish. The stock’s recent performance, combined with improved moving averages and positive MACD signals, suggests a strengthening trend that investors should closely monitor.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b45373c86158c043d18659675a0ea62e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doms Industries Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts to Bullish Amid Mixed Returns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/doms-industries-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-to-bullish-amid-mixed-returns-3785173</link><description>Doms Industries Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling an upgrade from a mildly bullish to a bullish trend. Despite a slight dip in the stock price on 8 Jan 2026, the underlying technical parameters suggest strengthening momentum that could favour investors seeking growth in the miscellaneous sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>95f6e2b87974f078bf556c67e2b07109</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajel Projects Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajel-projects-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-market-signals-3785171</link><description>Bajel Projects Ltd, a key player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has exhibited a subtle shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bearish to a mildly bearish stance. Despite a modest day gain of 1.09%, the stock’s technical indicators present a complex picture, with mixed signals from MACD, RSI, moving averages, and other momentum oscillators. This analysis delves into the nuances of these technical parameters and their implications for investors navigating a challenging market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>af46378cc3ddad684083e5da43317207</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Technologies Ltd Sees Mixed Technical Signals Amid Price Momentum Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-technologies-ltd-sees-mixed-technical-signals-amid-price-momentum-shift-3785168</link><description>Tata Technologies Ltd has experienced a notable shift in price momentum, reflected in a 5.32% gain on the day to close at ₹683.45, signalling a mild improvement in technical indicators despite lingering bearish undertones. This article analyses the recent technical parameter changes, key momentum indicators, and the stock’s performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>59716371ca8f3ca59ce69fdedd3f954b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ASK Automotive Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Downshift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ask-automotive-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downshift-3785167</link><description>ASK Automotive Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, transitioning from a sideways trend to a bearish stance. This change is underscored by a series of technical indicators signalling increased selling pressure and weakening price momentum, raising concerns among investors as the stock underperforms relative to the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1e46ff752fae2b4dca43a61e214b5b81</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Honasa Consumer Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Signal Mildly Bullish Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/honasa-consumer-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-signal-mildly-bullish-outlook-3785166</link><description>Honasa Consumer Ltd has exhibited a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bearish to a mildly bullish trend, signalling renewed investor interest in this FMCG sector player. With a current price steady at ₹300.05 and a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade from Sell to Hold, the stock’s technical indicators suggest a cautiously optimistic outlook as it navigates sector headwinds and broader market volatility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>73bd5628260151107080e3a8afdcfdf1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRM Energy Ltd Faces Technical Headwinds Amid Weak Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/irm-energy-ltd-faces-technical-headwinds-amid-weak-price-momentum-3785165</link><description>IRM Energy Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a transition from bearish to mildly bearish trends. Despite some bullish signals on volume, the overall technical landscape remains challenging for the gas sector player as it navigates a subdued market environment and underperforms relative to the broader Sensex.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>26e4ea45a18d135d5c611cf8c70fedc0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>