<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771425</link><description>Hindustan Unilever, a leading FMCG stock, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7e097a322a1195626be019d5d787bba1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advait Energy Transitions Limited Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/advait-energy-transitions-limited-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-momentum-3771423</link><description>Advait Energy Transitions Limited, a player in the Cables - Electricals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock's medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c3faf29453be1428d999e78ce913f649</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Cards &amp; Payment Services Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-cards-payment-services-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771424</link><description>SBI Cards &amp; Payment Services has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b7e190324a13b6cbb0c64899bfbd082f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airo Lam Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/airo-lam-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771422</link><description>Airo Lam, a micro-cap player in the Plywood Boards and Laminates sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price movement over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1cc427a236279389cce368b9a7f819ef</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ERIS Lifesciences Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eris-lifesciences-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771421</link><description>ERIS Lifesciences has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock's price action over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>83ab8336208084a3a33618f867cb66c6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uday Jewellery Industries Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uday-jewellery-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771420</link><description>Uday Jewellery Industries has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>01558119b5c0a3059540542606ece0a6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expleo Solutions Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/expleo-solutions-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771419</link><description>Expleo Solutions, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1e73e0586c501f39e6c5b3a11cee5d51</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CCL International Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ccl-international-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771417</link><description>CCL International, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>53b7d39e150c51171f123570f0bff916</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Energy Services Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asian-energy-services-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771418</link><description>Asian Energy Services has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>73d38c2520b7cd8c64b3ab7a185d6940</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ace Software Exports Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ace-software-exports-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771413</link><description>Ace Software Exports, a micro-cap player in the Software Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2593a87d511d2cecb4e37684a9f923a3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sacheta Metals Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sacheta-metals-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771416</link><description>Sacheta Metals, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5537110b77db414557f9de948af57042</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aarti Drugs Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aarti-drugs-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771414</link><description>Aarti Drugs, a player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>eea6627eece8e62254592249053e03fc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Esaar (India) Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/esaar-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771412</link><description>Esaar (India), a player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price movement.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0d9dea0205ae6a8bbe6b9ea43e86270b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saint-Gobain Sekurit India Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saint-gobain-sekurit-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3771415</link><description>Saint-Gobain Sekurit India, a player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and may indicate a weakening momentum in the stock's price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>11c705629785c00f68a3ee6fba6a56fa</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equitas Small Finance Bank Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/equitas-small-finance-bank-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3771407</link><description>Equitas Small Finance Bank has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend and a long-term momentum change for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e3baaf0c13d8ade0d52903e9e1e40dab</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIE Automotive India Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cie-automotive-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771403</link><description>CIE Automotive India has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, often interpreted as a signal of weakening momentum and a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price performance and mixed technical indicators, raising questions about the stock’s near-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>850e2ab78c4ccd040958375ff489535d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Technology Services Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-technology-services-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3771402</link><description>L&amp;T Technology Services, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently witnessed a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed above the 200-day moving average, forming what is widely recognised as a Golden Cross. This event is often interpreted by market participants as a bullish signal, suggesting a possible shift in long-term momentum and a potential trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6b15c5fea16bd934c9378712a1c68d62</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eureka Industries Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eureka-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3771404</link><description>Eureka Industries, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development is often interpreted as a signal of weakening momentum and potential bearish trends ahead, raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>92d3109bb95081c2d3bc7d437ab8a930</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Birlasoft Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/birlasoft-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3771408</link><description>Birlasoft, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator that often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>25d8578b615c335b518e6b0d447df9b9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P. H. Capital Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/p-h-capital-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3771409</link><description>P. H. Capital, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend and long-term momentum change for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>aa49b596f8c048c730c2a5a658585f51</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>