<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Garuda Construction and Engineering Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Strong Financials and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/garuda-construction-and-engineering-upgraded-to-buy-on-strong-financial-and-technical-signals-3759737</link><description>Garuda Construction and Engineering has experienced a notable revision in its market assessment, reflecting a combination of robust financial results, valuation considerations, and evolving technical indicators. The construction sector stock’s recent performance and underlying fundamentals have prompted a fresh analytical perspective, highlighting both opportunities and risks for investors.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>cec22e60ae28debfe36ae36baae40b98</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manba Finance Evaluation Sees Shift Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/manba-finance-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3759736</link><description>Manba Finance, a key player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market assessment following recent developments across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article explores the factors influencing the current evaluation of the stock, highlighting its performance relative to benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>0d73291afc53f3de675dca1e9c61459c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tolins Tyres: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tolins-tyres-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-mixed-financial-and-technical-signals-3759734</link><description>Tolins Tyres has experienced a revision in market assessment following a detailed analysis of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. Despite recent quarterly setbacks and underwhelming returns relative to benchmarks, certain valuation metrics and technical signals have prompted a nuanced re-evaluation of the company’s investment profile.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>7b53b429d93214d27536af8dd2d4e99d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/premier-energies-upgraded-to-buy-on-strong-fundamentals-and-improving-technicals-3759735</link><description>Premier Energies, a key player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation following recent developments across technical indicators, financial performance, valuation metrics, and overall quality parameters. This article analyses the factors influencing the current market perspective on the stock, highlighting its recent price movements, financial results, and technical trends.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>73338a307f1dc9894a1cdd5517759615</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Industries: Analytical Perspective Shift Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bansal-wire-industries-stock-rating-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technical-and-financial-signals-3759733</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries, a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. Despite ongoing challenges in financial performance, recent changes in technical trends and valuation metrics have influenced the overall analytical perspective on the stock.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>cfd750dc5f275dd0c6a18250ed2036d9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Forgings Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Technical and Financial Developments</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/happy-forgings-upgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-on-strong-technical-and-financial-performance-3759731</link><description>Happy Forgings, a key player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, driven by changes across technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and overall quality parameters. This article analyses the factors influencing the recent shift in the company's assessment and what it means for investors navigating the current market landscape.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>eac943f80a159a7b578569b0472dbd3d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox India’s Market Assessment Reflects Mixed Signals Amidst Flat Financials and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/inox-india-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-financials-and-technical-signals-3759732</link><description>Inox India, a key player in the Other Industrial Products sector, has recently undergone a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a nuanced picture shaped by technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and quality parameters. This article analyses the factors influencing the current assessment of the stock, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its recent performance and outlook.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>3e736fe98c162352bb243173b527b61f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doms Industries: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/doms-industries-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3759730</link><description>Doms Industries, a key player in the miscellaneous sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This nuanced shift reflects a complex interplay of strong fundamentals tempered by evolving market dynamics and technical signals.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>3f023a7b6030d20107351c77de923f63</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flair Writing Industries Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/flair-writing-industries-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-and-financial-improvements-3759727</link><description>Flair Writing Industries has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a nuanced interplay of financial performance, valuation metrics, technical indicators, and broader market trends. This shift highlights the complexities investors face when analysing the stock amid contrasting signals from various assessment parameters.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>20999e327b144b18670b63631a1ef5c8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ARCL Organics Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Strong Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/arcl-organics-upgraded-to-strong-buy-on-robust-financials-and-bullish-technicals-3759728</link><description>ARCL Organics, a key player in the commodity chemicals sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a combination of robust financial results and evolving technical indicators. This shift highlights the company’s sustained growth trajectory and market performance relative to broader indices.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>e6219d4c5ef53f84a212d9e42488f0a7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ratnaveer-precision-engineering-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3759726</link><description>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering, a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently experienced a revision in its market assessment driven by nuanced changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article examines the factors influencing the evolving analytical perspective on the company amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>b523e66c518a12048573da5ffb00bff2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Terminals: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/allcargo-terminals-upgraded-to-sell-as-technicals-improve-amid-lingering-financial-challenges-3759729</link><description>Allcargo Terminals has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. Despite ongoing challenges in financial performance, recent technical signals and valuation metrics have prompted a nuanced reassessment of the company’s standing within the transport infrastructure sector.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>36cab290ba13489f620b44e9d2b4d54c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jio-financial-services-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-mixed-fundamentals-and-technicals-3759724</link><description>Jio Financial Services has experienced a revision in its market assessment, reflecting nuanced changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This shift comes amid a backdrop of strong quarterly financials contrasted by subdued stock performance and evolving technical patterns, prompting a fresh analytical perspective on the company’s standing within the NBFC sector.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>e418f4d31dd5cf1c2bf4986b1cb697ad</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishival Foods: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/krishival-foods-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-and-valuation-concerns-3759725</link><description>Krishival Foods has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. While the company demonstrates robust sales growth and profitability, certain valuation and technical factors have prompted a nuanced re-evaluation of its investment profile.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>4de10cefa34d09d93a16e6467f1e62a1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Metro Brands Faces Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/metro-brands-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3759723</link><description>Metro Brands, a leading player in the Indian footwear sector, has experienced a notable shift in its market evaluation, reflecting a complex interplay of financial performance, valuation metrics, and technical indicators. This article analyses the recent changes in the company’s assessment across four key parameters: quality, valuation, financial trend, and technicals, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the current landscape.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>31ddd7bb63eb2644602795489efb7e75</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CMS Info Systems: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cms-info-systems-upgraded-to-hold-as-technicals-improve-amid-mixed-financials-3759722</link><description>CMS Info Systems has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed analysis of its financial performance, valuation metrics, technical indicators, and quality parameters. This shift reflects a nuanced view of the company’s current position within the diversified commercial services sector, highlighting both strengths and challenges amid evolving market conditions.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>5cfd877ae4bdb5b712aabe1f41eac568</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aether Industries Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Strong Financials and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aether-industries-upgraded-to-buy-comprehensive-analysis-of-quality-valuation-financial-trend-and-technicals-3759721</link><description>Aether Industries, a key player in the specialty chemicals sector, has experienced a notable shift in market assessment driven by recent changes across technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and overall quality parameters. This development comes against a backdrop of robust quarterly results and evolving market dynamics, prompting investors and analysts to revisit the company’s outlook.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>e643ce07b51e1952945435c267613108</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paradeep Phosphates: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Technical and Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/paradeep-phosphates-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3759720</link><description>Paradeep Phosphates has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. While the company continues to demonstrate robust financial performance and long-term growth potential, recent technical signals and valuation comparisons have influenced the overall analytical perspective.
Time: 34 minutes ago</description><guid>7f89e76342b8e24a73afa9e26e4c3fae</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hariom Pipe Industries: Analytical Reassessment Reflects Mixed Signals Across Key Parameters</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/hariom-pipe-industries-downgraded-to-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3759719</link><description>Hariom Pipe Industries, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has undergone a revision in its market assessment following a detailed evaluation of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This reassessment highlights a complex picture of the company’s current standing amid challenging market conditions and sectoral dynamics.
Time: 34 minutes ago</description><guid>02b20f0958e8bc00d6720cd2ce488307</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GMR Power &amp; Urban Infra: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gmr-power-urban-infra-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technicals-and-financial-strains-3759718</link><description>GMR Power &amp; Urban Infra has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. Despite ongoing challenges in its financial performance and capital structure, recent technical signals and valuation metrics have prompted a nuanced shift in the company’s evaluation.
Time: 34 minutes ago</description><guid>42ffa69ffaa388fab3c883118f5f7500</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>