<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-outperformance-3824538</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with robust price gains and heightened market activity. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, signalling increased investor confidence and potential directional bets in the heavy electrical equipment space.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>66f225adf360be8b2813cffe75b285cd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Strong Price Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amber-enterprises-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-strong-price-rally-3824540</link><description>Amber Enterprises India Ltd (AMBER) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market interest and potential directional bets. The stock has outperformed its sector and broader indices, supported by a seven-day consecutive gain, even as investor participation shows signs of moderation. This article analyses the recent OI spike, volume patterns, and market positioning to provide a comprehensive view of Amber’s evolving market dynamics.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>f1335d2459a1a6d0356c7af72636d7ce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tube-investments-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3824535</link><description>Tube Investments of India Ltd (TIINDIA) has witnessed a notable 12.05% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and declining prices, suggests a complex interplay of market positioning and directional bets among investors in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>7dc72dd83b1e57173bb45a36ccf8987b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Ltd. Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3824536</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd., a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a significant 24.8% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This sudden spike in open interest, coupled with falling prices and volume patterns, suggests a complex shift in market positioning and directional bets among investors.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>d0cc4a3fd569d92a52879c7833a04457</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uno Minda Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uno-minda-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-performance-3824537</link><description>Uno Minda Ltd (UNOMINDA), a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, witnessed a notable 12.7% surge in open interest on 6 Feb 2026, signalling heightened derivatives market activity despite the stock’s underperformance. This spike in open interest, coupled with increased volume and declining prices, suggests a shift in market positioning and potential directional bets by traders.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>a45d1f0f8542be4d75126aa5be91a45c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oracle Financial Services Software Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oracle-financial-services-software-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-momentum-3824534</link><description>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd (OFSS) has witnessed a notable 14.9% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This spike in open interest, coupled with declining prices and volume patterns, suggests a complex interplay of bearish positioning and speculative bets among traders.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>a6d5a3988fabccffaeba04e095b5b17c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fischer Medical Ventures Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fischer-medical-ventures-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3824525</link><description>Fischer Medical Ventures Ltd, a small-cap player in the commodity chemicals sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 6 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and sustained investor enthusiasm. The stock closed at ₹44.09, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.99%, significantly outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>91dbbd6b27e3e2e89e06395828374c01</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/persistent-systems-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3824527</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd (PERSISTENT) has witnessed a notable 14.46% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and shifting investor positioning, offers a complex picture of market sentiment for this mid-cap software and consulting firm.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>13637943dc349bcd2d7376ae0332c8a2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axita Cotton Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axita-cotton-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3824529</link><description>Shares of Axita Cotton Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 6 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors. The stock recorded its maximum daily loss, underperforming both its sector and the broader market, as unfilled supply overwhelmed demand despite recent positive momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>e54201dd8d28c80612770d7106d480b4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFB Agro Industries Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ifb-agro-industries-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3824532</link><description>IFB Agro Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the beverages sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 6 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit of 5% and closing at ₹985. The stock has been under intense selling pressure, marking its eighth consecutive day of losses and underperforming its sector by 5.66% today, signalling growing investor concern and panic selling.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>a0a7085681da569137def15d218698bf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Embassy Developments Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/embassy-developments-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-pressure-3824531</link><description>Embassy Developments Ltd (BE) surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 6 Feb 2026, closing at ₹68.02, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.99%. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, with the stock outperforming its Realty sector peers and the broader Sensex despite subdued market conditions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b0859085102c9e6c448b68efb11b9dbb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3824524</link><description>Bosch Ltd., a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent downtrend in its share price, the stock’s derivatives market is showing signs of increased speculative interest, with implications for potential directional bets in the near term.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>af67895c8179680068cca8b2ee703ad5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3824522</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 1,480 companies declared results signalling a modest improvement in profitability and sales growth. While mid-cap firms continue to outperform their large-cap counterparts in terms of positive earnings surprises, sectoral performances remain varied, reflecting ongoing macroeconomic and industry-specific challenges.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>8467a73600cccc8f2450936080782a95</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Setco Automotive Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/setco-automotive-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3824530</link><description>Setco Automotive Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 6 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit amid intense selling pressure. The stock closed at ₹15.57, down 4.95% on the day, marking its maximum permissible daily loss and signalling panic selling among investors.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>da53d6707a01463c33f5e8ee212086a4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd Sees Robust Value Trading Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-sees-robust-value-trading-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3824528</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd (RELIANCE) maintained its position as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 6 February 2026, with a total traded volume exceeding 62 lakh shares and a turnover nearing ₹900 crore. Despite a modest 0.17% gain on the day, the stock’s technical indicators and institutional participation reveal a nuanced picture for investors navigating the oil sector’s evolving landscape.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6923b43693655df695562994730a2d8d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siemens Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3824526</link><description>Siemens Ltd., a heavyweight in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a significant 27.7% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader benchmarks, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>5eeafd31c6b86fe60f45fe6643bf609b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nazara Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 6 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nazara-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-6-feb-2026-3824517</link><description>Nazara Technologies Ltd experienced a notable decline in its share price on 6 Feb 2026, touching an intraday low of Rs 258.35, down 6.73% from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>90d075b4c862cab33df6cecd53a45743</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd. Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3824516</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high, reflecting a sustained period of robust performance and market confidence. The stock’s recent surge underscores the company’s strong position within the ferrous metals sector and highlights its impressive returns over multiple time horizons.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>31b390bcd731b41c065baebc783eef2a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digidrive Distributors Q3 FY26: Profitability Surge Masks Deeper Revenue Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/digidrive-distributors-q3-fy26-profitability-surge-masks-deeper-revenue-concerns-3824533</link><description>Digidrive Distributors Ltd., a specialised master distributor for retailing goods on digital marketplaces, delivered a paradoxical Q3 FY26 performance that highlights the structural challenges facing this micro-cap e-commerce player. Whilst consolidated net profit surged an impressive 226.86% quarter-on-quarter to ₹5.72 crores, revenue contracted 22.57% to ₹11.73 crores, raising serious questions about the sustainability of this profitability spike. The stock plunged 10.47% to ₹22.66 following the results announcement, as investors grappled with deteriorating topline momentum despite the earnings beat.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>934a5ecb5439c09f7a4860e58503d7d0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tarsons Products Q3 FY26: Margin Pressures Mount as Profitability Struggles Continue</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/tarsons-products-q3-fy26-margin-pressures-mount-as-profitability-struggles-continue-3824523</link><description>Tarsons Products Ltd., a small-cap healthcare services company with a market capitalisation of ₹1,149.26 crores, reported net profit of ₹5.04 crores for Q3 FY26 (Oct-Dec'25), marking a modest sequential improvement of 51.81% from Q2 FY26's ₹3.32 crores but declining 4.18% year-on-year. The stock closed at ₹216.00 on February 6, 2026, reflecting a sharp one-day gain of 5.11%, though this offers little respite for long-suffering shareholders who have endured a brutal 43.34% decline over the past year and a staggering 68.68% drawdown over three years.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>00f81bf71f8cfaebb4aee0706151595b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>