<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Gopal Snacks Q3 FY26: Profitability Recovers Sharply But Revenue Pressures Persist</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/gopal-snacks-q3-fy26-profitability-recovers-sharply-but-revenue-pressures-persist-3806506</link><description>Gopal Snacks Ltd., a Rajkot-based packaged snacks manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹3,714.00 crores, delivered a remarkable turnaround in profitability during Q3 FY26, posting net profit of ₹25.69 crores compared to a loss of ₹39.51 crores in the previous quarter. However, the company's revenue trajectory remains concerning, with net sales declining 7.23% year-on-year to ₹370.04 crores, marking the third consecutive quarter of YoY revenue contraction. The stock has struggled significantly, declining 9.31% over the past year whilst the Sensex gained 8.61%, resulting in a negative alpha of 17.92 percentage points.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0c07ea1a18cdac76a7cf6c0a0a0f5364</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paushak Ltd Q2 FY26: Profit Slumps 39% as Margin Pressures Mount</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/paushak-ltd-q2-fy26-profit-slumps-39-as-margin-pressures-mount-3806505</link><description>Paushak Limited, India's largest phosgene-based speciality chemicals manufacturer, reported a disappointing performance in Q2 FY26, with net profit plunging 39.33% quarter-on-quarter to ₹8.61 crores from ₹12.03 crores in Q1 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, the decline was even steeper at 39.37% compared to ₹14.20 crores in Q2 FY25. The Vadodara-based company, with a market capitalisation of ₹1,323 crores, saw its stock price decline 26.02% over the past three months, reflecting investor concerns about deteriorating profitability and operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5012093f16ba3ba5bed590931abbdca0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vishal Mega Mart Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vishal-mega-mart-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806501</link><description>Vishal Mega Mart Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show a mixed performance, with a net profit decline of 26.09% quarter-over-quarter but a 46.47% year-on-year increase, alongside a revenue drop of 5.06% sequentially and a 22.38% rise year-on-year. The company's operating and PAT margins have decreased, raising concerns about sustainability, making the upcoming Q3 results critical for assessing future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d9e1dc410fb3dd1eb7eaf316c61e048f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-international-gemmological-institute-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806500</link><description>International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are strong year-on-year, with a net profit of ₹129.79 crores and a revenue increase of 21.43%. However, sequential growth is modest, indicating potential demand normalization, and the stock has declined 43.77% from its 52-week high, suggesting a cautious outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>34df31621cfbcab79a9258148073c385</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Raymond Lifestyle Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-raymond-lifestyle-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806499</link><description>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show mixed performance, with record revenue of ₹1,848.72 crores but a significant net profit decline of 43% to ₹42.86 crores, indicating ongoing profitability challenges despite slight operational improvements. Overall, the company faces substantial structural issues and low capital efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4b429474a85ab2a9d6c675e2f08e1cba</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sumitomo Chemical India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sumitomo-chemical-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806498</link><description>Sumitomo Chemical India Ltd's latest results for Q3 FY26 are concerning, with a 38.92% decline in net sales to ₹567.98 crores and a 57.46% drop in net profit to ₹75.63 crores, primarily due to seasonal challenges in the agrochemical sector. Despite these operational difficulties, the company has a strong balance sheet with no long-term debt.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fa5d0b38e0ab354b3357cb5af6741cbc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bikaji Foods International Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bikaji-foods-international-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806497</link><description>Bikaji Foods International Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are strong, with net sales up 27.22% sequentially and net profit increasing by 33.19%, driven by seasonal demand. However, its premium valuation compared to peers raises questions about the sustainability of growth and profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>af5ec8ec9453db391a1916d1d98a5a16</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tips Films Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tips-films-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806496</link><description>Tips Films Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 92.81% decline in net sales to ₹4.06 crores and a net loss of ₹2.87 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and financial instability. Despite a year-on-year sales growth of 361.36%, the company's volatility and increasing liabilities raise red flags for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a800b4957ccb332d7852e926fc2c34b8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Dynamic Cables Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dynamic-cables-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806495</link><description>Dynamic Cables Ltd's latest results are strong, with a 41.90% increase in net profit and an 18.80% rise in revenue, showcasing improved operational efficiency and margin expansion, despite facing some technical selling pressure in the market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e6b756ed30b7223a6b67daa8f859676b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Spandana Sphoorty Financial Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-spandana-sphoorty-financial-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806494</link><description>Spandana Sphoorty Financial Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹94.97 crores and a 57.53% decline in interest income, indicating significant operational challenges and capital erosion. Despite a slight increase in net sales, the overall financial performance reflects distress and a critical need for restructuring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8126db34520f050d9e0420c4e0195cc5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sambhaav Media Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sambhaav-media-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806493</link><description>Sambhaav Media Ltd's latest results show a net profit decline of 36% year-on-year, despite a 12% sequential revenue growth. While the company returned to profitability, ongoing operational challenges and low return on equity raise concerns about its long-term financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dd0c2d2f128d98386eaae0aab1474cf5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-motilal-oswal-financial-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806492</link><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd's latest results show mixed performance, with a 5.93% year-on-year increase in net sales and a slight 0.26% rise in net profit, but declining operating margins and rising interest expenses indicate challenges in sustaining growth. Investors should be cautious due to the company's reliance on market conditions and the inherent volatility in its business model.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dcb05c7c190d551dedccd90f41579bdb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aditya Vision Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aditya-vision-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806491</link><description>Aditya Vision Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 27.62% year-on-year, with net profit increasing by 12.77%. However, operating margins declined to 8.16%, indicating challenges in maintaining profitability amid competitive pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e60309f419f162fc8af9bc1f7d5efb05</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mahindra Logistics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mahindra-logistics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806490</link><description>Mahindra Logistics Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show a positive turnaround with a net profit of ₹3.25 crores and a 19.06% revenue growth, but ongoing challenges like low return on equity and cumulative losses raise concerns about long-term sustainability. Overall, the results are encouraging but require careful monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bf7a97c2a4014da0a33b3067ccca1de9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Arex Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-arex-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806489</link><description>Arex Industries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a slight decline in net sales and a significant 74% drop in net profit, alongside the lowest operating margin in eight quarters. The company faces critical operational challenges and a lack of investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2fa76f99165dd137d6163d8edce8955e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are NESCO Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nesco-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806488</link><description>NESCO Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 24.51% year-on-year, reaching ₹239.18 crores, but also a decline in operating and profit margins, raising concerns about profitability sustainability amid rising costs. Investors should monitor these margin pressures despite the company's solid financial position.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9c2729377bd9188ee908570cf16f1b4c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Marico Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-marico-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806487</link><description>Marico Ltd.'s Q3 FY26 results show strong net sales growth of 26.59% and a 12.03% increase in net profit, but operating profit margins contracted due to rising costs, indicating challenges in maintaining profitability. Overall, the results are positive but highlight the need for careful management of margins moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1d0453d979c49c8aaa13f574b7582725</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Kaiser Corporation Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kaiser-corporation-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806486</link><description>Kaiser Corporation Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 22.67% decline in quarterly net sales to ₹2.32 crores, despite a year-on-year growth of 36.47%. While the company reported a net profit of ₹0.17 crores, its negative return on equity and high interest costs indicate ongoing financial instability and challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0f83b6b276049e7cfefbba2a2ee98476</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nila Infrastructures Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nila-infrastructures-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806485</link><description>Nila Infrastructures Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 43.35% year-on-year, but a decline in net profit by 23.52% from the previous quarter raises concerns about profitability and operational efficiency. Investors should monitor future performance for improvements in margins and overall financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d43aaa6e6436c3eb65f5f10bd501aa64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Orient Bell Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-orient-bell-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3806484</link><description>Orient Bell Ltd.'s latest Q3 FY26 results are positive, showing a net profit of ₹3.39 crores, a 245.92% year-on-year increase, and improved operating margins. However, challenges in capital efficiency and valuation concerns remain, prompting cautious optimism among investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>aa965eea951f0ef51f5da217f0dd5cfb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>