<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>When is the next results date for Croissance Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-croissance-ltd-3779224</link><description>The next results date for Croissance Ltd is January 6, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>374f1a68477276671e1af1d6c5d1d2f4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Swaraj Engines Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-swaraj-engines-ltd-3779223</link><description>The next results date for Swaraj Engines Ltd is 15 January 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>06c363e161b141fee13569c0d09955a8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Yes Bank Ltd.?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-yes-bank-ltd-3779222</link><description>Yes Bank Ltd. will announce its results on January 17, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>f3cef40c401fe51424d526663e0759b5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-transformers-rectifiers-india-ltd-3779221</link><description>The next results date for Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd is January 8, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>d0dda7679e5e6e4bf8387e64cba77595</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Premier Energy &amp; Infrastructure Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-premier-energy-infrastructure-ltd-3779220</link><description>The next results date for Premier Energy &amp; Infrastructure Ltd is January 7, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>f09ecb8f472060dfc4f4699d22f7c298</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the bonus history of Orient Tech.?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/what-is-the-bonus-history-of-orient-tech-3779217</link><description>Orient Tech has announced a 1:10 bonus issue effective January 5, 2026, meaning shareholders will receive one additional share for every ten shares held. The record date and ex-date for this bonus are both January 5, 2026.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>d5aef7008675a1ba8e0a46443d1d912b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Ltd’s Mixed Week: -1.34% Price Change Amid High Volume and Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vodafone-idea-ltds-mixed-week--134-price-change-amid-high-volume-and-volatility-3779196</link><description>Vodafone Idea Ltd experienced a volatile trading week from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026, closing marginally lower by 1.34% at Rs.11.79, while the Sensex advanced 1.35% over the same period. The stock demonstrated notable intraday swings, hitting multiple 52-week highs before retreating amid heavy option activity and mixed investor sentiment. Despite strong volume and value turnover, the telecom operator’s Mojo Score remains at 46.0 with a Sell rating, reflecting ongoing fundamental challenges amid a cautiously optimistic technical backdrop.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d4db5aca2ba65c2fed27165e56ffdf79</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Motor Parts &amp; Accessories Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-motor-parts-accessories-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3779187</link><description>India Motor Parts &amp; Accessories Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>607f5c755071154d4229056e7dfd3327</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Honasa Consumer Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/honasa-consumer-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779183</link><description>Honasa Consumer Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e97f4e959e422b4624b5b0d71c3f70b8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Properties Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shriram-properties-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3779186</link><description>Shriram Properties Ltd, a small-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>69cc7c6e4e17f61b4a7d29397baee0ce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krsnaa-diagnostics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779185</link><description>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already subdued performance metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>07704da63d3c66fd7adb978e532be094</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amber-enterprises-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3779184</link><description>Amber Enterprises India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook within the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c7af1996b36bc91ecce79de5e29eadd5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GTV Engineering Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gtv-engineering-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779177</link><description>GTV Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about its near-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9f83d5c00c328d72dd403ecfbe479a36</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astra Microwave Products Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astra-microwave-products-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779181</link><description>Astra Microwave Products Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>da7432ce50ca5fdc9ee440c6e01fa6a1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-toners-developers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3779180</link><description>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>4c930bbe6214595f88ceaf048f3b0452</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Algoquant Fintech Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/algoquant-fintech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779182</link><description>Algoquant Fintech Ltd, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development points to a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid mixed fundamental and technical signals.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>19bacfcff0d516f8e65b3feee843b5f6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>