<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd Gains 30.58%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-ltd-gains-3058-5-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3838884</link><description>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 30.58% from Rs.100.54 to Rs.131.29 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by strong volume spikes, multiple intraday highs, and a notable shift in technical momentum, reflecting renewed investor interest amid mixed sector and market conditions.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>aed679291416688e61af0ca8c1a04025</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pyramid Technoplast Declines 1.70%: 4 Key Factors Shaping This Week’s Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pyramid-technoplast-declines-170-4-key-factors-shaping-this-weeks-performance-3838880</link><description>Pyramid Technoplast Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.153.00, down 1.70% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.155.65. The stock’s performance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which declined by 0.54% over the same period. Despite early gains on 9 February, the stock faced pressure following a sharp quarterly profit decline and mixed technical signals, culminating in a week marked by financial challenges and valuation shifts within the packaging sector.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>87a0642859fbef29455783e0b2b13381</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aeroflex Industries Gains 0.76%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aeroflex-industries-gains-076-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3838881</link><description>Aeroflex Industries Ltd closed the week ending 13 February 2026 with a modest gain of 0.76%, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock showed strong early-week momentum, driven by technical upgrades and intraday highs, before retreating in the final session amid broader market weakness. This review analyses the key events shaping Aeroflex’s price action and technical outlook during the week.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>049f5336446aefca977514bdddf2dad8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRB Infrastructure Trust Stagnates at Rs.220.22 Despite Record Quarterly Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/irb-infrastructure-trust-stagnates-at-rs22022-despite-record-quarterly-results-3838883</link><description>IRB Infrastructure Trust’s stock price remained unchanged at Rs.220.22 throughout the week ending 13 February 2026, despite the company reporting an outstanding quarterly performance that marked record revenues and profitability. While the Sensex declined by 0.54% over the same period, the trust’s flat price performance reflects a cautious market response amid mixed signals from financial quality and valuation metrics.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>ef9e8e010a9866b67bcaabe862c5722f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Gains 2.25%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zaggle-prepaid-ocean-services-gains-225-3-key-factors-driving-the-move-3838882</link><description>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd recorded a modest gain of 2.25% over the week ending 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54%. The stock showed notable intraday strength midweek, reaching an intraday high of Rs.306.55 on 10 February, before retreating sharply on the final trading day amid heavy volume. Key developments including a valuation upgrade, a strong intraday rally, and robust quarterly results shaped the stock’s trajectory during the week.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>ed41498df1b73f22f382565a705c87f6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd Falls 4.08%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-falls-408-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3838878</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.08% to close at Rs.1,299.15, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by significant technical momentum shifts, a downgrade in analyst ratings, and heightened market volatility, all contributing to the stock’s downward trajectory despite some early optimism.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>6f581bd92ed50a91d328762354f60ed0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yatra Online Ltd Gains 13.13%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yatra-online-ltd-gains-1313-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3838879</link><description>Yatra Online Ltd delivered a strong performance during the week ending 13 February 2026, with its stock price rising 13.13% from Rs.147.70 to Rs.167.10, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by notable intraday volatility, a sharp rebound following a gap down, and a shift in valuation metrics that together shaped investor sentiment and trading activity.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>da5a0f13454e92bb37fe921fb62c20a5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ARCL Organics Falls 9.79%: Four Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arcl-organics-falls-979-four-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3838877</link><description>ARCL Organics Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 13 February 2026, with its share price declining 9.79% from Rs.242.00 to Rs.218.30, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp deterioration in quarterly financial results, a downgrade in quality and rating grades, and bearish technical signals, all contributing to heightened investor caution amid challenging sector conditions.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>0ab31ea4b637320023b45a9ba7d9ce79</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd Gains 8.20%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manoj-vaibhav-gems-n-jewellers-ltd-gains-820-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3838876</link><description>Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd experienced a volatile week, opening at Rs.173.20 and closing slightly lower at Rs.172.70, marking a marginal weekly decline of 0.29%. Despite this, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was characterised by a strong initial rally driven by technical upgrades and positive quarterly results, followed by a gradual correction amid mixed technical signals and profit-taking.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>9cac6f7483a772b8529d03c80903c869</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd Falls 3.27%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-jet-healthcare-ltd-falls-327-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3838874</link><description>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd experienced a volatile week from 9 to 13 February 2026, ending with a 3.27% decline to close at Rs.397.45, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The stock showed early strength with a 7.07% gain on Monday but succumbed to heavy selling pressure later in the week, culminating in a near 10% drop and a lower circuit hit on Friday. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>e7618fe90d351b17e5b38f0e7904d90e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Estates Ltd Gains 8.44%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-estates-ltd-gains-844-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-momentum-3838875</link><description>Max Estates Ltd delivered a volatile yet overall positive week, closing at Rs.409.35 on 13 February 2026, marking an 8.44% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.377.50. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period, reflecting a divergence between the stock’s momentum and broader market trends amid mixed technical signals and sector-specific developments.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>2588913ecc0743f2795b1c8e7d2f041b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Honasa Consumer Ltd Gains 5.72%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/honasa-consumer-ltd-gains-572-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-momentum-3838873</link><description>Honasa Consumer Ltd delivered a robust weekly gain of 5.72%, closing at Rs.301.50 on 13 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market conditions, buoyed by technical momentum shifts, strong quarterly results, and notable volume spikes that underscored investor interest.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>2d75ee3fec594dbc613ec8dc505892ec</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Protean eGov Technologies Ltd Gains 2.47%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/protean-egov-technologies-ltd-gains-247-6-key-factors-driving-the-week-3838871</link><description>Protean eGov Technologies Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 2.47%, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock exhibited notable intraday volatility and mixed technical signals amid a backdrop of valuation shifts and quarterly results, reflecting a complex market sentiment. Despite a strong start on 9 February with an 8.18% surge, the stock faced selling pressure in subsequent sessions, ending the week at Rs.633.60 on 13 February 2026.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>2e849f987804fd323b6add290ae7323f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd Falls 3.70%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-renewable-energy-development-agency-ltd-falls-370-3-key-factors-driving-the-decline-3838872</link><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd (IREDA) experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 3.70% to close at Rs.123.55, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of bearish developments including a sharp surge in derivatives open interest amid falling prices, the stock hitting fresh 52-week lows on consecutive days, and sustained technical weakness below all key moving averages.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>d199b0ceacb1ab37925a66d220b4b0ed</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Shelter Finance Falls 6.54%: Downgrade and Valuation Shift Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-shelter-finance-falls-654-downgrade-and-valuation-shift-drive-weekly-decline-3838870</link><description>India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 6.54% from Rs.789.55 to Rs.737.95, significantly underperforming the Sensex, which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp gap down on 9 February, a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, valuation shifts signalling changing market sentiment, and continued financial performance amidst elevated promoter pledge risks.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>5241eada2494c9a5499bffb56d090555</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Technologies Falls 3.20%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-technologies-falls-320-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-decline-3838869</link><description>Tata Technologies Ltd’s shares fell 3.20% over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.597.75 compared to Rs.617.50 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% decline, highlighting the stock’s relative weakness amid deteriorating financial results, valuation pressures, and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>6d770ff5a7e976d3e430c4481c5ba56c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox India Ltd Gains 4.50%: Key Financial and Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-india-ltd-gains-450-key-financial-and-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3838868</link><description>Inox India Ltd delivered a solid weekly gain of 4.50%, closing at Rs.1,169.20 on 13 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a blend of mixed technical signals and a robust quarterly earnings report, driving investor attention amid cautious momentum shifts. Despite some short-term bearish technical indicators, the company’s record quarterly sales and profitability underscored a positive financial trend that supported the stock’s relative strength.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>95fb7deec1da82da2bd21b4e289ad7ea</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin Gains 5.17%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/muthoot-microfin-gains-517-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3838867</link><description>Muthoot Microfin Ltd delivered a mixed but ultimately positive week, closing at Rs.190.20 on 13 February 2026, up 5.17% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.180.85. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period, reflecting the stock’s resilience amid fundamental concerns and technical momentum shifts. The week was marked by sharp intraday swings, a significant downgrade in quality and valuation grades, and a technical upgrade signalling renewed bullish momentum.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>164c4505bc57aa1404a9b68819fb919c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motisons Jewellers Gains 16.62%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motisons-jewellers-gains-1662-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3838866</link><description>Motisons Jewellers Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance from 9 to 13 February 2026, surging 16.62% to close at Rs.15.79, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock exhibited notable intraday volatility and volume spikes, supported by a series of positive technical signals, an upgrade in analyst rating, and robust quarterly financial results. Despite some midweek profit-taking, the overall momentum remained positive, reflecting renewed investor interest in this small-cap jewellery stock amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>fa78dc298b4cb813dc0178b9e89299aa</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Forgings Ltd Gains 18.58%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/happy-forgings-ltd-gains-1858-7-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3838862</link><description>Happy Forgings Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 18.58% from Rs.1,095.50 to Rs.1,299.00 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s rally was fuelled by a combination of strong quarterly results, technical momentum upgrades, multiple new 52-week highs, and robust buying interest culminating in an upper circuit hit. Despite a recent downgrade in quality grade, the stock’s price action and volume trends underscore sustained investor enthusiasm amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>afe57cb7fc2339b8f0a4210d74dc2208</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>