<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-virtual-galaxy-infotech-ltd-fallingrising-3851890</link><description>On 23-Feb, Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.76% to close at ₹129.05. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by subdued investor participation and technical weaknesses.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>f911b94f8b571e0ba49439a21cc8788e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ken Enterprises Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ken-enterprises-ltd-fallingrising-3851889</link><description>On 23-Feb, Ken Enterprises Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.39% to close at ₹39.20. This downturn reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9356cf78eedb353a4ac548784a95a04b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ventive Hospitality Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ventive-hospitality-ltd-fallingrising-3851888</link><description>As of 23-Feb, Ventive Hospitality Ltd’s stock price has declined marginally by 0.33% to ₹705.00, continuing a downward trend that has persisted over the past nine trading sessions. Despite strong long-term growth metrics, the stock’s recent performance reflects investor caution amid valuation concerns and management efficiency issues.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b7dc6bd306423a03130d05c9736217ae</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3851887</link><description>On 23-Feb, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 6.12% to ₹41.60 by 09:21 PM, reflecting robust investor enthusiasm and strong technical indicators that have propelled the stock to new heights.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7a1c5c0912d785ac859c6a3baf6d81ae</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3851886</link><description>On 23-Feb, Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, continuing a sustained downward trajectory that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>6c123e5fec10a970db4120429194e9be</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3851885</link><description>As of 23-Feb, Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd’s stock price has declined by 1.77% to ₹1,061.75, continuing a recent downward trend despite the company’s strong operational performance and healthy fundamentals.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>8ee6fe24afd874e62a352b67e4973e7f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Harsha Engineers International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-harsha-engineers-international-ltd-fallingrising-3851884</link><description>As of 23-Feb, Harsha Engineers International Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting ongoing concerns over its subdued growth trajectory and consistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>24f00add66b62d4359be773aca50dd70</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Homesfy Realty Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-homesfy-realty-ltd-fallingrising-3851883</link><description>As of 23-Feb, Homesfy Realty Ltd’s stock price declined by 0.97% to ₹159.00, continuing a sustained period of underperformance relative to key benchmarks and sector averages.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>6159b51dddde17c434d81ef5ea2af666</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shri Venkatesh Refineries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shri-venkatesh-refineries-ltd-fallingrising-3851882</link><description>On 23-Feb, Shri Venkatesh Refineries Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹276.85, up ₹4.85 or 1.78% as of 09:15 PM. This increase follows a period of heightened volatility and strong weekly performance, despite some intraday setbacks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b70ac65a26fc541308f253ae61840f71</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bazel International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bazel-international-ltd-fallingrising-3851881</link><description>On 23-Feb, Bazel International Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 14.76% to close at ₹29.00. This drop marks the third consecutive day of losses, reflecting a sustained downtrend amid weakening investor interest and heightened volatility.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3df7bcb8fe4023a0b787f5a711148595</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hindustan-aeronautics-ltd-fallingrising-3851880</link><description>On 23-Feb, Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL) witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.56% to close at ₹4,024.15. This drop reflects a broader short-term underperformance despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals and impressive historical returns.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e1985c83ea4d356d681a7da5113f005a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-fallingrising-3851879</link><description>On 23-Feb, SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹2,106.05 with a gain of ₹25.65 or 1.23%. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust long-term returns, strong investor participation, and favourable valuation metrics that have bolstered market sentiment towards the stock.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>eb0ad7be6f7bc20f76028ebf0c3e5892</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is M K Proteins Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-m-k-proteins-ltd-fallingrising-3851878</link><description>On 23-Feb, M K Proteins Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹5.16, down by ₹0.12 or 2.27%. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s extended underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>60c113d8bfbfe0c623143959794228e5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-housing-development-infrastructure-ltd-fallingrising-3851877</link><description>As of 23-Feb, Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.98% to close at ₹2.48. This drop comes despite the stock's strong monthly and year-to-date gains, reflecting a complex interplay of recent trading patterns and investor sentiment.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>bf67457efeb45d0c6080ee1f5ee5667a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Archidply Decor Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-archidply-decor-ltd-fallingrising-3851876</link><description>On 23 Feb, Archidply Decor Ltd witnessed a 2.0% increase in its share price, closing at ₹77.42. This rise comes despite several bearish technical indicators and erratic trading patterns, reflecting a complex market sentiment surrounding the stock.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>172fe03941495a1be7752b6f640e1fc6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vivid Mercantile Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vivid-mercantile-ltd-fallingrising-3851875</link><description>On 23-Feb, Vivid Mercantile Ltd’s stock price declined by 1.41%, closing at ₹6.97, reflecting a short-term pullback despite strong longer-term gains relative to the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>4a789c6d7fc49a6ec451299758fa69c3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GACM Technologies Ltd-DVR falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gacm-technologies-ltd-dvr-fallingrising-3851874</link><description>As of 23-Feb, GACM Technologies Ltd-DVR's stock price remains unchanged at ₹0.48, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term resilience and long-term underperformance against key market benchmarks.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>a9f7de1d984857a4dee9c417deaf6378</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-indo-rama-synthetics-india-ltd-fallingrising-3851873</link><description>On 23-Feb, Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.2% to close at ₹36.05. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, underscored by subdued investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>5336fba24da11632812d7f2c20c1f1cc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is UPL Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-upl-ltd-fallingrising-3851872</link><description>On 23-Feb, UPL Ltd. witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 14.25% to close at ₹644.65. This steep drop reflects a combination of sector-wide weakness, technical pressures, and heightened volatility, despite the company’s strong recent financial performance.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>76b1deb70c8e4b27436097e7f3e7f975</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is IGC Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-igc-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3851871</link><description>On 23-Feb, IGC Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.81% to close at ₹2.27. This drop reflects ongoing challenges for the stock, which has underperformed both its sector and key market benchmarks in recent trading sessions.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>91446f1c7e5e090a7377eb2cb6b5195a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:44:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>