<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>When is the next results date for Tech Mahindra Ltd.?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-tech-mahindra-ltd-3777855</link><description>The next results date for Tech Mahindra Ltd. is 16 January 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>1bed4f0f7b9684616d6f86984eb5d239</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Eimco Elecon (India) Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-eimco-elecon-india-ltd-3777854</link><description>The next results date for Eimco Elecon (India) Ltd is January 8, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>f7933d9157e66a8b77092631e25cd5df</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-hdfc-life-insurance-company-ltd-3777853</link><description>The next results date for HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd is January 15, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>c52510aa031450a333f7215b9fbd37c8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Mahindra EPC Irrigation Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-mahindra-epc-irrigation-ltd-3777852</link><description>The next results date for Mahindra EPC Irrigation Ltd is January 16, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>2a751ca03ef50d09f2262d1afbca745b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for CDG Petchem Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-cdg-petchem-ltd-3777851</link><description>The next results date for CDG Petchem Ltd is January 5, 2026.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>4b16eaea0cc618dd396be34e73feb9d8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the bonus history of CWD?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/what-is-the-bonus-history-of-cwd-3777849</link><description>CWD Ltd announced a 4:1 bonus issue with an ex-date and record date of January 2, 2026, meaning shareholders will receive one additional share for every four shares held.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>ec5d4f517006a544311734c90b55c1d6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ipca Laboratories Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ipca-laboratories-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3777826</link><description>Ipca Laboratories Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a possible trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the pharmaceutical and biotechnology company.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e53bf983889deb6f840592e711ccc2e8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3777825</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd., a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator that suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift towards long-term upward momentum. This development marks a pivotal moment for the stock, which has shown mixed performance against the broader market over the past year.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b710fd84081f59db0bcf6a52dba37c84</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paras-defence-and-space-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3777819</link><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, indicating a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its long-term strength within the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7394214eaca152bad96e14210cca3951</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kewal Kiran Clothing Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kewal-kiran-clothing-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3777820</link><description>Kewal Kiran Clothing Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns over the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9d9d8de6c8d9f079652203da22a1b591</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vani Commercials Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vani-commercials-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3777818</link><description>Vani Commercials Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its long-term weakness amid broader market challenges.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>db20dee6224b09d8eff37f40f3f16a68</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godfrey-phillips-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3777821</link><description>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd., a prominent player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near- to medium-term momentum and long-term strength.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7df3de8ebc4db3df402e6f042e5cd1f5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kwality Pharmaceuticals Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kwality-pharmaceuticals-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3777822</link><description>Kwality Pharmaceuticals Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the micro-cap pharmaceutical company, which has demonstrated robust performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d410b6c783d6022f0d3e8ca03db80586</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gravita India Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gravita-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3777812</link><description>Gravita India Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the Minerals &amp; Mining company, which has seen mixed performance against the broader market in recent years.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d316f5c91089dd0dc4466a043de3e2b2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JK Agri Genetics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jk-agri-genetics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3777816</link><description>JK Agri Genetics Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average, forming a Death Cross. This event is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raising concerns about its long-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e194b3979537d18b7e7374c35e475eb5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Globus Spirits Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/globus-spirits-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3777808</link><description>Globus Spirits Ltd, a prominent player in the beverages sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d01ca62af970b64223f0c8e072141dea</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>