<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Trident Ltd Falls 2.96%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trident-ltd-falls-296-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788672</link><description>Trident Ltd’s shares declined by 2.96% over the week ending 9 January 2026, closing at ₹26.23 from ₹27.03, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by a steady downtrend early on, a sharp rebound on 8 January amid exceptional volume, and a subsequent pullback on the final trading day. Mixed technical signals and sector headwinds shaped investor sentiment throughout.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>66bf8569dcc54aa1db3a263942fad583</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Bank of India Gains 0.07%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/state-bank-of-india-gains-007-4-key-factors-driving-the-week-3788671</link><description>State Bank of India (SBI) closed the week ending 09 January 2026 with a marginal gain of 0.07%, closing at Rs.1,000.00, while the Sensex declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid a broadly weak market, supported by new 52-week and all-time highs early in the week and sustained technical momentum. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping SBI’s performance during the week.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>7ae5c408aba4f75c7728cf909114574d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineers India Ltd. Falls 6.20%: Technical Shifts and Mixed Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/engineers-india-ltd-falls-620-technical-shifts-and-mixed-signals-shape-the-week-3788670</link><description>Engineers India Ltd. experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 6.20% from ₹206.35 on 2 January to ₹193.55 on 9 January 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical upgrade to a Hold rating early on, followed by a shift to mildly bearish momentum amid mixed indicator signals, reflecting uncertainty in the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>962ecc34792943875bd74cc7b43a7989</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astral Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.33% Price Change Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astral-ltds-mixed-week--033-price-change-amid-technical-shifts-3788669</link><description>Astral Ltd closed the week ending 9 January 2026 marginally lower by 0.33%, settling at Rs.1,449.00, while the Sensex declined more sharply by 2.62%. The stock showed resilience amid a volatile market, supported by a technical upgrade to Hold and mixed signals from key momentum indicators. Despite intraday fluctuations and a late-week dip, Astral outperformed the broader market benchmark, reflecting cautious investor interest amid sectoral and macroeconomic uncertainties.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>52eadf389d123589b4930c52aff71063</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd Falls 18.45%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/transformers-rectifiers-india-ltd-falls-1845-6-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3788668</link><description>Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd (TARIL) endured a challenging week ending 9 January 2026, with its share price plunging 18.45% from Rs.336.40 to Rs.274.35, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% decline. The stock faced intense selling pressure amid mixed technical signals, a downgrade to a Sell rating, and volatile trading volumes, despite reporting a strong quarterly turnaround. This review analyses the key events shaping TARIL’s turbulent week and their impact on price action.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>705e87f1422fc800dd683ef1e549e797</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poonawalla Fincorp Declines 3.79%: Mixed Technical Signals and Valuation Concerns Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/poonawalla-fincorp-declines-379-mixed-technical-signals-and-valuation-concerns-shape-week-3788667</link><description>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd closed the week ending 9 Jan 2026 at Rs.462.30, down 3.79% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.480.50. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 2.62% decline over the same period, signalling a slightly weaker sentiment towards the stock amid mixed technical signals and valuation concerns. The week saw a shift in technical momentum and a downgrade in the company’s rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting a cautious stance despite strong quarterly financials and promoter confidence.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>9c2f4476dcb2562eedbf8abb4e32171d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd Falls 23.34%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/systematix-corporate-services-ltd-falls-2334-3-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3788666</link><description>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd endured a turbulent week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price plunging 23.34% to close at Rs.108.70, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% decline. The week was marked by extreme volatility, including a lower circuit hit on 6 January and a brief rebound on 8 January, reflecting intense selling pressure and cautious investor sentiment amid broader market weakness.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>ae7dbb048e83d2191e499b11ffa7b306</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVR Inox Ltd Falls 2.69%: 4 Key Factors Shaping This Week’s Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pvr-inox-ltd-falls-269-4-key-factors-shaping-this-weeks-market-moves-3788665</link><description>PVR Inox Ltd’s stock closed the week ending 9 January 2026 at ₹1,004.50, down 2.69% from ₹1,032.25 the previous Friday, slightly underperforming the BSE Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp shift in technical momentum, an initial upgrade to Buy followed by a downgrade to Hold, and mixed financial signals that influenced investor sentiment amid broader market volatility.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>6a669eb7ecd3681bb1ca1359996b6544</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Procter &amp; Gamble Health Ltd Falls 2.50%: Mixed Technicals and Valuation Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/procter-gamble-health-ltd-falls-250-mixed-technicals-and-valuation-weigh-on-stock-3788664</link><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Health Ltd closed the week down 2.50%, ending at Rs.5,571.90 on 9 January 2026, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s week was marked by a significant technical shift, a downgrade to a Sell rating, and mixed momentum signals, all contributing to a cautious market sentiment despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>de77f104f2e2780d66f83de348b89095</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance Ltd Falls 8.21%: Key Events and Market Pressure Explained</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manappuram-finance-ltd-falls-821-key-events-and-market-pressure-explained-3788663</link><description>Manappuram Finance Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 9 January 2026, with its share price declining 8.21% from Rs.310.70 to Rs.285.20, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a new 52-week high on 7 January followed by sharp price pressure and an intraday low on 9 January, reflecting a swift reversal in market sentiment amid broader volatility.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>330d9d290ea68b40e98d55cfbe31c2f4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nutricircle Ltd Gains 0.99%: Key Milestones and Market Context from 5-9 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nutricircle-ltd-gains-099-key-milestones-and-market-context-from-5-9-jan-2026-3788662</link><description>Nutricircle Ltd closed the week at Rs.411.40, marking a 0.99% gain from its previous close of Rs.407.35, while the Sensex declined by 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s resilience amid a broadly negative market backdrop was highlighted by its new 52-week and all-time high on 5 January 2026, supported by sustained momentum and technical strength. Despite a lack of price movement in the subsequent days, Nutricircle’s ability to hold its gains contrasts with the Sensex’s steady decline, underscoring the stock’s relative stability this week.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>6f2debf15ce4dbe31efcde6b8cebe5f6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indian-renewable-energy-development-agency-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788593</link><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd's latest results are strong, with a record net profit of ₹585.16 crores and a 37.56% year-on-year growth. However, the stock faces selling pressure and trades below key moving averages, indicating market concerns despite solid operational performance.
Time: Jan 10 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>d25a90a2f3701821d36f09fd0896fd52</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tejas Networks Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tejas-networks-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788592</link><description>Tejas Networks Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, with net sales plummeting 88.39% year-on-year to ₹306.79 crores and a net loss of ₹196.55 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and a deteriorating financial position. Despite a slight sequential improvement in sales, the overall outlook remains negative due to ongoing losses and rising debt.
Time: Jan 10 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>ed2e93933521015b6a3364e440e5e3a8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gretex Corporate Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gretex-corporate-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788591</link><description>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd's latest results show a strong quarter-on-quarter recovery with net sales up 261.97% and net profit up 1,387.01%. However, concerns about year-on-year revenue decline, negative cash flow, and earnings volatility suggest caution regarding long-term sustainability.
Time: Jan 10 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>e7869d0b13895662f7c4645b42b8de83</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Hawa Engineers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-hawa-engineers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788590</link><description>Hawa Engineers Ltd's latest results show some sequential improvement in net profit and revenue, but significant year-on-year declines and compressed margins indicate ongoing operational challenges and a difficult environment ahead. Overall, the financial performance is concerning, reflecting struggles in the industrial valve segment and issues with debt management.
Time: Jan 10 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>b201139f2c12be971b9caf1259d6f595</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gretex Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gretex-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788589</link><description>Gretex Industries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 62.71% year-on-year, but limited profitability improvement with a net profit increase of only 8.41%. While the company is debt-free, concerns about its low operating margins and declining return on equity suggest challenges in sustaining growth and justifying its high valuation.
Time: Jan 10 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>024e0b9aaa81c33496860a9f75573672</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are G G Engineering Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-g-g-engineering-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3788588</link><description>G G Engineering Ltd's latest results show a significant net profit increase of 394.89% to ₹4.04 crores, despite a 16.35% decline in revenue to ₹28.35 crores, raising concerns about sustainability and capital efficiency, as indicated by low return metrics and minimal promoter holding. Overall, the results are mixed, highlighting operational challenges despite the profit surge.
Time: Jan 10 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>2ad3d10c5e78195e11c720ecdb74d969</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>