<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Torrent Power Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 11 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-power-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-11-feb-2026-3832599</link><description>Torrent Power Ltd. experienced a notable intraday decline on 11 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 1,398.8, reflecting a 5.7% drop from previous levels. This downturn occurred amid broader market pressures and a reversal following a week-long rally, signalling immediate selling interest and subdued sentiment within the power sector.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>e6747c5ca85bfbe989b60bf95bebd777</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SJVN Ltd. is Rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sjvn-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-by-marketsmojo-3832587</link><description>SJVN Ltd. is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 November 2024. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>799a06c1a2b025571e3905f3efc08331</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajkamal Synthetics Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rajkamal-synthetics-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3832585</link><description>Rajkamal Synthetics Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the company’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>2d398d2f5873574f0e3aa06d318e5fe9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kabsons Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kabsons-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3832584</link><description>Kabsons Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 30 October 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are based on the company’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and valuation.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>41e0d6dcb1f1ea35c433ba2d992f3fbe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poly Medicure Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/poly-medicure-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3832583</link><description>Poly Medicure Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>2b403b2e36cea0427033bee6b9a41964</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Highways Infra Trust is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/national-highways-infra-trust-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3832582</link><description>National Highways Infra Trust is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, a rating that was last updated on 29 May 2025. While this rating change occurred several months ago, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>c9b4548b14d9a1b2f090c5e1a3287fae</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/international-gemmological-institute-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3832581</link><description>International Gemmological Institute (India) Ltd is rated Hold by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 July 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>395ead8478c07a8fb4649c6a8507d729</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sumitomo Chemical India Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sumitomo-chemical-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3832580</link><description>Sumitomo Chemical India Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>26c98192908998294da3454439f3497a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of Baroda is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bank-of-baroda-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3832579</link><description>Bank Of Baroda is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>d7722b3e08400c9f1eabe8a86e30db99</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Pharmova Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jubilant-pharmova-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3832578</link><description>Jubilant Pharmova Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>fa164a3b2a418239df8d46aa894e3994</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Grid Infrastructure Trust is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/india-grid-infrastructure-trust-is-rated-sell-3832573</link><description>India Grid Infrastructure Trust is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on its performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>abb919d9cefc0f4ff6bf3b7ecb3644d5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clean Science &amp; Technology Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/clean-science-technology-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3832577</link><description>Clean Science &amp; Technology Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>dd84731733cfa95796e2f585f198a78e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishal Mega Mart Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vishal-mega-mart-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3832576</link><description>Vishal Mega Mart Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 28 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>d56fe225b8113b71ec007a072ef59957</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Relic Technologies Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/relic-technologies-ltd-is-rated-sell-3832575</link><description>Relic Technologies Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 26 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>7c2547ae8fafbc5c22d1a4b95db8cd8d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KEC International Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kec-international-ltd-is-rated-sell-3832574</link><description>KEC International Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 28 October 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>57d1517ff26318e0174d9cb166109937</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Saw Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jindal-saw-ltd-is-rated-sell-3832572</link><description>Jindal Saw Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>6bba6dace26bb54022392b4558d5a96b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/procter-gamble-hygiene-health-care-ltd-is-rated-sell-3832571</link><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Ltd. is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 October 2024. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>02bee04d274066222107f0b1d86c80a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortis Healthcare Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/fortis-healthcare-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3832570</link><description>Fortis Healthcare Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 January 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>ae0add505b1938f029334e69e1331012</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd is Rated Strong Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/multi-commodity-exchange-of-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-buy-3832569</link><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd is rated Strong Buy by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 27 January 2026, reflecting a positive assessment of the stock’s prospects. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with the latest comprehensive view of the company’s position.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>70a96685f3e7a29e1e2b52e90687d75f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/lumax-auto-technologies-ltd-is-rated-buy-3832567</link><description>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 11 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on its performance and outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>0206f2ec11d50165968a4b232534893e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>