<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>W H Brady &amp; Co Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/w-h-brady-co-ltd-is-rated-sell-3846700</link><description>W H Brady &amp; Co Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the most recent and relevant data to assess the company’s outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>d8e93088a49ee9373fbc473dd03972af</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trigyn Technologies Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/trigyn-technologies-ltd-is-rated-sell-3846701</link><description>Trigyn Technologies Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the most recent insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b62db1cdef0e75475c4f89c5b71ae73a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DRC Systems India Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/drc-systems-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3846703</link><description>DRC Systems India Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>124587351bfd18bf1acbc5d95c7beacc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/qms-medical-allied-services-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3846702</link><description>QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>5d658b8cc2f4ff19a23ab83e2268a0ce</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ramco Cements Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/the-ramco-cements-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3846699</link><description>The Ramco Cements Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>7d433713f55200cf38109f0449d53786</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/uday-jewellery-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3846696</link><description>Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6f91b76f1a3603fc793a3d7b1df16337</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPT Industries Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kpt-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3846697</link><description>KPT Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>3014868f3557c37fd7477d4569879fa8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Destiny Logistics &amp; Infra Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/destiny-logistics-infra-ltd-is-rated-sell-3846698</link><description>Destiny Logistics &amp; Infra Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>8640383a3f4839dc6dc6aa141224fd77</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atishay Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/atishay-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3846694</link><description>Atishay Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, a rating that was last updated on 27 Nov 2025. While this rating change occurred several months ago, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the company’s current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ad0322335e3a42f44c3995dd1d087c4d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aarvi Encon Ltd is Rated Buy by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aarvi-encon-ltd-is-rated-buy-by-marketsmojo-3846693</link><description>Aarvi Encon Ltd is currently rated as a Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 February 2026. While the rating adjustment occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ee2671246f142a0cf912ca7637e08cd4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Permanent Magnets Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/permanent-magnets-ltd-is-rated-sell-3846695</link><description>Permanent Magnets Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 Feb 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b7a0339e564ccc40b8386337c8b4cf4f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G S Auto International Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/g-s-auto-international-ltd-is-rated-sell-3846692</link><description>G S Auto International Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>07722b60b99c0a365a6c06abe88fdfff</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TeleCanor Global Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/telecanor-global-ltd-is-rated-hold-3846691</link><description>TeleCanor Global Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>2862df94fb566f2b62917c62405d7b98</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanchi Karpooram Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kanchi-karpooram-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3846687</link><description>Kanchi Karpooram Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>8c7918adc2b027cfdce8b66a3f4798e2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kritika Wires Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kritika-wires-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3846688</link><description>Kritika Wires Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 07 July 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>0104d3ce5929a204726280bc68f4676f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMJ Land Holdings Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/amj-land-holdings-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3846690</link><description>AMJ Land Holdings Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>bbcd8d5a34d19542bdd2c81a07c4bbb8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ion Exchange (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ion-exchange-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3846686</link><description>Ion Exchange (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date analysis.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>bfd8f74e3c19619e71714c1aae22a830</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CP Capital Limited is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cp-capital-limited-is-rated-sell-3846689</link><description>CP Capital Limited is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 April 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>28272891ca3939746c3991a79c7aef00</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhusudan Masala Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/madhusudan-masala-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3846683</link><description>Madhusudan Masala Ltd is currently rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 January 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>a95f5db37371f5dc2b904517f61c5992</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punjab National Bank is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/punjab-national-bank-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3846684</link><description>Punjab National Bank is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>e0d74eba1b86a256a43f0e7c52e37bd4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>