<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Raymond Lifestyle Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-raymond-lifestyle-ltd-fallingrising-3812272</link><description>On 30-Jan, Raymond Lifestyle Ltd witnessed a significant price surge of 11.82%, closing at ₹1,031.65, driven by strong quarterly results and increased promoter confidence despite lingering concerns over its long-term fundamentals and past performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>14c391f8fc6492d19356ac371a5d6409</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jasch-gauging-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3812271</link><description>On 30-Jan, Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 10.55% to close at ₹465.00. This significant drop marks a reversal after three consecutive days of gains and highlights ongoing challenges faced by the stock amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>80e8a3e95f92c89d758f457cb15f62ce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Digidrive Distributors Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-digidrive-distributors-ltd-fallingrising-3812270</link><description>On 30-Jan, Digidrive Distributors Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹21.61, down 3.53% from the previous close. This drop reflects a continuation of a sustained downward trend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market indices over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5a8e466075bae87f92f80c208fd83a94</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is C P S Shapers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-c-p-s-shapers-ltd-fallingrising-3812269</link><description>On 30-Jan, C P S Shapers Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹1,182.00, up ₹55.00 or 4.88% from the previous close. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong short-term performance, robust investor participation, and favourable technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>90b45730154a459878e0ad213cfb78ce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gateway Distriparks Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gateway-distriparks-ltd-fallingrising-3812268</link><description>On 30-Jan, Gateway Distriparks Ltd saw its share price rise by 1.49% to ₹58.77, continuing a four-day gaining streak that has delivered a 3.7% return over this period despite broader challenges in its long-term performance and investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e7316a733a37ac340ee7b8fee35ec4bb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Integrated Personnel Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-integrated-personnel-services-ltd-fallingrising-3812267</link><description>On 30-Jan, Integrated Personnel Services Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.81% to close at ₹260.00. This drop reflects a broader underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, signalling investor caution and subdued market sentiment towards the stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a595cb6a490f0f24c95350945984c0fe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-qms-medical-allied-services-ltd-fallingrising-3812266</link><description>On 30-Jan, QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 10.62%, closing at ₹88.50. This sharp rise comes despite the company’s longer-term underperformance and mixed financial indicators, reflecting a complex interplay of valuation appeal and investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>efdbb89cd6e9dffd35d648079d230053</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Fine Organic Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-fine-organic-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3812265</link><description>On 30-Jan, Fine Organic Industries Ltd witnessed a notable rise of 4.28%, closing at ₹4,233.30, driven by strong short-term market momentum despite underlying challenges in its longer-term performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c51c48bf032f8041a5e998eb3d0c7f93</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree Vasu Logistics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-vasu-logistics-ltd-fallingrising-3812264</link><description>As of 30-Jan, Shree Vasu Logistics Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply by 5.0% to ₹632.35, reflecting investor concerns over recent quarterly results and the company’s financial health despite its strong long-term returns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fa42324da8b4a82f13a54b53865aec22</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-garden-reach-shipbuilders-engineers-ltd-fallingrising-3812263</link><description>On 30-Jan, Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 7.08%, closing at ₹2,765.70. This rise reflects a combination of strong financial performance, sustained investor confidence, and favourable sector dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>20ede0b1eb00f869939d6ea53f3497bd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-power-instrumentation-gujarat-ltd-fallingrising-3812262</link><description>On 30-Jan, Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.07% to close at ₹112.45. This upward movement comes despite a challenging year marked by significant underperformance relative to the broader market, reflecting a complex interplay of recent gains and underlying fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5b07b7cba95734d9100e8a383308f9fd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sampann Utpadan India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sampann-utpadan-india-ltd-fallingrising-3812261</link><description>On 30-Jan, Sampann Utpadan India Ltd witnessed a notable rise of 6.11% in its share price, closing at Rs 33.32. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust quarterly results, sustained long-term growth, and increased investor participation, positioning the stock favourably against its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>db9cf7da97037343481ad34ac9fce3a4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Eiko Lifesciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-eiko-lifesciences-ltd-fallingrising-3812260</link><description>On 30-Jan, Eiko Lifesciences Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹54.40 with a gain of ₹3.39 or 6.65%. This upward movement reflects a strong short-term performance, supported by increased investor participation and favourable technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>29e2b4068bcdb5661a1bbc8525639988</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gautam Gems Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gautam-gems-ltd-fallingrising-3812259</link><description>On 30-Jan, Gautam Gems Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹3.30, down by ₹0.20 or 5.71% from the previous session. This drop continues a persistent downward trend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>512f3921f70dcb29d9d6991bc41010ab</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is RSWM Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rswm-ltd-fallingrising-3812258</link><description>On 30-Jan, RSWM Ltd's stock price rose by 1.74% to close at ₹140.40, continuing a recent upward trend despite a challenging longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>68514d8006a25b03b777e6940458ae96</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Artemis Medicare Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-artemis-medicare-services-ltd-fallingrising-3812257</link><description>On 30-Jan, Artemis Medicare Services Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 4.7%, closing at ₹246.35, reflecting a strong short-term rebound despite its longer-term underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>425ef45e139e129318e1f92e3bf50f99</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sumit Woods Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sumit-woods-ltd-fallingrising-3812256</link><description>On 30-Jan, Sumit Woods Ltd saw its share price rise by 6.98% to ₹52.85, outperforming its sector and the broader market despite a challenging recent performance record and mixed financial indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d92f3c758f7627503e31197878caf084</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Add-Shop E-Retail Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-add-shop-e-retail-ltd-fallingrising-3812255</link><description>On 30-Jan, Add-Shop E-Retail Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 4.91% to close at ₹8.54. This gain reflects a short-term positive momentum despite the stock's prolonged underperformance against the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d4990df43fedb0e2665bc90b9305fc8e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Tsf Investments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tsf-investments-ltd-fallingrising-3812254</link><description>On 30-Jan, Tsf Investments Ltd saw its share price rise by 4.5% to ₹434.55, reflecting investor optimism driven by robust long-term fundamentals and recent positive quarterly performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>126db39cbef0ed5634ca3a2ed1e5771f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Algoquant Fintech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-algoquant-fintech-ltd-fallingrising-3812253</link><description>On 30-Jan, Algoquant Fintech Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.58% to close at ₹59.99, reflecting a notable underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices despite its strong long-term returns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>251c2daabbe99d66d24c8df5c6524aaf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>