<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 1082</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-1082-3853367</link><description>Network People Services Technologies Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, closing at Rs.1082, marking a significant decline amid broader sectoral and market pressures. The stock’s recent performance reflects a combination of valuation concerns and subdued profit trends over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3fec07f77512c5fc89ba21830f18b6e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853366</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.23.68 on 24 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid a broader market correction and persistent company-specific headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>da765713a7d7ad1b4475c1dfe0908b77</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D P Wires Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/d-p-wires-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853365</link><description>D P Wires Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.154 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing downward momentum. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind sector peers and broader market indices, reflecting persistent challenges in financial metrics and market sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4b45a37f6b4b39398d1278e0268f3287</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3853364</link><description>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd’s stock has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near Rs 3,967, marking a significant decline in its market valuation. This downturn reflects a combination of valuation concerns and underwhelming financial performance over the past year, positioning the stock distinctly below key moving averages and sector benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>cac127ffe74497aa999f33cc5bd4e89c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RBZ Jewellers Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rbz-jewellers-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853362</link><description>RBZ Jewellers Ltd has reached a 52-week low, with its stock price touching Rs 122.35, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns despite some positive quarterly financial results.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ad0482fc2fd8153de6f84da000e2b7e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uma Exports Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uma-exports-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853363</link><description>Shares of Uma Exports Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance. The stock’s latest low price marks a significant milestone in its downward trajectory, underscoring ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and market position within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0ec96fb2a858633dd9d178992c32621e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fino-payments-bank-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3853357</link><description>Fino Payments Bank Ltd has reached a fresh 52-week low, with its stock price touching an intraday low of Rs 199.55, marking a decline of 5.92% on the day. This significant drop reflects ongoing pressures on the company’s financial performance and market sentiment within the Financial Technology sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8e15fcc9b7c70b4d7e20e3bd2eac7881</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matrimony.com Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Earnings Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/matrimonycom-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-earnings-pressure-3853360</link><description>Matrimony.com Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges in both its near-term and long-term financial performance. The stock’s latest low price underscores a period of subdued growth and valuation pressures within the e-retail and e-commerce sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b0bc60d2fc3d5691f767e32fe23e6935</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khadim India Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/khadim-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853361</link><description>Khadim India Ltd’s stock has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing just 1% above its lowest price in the past year at ₹134.15. This marks a significant milestone in the company’s ongoing downward trajectory, reflecting persistent challenges in both its financial performance and market valuation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ab1f40dc26a25b05d8250e93ef54e87e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pudumjee-paper-products-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853359</link><description>Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd has reached a fresh 52-week low, with its stock price touching an intraday low of Rs 80.9, just 2.12% above its lowest level of Rs 80.46 in the past year. This marks a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing decline, reflecting a series of challenges that have weighed on its market performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4584f5948a83b2d3a18c673a394aa067</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electrotherm (India) Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/electrotherm-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853358</link><description>Electrotherm (India) Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing just 1.93% above the lowest price recorded in the past year at Rs 701. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures within the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, with the share price retreating amid broader market weakness and company-specific financial trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d774b7c6c900327c7962ed8e60895a06</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surana Solar Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/surana-solar-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853354</link><description>Surana Solar Ltd, a player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has recently touched a 52-week low price of ₹22.2, marking a significant decline in its stock value. This new low comes amid a backdrop of subdued financial results and persistent challenges reflected in its key performance indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6c15e1927bcec180a3db2940bd60f9f6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Landmark Property Development Company Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low on 24 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/landmark-property-development-company-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-on-24-feb-2026-3853350</link><description>Shares of Landmark Property Development Company Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing at ₹6.20 on 24 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance over the past year amid broader sectoral and market pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4577a785094e35d25f2399e8423c5f91</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vindhya Telelinks Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vindhya-telelinks-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853356</link><description>Vindhya Telelinks Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, closing just 0.68% above its lowest price of Rs 1,042.9. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures within the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, with the share price continuing to trade below all key moving averages.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f8517d0c4e842bba1be3137fcd33db53</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everest Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/everest-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-weakness-3853355</link><description>Everest Industries Ltd has declined to a new 52-week low, closing just 0.28% above its lowest price of Rs 389, reflecting ongoing pressures on the stock amid a challenging financial backdrop and subdued sector performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>69a96632db0bb20648af9942f858ac5c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajmera-realty-infra-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853352</link><description>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near ₹130.1, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained downward trend over the past several sessions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>92e83e58ee894208eb06279bb23269ee</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Damodar Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/damodar-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3853353</link><description>Damodar Industries Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently touched a 52-week low, closing just 0.2% above its lowest price of Rs 25.05. This marks a significant decline for the stock, which has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d3d3df3258fbcdc13a3c3df0b2a3dd8e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shalimar Paints Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shalimar-paints-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-weakness-3853351</link><description>Shalimar Paints Ltd. has reached a new 52-week low, with its stock price touching an intraday low of ₹54.22, marking a significant decline amid ongoing financial pressures and market underperformance. The stock closed just 2.52% above its lowest price in the past year, reflecting sustained downward momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1f08f757757da5e8b8c01ef043c811a9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Sees Mixed Performance Amid Defensive and Cyclical Divergence</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-sees-mixed-performance-amid-defensive-and-cyclical-divergence-3853348</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, has experienced a modest decline over recent sessions, reflecting a cautious market mood. While select heavyweight stocks have demonstrated resilience, the broader index has slipped by 0.93% on the day and 1.59% over the past five trading days, underscoring the ongoing tussle between defensive and cyclical sectors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4bca3e9fc3e79e50fd9f1b656e05deb4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Breadth and Selective Upgrades</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-breadth-and-selective-upgrades-3853347</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index edged higher by 0.21% on 24 Feb 2026, marking a modest gain in a market environment characterised by uneven breadth and sectoral divergence. While select small-cap stocks delivered robust returns, the overall segment grappled with a significant number of decliners, reflecting cautious investor sentiment and selective buying interest.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ac2cd11f023fbe84fbe0c7000affbf73</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>