<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.855 on 11 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pashupati-cotspin-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs855-on-11-feb-2026-3833094</link><description>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, reached a new all-time high of Rs.855 today, underscoring a notable phase of strong performance and market resilience. This milestone reflects the company’s sustained upward momentum amid a competitive industry landscape.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>fd8b79096a3c089ff19239fd57bf3e29</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motisons Jewellers Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 11 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motisons-jewellers-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-11-feb-2026-3833092</link><description>Motisons Jewellers Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 11 Feb 2026, with the stock touching a low of Rs 15.05, reflecting a 6.52% drop from its previous close. This downturn occurred despite an initial positive opening, signalling immediate selling pressure and a shift in market sentiment within the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>90e7195059e3bc5e14c5b48f5b8c4300</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sandhar Technologies Limited Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sandhar-technologies-limited-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3833091</link><description>Sandhar Technologies Limited experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 515, reflecting a sharp price correction of 8.62% from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market, facing immediate selling pressure amid subdued market sentiment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>fbdcad5ff15f601eb0374458cabcadb6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Mart Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.05% Surge on 11 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sg-mart-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-805-surge-on-11-feb-2026-3833090</link><description>SG Mart Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 11 Feb 2026, surging to a new 52-week high of Rs 445.35, marking a significant 7.77% rise from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum and heightened volatility throughout the session.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>46e763c30f485faab3aafa5e7e27cb0e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K P R Mill Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 11 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/k-p-r-mill-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-11-feb-2026-3833089</link><description>K P R Mill Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 11 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 899, reflecting a 5.4% drop as the stock faced significant price pressure amid broader market fluctuations and sector underperformance.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>f87395ab5427278fb945803ed646def1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hind Rectifiers Ltd Opens Strong with Significant Gap Up Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hind-rectifiers-ltd-opens-strong-with-significant-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3833088</link><description>Hind Rectifiers Ltd commenced trading on 11 Feb 2026 with a significant gap up, opening at Rs 1,519.8, marking a 7.18% increase from its previous close. This strong start outpaced the Industrial Manufacturing sector and the broader market, signalling positive sentiment among market participants.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>9f22b39897e8a753b4f20161856bbfad</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-renewable-energy-development-agency-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3833085</link><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd (IREDA) has witnessed a notable 10.6% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance and bearish technical indicators. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and price action, suggests a complex positioning landscape with potential directional bets emerging among traders.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>a24f09d16eac4b9c3712815dba8cd605</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3833086</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd (MAXHEALTH) has witnessed a notable 10.56% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent upgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, the stock has gained 3.15% in the latest session, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments within the hospital sector.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>2048566e03edd8fdad1e7485c0e0aa40</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Ltd. Sees Sharp Surge in Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-ltd-sees-sharp-surge-in-open-interest-amid-mixed-market-signals-3833087</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd. (ASHOKLEY) witnessed a significant 25.6% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 11 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among traders. Despite hitting a new 52-week high of Rs 215.42 intraday, the stock closed lower by 1.54%, underperforming its sector and reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>06dc76a0ac21921e19ed0db6f0e58fcc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortis Healthcare Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fortis-healthcare-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-bullish-momentum-3833084</link><description>Fortis Healthcare Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price gains, coupled with increased volumes and shifting investor positioning, suggest renewed optimism in the hospital sector amid broader market stability.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>7d17b07d7d56b9dca0feba1c646c40cf</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P I Industries Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/p-i-industries-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-derivatives-activity-3833083</link><description>P I Industries Ltd (PIIND), a key player in the pesticides and agrochemicals sector, witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 11 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector peers and broader indices, reflecting increased investor participation and evolving market positioning.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>83450664da0f8633bc101f66021c0574</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi Commodity Exchange Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/multi-commodity-exchange-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3833082</link><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) witnessed a notable 10.78% surge in open interest on 11 Feb 2026, signalling heightened derivatives market activity despite the stock’s underperformance in the cash segment. This spike in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and price movements, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>6f402bda6845b421b9b2f1eef280e1cd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Finance Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-finance-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3833077</link><description>L&amp;T Finance Ltd (LTF), a mid-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has witnessed a notable 12.4% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader benchmarks, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>d210282ad296554e288c3f4f0b4db984</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jubilant-foodworks-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3833081</link><description>Jubilant Foodworks Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, with a 36.8% increase signalling heightened market activity. Despite this, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of investor positioning and market sentiment in the leisure services sector.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>fbc54067b94c0042b16b3a85d28bdf1e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd Surges on Exceptional Volume Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-ltd-surges-on-exceptional-volume-amid-strong-market-momentum-3833079</link><description>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd (TVSSCS) witnessed a remarkable surge in trading volume on 11 Feb 2026, emerging as one of the most actively traded stocks in the Transport Services sector. The stock outperformed its sector peers and broader market indices, driven by robust investor participation and a sustained upward price trend over the past three days.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>2a7822b8c1ad26e034bdc71cba29f685</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quest Laboratories Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/quest-laboratories-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3833078</link><description>Quest Laboratories Ltd witnessed a remarkable surge on 11 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit of 20% and closing at ₹129.60. This extraordinary price movement was driven by strong buying interest, significant unfilled demand, and a regulatory freeze on further trading, marking a notable day for the micro-cap pharmaceutical player.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>e77a6d89915edbddcc2c2cdbd50faad7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Trading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-power-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-trading-3833075</link><description>Torrent Power Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting a notable shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. Despite the stock underperforming its sector and closing lower on 11 Feb 2026, the sharp increase in OI and trading volumes suggests heightened activity and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>f5dbff28a3ed4edd72c0be920c3e4c7c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Ltd. Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-market-signals-3833076</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd., a prominent player in the Indian automobile sector, witnessed one of the highest value turnovers on 11 Feb 2026, with significant institutional interest and large order flows shaping its trading session. Despite hitting a new 52-week high intraday, the stock closed lower, reflecting a complex interplay of market dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>964b7cf5e9b1a1773c01461cd97ededa</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Power Equipment Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-power-equipment-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3833074</link><description>Shares of Supreme Power Equipment Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, plunged sharply on 11 Feb 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit amid intense selling pressure. The stock closed at ₹140.85, down 15.32% on the day, underperforming its sector by over 13 percentage points and marking one of its steepest single-day declines in recent months.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>bc616a925f5e754dcf128c60043e822b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Debock Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/debock-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3833073</link><description>Debock Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the industrial manufacturing sector, surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 11 Feb 2026, reflecting robust investor demand and intense buying interest. The stock closed at ₹1.36, marking a maximum daily gain of 3.82%, significantly outperforming its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>a4fe494152ab13db3941c20b221460f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>