<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Gajanand International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gajanand-international-ltd-fallingrising-3806692</link><description>On 27-Jan, Gajanand International Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 12.5% to ₹9.10, marking a new 52-week and all-time low. This steep drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9f52ea55a6634d616130d140ad94e088</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Standard Glass Lining Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-glass-lining-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3806691</link><description>On 27-Jan, Standard Engineering Technology Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹114.40, down ₹7.10 or 5.84% from the previous close, marking a continuation of a sustained downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks and months.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e0f571bdf6c0219dee54903d8c8c2d67</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sanstar Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanstar-ltd-fallingrising-3806690</link><description>On 27-Jan, Sanstar Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.48% to ₹91.07, continuing a recent downward trend driven by disappointing financial performance and waning investor confidence.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2f6c70201930f7bb03ad41e536185936</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is National Peroxide Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-national-peroxide-ltd-fallingrising-3806689</link><description>On 27-Jan, National Peroxide Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹405.00, down ₹9.55 or 2.3% from the previous close. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, both in terms of its financial performance and market sentiment, as it continues to underperform relative to key benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ce38408e9c6804f50301a992ffec012c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vishwas-agri-seeds-ltd-fallingrising-3806688</link><description>On 27-Jan, Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 10.35% to close at ₹39.40. This steep drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by negative technical indicators and rising investor activity signalling selling pressure.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ff97a18e5c49d1f4f5a8054e20599361</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-fallingrising-3806687</link><description>As of 27-Jan, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd’s stock price has experienced a notable decline, falling 4.01% to ₹1,280.00 by 9:12 PM. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative momentum, driven by a combination of valuation pressures, subdued short-term trading activity, and concerns over promoter share pledging.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ebf5ccbe07b7d4f1b3c784bedf5632b0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enser Communications Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enser-communications-ltd-fallingrising-3806686</link><description>On 27-Jan, Enser Communications Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 10.0% to close at ₹13.50, marking a new 52-week low. This significant drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>6c977c05435629b84a27f0e2d99e57ff</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anand-rathi-wealth-ltd-fallingrising-3806685</link><description>On 27-Jan, Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd's stock price fell by 2.86% to close at ₹2,873.60, continuing a recent downward trend despite the company's robust long-term financial performance and growing institutional interest.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>4a768b690630918588204d50d7b15ed2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Acutaas Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-acutaas-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3806684</link><description>On 27-Jan, Acutaas Chemicals Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.3% to ₹1,722.40 by 9:08 PM. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust financial performance, sustained market outperformance, and positive investor sentiment despite some cautionary valuation metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7a76628a6237853b3e1f9c8257e77b8b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-qms-medical-allied-services-ltd-fallingrising-3806683</link><description>As of 27-Jan, QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd has seen its share price fall by 4.93% to ₹82.00, continuing a trend of underperformance relative to key market benchmarks and raising questions about the stock’s near-term prospects despite some positive operational metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3a33594410e16516db156aed9d15ca21</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cohance Lifesciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cohance-lifesciences-ltd-fallingrising-3806682</link><description>On 27-Jan, Cohance Lifesciences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹374.95, down ₹6.45 or 1.69%. This drop reflects a continuation of a broader downward trend driven by disappointing financial results, weak investor participation, and market concerns over promoter share pledging.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>de19d9d3b37a09d0c12616b8bc0e7802</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anuroop Packaging Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anuroop-packaging-ltd-fallingrising-3806681</link><description>On 27-Jan, Anuroop Packaging Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 9.36% to close at ₹9.49. This drop reflects a continuation of a broader downward trend that has persisted over multiple time frames, underscoring challenges faced by the stock in recent months.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e8cd01ce5584927c9375445d86875330</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ksolves India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ksolves-india-ltd-fallingrising-3806680</link><description>As of 27-Jan, Ksolves India Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹273.00, down 1.85% on the day, marking a continuation of a downward trend driven by disappointing financial results and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>eefc91af812e3bf7ecaca29abf49dad3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Anup Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-anup-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3806679</link><description>On 27-Jan, The Anup Engineering Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹1,731.00, down ₹100.20 or 5.47%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid valuation pressures and underwhelming market performance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>bb09e3eecd2afc697a802162d6220436</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nila Spaces Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nila-spaces-ltd-fallingrising-3806678</link><description>On 27-Jan, Nila Spaces Ltd witnessed a notable increase in its share price, rising by 6.27% to close at ₹14.74. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong short-term performance and heightened investor participation, setting the stock apart from broader market trends.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>a8865098131b097f185979d24776912f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Hardwyn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hardwyn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3806677</link><description>On 27-Jan, Hardwyn India Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.54% to ₹16.00, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share lose value over the past week and month, significantly underperforming the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>0d2a331132952fda351f14d842ddbca2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-affordable-robotic-automation-ltd-fallingrising-3806676</link><description>On 27-Jan, Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹158.50, down ₹6.20 or 3.76% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks, significantly underperforming the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>19a7d2ba49a95f04f5f4f904183f4776</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-power-instrumentation-gujarat-ltd-fallingrising-3806675</link><description>As of 27-Jan, Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at Rs 99.10, down by 4.99% or Rs 5.20. This drop marks a new 52-week low for the stock and reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>46612bba38e74386b0985ef6158a2625</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sikko Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sikko-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3806673</link><description>On 27 Jan, Sikko Industries Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 3.87% to close at ₹3.97. This drop comes despite the company’s impressive long-term returns and recent positive quarterly results, reflecting a complex interplay of market dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>12c193963b2d987b06e4cb22f4b1170e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Zota Health Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-zota-health-care-ltd-fallingrising-3806674</link><description>On 27-Jan, Zota Health Care Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.3% to ₹1,284.00, reflecting investor concerns despite the company’s strong long-term returns and increased institutional interest.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>8e04f60c555ae3883edd6dc819f13696</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>