<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Carraro India Ltd Upgraded to Buy on Improved Valuation and Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/carraro-india-ltd-upgraded-to-buy-on-improved-valuation-and-financial-metrics-3775849</link><description>Carraro India Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has seen its investment rating upgraded from Hold to Buy as of 30 December 2025. This upgrade reflects a marked improvement in the company’s valuation metrics, robust financial trends, and solid quality indicators, despite recent market underperformance. The revised Mojo Score now stands at 71.0, signalling increased investor confidence in the stock’s medium-term prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>66e55634dd6dea7e74c317f1a3e386c5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd Upgraded to Hold Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jyoti-cnc-automation-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-financial-and-technical-signals-3775850</link><description>Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold as of 30 December 2025, reflecting a notable improvement in technical indicators alongside steady fundamental performance. The upgrade comes amid a mixed financial backdrop but is underpinned by enhanced market sentiment and robust management efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1aeb04f400830e01147df703c88f6d95</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd Upgraded to Hold on Attractive Valuation and Strong Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/india-shelter-finance-corporation-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-on-attractive-valuation-and-strong-financials-3775848</link><description>India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold, driven primarily by an improved valuation profile and sustained financial performance. The housing finance company’s recent quarterly results, alongside its relative valuation metrics and technical indicators, have collectively contributed to this reassessment by analysts as of 30 December 2025.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fe2281d73c7465c7d4c58deb88a73fe2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Growth Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sai-silks-kalamandir-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-growth-concerns-3775845</link><description>Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 30 Dec 2025, driven primarily by deteriorating technical indicators and a mixed fundamental outlook. Despite positive quarterly financial results, the stock’s long-term growth prospects and institutional participation have weakened, prompting a reassessment of its investment appeal.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>af85461cdc9e778355db227dfc1213dd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd Upgraded to Sell on Technical Improvement Despite Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-on-technical-improvement-despite-weak-fundamentals-3775847</link><description>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 30 December 2025, driven primarily by a shift in technical indicators despite persistent fundamental weaknesses. The company’s stock price has shown modest recovery in recent sessions, but long-term financial challenges continue to weigh on investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d01cd7383086759044b52d3bf3deda22</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senco Gold Ltd Upgraded to Hold by MarketsMOJO Amid Mixed Fundamentals and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/senco-gold-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-mixed-fundamentals-and-technical-signals-3775846</link><description>Senco Gold Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold as of 30 December 2025, reflecting a nuanced shift in its technical outlook and valuation metrics despite ongoing challenges in financial performance and market returns. This article analyses the four key parameters driving this change: Quality, Valuation, Financial Trend, and Technicals, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the company’s current standing within the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f170c702780fc9ecbca91c0966012172</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NMDC Steel Ltd Upgraded to Sell on Technical Improvements Despite Lingering Fundamental Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nmdc-steel-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-on-technical-improvements-despite-lingering-fundamental-concerns-3775843</link><description>NMDC Steel Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 30 Dec 2025, driven primarily by a shift in technical indicators despite ongoing fundamental challenges. The company’s stock price rose 3.54% on the day, reflecting renewed investor interest amid a mildly bullish technical trend, even as long-term financial metrics remain subdued.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>18fb6dd37dd7444f292e30d1ce305143</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CMS Info Systems Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Weak Technicals and Earnings</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cms-info-systems-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-weak-technicals-and-earnings-3775844</link><description>CMS Info Systems Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 30 December 2025, reflecting a deterioration in technical indicators and flat financial performance. Despite a strong return on equity and low debt levels, the stock’s recent price action and earnings trends have raised concerns among analysts, prompting a reassessment of its outlook within the diversified commercial services sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>34ab4857d80aa2bf93e30189b200f641</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>C.E. Info Systems Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Deteriorating Technicals and Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ce-info-systems-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-deteriorating-technicals-and-financials-3775839</link><description>C.E. Info Systems Ltd, a player in the Software Products sector, has been downgraded from a Sell to a Strong Sell rating as of 30 Dec 2025. This revision reflects deteriorating technical indicators, weakening financial trends, and valuation concerns despite the company’s historically strong management efficiency. Investors should carefully consider these factors amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dca29ad84503a800989e21f0eb69d892</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Downgraded to Sell Amid Mixed Technicals and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technicals-and-valuation-concerns-3775840</link><description>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 30 Dec 2025, driven primarily by a deterioration in technical indicators and valuation concerns despite solid financial performance. The company’s Mojo Score has slipped to 48.0, reflecting a cautious stance amid mixed signals across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technicals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e71e3e1899b18b93528c6270d3a6fca4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd Upgraded to Hold on Improved Technicals and Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/paras-defence-and-space-technologies-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-on-improved-technicals-and-financial-trends-3775842</link><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold as of 30 December 2025, reflecting a combination of improved technical indicators, solid financial performance, and a more balanced valuation. This shift comes amid a backdrop of strong stock returns and positive quarterly results, signalling a cautious but optimistic outlook for the aerospace and defence company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>503622ce7219105efeefb18d215a26ad</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd Upgraded to Hold on Technical and Valuation Improvements</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vijaya-diagnostic-centre-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-and-valuation-improvements-3775841</link><description>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold as of 30 Dec 2025, driven primarily by a shift in technical indicators and a reassessment of valuation metrics. Despite flat financial performance in the recent quarter, the company’s strong management efficiency and low leverage underpin a cautious optimism among investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a50bd78a5e3b623404fdf2a2aef05586</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antony Waste Handling Cell Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Technical and Financial Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/antony-waste-handling-cell-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-technical-and-financial-weakness-3775838</link><description>Antony Waste Handling Cell Ltd has been downgraded from a Sell to a Strong Sell rating as of 30 Dec 2025, reflecting deteriorating technical indicators and disappointing financial trends. The company’s Mojo Score has fallen to 28.0, signalling heightened risk for investors amid ongoing operational challenges and market underperformance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>297f8013700097422493630e0a100266</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A-1 Ltd Upgraded to Hold by MarketsMOJO Amid Mixed Financials and Bullish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/a-1-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-mixed-financials-and-bullish-technicals-3775836</link><description>A-1 Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold as of 30 Dec 2025, reflecting a notable shift in technical indicators and growing institutional participation despite recent financial headwinds. The company’s stock price surged 5.00% on the day, supported by bullish technical signals and a strong long-term market performance that contrasts with its recent quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb00e8d0ce7ed0ed4a080fcbcd6eff8d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tirupati Foam Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Weak Fundamentals and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tirupati-foam-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3775837</link><description>Tirupati Foam Ltd, a player in the Furniture and Home Furnishing sector, has been downgraded from a Sell to a Strong Sell rating as of 30 Dec 2025. This revision reflects deteriorating technical indicators, stagnant financial performance, and weak long-term fundamentals, signalling caution for investors amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1feeb7e2cc9d62518eb2248fcbd04a07</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goyal Associates Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Weak Fundamentals and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/goyal-associates-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3775833</link><description>Goyal Associates Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has been downgraded from a Sell to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO as of 30 December 2025. This revision reflects deteriorating technical indicators, stagnant financial performance, and weak long-term fundamentals, signalling heightened risks for investors amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5ed3abc9d36e15af40b3ed2b3158a093</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Standard (India) Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Weak Fundamentals and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/national-standard-india-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3775832</link><description>National Standard (India) Ltd, a player in the realty sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Sell to Strong Sell as of 30 Dec 2025, reflecting deteriorating fundamentals and increasingly bearish technical indicators. The company’s weak financial performance, poor valuation metrics, and negative technical trends have collectively triggered this downgrade, signalling heightened risk for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0b4b2570cf1f57587f51daf5a8833a64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medico Remedies Downgraded to Hold Amid Mixed Technicals and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/medico-remedies-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technicals-and-valuation-concerns-3775834</link><description>Medico Remedies Ltd, a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Buy to Hold as of 30 December 2025. This adjustment reflects a nuanced reassessment across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators, signalling a more cautious stance despite the company’s solid financial performance and operational strengths.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>be1ebafd189585cb90ff259e087b3776</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eiko Lifesciences Ltd Upgraded to Hold on Technical and Financial Improvements</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/eiko-lifesciences-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-and-financial-improvements-3775829</link><description>Eiko Lifesciences Ltd, a specialty chemicals company, has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold as of 30 December 2025. This change reflects a combination of improved technical indicators, robust quarterly financial results, attractive valuation metrics, and a cautiously optimistic financial trend. Despite recent underperformance relative to the broader market, the company’s operational momentum and technical signals have prompted a reassessment of its outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fc8439582a6c3e2cc18b01c2a4916d1c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wealth First Portfolio Managers Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Technical and Financial Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/wealth-first-portfolio-managers-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-technical-and-financial-weakness-3775835</link><description>Wealth First Portfolio Managers Ltd has been downgraded from a Sell to a Strong Sell rating as of 30 Dec 2025, reflecting deteriorating technical indicators and disappointing financial results. Despite a strong long-term fundamental profile, recent quarterly performance and valuation concerns have weighed heavily on investor sentiment, prompting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9a756384231c49d85ccfba38442587f0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>