<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Interglobe Aviation Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/interglobe-aviation-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3847247</link><description>Interglobe Aviation Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 4,824 as the stock faced significant price pressure amid a broader market downturn and sector weakness.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>ea7397cce85dbdb1cd1a51b1dafb89ce</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-petroleum-corporation-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3847246</link><description>Shares of Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd (BPCL) declined sharply on 19 Feb 2026, hitting an intraday low of Rs 369.3, reflecting a 3.01% drop amid broader market weakness and sector-specific pressures. The stock underperformed the oil sector and the benchmark Sensex, signalling immediate selling pressure and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>db4cfeef53080232ed322dbdf3868f98</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meghmani Organics Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.52.01</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/meghmani-organics-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs5201-3847242</link><description>Meghmani Organics Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.52.01 on 19 Feb 2026, marking a significant decline amid persistent downward momentum. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial health and market positioning.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>f2556b76d6f698a09d356a786aaf014e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Southern Infoconsultants Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.19.69</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/southern-infoconsultants-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1969-3847239</link><description>Southern Infoconsultants Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, with its stock price falling to Rs.19.69 today. This marks a significant decline amid broader market fluctuations and ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and performance metrics.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>bdaf6295e0334d7b8d085a555b814bcc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inani Marbles &amp; Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.11.49</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inani-marbles-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1149-3847244</link><description>Inani Marbles &amp; Industries Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.11.49 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing challenges reflected in its financial and market performance. The stock’s fall comes despite a brief two-day rally, signalling persistent pressures within the company and its sector.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>bfacde921bebdbd99a64e8f39e72c198</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shelter Infra Projects Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.11</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shelter-infra-projects-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs11-3847237</link><description>Shelter Infra Projects Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.11 today, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The stock’s performance has been notably weak over recent sessions, reflecting a combination of financial pressures and market dynamics within the construction sector.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>8c2c1e083c223e929addeb078e6d6e27</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ind-Agiv Commerce Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.66.3</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ind-agiv-commerce-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs663-3847245</link><description>Ind-Agiv Commerce Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.66.3 today, marking a significant decline amid persistent downward momentum. This new low reflects ongoing pressures on the stock, which has underperformed both its sector and the broader market over the past year.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>5fa7fa1feb1ba6dddef0bf29f980a2d1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bang Overseas Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.42.08 Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bang-overseas-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs4208-amidst-market-volatility-3847236</link><description>Bang Overseas Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed its stock price decline to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.42.08 today, marking a significant milestone in its recent market performance amid broader sectoral and market fluctuations.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>87eb77636c14665100ba3ecc8c5ffc1c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox Wind Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.97.35 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-wind-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs9735-amid-market-pressure-3847238</link><description>Inox Wind Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.97.35 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downtrend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns related to valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>a03f0dfe833a3da4f3cc6b877dc34a79</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/patel-integrated-logistics-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3847241</link><description>Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.11.68 today, marking a significant decline amid a broader market environment where the Sensex has experienced sharp reversals. The stock’s recent performance highlights ongoing concerns within the transport services sector and reflects a continuation of a downward trend over the past several days.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>23ecf5e90db72a5c012881421007e219</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Choksi Asia Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.177</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/choksi-asia-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs177-3847243</link><description>Choksi Asia Ltd, a prominent player in the FMCG sector, reached a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.177 today, underscoring a remarkable rally that has seen the stock more than double over the past year. This milestone reflects sustained momentum supported by strong market dynamics and favourable trading patterns.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>ed70323458b841c9e715737da255e194</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Holdings &amp; Hospitality Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.53.19</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-holdings-hospitality-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs5319-3847240</link><description>Supreme Holdings &amp; Hospitality Ltd, a player in the Realty sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.53.19 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a volatile trading session. Despite a brief intraday recovery, the stock remains under pressure, reflecting ongoing concerns about the company’s financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>3040b32b5ef90154bf1f394c3b9698dd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil India Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.09% Surge on 19 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-509-surge-on-19-feb-2026-3847234</link><description>Oil India Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday momentum on 19 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 474.8, marking a 4.77% rise from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading activity amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>7d30b02f34f9c4c3951f37ffccc517d4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meghmani Organics Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/meghmani-organics-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3847233</link><description>Meghmani Organics Ltd, a player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has recorded a new all-time low in its stock price, closing just 0.1% above its 52-week low of ₹52.2. This marks a continuation of a sustained decline, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7c27bf6af5600bba8280092da34616ab</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3847232</link><description>Swiggy Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, witnessed a significant 14.5% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 19 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish sentiment and speculative bets.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>db09281c93407a5c8aa740006e81d95d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3847229</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd (POLICYBZR) has witnessed a significant 11.23% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a cautious sentiment among traders amid deteriorating technical indicators and falling investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e0fe21aaebd6e9da6e86710b753ed1e5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-momentum-3847231</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd has witnessed a significant 11.3% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting cautious sentiment amid bearish technical indicators and falling investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e8caf33212b8907e4f310ff99a33f0de</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-momentum-3847230</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a major player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has witnessed a notable 13.56% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining price trends and subdued investor participation, suggests a complex market positioning that warrants close attention from investors and analysts alike.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>06302e3ddf2693c9b6599e279070edc6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Positive Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sona-blw-precision-forgings-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-positive-market-momentum-3847226</link><description>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd (SONACOMS) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor sentiment. The 13.02% increase in OI, coupled with rising volumes and sustained price gains, suggests a growing bullish bias among traders, despite a recent dip in delivery volumes. This article analyses the implications of these developments for investors and the stock’s near-term outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>69b38f62a97a53872c9721ab3458d33f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lodha-developers-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3847225</link><description>Lodha Developers Ltd (LODH) witnessed a significant 17.7% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment on 19 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s underperformance. The surge in open interest, coupled with falling prices and declining delivery volumes, suggests a shift in market positioning that may indicate bearish bets among traders.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>95291299e605d0995eeb7afa90f018e5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>