<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Dishman Carbogen Amcis Hits Intraday High with Strong Trading Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dishman-carbogen-amcis-hits-intraday-high-with-1245-surge-on-17-dec-2025-3761428</link><description>Dishman Carbogen Amcis demonstrated robust intraday performance on 17 Dec 2025, reaching a day’s high of Rs 242.6, reflecting a 5.2% rise during trading hours and outperforming its sector by 4.35% amid a broadly subdued market environment.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>176427273dfe1c6518e69e6233c1c71d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palash Securities Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/palash-securities-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3761427</link><description>Palash Securities has reached a new 52-week low, with its share price approaching Rs 104.1, marking a significant milestone in its recent market performance. This development reflects ongoing pressures within the FMCG sector and highlights the challenges faced by the company over the past year.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>dc16bb9d972b862dacaf4a76b86161fa</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unipro Technologies Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.7.52</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/unipro-technologies-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs752-3761419</link><description>Unipro Technologies reached a significant milestone today by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.7.52, marking a notable moment in the stock’s recent trading history. This fresh peak reflects a period of positive momentum amid a fluctuating broader market environment.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>5dd0038f384428617a92532e65fb2543</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suraj Estate Developers Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.251</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suraj-estate-developers-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3761425</link><description>Suraj Estate Developers has reached a new 52-week low, with its stock price touching Rs.251 today. This marks a significant decline amid a broader market environment where the Sensex has shown mixed performance, underscoring the challenges faced by the company within the realty sector.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>1cf7f2223f9f74bf82064717b4429157</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Minds Technologies Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.484</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/happiest-minds-technologies-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs484-3761420</link><description>Happiest Minds Technologies has reached a new 52-week low, closing at Rs.484 today, marking a significant price level for the software and consulting company amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>4b8e2eda03a8a4126a7ee42d34c7bfff</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kretto Syscon Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.75 Amidst Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kretto-syscon-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs075-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3761421</link><description>Kretto Syscon, a player in the realty sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.0.75, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>3759becfdbc545078bbeffc9481f2cbd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saregama India Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saregama-india-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-17-dec-2025-3761417</link><description>Saregama India witnessed a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 347.35, reflecting significant price pressure amid a volatile trading session. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, signalling immediate challenges in market sentiment.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>fa966a2f852ca67f0b67e82c2daab23c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>COSCO (India) Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.206.3 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cosco-india-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2063-amidst-continued-downtrend-3761418</link><description>COSCO (India) has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.206.3 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures within the company’s financial and operational landscape.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>7ec8a2c498783b097493acf8c3f8f999</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alps Industries Reaches New 52-Week High, Marking Significant Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alps-industries-hits-new-52-week-high-marking-significant-rally-3761422</link><description>Alps Industries, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has achieved a notable milestone by reaching a new 52-week high price of ₹3.48. This marks a significant rally for the stock, which has demonstrated strong momentum over recent trading sessions.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>b0109dbf67b5391ff3d8e439a616c4fb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Upsurge Investment &amp; Finance Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.66</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/upsurge-investment-finance-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs66-3761424</link><description>Upsurge Investment &amp; Finance has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.66, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>e8524e26ccc5550d485665f2bc6d3e03</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Riddhi Siddhi Gluco Biols Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.451.2 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/riddhi-siddhi-gluco-biols-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3761423</link><description>Riddhi Siddhi Gluco Biols touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.451.2 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on the company’s financial performance and market valuation.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>4acacf51d50756cd3151a4c762d61fd0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RPP Infra Projects Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.98.45 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rpp-infra-projects-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3761426</link><description>RPP Infra Projects has reached a fresh 52-week low of Rs.98.45, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trajectory over the past week. The stock’s recent performance contrasts sharply with broader market trends, reflecting ongoing pressures within the construction sector.
Time: 43 minutes ago</description><guid>588f7b7c407ccc8787ba59fe1585e447</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suraj Estate Developers Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suraj-estate-developers-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3761414</link><description>Suraj Estate Developers has reached an all-time low, trading just 0.19% above its 52-week low of ₹258, marking a significant milestone in its recent market performance. The stock has experienced a sustained decline over the past year, reflecting a challenging period for the company within the Realty sector.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>6ffbd642f1c24ae49d0d106897e29c44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-weak-price-action-3761415</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a decline in its share price and subdued investor participation. This development highlights evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders in the hospital sector stock.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>1a30c546bdd631144cb7a69a2d297cfd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance Company Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cholamandalam-investment-finance-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3761416</link><description>Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance Company Ltd (CHOLAFIN) has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of recent price softness and subdued investor participation, raising questions about the underlying directional bets and potential implications for the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>889e06fe5bab311cee67c9a95c779965</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganga Forging Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganga-forging-surges-179-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3761413</link><description>Shares of Ganga Forging Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 17 Dec 2025, reflecting intense buying interest and a maximum daily gain of 17.88%. The micro-cap stock, operating in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, witnessed a significant spike in price and trading volume, prompting a regulatory freeze on further transactions for the day.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>0e9608e7aea94d4cd92220dbe1bf1558</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JITF Infra Logistics Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jitf-infra-logistics-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3761407</link><description>Shares of JITF Infra Logistics Ltd witnessed intense selling pressure on 17 Dec 2025, hitting the lower circuit limit as the stock recorded its maximum daily loss. The micro-cap company, operating in the Other Utilities sector, faced a sharp decline amid falling investor participation and unfilled supply, signalling a period of heightened market caution.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>116803f17a2be41bc4c8eacc7b3462c0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cyient Ltd Sees Notable Surge in Open Interest Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cyient-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3761408</link><description>Cyient Ltd, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has experienced a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price performance and declining investor participation, raising questions about potential directional bets and future market trends for the stock.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>32f540156c8bd5da870966528b296b3c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flexituff Ventures International Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/flexituff-ventures-international-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3761409</link><description>Flexituff Ventures International Ltd witnessed a significant surge in trading activity on 17 Dec 2025, hitting its upper circuit price limit of ₹16.09. This movement was driven by robust buying interest, resulting in the maximum permissible daily gain of 4.96%, reflecting heightened investor enthusiasm in the micro-cap garment and apparel sector stock.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>8a843b603a3eb1a8d55d42c10e18ea38</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gretex Industries Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gretex-industries-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3761404</link><description>Shares of Gretex Industries Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 17 Dec 2025, reflecting intense selling pressure and a sharp decline in investor confidence. The stock closed at ₹180.5, marking a new 52-week low and underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>97489114af2a410928291c2b36aab6a4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>