<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>S.M. Gold Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.10.9 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sm-gold-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3765866</link><description>S.M. Gold, a company operating in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.10.9 today, marking a significant milestone in its recent price trajectory. This decline comes amid a sustained period of underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>6333464aa47579801b8112f9f1e80ea0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajnish Wellness Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.61</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rajnish-wellness-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3765859</link><description>Rajnish Wellness, a company in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has reached a new 52-week low price of Rs.0.61, marking a significant decline in its stock value amid a broader market environment where benchmark indices continue to show strength.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>5ec948008826bde5d5424ab09b486673</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemfab Alkalis Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.435.05 Amidst Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chemfab-alkalis-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3765862</link><description>Chemfab Alkalis has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.435.05, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a broader market environment where the Sensex continues to show strength. The stock’s recent performance contrasts sharply with the overall positive trend in the commodity chemicals sector and the wider market indices.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>1dd094948b0885b063c2060194dcf2e4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rossell India Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.50 Amidst Market Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rossell-india-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs50-amidst-underperformance-3765864</link><description>Rossell India’s share price touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.50 today, marking a significant decline amid a broadly positive market environment where the Sensex advanced towards its own 52-week high.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>cd138a5078547b73a8e8d955b5ff8adc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Reaches New 52-Week High of Rs.1463.7 Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-forge-reaches-new-52-week-high-of-rs14637-on-22-dec-2025-3765861</link><description>Bharat Forge has attained a new 52-week high, touching Rs.1463.7 today, underscoring a notable milestone in its market journey. This achievement reflects sustained momentum supported by robust financial metrics and favourable market conditions within the auto components sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>5d712fd8a03c22e9051f1a9f99a559d1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sea TV Network Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.3.92 Amid Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sea-tv-network-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3765863</link><description>Sea TV Network's stock price reached a fresh 52-week low of Rs.3.92 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market gains and sector underperformance. The media and entertainment company’s shares have been on a downward trajectory, reflecting ongoing challenges in both its financial metrics and market positioning.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>434ef0e137c0de5490b4e28c8d8446da</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TCPL Packaging . Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.2864.1 Amid Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tcpl-packaging-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs28641-amid-market-outperformance-3765860</link><description>TCPL Packaging . has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.2864.1 today, marking a significant price level for the packaging sector stock. This decline comes despite a broadly positive market environment, with the Sensex advancing towards its own 52-week high.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>67f0f183c6b8de2d38c957fbfd381c6c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Betex India Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.266.25 Amid Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/betex-india-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs26625-amidst-market-rally-3765858</link><description>Betex India, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.266.25 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market gains. The stock's performance contrasts sharply with the upward trajectory of the Sensex and sector indices, reflecting ongoing challenges for the company.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>944e2fb74026701b91a5d9187ee95308</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Union Bank Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.284.5, Marking Significant Market Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-union-bank-reaches-new-52-week-high-of-rs2845-on-22-dec-2025-3765865</link><description>City Union Bank has reached a new 52-week high of Rs.284.5, reflecting a notable milestone in its market performance. This achievement underscores the bank's sustained momentum amid a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b547e42e6bffb56b4197e72eb6c92fb3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pitti Engineering Hits Intraday High with Strong 7.4% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pitti-engineering-hits-intraday-high-with-715-surge-on-22-dec-2025-3765856</link><description>Pitti Engineering recorded a robust intraday performance on 22 December 2025, touching a day’s high of Rs 848.7, reflecting a 7.4% rise. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, marking a notable trading session for the industrial manufacturing company.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>0c0dff2a37b515e0f1e31733f44e952f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trent . Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.38% Surge Amid Market Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trent-hits-intraday-high-with-368-surge-on-22-dec-2025-3765855</link><description>Trent . recorded a notable intraday high of Rs 4,199 today, reflecting a 3.38% rise as it outpaced the broader Garments &amp; Apparels sector and the Sensex. The stock’s performance marks a continuation of its recent upward momentum, supported by positive market conditions and sectoral trends.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>dc4245d20efc02f1e4131afc9ea8a3fe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Union Bank Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-union-bank-stock-hits-all-time-high-on-22-dec-2025-3765852</link><description>City Union Bank has reached an all-time high, underscoring a period of robust performance and sustained growth. The stock’s recent surge reflects a combination of strong financial metrics and consistent market outperformance, positioning the bank prominently within the private sector banking space.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>ec2a72c263a9a06c5cf0bbff24be36fd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees Notable Surge in Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3765846</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has experienced a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning and investor sentiment. Despite a modest price movement and subdued delivery volumes, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and hedging strategies among market participants.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>b0205346658496772b8ef55d905064a5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods Sees Notable Surge in Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/patanjali-foods-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3765844</link><description>Patanjali Foods Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning and investor sentiment. Despite a modest decline in the stock price, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests active trading interest and potential directional bets within the edible oil sector.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>074abb99c8d4fe5eba6053e7fa17aecc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/glenmark-pharmaceuticals-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3765845</link><description>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development coincides with the stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and broader indices, signalling increased investor focus on the pharmaceutical and biotechnology company.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>6b402c032a0029e23410720bc2d26538</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synoptics Technologies Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/synoptics-technologies-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3765841</link><description>Shares of Synoptics Technologies Ltd surged to their upper circuit limit on 22 Dec 2025, reflecting intense buying interest and a maximum permissible daily gain of 5.0%. The stock closed at ₹65.15, marking a notable outperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>4f840579b75cb13de9d1ce49137fb67e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/multi-commodity-exchange-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3765843</link><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest within its derivatives segment, coinciding with robust price performance and heightened investor participation. This development reflects evolving market positioning and potential directional bets as the stock trades near record highs.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>19175b35f86f45cd058995b924c867ef</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shreeoswal Seeds &amp; Chemicals Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shreeoswal-seeds-chemicals-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3765842</link><description>Shreeoswal Seeds &amp; Chemicals Ltd witnessed a robust trading session on 22 Dec 2025, hitting its upper circuit limit with an 8.47% gain, reflecting intense buying interest and a surge in investor participation within the Other Agricultural Products sector.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>b37787e29244dd619024d13dcd1920f4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Star Ltd. Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-star-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-and-rising-investor-participation-3765838</link><description>Blue Star Ltd., a key player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has witnessed a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning and investor sentiment. Despite recent price softness, the surge in open interest and trading volumes suggests active participation and potential directional bets among market participants.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>b8bc95e238bc9e85d0df65ddadcba4cd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrenik Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure and Market Enthusiasm</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shrenik-ltd-surges-196-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3765835</link><description>Shares of Shrenik Ltd surged to their upper circuit limit on 22 Dec 2025, reflecting intense buying interest and a maximum permissible daily gain of 19.61%. The stock closed at ₹0.61, marking a significant outperformance relative to its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>2bfb568cc15e5785f1e1cc8ec9087acd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>