<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Axis Bank Ltd Gains 0.18%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axis-bank-ltd-gains-018-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3789063</link><description>Axis Bank Ltd. closed the week with a modest gain of 0.18%, ending at Rs.1,271.95 on 9 January 2026, marginally outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by strong call option activity, fresh 52-week highs, and robust institutional interest, reflecting a cautiously optimistic market sentiment despite broader market weakness.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9f8cdf735ae5db2714c5444cab9ee620</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd’s Volatile Week: 5.45% Surge Followed by Sharp 10.06% Drop</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rajratan-global-wire-ltds-volatile-week-545-surge-followed-by-sharp-1006-drop-3789062</link><description>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd experienced a turbulent trading week from 5 to 9 January 2026, ending with a slight decline of 0.93% to close at Rs.461.65. This performance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period, indicating relative resilience despite significant intraday volatility and valuation concerns. The stock saw sharp gains early in the week, including new 52-week highs on 7 and 8 January, before succumbing to heavy selling pressure on the final trading day.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6b415c18d7633e1958de168cc0c13163</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JTL Industries Ltd Falls 13.81%: 4 Key Events Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jtl-industries-ltd-falls-1381-4-key-events-driving-the-sharp-decline-3789060</link><description>JTL Industries Ltd endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price tumbling 13.81% to close at Rs.51.54, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% decline over the same period. The stock hit successive 52-week lows amid persistent negative financial results, reduced institutional interest, and sectoral headwinds, culminating in a sustained downtrend that overshadowed broader market resilience.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0644b7095746e19889a9b181d5011086</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pankaj Polymers Gains 15.44%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pankaj-polymers-gains-1544-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3789057</link><description>Pankaj Polymers Ltd delivered a strong performance in the week ending 9 January 2026, gaining 15.44% to close at Rs.51.65, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, reflecting sustained momentum and robust investor interest despite a broadly weak market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3bba497d13bbf267a71e51eb87d4b673</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crimson Metal Engineering Company Ltd Gains 10.28%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/crimson-metal-engineering-company-ltd-gains-1028-5-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3789056</link><description>Crimson Metal Engineering Company Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 10.28% from Rs.43.60 to Rs.48.08 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock consistently hit new 52-week and all-time highs each trading day, reflecting strong momentum amid a broadly negative market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9c2802be1f9353b70c4fe2a1309edf4d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHV Infra Projects Ltd Falls 10.59%: Key Technical Shifts and Market Reaction</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ghv-infra-projects-ltd-falls-1059-key-technical-shifts-and-market-reaction-3789061</link><description>GHV Infra Projects Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 10.59% from Rs.287.90 on 2 January to Rs.257.40 on 9 January 2026. This underperformance was notably sharper than the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting heightened market concerns and mixed technical signals that influenced investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a6997eb2053ae9cb4a6b33fe868f264a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pilani Investment Falls 4.82%: Downgrade and Technical Weakness Drive the Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pilani-investment-falls-482-downgrade-and-technical-weakness-drive-the-slide-3789059</link><description>Pilani Investment &amp; Industries Corporation Ltd endured a challenging week, with its stock price declining 4.82% from Rs.5,185.95 to Rs.4,935.90, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating financials and a notable shift in technical momentum, signalling increased caution among investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f2044d52b79bce3cc2972ee307e98176</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Declines 4.72%: Technical Weakness and Financial Struggles Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hathway-cable-datacom-declines-472-technical-weakness-and-financial-struggles-weigh-3789058</link><description>Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.72% to close at ₹12.10, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by fluctuating technical signals, a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, and persistent financial weaknesses, all contributing to the downward pressure on the stock despite some early optimism on 5 January.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>25a9643e128a328f62e5ae69bf7cd13d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd. Falls 3.27%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karur-vysya-bank-ltd-falls-327-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3789055</link><description>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd. (KVB) experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price declining by 3.27% to close at Rs.263.55, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite early gains marked by new 52-week and all-time highs on 5 and 6 January, the stock faced selling pressure later in the week amid broader market weakness and elevated volatility, culminating in a notable drop on the final trading day.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ef79331999b60454068de25faaa6fa4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Petrochem Ltd Falls 5.74%: Mixed Technical Signals and Hold Upgrade Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/panama-petrochem-ltd-falls-574-mixed-technical-signals-and-hold-upgrade-shape-the-week-3789054</link><description>Panama Petrochem Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 5.74% from ₹312.00 to ₹294.10, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite the downward price movement, the stock's technical indicators shifted from a mildly bearish to a sideways trend, reflecting a phase of consolidation amid mixed signals from fundamental and technical data.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4c84361eab294919e4c1c6e35ed82f96</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Embassy Developments Ltd Gains 18.39%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/embassy-developments-ltd-gains-1839-5-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3789042</link><description>Embassy Developments Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 18.39% from Rs.56.62 to Rs.67.03 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by consecutive upper circuit hits on four trading days, reflecting intense buying interest amid a challenging fundamental backdrop and a prevailing strong sell rating.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>68d3a5fcaa46493bcd68a830a749a154</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd Falls 3.41%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shriram-pistons-rings-ltd-falls-341-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3789041</link><description>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 09 Jan 2026, closing at Rs.3,187.00, down 3.41% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.3,299.65. Despite this decline, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by significant price milestones, including new all-time and 52-week highs, followed by a sharp correction in the latter half of the week amid broader market weakness.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9eed04ba1ba2ad287124251127f7e419</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Synthetics Ltd Gains 11.22%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-synthetics-ltd-gains-1122-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3789040</link><description>Garware Synthetics Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 11.22% from ₹12.30 to ₹13.68 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s rebound from a 52-week low and a strong gap up midweek were the defining moments that shaped this volatile but ultimately positive week for the company’s shares.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>77ae8870ae05da51f6b94342b959fd3e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Explosives Falls 4.20%: Mixed Technicals and Financials Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-explosives-falls-420-mixed-technicals-and-financials-shape-weekly-trend-3789039</link><description>Premier Explosives Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 9 January 2026, closing at ₹518.30, down 4.20% from ₹541.05 the previous Friday. Despite this decline, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical upgrade to a Hold rating, signalling cautious optimism amid mixed momentum indicators and fluctuating daily price movements.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>706b6f1a330345d6f292b5ee205325be</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maithan Alloys Falls 4.86%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maithan-alloys-falls-486-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3789038</link><description>Maithan Alloys Ltd. experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 4.86% from ₹1,016.30 to ₹966.90 between 5 and 9 January 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period, signalling heightened selling pressure on the stock amid deteriorating fundamentals, bearish technical signals, and valuation shifts. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, mixed technical momentum, and a nuanced improvement in valuation attractiveness, all contributing to the stock’s volatile trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c55759d522574a848aa6f232cb013370</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piccadily Agro Industries Ltd Falls 7.68%: Bearish Momentum and Mixed Technical Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piccadily-agro-industries-ltd-falls-768-bearish-momentum-and-mixed-technical-signals-shape-the-week-3789037</link><description>Piccadily Agro Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 7.68% from Rs.615.00 on 5 January to Rs.567.75 on 9 January 2026. This underperformance came despite the broader Sensex falling 2.62% over the same period, indicating that the stock faced more severe selling pressure amid bearish technical signals and sector headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7609749b4780d1dd174860c8a4326b41</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd Falls 3.81%: 4 Key Factors Behind This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-hi-tech-films-ltd-falls-381-4-key-factors-behind-this-weeks-volatility-3789036</link><description>Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd closed the week at Rs.3,045.30, down 3.81% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.3,166.00, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock experienced volatile trading marked by mixed technical signals, a sharp intraday low on 8 January, and a late-week rebound attempt, reflecting a complex momentum shift amid broader market pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a4379de340f7df77a523decc3b81e556</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NACL Industries Gains 2.53%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nacl-industries-gains-253-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3789035</link><description>NACL Industries Ltd recorded a volatile week from 5 to 9 January 2026, ending with a modest gain of 2.53% despite sharp intraday swings. The stock outperformed the Sensex, which declined 2.62% over the same period, driven by two consecutive upper circuit hits on 6 and 7 January, followed by a lower circuit hit on 9 January amid heavy selling pressure. This rollercoaster price action reflected strong investor interest, regulatory trading halts, and shifting market sentiment within the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8d213267e8c49333a3d769eea2d83fe3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pearl Global Industries Ltd Falls 8.24%: Technical Shifts and Market Pressure Define Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pearl-global-industries-ltd-falls-824-technical-shifts-and-market-pressure-define-week-3789034</link><description>Pearl Global Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 8.24% to close at Rs.1,510.80, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp correction following an initial upgrade to Buy, technical momentum shifts, and sector-specific pressures that weighed on the garment and apparel company’s shares.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8187a20583bc407dff6b465632f16f84</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd Falls 4.46%: Mixed Technical Signals Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhuveer-com-18-network-ltd-falls-446-mixed-technical-signals-shape-weekly-performance-3789033</link><description>Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd experienced a volatile week marked by a 4.46% decline in its stock price, closing at Rs.268.70 on 9 January 2026, despite outperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall. The week featured a complex interplay of technical momentum shifts, including a downgrade to a mildly bearish stance midweek followed by an upgrade to a Sell rating driven by technical improvements. These developments unfolded amid weak fundamental performance, creating a nuanced outlook for investors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c6e88df02acc797765f1bf1e4c2be350</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>