<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>MSR India Q3 FY26: Revenue-Less Operations Continue as Losses Mount</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/msr-india-q3-fy26-revenue-less-operations-continue-as-losses-mount-3842938</link><description>MSR India Ltd., a micro-cap infrastructure and construction company with a market capitalisation of ₹33.00 crores, reported another quarter of operational distress in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), posting a net loss of ₹0.29 crores with zero revenue generation. The Hyderabad-based firm, which trades at ₹5.35 on the NSE, has now recorded seven consecutive quarters without any sales, marking a stark departure from its historical operations in civil works and land development activities.
Time: Feb 16 2026 10:41 PM IST</description><guid>b8d2a718fbc255241a610d669bc8cc00</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>V2 Retail Joins Reliable Performers List Following Robust Quarterly Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/v2-retail-joins-reliable-performers-list-following-robust-quarterly-growth-3842917</link><description>V2 Retail, a small-cap player in the garments and apparels sector, has been added to the esteemed Reliable Performers list as of 16 February 2026, following a robust quarterly financial performance that underscores its growing fundamental strength and promising outlook.
Time: Feb 16 2026 10:30 PM IST</description><guid>28c0a19b3a5795d12b0579f3f808b592</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Fertilizer Joins Hidden Turnarounds List on Strong Quarterly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/national-fertilizer-joins-hidden-turnarounds-list-on-strong-quarterly-performance-3842916</link><description>Natl.Fertilizer has been added to the Hidden Turnarounds list as of 16 February 2026, following a remarkable quarterly financial performance that signals a potential fundamental turnaround. The small-cap stock, trading at Rs 81.16 at the time of inclusion, has demonstrated robust growth metrics and improved profitability, positioning it as a compelling candidate for investors seeking early-stage recovery plays in the fertiliser sector.
Time: Feb 16 2026 10:30 PM IST</description><guid>ded910090dbd163deffe4aab86273b26</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lexus Granito Q3 FY26: Severe Revenue Contraction Deepens Operational Crisis</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/lexus-granito-q3-fy26-severe-revenue-contraction-deepens-operational-crisis-3842937</link><description>Lexus Granito (India) Ltd., a micro-cap diversified consumer products company with a market capitalisation of ₹72.00 crores, reported deeply troubling Q3 FY26 results that underscore mounting operational distress. The company posted a net profit of ₹0.71 crores for the December 2025 quarter, up 91.89% quarter-on-quarter from ₹0.37 crores but down 787.50% year-on-year from ₹0.08 crores. However, this headline profit figure masks a catastrophic revenue collapse and severe margin deterioration that signal fundamental business challenges.
Time: Feb 16 2026 10:21 PM IST</description><guid>0157c7ecb6f55624f0d73ec7b4ec05b9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parmax Pharma Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Deepen as Revenue Plummets 72% YoY</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/parmax-pharma-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-deepen-as-revenue-plummets-72-yoy-3842936</link><description>Parmax Pharma Ltd., a micro-cap pharmaceutical company specialising in Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients (API) and Contract Manufacturing Operations (CMO), has reported deeply concerning financial results for Q3 FY26, with net losses widening to ₹0.73 crores whilst revenues collapsed 72.74% year-on-year to ₹2.53 crores. The company, trading at ₹32.00 with a market capitalisation of just ₹12.00 crores, has now recorded consecutive quarterly losses throughout FY26, raising serious questions about operational viability and management execution.
Time: Feb 16 2026 10:05 PM IST</description><guid>8ce19f16677eef7a4ef3bb038339f479</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Industrial Development Q3 FY26: Losses Deepen Amid Revenue Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/dalmia-industrial-development-q3-fy26-losses-deepen-amid-revenue-volatility-3842935</link><description>Dalmia Industrial Development Ltd., a micro-cap trading and distribution company, reported a challenging third quarter for FY2026, posting a net loss of ₹0.11 crores in Q3 FY26 compared to a profit of ₹0.19 crores in the preceding quarter. The company's market capitalisation stands at ₹19.00 crores, with shares trading at ₹9.60 following a 4.46% gain on February 16, 2026, as investors reacted to the mixed quarterly performance.
Time: Feb 16 2026 09:48 PM IST</description><guid>917127f3c700b2a77d9607f81087f92c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lorenzini Apparels Q3 FY26: Profitability Returns But Margin Pressure Persists</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/lorenzini-apparels-q3-fy26-profitability-returns-but-margin-pressure-persists-3842934</link><description>Lorenzini Apparels Ltd., a micro-cap garments and apparels manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹146.00 crores, reported a modest return to profitability in Q3 FY26 with net profit of ₹1.10 crores, declining 22.54% quarter-on-quarter but reversing from a loss of ₹1.62 crores in the year-ago period. However, the quarter's results reveal persistent margin pressures and operational challenges that continue to weigh on the company's financial performance.
Time: Feb 16 2026 09:34 PM IST</description><guid>e83e2db74f3ca9605190c3ffaf8e4398</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3842876</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across market capitalisations, sectors, and individual companies. With over 4,000 stocks reporting, the aggregate data reveals a modest improvement in positive results, led by mid-cap companies, while large caps continue to face challenges amid a cautious economic backdrop.
Time: Feb 16 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>89615e924d99af0bfa83583f6615340a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chandrima Mercantiles Q3 FY26: Profit Volatility Masks Underlying Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/chandrima-mercantiles-q3-fy26-profit-volatility-masks-underlying-concerns-3842933</link><description>Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd., a micro-cap agricultural products trading company with a market capitalisation of ₹224.00 crores, reported net profit of ₹0.41 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), representing a sharp 90.31% decline quarter-on-quarter from ₹4.23 crores in Q2 FY26. Year-on-year, profits rose 2.50% from ₹0.40 crores in Q3 FY25. The stock closed at ₹6.38 on February 16, 2026, down 0.78% on the day, trading 55.94% below its 52-week high of ₹14.48 but still up 173.82% from its 52-week low of ₹2.33.
Time: Feb 16 2026 08:41 PM IST</description><guid>32753f84a055c97c76f5d97830f41a5a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Opala RG Q3 FY26: Profit Resilience Amid Revenue Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/la-opala-rg-q3-fy26-profit-resilience-amid-revenue-pressure-3842932</link><description>La Opala RG Ltd., the Kolkata-based premium glassware and lifestyle products manufacturer, reported a net profit of ₹24.00 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a marginal decline of 3.57% quarter-on-quarter but a modest improvement of 3.58% year-on-year. The company, with a market capitalisation of ₹2,153 crores, continues to navigate challenging demand conditions whilst maintaining profitability through disciplined cost management. However, the stock has faced significant selling pressure, declining 3.83% on February 16, 2026, to close at ₹190.85, reflecting investor concerns about sustained revenue headwinds and margin compression.
Time: Feb 16 2026 08:38 PM IST</description><guid>773c2f15348294bdd87f267cee55b651</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heera Ispat Q3 FY26: Operational Dormancy Continues as Losses Persist</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/heera-ispat-q3-fy26-operational-dormancy-continues-as-losses-persist-3842930</link><description>Heera Ispat Ltd., the Gujarat-based iron and steel products manufacturer, reported another quarter of operational inactivity in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), with zero revenue generation and continued losses. The company posted a net loss of ₹0.01 crores for the quarter, marking no improvement from the previous quarter's loss of ₹0.05 crores. With a minuscule market capitalisation of just ₹4.00 crores and a negative book value per share of ₹0.95, the company remains in a state of effective dormancy, having generated no sales revenue for several consecutive quarters.
Time: Feb 16 2026 08:35 PM IST</description><guid>123d24480c28b9f2dfa19ee22e66d992</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GP Petroleums Q3 FY26: Volume Growth Masks Margin Erosion Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/gp-petroleums-q3-fy26-volume-growth-masks-margin-erosion-concerns-3842929</link><description>GP Petroleums Ltd., a Mumbai-based lubricants manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹175.00 crores, reported mixed results for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), with net profit declining 4.21% quarter-on-quarter to ₹5.24 crores despite robust revenue expansion. The stock plunged 6.51% to ₹32.59 following the announcement, reflecting investor disappointment over margin compression that overshadowed the company's 11.22% sequential sales growth to ₹169.23 crores.
Time: Feb 16 2026 08:33 PM IST</description><guid>4a69e53a2f39b6e40efe28b64d83af21</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>True Green Bio Energy Q3 FY26: Explosive Revenue Surge Masks Fundamental Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/true-green-bio-energy-q3-fy26-explosive-revenue-surge-masks-fundamental-concerns-3842928</link><description>True Green Bio Energy Ltd., a micro-cap player in the garments and apparels sector, reported a dramatic revenue surge in Q3 FY26, with net sales skyrocketing to ₹84.20 crores—a staggering 3,727.27% quarter-on-quarter increase and 4,476.09% year-on-year growth. However, the company's net profit of ₹2.19 crores, whilst representing the highest quarterly profit in recent history, reflects a PAT margin of just 2.60%, raising questions about the sustainability and quality of this explosive growth. Trading at ₹71.15 with a market capitalisation of ₹243.00 crores, the stock has declined 32.27% over the past year, significantly underperforming the sector's 1.26% gain.
Time: Feb 16 2026 08:32 PM IST</description><guid>8485016e4a4b828e89eb53384c520e7c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajasthan Tube Manufacturing Q3 FY26: Sharp Profit Rebound Masks Severe Revenue Collapse</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/rajasthan-tube-manufacturing-q3-fy26-sharp-profit-rebound-masks-severe-revenue-collapse-3842926</link><description>Rajasthan Tube Manufacturing Company Ltd., a micro-cap steel pipes and tubes manufacturer, reported a dramatic turnaround in Q3 FY26 profitability whilst simultaneously experiencing a catastrophic revenue collapse that raises fundamental questions about business sustainability. The company posted net profit of ₹2.89 crores in Q3 FY26, a remarkable recovery from a loss of ₹0.28 crores in Q3 FY25, yet this improvement came against the backdrop of net sales plummeting 80.07% year-on-year to just ₹3.51 crores from ₹17.61 crores in the corresponding quarter last year.
Time: Feb 16 2026 08:13 PM IST</description><guid>aeedb490a082c99061bb8626f8c2a8e0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kay Power &amp; Paper Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Signal Deepening Operational Crisis</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kay-power-paper-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-signal-deepening-operational-crisis-3842927</link><description>Kay Power &amp; Paper Ltd., a Maharashtra-based MG Kraft paper manufacturer, reported a net loss of ₹0.09 crores in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sharp deterioration from the marginal profit of ₹0.02 crores in Q2 FY26. The 550% quarter-on-quarter decline represents the company's worst quarterly performance in recent periods, as revenues collapsed 37.75% sequentially to just ₹4.75 crores. The micro-cap company, valued at ₹33 crores, saw its shares plunge 10.17% on February 16, 2026, closing at ₹8.48—a staggering 72.47% below its 52-week high of ₹30.80.
Time: Feb 16 2026 08:02 PM IST</description><guid>0187f360d2259a85a2fb6792457e4b57</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sigma Advanced System Q3 FY26: Revenue Surge Masks Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sigma-advanced-system-q3-fy26-revenue-surge-masks-profitability-concerns-3842925</link><description>Sigma Advanced System Ltd., the Chennai-based telecom services company, reported a dramatic revenue revival in Q3 FY26, posting net sales of ₹145.70 crores—a staggering 702.75% quarter-on-quarter surge and 667.25% year-on-year growth. However, the company's consolidated net profit turned negative at ₹-1.03 crores, falling 124.35% from the previous quarter's ₹4.23 crores, raising serious questions about the sustainability and profitability of this revenue expansion. The stock closed at ₹176.20 on February 16, 2026, down 4.94% from the previous day, reflecting investor concerns about the company's ability to translate top-line growth into bottom-line performance.
Time: Feb 16 2026 07:31 PM IST</description><guid>6b4081fd92f1f826799570723c0f37ff</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Healthy Life Agritec Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-healthy-life-agritec-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842853</link><description>Healthy Life Agritec Ltd's latest results show a recovery with a 7.67% increase in net sales and a 68.35% rise in net profit compared to the previous quarter. However, ongoing challenges, including a significant stock price decline and low return on equity, raise concerns about long-term investor confidence.
Time: Feb 16 2026 07:12 PM IST</description><guid>5fda4456240ffd57c20f67106a588596</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Athena Global Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-athena-global-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842852</link><description>Athena Global Technologies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net profit of ₹1.14 crores primarily due to a one-off income, while revenue declined by 47.26% year-on-year, indicating ongoing operational challenges and an unsustainable business model. The company faces significant financial strain with high employee costs and a deteriorating operating margin.
Time: Feb 16 2026 07:12 PM IST</description><guid>2a75f736a9d6281a7e98c7fd8ea7a3a1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Uma Exports Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-uma-exports-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842851</link><description>Uma Exports Ltd's latest results show strong sequential revenue growth of 38.31% to ₹560.44 crore, but a significant year-on-year net profit decline of 41.47% to ₹1.27 crore, indicating operational challenges and rising costs that may concern investors.
Time: Feb 16 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>60b44d56628759e9b04fb06d5a38a3e6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vishvprabha-ventures-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3842850</link><description>Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹0.75 crore and an 80% revenue decline to ₹0.98 crore, alongside negative operating margins and deteriorating return on equity, indicating significant operational challenges and questions about its long-term viability.
Time: Feb 16 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>697874ee5ddef76ef741d24fe59b38a7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>