<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Arkade Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arkade-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3857150</link><description>As of 25-Feb, Arkade Developers Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹113.70, down by 2.07% on the day, reflecting mounting concerns over its long-term growth prospects and subdued investor participation despite some positive financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b2afd0359f6ce4a82d7c7ae5593334d1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Muthoot Microfin Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-muthoot-microfin-ltd-fallingrising-3857149</link><description>On 25-Feb, Muthoot Microfin Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.01% to ₹176.00, continuing a downward trend over the past week despite strong quarterly earnings and impressive one-year returns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f0fa1594379d24213c8fcc86e10feb4f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Goldkart Jewels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-goldkart-jewels-ltd-fallingrising-3857148</link><description>On 25-Feb, Goldkart Jewels Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹252.10 with an increase of ₹6.10 or 2.48%. This upward movement reflects the stock’s sustained outperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks over multiple time horizons.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>62818049190176d4a6d3eed06b0d5459</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is TCC Concept Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tcc-concept-ltd-fallingrising-3857147</link><description>On 25-Feb, TCC Concept Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 6.67%, closing at ₹467.95, reflecting robust short-term gains despite mixed longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0c72bfe02168c5b37a3e20661f18ca9b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-affordable-robotic-automation-ltd-fallingrising-3857146</link><description>On 25-Feb, Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.65% to close at ₹191.60. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, driven by subdued investor participation and technical weaknesses.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0bb1a2ea58ae569f11db43431ec32940</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Halder Venture Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-halder-venture-ltd-fallingrising-3857145</link><description>On 25-Feb, Halder Venture Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.25%, closing at ₹250.00, reflecting a continuation of recent downward momentum despite its strong long-term performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9132f32a1adb107bb88eead260bf35f6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ashapuri Gold Ornament Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ashapuri-gold-ornament-ltd-fallingrising-3857144</link><description>On 25-Feb, Ashapuri Gold Ornament Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹4.77, down by ₹0.15 or 3.05% as of 09:09 PM. This drop continues a sustained downward trajectory that has persisted over recent weeks and months, reflecting broader challenges faced by the stock relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7d5849637266946b2cf8b93444c9e5dd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jubilant-ingrevia-ltd-fallingrising-3857143</link><description>On 25-Feb, Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.51% to ₹593.55, continuing a recent downward trend amid a complex interplay of financial performance and market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0087fdc62fea68df6cfeaf80e1d8ea20</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ircon International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ircon-international-ltd-fallingrising-3857142</link><description>As of 25-Feb, Ircon International Ltd’s stock price has declined to ₹146.80, reflecting a drop of 0.84% on the day. This fall is part of a broader downward trend driven by persistent negative financial results and underwhelming market returns compared to benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dd5929105d347b70c6668fe270a1bc09</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is G G Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-g-g-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3857141</link><description>On 25-Feb, G G Engineering Ltd’s stock price fell to a fresh 52-week and all-time low of ₹0.48, reflecting a sustained downward trajectory that has significantly underperformed the broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>942f4869491ce82c7aacce3eb92f52a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aarnav Fashions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aarnav-fashions-ltd-fallingrising-3857140</link><description>On 25-Feb, Aarnav Fashions Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.28% to close at ₹27.75. This drop followed three consecutive days of gains, signalling a short-term trend reversal despite the stock's recent outperformance against the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e1dd04476e31afec3f842c0a5bae8697</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Indian Wood Products Company Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-indian-wood-products-company-ltd-fallingrising-3857139</link><description>On 25-Feb, The Indian Wood Products Company Ltd recorded a modest rise in its share price, gaining 0.98% to close at ₹33.00. This increase follows two consecutive days of decline, signalling a short-term reversal despite the stock's continued underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>18cbfa453aeb915766b343431e879a09</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jyothy Labs Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jyothy-labs-ltd-fallingrising-3857138</link><description>On 25-Feb, Jyothy Labs Ltd. witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 1.5% to ₹259.75, reflecting a broader trend of short-term gains despite longer-term challenges faced by the company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9d2d8c58f64b5f68e558533faa003502</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Flomic Global Logistics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-flomic-global-logistics-ltd-fallingrising-3857137</link><description>On 25-Feb, Flomic Global Logistics Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 1.94% to close at ₹47.01. This downturn reflects a continuation of recent negative trends, with the stock underperforming both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>07c894d0d5ad4a46d200ef1c8e26da7b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gautam Exim Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gautam-exim-ltd-fallingrising-3857136</link><description>On 25-Feb, Gautam Exim Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.44% to close at ₹275.00. This drop reflects a combination of short-term trading pressures and waning investor engagement, despite the stock's impressive long-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ef7ef10a3b76131e7e4a8c57e2d8acd2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Steel Authority Of India Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-steel-authority-of-india-ltd-fallingrising-3857135</link><description>On 25-Feb, Steel Authority Of India Ltd. (SAIL) witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹164.90 with a gain of ₹4.65 or 2.9%. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust market performance, favourable sector trends, and increased investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f386890643928f64a80d6ddacafd7842</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Caprihans India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-caprihans-india-ltd-fallingrising-3857134</link><description>On 25-Feb, Caprihans India Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹76.87, down ₹4.25 or 5.24% from the previous close. This drop marks a continuation of a sustained downward trend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3cc99130ef3fceebf51e840cc2426ecf</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cantabil Retail India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cantabil-retail-india-ltd-fallingrising-3857133</link><description>On 25-Feb, Cantabil Retail India Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.49% to ₹270.40, continuing a three-day losing streak that has seen the share price decline by 5.5%. This downward movement contrasts with the company’s robust operational performance and long-term growth prospects, highlighting a divergence between short-term market sentiment and underlying fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>11d27b038e6f957999168081a8e2f683</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sheela Foam Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sheela-foam-ltd-fallingrising-3857132</link><description>As of 25-Feb, Sheela Foam Ltd. shares have experienced a decline, closing at ₹552.00 with a loss of 0.57% on the day. This movement reflects a complex interplay of recent financial results, long-term performance challenges, and market sentiment that has weighed on the stock despite some positive operational indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>17215444c8e609e929dbdc61cfbe5a39</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Meera Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-meera-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3857131</link><description>On 25-Feb, Meera Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.48% to close at ₹66.28. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends driven by disappointing financial results and subdued investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c3c942203ecd905f7f91c52ca3cee9ed</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>