<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Spice Islands Industries Ltd Gains 5.73%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spice-islands-industries-ltd-gains-573-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3803881</link><description>Spice Islands Industries Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 5.73% from Rs.214.80 to Rs.227.10 between 19 and 23 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, reflecting strong momentum amid a broadly weak market backdrop.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>9edebcff2dfdd4c8def158ffcec6f483</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piramal Finance Ltd Falls 5.73%: 5 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piramal-finance-ltd-falls-573-5-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-volatility-3803885</link><description>Piramal Finance Ltd’s shares declined by 5.73% over the week ending 23 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The stock exhibited significant intraday volatility, including a new 52-week and all-time high early in the week, followed by notable price pressure and sectoral headwinds towards the close. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance and the broader market context influencing investor sentiment.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>682ad2767e6d0234b52d87789776fd7c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PG Electroplast Declines 12.81%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pg-electroplast-declines-1281-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-downtrend-3803882</link><description>PG Electroplast Ltd endured a challenging week, with its share price declining sharply by 12.81% from Rs.585.30 on 16 Jan 2026 to Rs.510.35 on 23 Jan 2026. This underperformance was notably steeper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting intensified bearish momentum and heightened market activity amid technical and derivatives-driven pressures.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>cebbda93784bb15b4293a176fa5a9851</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVR Inox Ltd Falls 9.44%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pvr-inox-ltd-falls-944-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803886</link><description>PVR Inox Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 9.44% to close at Rs.931.85, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s downward trajectory was influenced by a combination of shifting technical momentum, a downgrade in investment rating, and mounting market pressure amid broader sectoral headwinds.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>8ef2de9e44f09136b3515a638ba7f05d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd Drops 20.31%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/systematix-corporate-services-ltd-drops-2031-6-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3803884</link><description>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price plunging 20.31% to close at Rs.82.20, significantly underperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid sharp quarterly profit declines, sustained selling pressure, and technical weakness, reflecting a challenging environment for the company’s shares.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>fc5ceb4890ff229ae0989027f6b08c99</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Holdings Ltd Falls 4.10%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-holdings-ltd-falls-410-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803883</link><description>TVS Holdings Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 4.10% from ₹14,096.50 to ₹13,518.55, slightly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid mixed technical signals and concerns over high leverage, despite the company’s valuation remaining very attractive and its long-term returns outperforming benchmarks.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>94a6ba95f2be79126c57091546353221</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Container Corporation Of India Ltd Falls 7.72%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/container-corporation-of-india-ltd-falls-772-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803880</link><description>Container Corporation Of India Ltd (CONCOR) endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining 7.72% to close at Rs.479.65, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall. The stock faced persistent bearish momentum amid rising derivatives activity and a fresh 52-week low, reflecting mounting investor caution and technical weakness in the transport services sector.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>fecb547e2c9e005f5d249df65214155f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indosolar Ltd Falls 6.76%: 5 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indosolar-ltd-falls-676-5-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-volatility-3803879</link><description>Indosolar Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.433.30, down 6.76% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.464.70. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting company-specific pressures amid broader market volatility. After four consecutive days of sharp losses capped by multiple lower circuit hits, the stock staged a strong two-day recovery rally, hitting upper circuit limits on 22 and 23 January, signalling renewed buying interest despite lingering caution among investors.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>f3670541099b0ad3b600c25aa153562c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Gains 1.95% Amid 14.7% Open Interest Surge and New 52-Week High</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-gains-195-amid-147-open-interest-surge-and-new-52-week-high-3803878</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.95%, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 3.31% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid a volatile market, hitting new intraday and 52-week highs on 22 and 23 January 2026 respectively, supported by strong derivatives market activity and sustained technical momentum.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>2eac2a610fde3c9a631d7378c7e49c10</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesh Housing Corporation Ltd Declines 2.28%: 4 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganesh-housing-corporation-ltd-declines-228-4-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-downtrend-3803874</link><description>Ganesh Housing Corporation Ltd’s stock declined by 2.28% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.721.10 compared to Rs.737.95 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s sharper 3.31% fall, signalling relative resilience amid a challenging market backdrop. The week was marked by intensified bearish momentum, a new 52-week low, and mixed technical signals that shaped investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>5d264fab62dfd9b2fbbeb9a8433fa659</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BF Utilities Ltd Falls 10.01%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bf-utilities-ltd-falls-1001-4-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3803870</link><description>BF Utilities Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 10.01% to close at Rs.530.50, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by fresh 52-week lows, heavy selling pressure culminating in a lower circuit hit, and a valuation shift that, while improving attractiveness, failed to halt the downtrend. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>5c7f79d1255017fe88d19c9fb2d00900</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ramco Cements Ltd Declines 1.46%: 5 Key Technical Shifts Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-ramco-cements-ltd-declines-146-5-key-technical-shifts-shape-the-week-3803877</link><description>The Ramco Cements Ltd closed the week down 1.46% at Rs.1,052.75, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by significant technical shifts, including the formation of both a Death Cross and a Golden Cross, alongside a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. Despite mixed signals, the stock showed resilience relative to the broader market, with notable intraday swings and evolving momentum indicators shaping investor sentiment.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>a836b8f202e808e027e484f2cf93a6d9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Bank of India Falls 1.24%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/state-bank-of-india-falls-124-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3803876</link><description>State Bank of India (SBI) closed the week ending 23 January 2026 at Rs.1,029.40, down 1.24% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,042.30. This modest decline came amid a broader market sell-off, with the Sensex falling 3.31% over the same period. Despite the weekly dip, SBI demonstrated relative resilience, outperforming the benchmark index by 2.07 percentage points. The week was marked by notable milestones including new 52-week and all-time highs, strong technical signals, and heightened volatility, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces impacting the banking heavyweight.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>70aa0fdfa5028b9ef615a486170e6881</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astral Ltd Falls 5.31%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astral-ltd-falls-531-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803875</link><description>Astral Ltd’s stock price declined by 5.31% over the week ending 23 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The week was marked by a sharp technical momentum shift to bearishness early on, followed by a strong intraday rebound on 22 January that briefly lifted the stock before it closed lower on the final day. These contrasting movements reflect a volatile trading environment amid mixed technical signals and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>96a903b95a5fd97316eddbd9ac0402c4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DLF Ltd Falls 9.40%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dlf-ltd-falls-940-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-downtrend-3803873</link><description>DLF Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining 9.40% to close at Rs.588.60, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The stock faced sustained selling pressure, hitting fresh 52-week lows and witnessing heightened activity in both put and call options, signalling a complex and cautious market sentiment amid sectoral headwinds and weak technical indicators.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>a6aea9d869803e02304db8eac1e1931b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty Falls 19.26%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajmera-realty-falls-1926-2-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3803872</link><description>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd endured a challenging week, with its share price plunging 19.26% from Rs.183.25 to Rs.147.95, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure amid sectoral headwinds and a marked shift in technical momentum, culminating in a series of steep daily losses that reflected growing investor caution and volatility.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>10da1b25df59a0477504da18865caea9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poonawalla Fincorp Declines 10.58%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/poonawalla-fincorp-declines-1058-4-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-slide-3803871</link><description>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 23 January 2026, with its stock price falling 10.58% from Rs.464.00 to Rs.414.90, significantly underperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. Despite an outstanding quarterly performance and a recent upgrade to a Buy rating, the stock faced notable volatility and selling pressure, culminating in a sharp intraday drop on the final trading day. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>47ffd0bc0d833388878797c780e0311f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robust Earnings Momentum Evident as 428 Companies Report Dec-2025 Quarter Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/robust-earnings-momentum-evident-as-428-companies-report-dec-2025-quarter-results-3803869</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 428 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings surprises has improved to 55.0%, this growth is unevenly distributed across market capitalisation segments and sectors, signalling a cautious but optimistic outlook for investors.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>4d9a49459ce85b9f28b3331765362907</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>