<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Vodafone Idea Ltd’s Mixed Week: -1.34% Price Change Amid High Volume and Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vodafone-idea-ltds-mixed-week--134-price-change-amid-high-volume-and-volatility-3779196</link><description>Vodafone Idea Ltd experienced a volatile trading week from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026, closing marginally lower by 1.34% at Rs.11.79, while the Sensex advanced 1.35% over the same period. The stock demonstrated notable intraday swings, hitting multiple 52-week highs before retreating amid heavy option activity and mixed investor sentiment. Despite strong volume and value turnover, the telecom operator’s Mojo Score remains at 46.0 with a Sell rating, reflecting ongoing fundamental challenges amid a cautiously optimistic technical backdrop.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d4db5aca2ba65c2fed27165e56ffdf79</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Motor Parts &amp; Accessories Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-motor-parts-accessories-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3779187</link><description>India Motor Parts &amp; Accessories Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>607f5c755071154d4229056e7dfd3327</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Honasa Consumer Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/honasa-consumer-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779183</link><description>Honasa Consumer Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e97f4e959e422b4624b5b0d71c3f70b8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Properties Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shriram-properties-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3779186</link><description>Shriram Properties Ltd, a small-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>69cc7c6e4e17f61b4a7d29397baee0ce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krsnaa-diagnostics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779185</link><description>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already subdued performance metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>07704da63d3c66fd7adb978e532be094</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amber-enterprises-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3779184</link><description>Amber Enterprises India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook within the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c7af1996b36bc91ecce79de5e29eadd5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GTV Engineering Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gtv-engineering-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779177</link><description>GTV Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about its near-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9f83d5c00c328d72dd403ecfbe479a36</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astra Microwave Products Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astra-microwave-products-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779181</link><description>Astra Microwave Products Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>da7432ce50ca5fdc9ee440c6e01fa6a1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-toners-developers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3779180</link><description>Indian Toners &amp; Developers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4c930bbe6214595f88ceaf048f3b0452</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Algoquant Fintech Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/algoquant-fintech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779182</link><description>Algoquant Fintech Ltd, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development points to a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid mixed fundamental and technical signals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>19bacfcff0d516f8e65b3feee843b5f6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kings Infra Ventures Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kings-infra-ventures-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3779179</link><description>Kings Infra Ventures Ltd, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>850044d1aacd03dfe40ef279c0422cc7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automobile Corporation Of Goa Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/automobile-corporation-of-goa-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3779178</link><description>Automobile Corporation Of Goa Ltd (Stock ID: 484249) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near- to medium-term outlook within the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3debb730736a4ed53e1298d46a9c0443</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Royal Orchid Hotels Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/royal-orchid-hotels-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3779169</link><description>Royal Orchid Hotels Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f439bf835e70aaf5729a652fef15651d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Restile Ceramics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/restile-ceramics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3779171</link><description>Restile Ceramics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1df78d82148d816372f9a4b9e62a1f85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEL Manufacturing Company Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sel-manufacturing-company-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3779173</link><description>SEL Manufacturing Company Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8f9dbff540011f35457dc546af101146</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Nilgiri Tea Estates Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/united-nilgiri-tea-estates-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779172</link><description>United Nilgiri Tea Estates Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook within the FMCG sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e6943444f874520de0128665130eeee3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Rasayan Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-rasayan-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779170</link><description>Bharat Rasayan Ltd., a key player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>37236f1aff01d7a4a97afc4c1375a00f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hind-aluminium-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3779175</link><description>Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift for the micro-cap non-ferrous metals company, which has already demonstrated strong performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3f64224e1ae054bf4b6990b8aa9fcaa2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pennar Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pennar-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3779168</link><description>Pennar Industries Ltd, a key player in the industrial manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—suggesting a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ace3c143e4626a997912d57fd22198c2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>