<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818889</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development reflects a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid ongoing market pressures.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7369e0a2e51ed9307579fc38adeddf8f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jasch-gauging-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3818888</link><description>Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action amid challenging market conditions.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>4a205ec0b46420f81fd8096ff0a964af</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aster DM Healthcare Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aster-dm-healthcare-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818887</link><description>Aster DM Healthcare Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s short- to medium-term momentum, raising concerns about its near-term price trajectory amid broader market pressures.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>2b956ae096e8c4471e97d6c338c24538</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-lombard-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818886</link><description>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>9b33a1fcfde470c1cdac4466a266ac94</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agro Phos India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/agro-phos-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3818885</link><description>Agro Phos India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>333b2e4a405aa5114fd4d4d3dfe93fb1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B.C. Power Controls Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bc-power-controls-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3818879</link><description>B.C. Power Controls Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Cables - Electricals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already challenging fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>ee37966e0046208eb6ac88b281803ed7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818884</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s short-to-medium term momentum, raising concerns about sustained weakness in the coming months.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>435911cba3e97ced0c8685e7837b1176</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hi-Tech Gears Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-hi-tech-gears-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818883</link><description>The Hi-Tech Gears Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>6228fe4f455d4330ed33ef77e84af945</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jai Corp Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jai-corp-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818881</link><description>Jai Corp Ltd, a player in the Plastic Products - Industrial sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>6e32cd8a3fd5ccecac091af1a48f3a33</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kavveri Defence &amp; Wireless Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kavveri-defence-wireless-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3818878</link><description>Kavveri Defence &amp; Wireless Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum amid mixed financial and technical signals.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>a0a417f6078576afaa8b59d5f2aa770b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Syschem (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/syschem-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818880</link><description>Syschem (India) Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7a213df8615561954933a62e26dd3c4f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moschip Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/moschip-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3818877</link><description>Moschip Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend and long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7bf6bf64fa5ad3460eacb04c889bc383</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parvati Sweetners and Power Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/parvati-sweetners-and-power-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3818876</link><description>Parvati Sweetners and Power Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that the stock may be poised for an upward trend despite recent volatility and mixed fundamental signals.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>353a6ba9b6d2e8505af32df7a88b04e2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheetal Cool Products Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sheetal-cool-products-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3818882</link><description>Sheetal Cool Products Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout, signalling a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the micro-cap FMCG company.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>1bc694d2b0014ad4332e1955468435eb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3818875</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 49.0% of companies reporting positive results, marking a notable improvement from the previous quarter’s 43.0%. Mid-cap stocks have emerged as the strongest performers, outpacing both large and small caps in terms of profit growth and operational metrics, while select large and small caps delivered standout performances that underscore sectoral strengths and evolving market dynamics.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>76df44496da8f4343977b74ff211a10f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaycee Industries Q3 FY26: Profit Growth Masks Margin Erosion Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kaycee-industries-q3-fy26-profit-growth-masks-margin-erosion-concerns-3818893</link><description>Kaycee Industries Limited, a Mumbai-based electrical equipment manufacturer, reported consolidated net profit of ₹1.09 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), representing a year-on-year growth of 15.96% but a sequential decline of 18.66% from Q2 FY26. The company's stock, currently trading at ₹729.30 with a market capitalisation of ₹225.00 crores, has witnessed significant volatility, plunging 36.12% over the past year despite strong three-year returns of 398.81%.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>29543306b5531d28a926d0b72b5a804e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Marine Industries Q3 FY26: Micro-Cap Struggles with Margin Compression Despite Modest Revenue Recovery</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/garware-marine-industries-q3-fy26-micro-cap-struggles-with-margin-compression-despite-modest-revenue-recovery-3818892</link><description>Garware Marine Industries Ltd., a micro-cap player in the garments and apparels sector with a market capitalisation of ₹15.00 crores, reported a net profit of ₹0.05 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sharp decline of 44.44% quarter-on-quarter and 16.67% year-on-year. The company's stock traded at ₹25.38 on February 03, 2026, down 30.06% from its 52-week high of ₹36.29, reflecting persistent concerns about operational performance and profitability sustainability in this Mumbai-based manufacturer.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>d2d2a445f4679476dba4b305c73e4aef</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamat Hotels Q3 FY26: Sharp Profit Decline Signals Margin Pressure Despite Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kamat-hotels-q3-fy26-sharp-profit-decline-signals-margin-pressure-despite-revenue-surge-3818890</link><description>Kamat Hotels (India) Ltd., the Mumbai-based operator of The Orchid near the domestic airport, reported consolidated net profit of ₹17.30 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sharp 33.92% year-on-year decline from ₹26.18 crores in Q3 FY25. The micro-cap hospitality company, with a market capitalisation of ₹645.00 crores, saw its stock plunge 9.04% to ₹200.35 following the results announcement, reflecting investor concerns about deteriorating profitability despite robust top-line growth.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>4a2ac8e5a8324ea001e192925ce0556f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/awfis-space-solutions-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-market-volatility-3818826</link><description>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.374.05 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a period of heightened volatility and sustained downward momentum. The stock’s performance contrasts sharply with broader market gains, reflecting ongoing concerns within the diversified commercial services sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e63ac539067a453ffdbf7a9a5a022c59</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1110.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rainbow-childrens-medicare-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs11105-3818823</link><description>Rainbow Childrens Medicare Ltd’s stock declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1110.5 on 3 February 2026, marking a significant setback after a brief two-day rally. The stock underperformed its sector by 4.66% and closed the day down 3.02%, reflecting growing concerns among market participants.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1bcf44e8f5ef08db49800703fb94508c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>