<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Wipro Ltd Sees Significant Surge in Open Interest Amid Volatile Trading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wipro-ltd-sees-significant-surge-in-open-interest-amid-volatile-trading-3818720</link><description>Wipro Ltd. has witnessed a notable 14.33% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and shifting positioning among traders. Despite underperforming its sector today, the stock’s recent volatility and volume patterns suggest evolving directional bets that merit close attention from investors and analysts alike.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>b0b18a5f1ffd82e604b645c60d067f54</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CG Power &amp; Industrial Solutions Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cg-power-industrial-solutions-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3818719</link><description>CG Power &amp; Industrial Solutions Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s recent outperformance, coupled with a 14.9% increase in open interest, suggests renewed directional bets amid a backdrop of strong volume and price gains.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>64b413ada7e4273d11d395c0d3080acf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3818717</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 1,054 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings surprises has improved to 49.0%, this marks a modest recovery from the previous quarter’s 42.0% but remains below the highs seen earlier in the year. Market cap segments continue to diverge, with mid-cap stocks outperforming large caps in terms of positive results, signalling varied sectoral momentum and investor sentiment heading into 2026.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>91fd3d5a9536b3b448392763cd25f8a6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaxtex Cotfab Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaxtex-cotfab-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3818721</link><description>Shares of Vaxtex Cotfab Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 3 Feb 2026, closing at ₹1.93, down 4.93% on the day. The stock witnessed intense selling pressure, with panic-driven trades and a significant volume of unfilled supply, signalling deep investor concerns amid sector underperformance.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>dc739551ca2aa9c8508bc9ccf2e348e9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/simbhaoli-sugars-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3818713</link><description>Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd has declined to its 52-week low, closing at ₹10.32 on 3 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop from its peak of ₹20.15 over the past year. This decline reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company within the sugar sector, as it continues to underperform relative to both its industry peers and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>d49e1a9ef17d209d26bff87979ccf113</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Electricals Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.67% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-electricals-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-767-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818709</link><description>Bajaj Electricals Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging 7.67% to touch a day’s high of Rs 440.25. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reversing a two-day decline amid heightened volatility and active trading.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>0fc4cc1251ce456e125cbeb5bd59323a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EFC (I) Ltd Surges to Intraday High with 7.75% Gain on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/efc-i-ltd-surges-to-intraday-high-with-775-gain-on-3-feb-2026-3818708</link><description>EFC (I) Ltd demonstrated a strong intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging by 7.75% to touch an intraday high of Rs 265, outperforming its Realty sector peers and the broader market indices amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>3b1bbe9403b119e111c16e350e6417b7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karnataka Bank Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.74% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karnataka-bank-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-774-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818711</link><description>Karnataka Bank Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 194.45, marking an 8.21% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum and a notable reversal after a three-day decline.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>6a7e5eb29d14bd3aeb020912f3985319</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhagiradha Chemicals &amp; Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.14% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bhagiradha-chemicals-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-714-surge-3818707</link><description>Bhagiradha Chemicals &amp; Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 228, marking a significant 7.14% increase. This strong upward movement outpaced the broader Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum in the stock.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>859d62c7188607eefdb25d15ff50b7c6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti Structures Ltd Opens Strong with Significant Gap Up on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-structures-ltd-opens-strong-with-significant-gap-up-on-3-feb-2026-3818710</link><description>Jyoti Structures Ltd witnessed a significant gap up at market open on 3 Feb 2026, surging by 6.79% and signalling a robust start amid positive market sentiment. This notable price jump follows a series of declines, marking a reversal in the stock’s recent trend within the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>124507aae12977424f9330a4e09e5e09</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Bank of India Opens with Strong Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/state-bank-of-india-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3818706</link><description>State Bank of India (SBI) commenced trading on 3 Feb 2026 with a significant gap up, opening 5.56% higher than its previous close. This robust start was accompanied by the stock hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1090, underscoring positive momentum within the public sector banking space.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>ecfa3c867ba45e012c8088bec1b0f3c4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indoco Remedies Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Deepen as Operational Challenges Persist</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/indoco-remedies-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-deepen-as-operational-challenges-persist-3818718</link><description>Indoco Remedies Ltd., a Mumbai-based pharmaceutical company with operations spanning 55 countries, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹29.79 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a significant deterioration from the ₹7.93 crores loss posted in the previous quarter. The stock surged 11.53% on February 3, 2026, to close at ₹236.00, though this represents a 32.20% decline from its 52-week high of ₹348.10, reflecting persistent investor concerns about the company's ability to return to profitability.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>0503196663a5269a4d9d3b944c3b1620</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharda Ispat Q3 FY26: Profitability Rebounds Sharply Despite Revenue Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sharda-ispat-q3-fy26-profitability-rebounds-sharply-despite-revenue-pressures-3818715</link><description>Sharda Ispat Ltd., a Nagpur-based micro-cap steel products manufacturer, reported a significant recovery in profitability for Q3 FY26, with net profit surging to ₹1.44 crores despite ongoing revenue headwinds. The quarter-on-quarter improvement comes as a relief after two consecutive quarters of subdued earnings, though the company continues to grapple with challenging year-on-year comparisons and persistent margin compression.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>68c876dfc2af05af4ff1c3c625028e93</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arvind SmartSpaces Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.09% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arvind-smartspaces-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-709-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818704</link><description>Arvind SmartSpaces Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging 7.09% to touch a day’s high of ₹558.3, outperforming its Realty sector peers and the broader market indices amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>8165a1bb131392b1ee31c250a1c9baa2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd Stock Hits Record High of Rs.302.05 on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-ltd-stock-hits-record-high-of-rs30205-on-3-feb-2026-3818705</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new all-time high of Rs.302.05 on 3 Feb 2026, reflecting its robust performance in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector. This achievement underscores the company’s sustained growth trajectory and strong market presence over recent periods.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>857d3188fd085e6fa130dd6addda1a5e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunshield Chemicals Q3 FY26: Margin Pressure Clouds Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sunshield-chemicals-q3-fy26-margin-pressure-clouds-strong-revenue-growth-3818714</link><description>Sunshield Chemicals Ltd., a Mumbai-based speciality chemicals manufacturer, reported a net profit of ₹4.89 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a sequential decline of 32.36% from Q2 FY26's ₹7.23 crores, though registering a robust year-on-year growth of 200.00% against Q3 FY25's ₹1.63 crores. The company's shares have declined 2.50% following the results announcement, trading at ₹815.00 and reflecting investor concerns about sequential momentum despite the impressive year-on-year comparison.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>d0be0042bc92295622b53add1c64f51d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMJ Land Holdings Q3 FY26: Sharp Profit Decline Amid Revenue Weakness Raises Red Flags</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/amj-land-holdings-q3-fy26-sharp-profit-decline-amid-revenue-weakness-raises-red-flags-3818712</link><description>AMJ Land Holdings Ltd., a Pune-based real estate and wind power company with a market capitalisation of ₹172 crores, reported a concerning set of numbers for Q3 FY26 ending December 2025. Consolidated net profit plunged 72.88% quarter-on-quarter to ₹1.31 crores from ₹4.83 crores in Q2 FY26, whilst revenue declined 6.87% sequentially to ₹11.82 crores. The stock, trading at ₹41.36, has fallen 27.31% over the past year, significantly underperforming the Sensex's 8.58% gain during the same period.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>9e878bcbde0bfbfb65cc31d375af5eab</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMC Global Securities Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.32% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smc-global-securities-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-732-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818703</link><description>SMC Global Securities Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 81.21, marking a 7.86% increase from the previous close. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum within the capital markets segment.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>17f9602671f7bf5bf267f4b7626298c1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.85% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-zinc-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-385-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818702</link><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 639.4, marking a 4.9% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting strong trading momentum amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>055759225973a49cd0288de64ffdb942</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uflex Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.35% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uflex-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-735-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818700</link><description>Uflex Ltd demonstrated robust intraday momentum on 3 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 499.95, marking an 8.55% rise from its previous close. The stock closed with a notable gain of 7.35%, outperforming the broader Sensex index, which advanced 2.68% on the day.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>f28b0efcb182b56bc06c3c854d9a4d02</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>