<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3863347</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded with 4,095 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced landscape of corporate performance across market capitalisations. While the proportion of companies delivering positive results has inched up to 46.0%, the data highlights divergent trends between large, mid, and small caps, alongside sector-specific standouts that are shaping investor sentiment as we move into the new fiscal year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ce8d79769bf82bf2973f52801ebf7115</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3863325</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has concluded with 4,095 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced picture of corporate performance across market capitalisations. While the overall proportion of companies delivering positive results has improved marginally to 46.0%, mid-cap firms continue to lead the charge with a 53.0% positivity rate, outpacing large caps which lag at 43.0%. This article analyses the key trends, sectoral highlights, and standout performers shaping the current earnings landscape.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>8329ba45709ebd816ef3f85c21837aee</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loyal Equipments Falls 8.23%: Technical Stabilisation and Valuation Shift Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/loyal-equipments-falls-823-technical-stabilisation-and-valuation-shift-mark-the-week-3863319</link><description>Loyal Equipments Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 8.23% from Rs.178.00 to Rs.163.35 between 16 and 20 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a cautious upgrade in the company’s rating to 'Sell' amid persistent financial headwinds, alongside a shift in valuation metrics that rendered the stock more attractive despite ongoing market pressure.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>30238bed7cce9280072dd39a41ecb567</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galaxy Surfactants Gains 3.62%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/galaxy-surfactants-gains-362-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3863320</link><description>Galaxy Surfactants Ltd recorded a 3.62% gain over the week ending 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock showed strong momentum early in the week, hitting an intraday high of Rs.2,048.50 on 17 February before retreating amid mixed technical signals and valuation concerns. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance and the implications for investors.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>65b2170bd0867c4fa85893974583c220</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>W S Industries Falls 1.81%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/w-s-industries-falls-181-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3863317</link><description>W S Industries (India) Ltd closed the week at ₹73.76, down 1.81% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹75.12, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable upgrade in the company’s quality parameters, a shift to bearish technical momentum, and a significant valuation reassessment, all contributing to a complex market sentiment around the stock.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>e726920433079870b62f1a38f5772fc4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indergiri Finance Surges 17.02% Amid Mixed Fundamentals and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indergiri-finance-surges-1702-amid-mixed-fundamentals-and-technical-shifts-3863316</link><description>Indergiri Finance Ltd delivered a robust weekly gain of 17.02%, closing at Rs.27.50 on 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by sharp daily advances, despite persistent fundamental challenges and mixed technical signals. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s volatile week.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>fe647b88a35f1512d208b0982d60345a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Praj Industries Gains 0.70%: 4 Key Factors Driving This Week's Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/praj-industries-gains-070-4-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-volatility-3863318</link><description>Praj Industries Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.70%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. The stock experienced significant intraday volatility, driven by a downgrade in its quality and mojo grades, a sharp rebound on 17 February, and a marked shift in valuation metrics amid mixed market conditions. Despite the week ending near its opening price, the stock’s trading activity and fundamental reassessments highlight a complex outlook for investors navigating this industrial manufacturing player’s near-term prospects.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>f0343f8734b13b2e48d088481f3dc69a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Hotels (East) Ltd Gains 6.17%: Downgrade and Mixed Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asian-hotels-east-ltd-gains-617-downgrade-and-mixed-signals-shape-the-week-3863321</link><description>Asian Hotels (East) Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 6.17%, closing at Rs.159.25 on 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose a modest 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade in the company’s quality grade and rating to Strong Sell, reflecting deteriorating fundamentals and bearish technical signals. Despite these headwinds, the stock showed resilience with a sharp rally midweek, followed by mixed price movements aligned with sector and market trends.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>fbc6c2b2fa979112f92b8989d3323d50</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HMT Ltd Gains 10.32%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hmt-ltd-gains-1032-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-surge-3863315</link><description>HMT Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 10.32% from ₹43.50 to ₹47.99 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. The stock’s rally was marked by two consecutive days hitting the upper circuit limit, reflecting intense buying momentum despite the company’s prevailing Strong Sell rating and mixed technical indicators.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>c92b3b18700a58ee8ceb097741318532</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd Falls 3.00%: Valuation Reset and Market Volatility Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eclerx-services-ltd-falls-300-valuation-reset-and-market-volatility-shape-week-3863314</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, closing down 3.00% from ₹3,666.85 on 13 Feb 2026 to ₹3,556.75 on 20 Feb 2026, while the Sensex gained 0.39% over the same period. Despite the stock’s underperformance relative to the benchmark, the week was marked by a significant upgrade to a Strong Buy rating by MarketsMOJO, driven by improved valuation metrics and robust financial fundamentals. The juxtaposition of a rating upgrade amid price weakness reflects a nuanced market response to valuation shifts and sector dynamics.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>c9b5fb3faad12b3b70702843cae89fd1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S I Capital &amp; Financial Services Ltd Gains 15.94%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/s-i-capital-financial-services-ltd-gains-1594-2-key-factors-driving-the-move-3863313</link><description>S I Capital &amp; Financial Services Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 15.94% from ₹34.00 to ₹39.42 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. This rally was underpinned by a notable shift in valuation perceptions and a technical upgrade, despite ongoing financial challenges and a cautious market outlook.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>c3f4596b183c443e63cefe9571af53f5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Symphony Ltd Falls 5.45%: 2 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/symphony-ltd-falls-545-2-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3863312</link><description>Symphony Ltd’s shares declined by 5.45% over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.828.65 compared to Rs.876.40 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, reflecting a challenging week marked by a shift to bearish technical momentum and the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low amid subdued financial results and valuation concerns.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>c85376c2f077a4adf17b0fd70b2b0125</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Union Bank Ltd. Dips 0.91% Despite Bullish Upgrade and Technical Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-union-bank-ltd-dips-091-despite-bullish-upgrade-and-technical-momentum-3863311</link><description>City Union Bank Ltd. closed the week at ₹281.80, down 0.91% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹284.40, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant upgrade to a 'Buy' rating by MarketsMOJO, driven by strong financials and a shift to bullish technical momentum, although the stock faced some profit-taking towards the end of the week amid mixed technical signals.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>b78f437c784902562e5144d61ad275dd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVV Infra Ltd Falls 4.46%: Valuation Shift and Mixed Signals Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pvv-infra-ltd-falls-446-valuation-shift-and-mixed-signals-shape-weekly-performance-3863310</link><description>PVV Infra Ltd’s share price declined by 4.46% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.4.93 from Rs.5.16 the previous Friday. This contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% during the same period, signalling underperformance amid a backdrop of mixed financial updates and valuation recalibrations. The week was marked by a downgrade in the company’s investment rating and a notable shift in valuation metrics, reflecting cautious investor sentiment despite strong quarterly results.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>15dce8a0d6d490a26038682f8fe61a87</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axis Bank Gains 2.58%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axis-bank-gains-258-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3863309</link><description>Axis Bank Ltd. delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 2.58% from Rs.1,333.80 to Rs.1,368.25 between 16 and 20 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. The week was marked by robust trading volumes, significant institutional interest, and a series of surges in derivatives open interest, signalling growing market conviction amid a cautiously optimistic backdrop for the private sector banking heavyweight.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>6bde6ae100ac04be5e381acdeae22bdc</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rana Sugars Ltd Stagnates at Rs.11.05: 2 Key Downgrades Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rana-sugars-ltd-stagnates-at-rs1105-2-key-downgrades-shape-the-week-3863308</link><description>Rana Sugars Ltd ended the week flat at Rs.11.05, despite a series of significant developments including a downgrade to Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO amid deteriorating financial and quality metrics. The stock marginally outperformed the Sensex, which gained 0.39% over the same period, as the company grappled with declining profitability, rising interest costs, and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>6d3a2eefc60c89421113fdf8fa907db3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>