<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>KPIT Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-29-jan-2026-3809853</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 29 Jan 2026, hitting a low of Rs 1,050.6, reflecting significant price pressure despite an initial positive opening. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and persistent downward momentum.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>f05257555cbb8247c28430f9d9609094</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manorama Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.22% Surge on 29 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manorama-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-722-surge-on-29-jan-2026-3809855</link><description>Manorama Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 29 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 1,387.4, marking an 8.54% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its FMCG sector peers and the broader market, reflecting strong trading momentum and sustained buying interest throughout the session.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>4a2a316394235426d597ba8a427a2ebe</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3809852</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock has outperformed its sector peers, supported by rising volumes and a sustained uptrend over the past three sessions, prompting a reassessment of its market positioning and investor sentiment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>93a106953aa826b71bfc81403312710a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Trading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-trading-3809851</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 29 Jan 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock trading close to its 52-week low, the sharp increase in open interest and volume points to a complex interplay of directional bets amid elevated volatility.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>70f778e94ff8fb41506b4970323c22be</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rail-vikas-nigam-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3809850</link><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL), a key player in the construction sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and technical factors.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>0d474ed5d671da914a3d5ebf17324646</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-dynamics-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3809849</link><description>Bharat Dynamics Ltd (BDL), a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defence sector, witnessed a notable 10.9% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 29 Jan 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock price declined by 2.61% amid mixed volume patterns and a sector-wide downturn, raising questions about the underlying directional bets and market sentiment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>9fdf82837e46afb9e25daa86c2a771ca</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dalmia-bharat-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3809848</link><description>Dalmia Bharat Ltd, a key player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, has witnessed a notable 15.5% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock’s price performance remains subdued, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces and investor sentiment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>a3016ec4f86fd423e89c372ce720a78f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-energy-exchange-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3809847</link><description>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd (IEX), a key player in the capital markets sector, has witnessed a notable 10.55% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance and proximity to its 52-week low. This development reflects shifting market positioning and potential directional bets that investors and traders are placing on the stock amid a challenging price environment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>4aabd82ecbbec34c6e11074dd0c10da2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi Commodity Exchange Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/multi-commodity-exchange-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3809846</link><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened investor participation and a potential shift in market sentiment. The stock’s recent price action, combined with elevated volumes and improved mojo ratings, suggests a bullish directional bias among traders and institutional players alike.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ce4446a83d8a72f59a0f2ddfc5ebeaf7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GAIL (India) Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gail-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3809841</link><description>GAIL (India) Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.01% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume and price dynamics, offers insights into evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>8d3e5dc0e1efcf4a1d8a7b8452ee4f08</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sammaan Capital Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sammaan-capital-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3809843</link><description>Sammaan Capital Ltd, a small-cap player in the housing finance sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock outperformed its sector peers with a 4.13% gain on 29 Jan 2026, supported by a 14.54% increase in open interest, reflecting growing bullish sentiment and increased liquidity.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>fe949cfdf559f60a162fabadd8e141e2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Star Ltd. Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-star-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3809845</link><description>Blue Star Ltd. (BLUESTARCO), a key player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock outperformed its sector peers and the broader Sensex, reflecting growing bullish sentiment despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>0ed6fd1fe916b73f96fec5003c3eab88</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3809839</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NATIONALUM) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market participation and a potential directional shift. The stock’s recent price action, coupled with robust volume and improving technicals, suggests growing investor confidence in the non-ferrous metals sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>d6ccd93e11d0c00566bbb1614f2476e8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A B Infrabuild Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/a-b-infrabuild-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3809842</link><description>Shares of A B Infrabuild Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 29 Jan 2026, reflecting robust buying interest and a significant turnaround in market sentiment. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.99%, as investors responded to renewed optimism despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>61b0877783b3ad5dc3a8e1e8c8289365</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cool Caps Industries Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cool-caps-industries-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3809844</link><description>Shares of Cool Caps Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the diversified consumer products sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 29 Jan 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit with a maximum daily loss of 16.15%. The stock closed at ₹52.45, down from its previous close, amid intense selling pressure and panic among investors, signalling a significant shift in market sentiment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>e0de8f0cfe95327ffcfc7ac2a09059b2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Surges 20% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-surges-20-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3809840</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd (NSE: HINDCOPPER) surged to its upper circuit limit of 20% on 29 Jan 2026, closing at a fresh 52-week high of ₹760.05. The stock demonstrated extraordinary buying momentum, outpacing its sector and broader market indices amid heightened investor interest and strong volume activity.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>90f561780c36fe6eb4206bd5f7df1cd8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3809837</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. (JINDALSTEL) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price action, coupled with rising volumes and improving investor participation, suggests a bullish sentiment taking hold in the ferrous metals sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>d19ae7222cfbc1538cfe8390ca5dab2d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Onelife Capital Advisors Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/onelife-capital-advisors-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3809838</link><description>Onelife Capital Advisors Ltd, a micro-cap player in the capital markets sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 29 Jan 2026, triggering the stock to hit its lower circuit limit. The stock closed at ₹16.06, down sharply from its previous levels, reflecting a maximum daily loss that underscored investor panic and unfilled supply in the market.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>d8a137b9356c3863aa235c89ced2520e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S.A.L Steel Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sal-steel-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-pressure-3809832</link><description>S.A.L Steel Ltd (Stock ID: 400413) surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 29 Jan 2026, reflecting robust buying interest and a significant daily gain of 4.77%. The ferrous metals company’s stock closed at ₹40.20, marking a notable outperformance against its sector and the broader market, despite a backdrop of falling investor participation and regulatory trading restrictions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>0a3efed518b460dc1275578ace6fac9f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siemens Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3809834</link><description>Siemens Ltd., a heavyweight in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a notable 19.2% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock’s recent gains and volume patterns suggest a complex interplay of bullish bets and cautious sentiment amid broader sectoral and market trends.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>f0ec0cbfa64c03c630d98aae8cd1f743</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>