<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Afcom Holdings Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/afcom-holdings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3851787</link><description>Afcom Holdings Ltd, a key player in the Transport Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>1a2e06ad2b68d3dba6ebacd930f092c2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spice Lounge Food Works Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spice-lounge-food-works-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3851792</link><description>Spice Lounge Food Works Ltd, a player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raising concerns about its long-term strength.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>f6b1c8257fc435b822fbcc49a65ff304</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaykay Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jaykay-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3851793</link><description>Jaykay Enterprises Ltd, a small-cap player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>0551c84994c66a3bd7efe18c34438417</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Regent Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/regent-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3851791</link><description>Regent Enterprises Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential long-term weakness and deteriorating momentum for the stock.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>7daeb276e17f068917baa2a241a5670b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mafatlal Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mafatlal-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3851790</link><description>Mafatlal Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>8b0244268d732cf70bd1960c6b3eb928</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zydus Wellness Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zydus-wellness-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3851789</link><description>Zydus Wellness Ltd, a notable player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term price trajectory amid mixed fundamental and technical indicators.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>9e4464e447852438fb0ef7269dacdf0d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mphasis Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mphasis-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3851785</link><description>Mphasis Ltd., a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>430ee9df3c225dc852ff03a58e86ba0a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Him Teknoforge Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/him-teknoforge-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3851788</link><description>Him Teknoforge Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>de4ca2b1bc589d731677a058e5b9daee</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neuland Laboratories Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/neuland-laboratories-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3851786</link><description>Neuland Laboratories Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum amid challenging market conditions.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>33621245725a8002b5b508588ec71c3f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vardhman Special Steels Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vardhman-special-steels-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3851784</link><description>Vardhman Special Steels Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near-term outlook amid broader market pressures.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>3e7a0bb0eff1dfc6dc1205ae074c7575</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra Logistics Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-logistics-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3851783</link><description>Mahindra Logistics Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-day moving average. This event often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the stock within the Transport Services sector.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>b59e30efec865ec41a4c434b9eaac8a8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uravi Defence &amp; Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uravi-defence-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3851780</link><description>Uravi Defence &amp; Technology Ltd, a player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.146.95, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a persistent downward trend. The stock’s recent performance highlights ongoing challenges reflected in its financial metrics and market positioning.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>630539c0e1d72c845137fe93500cc905</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 25</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-25-3851781</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd’s stock reached a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.25 on 23 Feb 2026, marking a significant decline amid persistent downward momentum. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting ongoing financial pressures and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>6549f22097bcd5beab1dff4eebaf191c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matrimony.com Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/matrimonycom-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3851782</link><description>Matrimony.com Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, touching an intraday price of Rs 433.2 on 23 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects a sustained period of underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>1b849863ed37669ee5c6cfb8627c24a4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CP Capital Limited Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cp-capital-limited-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3851779</link><description>CP Capital Limited’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 92.85, marking a significant downturn for the company within the Other Consumer Services sector. This new low reflects ongoing challenges in the company’s financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ff4ad1be3c23e1b0892e4ed3d5ec68f8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B A G Films &amp; Media Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b-a-g-films-media-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3851778</link><description>Shares of B A G Films &amp; Media Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges in the media and entertainment sector. The stock touched a new low price of ₹3.50, marking a significant drop from its 52-week high of ₹8.00 and underscoring a year-long downward trend.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c4e62bcd3b11b4e081e73430066780a8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Edges Higher Led by Aegis Vopak Term; IDFC First Bank Drags</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-edges-higher-led-by-aegis-vopak-term-idfc-first-bank-drags-3851776</link><description>The BSE Midcap index recorded a modest gain of 0.44% on 23 February 2026, continuing its status as the best-performing segment among broader market indices. Despite this overall positive movement, the mid-cap space exhibited a mixed performance with notable sectoral contributors and a breadth ratio indicating a cautious but optimistic market sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>882da9e1f23eb3eba434808f345db10f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>