<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3862269</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across India’s equity markets, as 4,094 companies reported results reflecting a cautious yet gradually improving corporate profitability landscape. While the proportion of companies delivering positive results has inched up to 46.0%, sectoral and market capitalisation segments reveal divergent trends that investors should carefully analyse.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>631f86af871b08489f70a925a563d49d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBC Exports Ltd Gains 0.56%: Key Milestones and Market Context This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbc-exports-ltd-gains-056-key-milestones-and-market-context-this-week-3862262</link><description>SBC Exports Ltd closed the week ending 27 February 2026 with a modest gain of 0.56%, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market conditions, highlighted by reaching both a new 52-week and all-time high on 23 February. Despite some volatility midweek, SBC Exports Ltd maintained its technical strength, supported by consistent volume and positive momentum indicators.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>260a9329f21e07fc1f7593dee1cba16f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Pulse Multiventures Ltd Gains 16.47%: 5 Key Technical Shifts Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-pulse-multiventures-ltd-gains-1647-5-key-technical-shifts-shape-the-week-3862261</link><description>City Pulse Multiventures Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 16.47%, closing at Rs.2,883.05 on 27 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by sharp intraday swings, technical momentum shifts, and a downgrade to a Sell rating, reflecting a complex trading environment for the stock amid broader market fluctuations.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>1e03305a5141681fbce6ba03f484e352</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A B Infrabuild Ltd Falls 16.97%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/a-b-infrabuild-ltd-falls-1697-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3862260</link><description>A B Infrabuild Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 27 February 2026, with its share price declining sharply by 16.97% from Rs.21.75 to Rs.18.06. This underperformance was stark compared to the Sensex’s modest 0.96% fall over the same period. The week was marked by a new 52-week high early on, followed by heavy selling pressure culminating in a lower circuit hit and a shift in technical momentum, reflecting a complex and volatile trading environment for the stock.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>723c278e366cd9e6edfafb72c2b4d728</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Ltd Gains 0.27%: 5 Key Factors Driving Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/360-one-wam-ltd-gains-027-5-key-factors-driving-mixed-momentum-3862259</link><description>360 ONE WAM Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.27%, ending at ₹1,102.70 on 27 February 2026, marginally outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock’s price action was marked by mixed technical signals and fluctuating momentum, reflecting a cautious market stance amid active derivatives positioning and evolving investor sentiment.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>51a8b2636a0ddd6ff200ec3eaebc5f17</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Railway Catering &amp; Tourism Corporation Ltd Falls 11.56%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-railway-catering-tourism-corporation-ltd-falls-1156-4-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3862258</link><description>Indian Railway Catering &amp; Tourism Corporation Ltd (IRCTC) endured a challenging week from 23 to 27 February 2026, with its share price declining sharply by 11.56%, closing at Rs.571.25 on Friday. This underperformance was stark compared to the Sensex’s modest 0.96% fall over the same period, signalling sector-specific pressures and technical headwinds impacting the stock. The week was marked by a steady erosion of investor confidence, culminating in fresh 52-week lows and sustained bearish momentum.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>7aadf08a02a3c4a0b8785ea4bf9f3bf2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Fluorochemicals Gains 1.78%: Technical Shifts Amid Financial Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-fluorochemicals-gains-178-technical-shifts-amid-financial-challenges-3862257</link><description>Gujarat Fluorochemicals Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.78%, closing at Rs.3,483.25 on 27 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock’s performance was shaped by a notable upgrade in technical momentum and a cautious shift in analyst ratings, despite ongoing financial challenges and mixed market signals throughout the week.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>b1b3ba7bf840f7e8d5c58da358a6d7da</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalam Global Enterprise Ltd Falls 4.29%: Key Technical and Financial Challenges This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalam-global-enterprise-ltd-falls-429-key-technical-and-financial-challenges-this-week-3862254</link><description>Mangalam Global Enterprise Ltd’s stock declined by 4.29% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.11.15 against a Sensex fall of 0.96%. The week was marked by a sharp drop to a 52-week low and a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting deteriorating technicals and financial concerns amid mixed operational performance.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>9072667ed9621a2f2ec41a2d6a9538e6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindware Home Innovation Declines 2.09%: Technical Shifts and Fundamental Concerns Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindware-home-innovation-declines-209-technical-shifts-and-fundamental-concerns-shape-week-3862255</link><description>Hindware Home Innovation Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.226.95 on 27 February 2026, down 2.09% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.231.80. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s more modest 0.96% fall over the same period, signalling relative underperformance amid mixed technical signals and persistent fundamental headwinds.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>4a112b66d00d24f444001866a311f422</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Artemis Medicare Services Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.40% Price Change Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/artemis-medicare-services-ltds-mixed-week--040-price-change-amid-technical-shifts-3862256</link><description>Artemis Medicare Services Ltd closed the week marginally lower by 0.40% at Rs.238.10, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96%. The week was marked by a technical upgrade from Sell to Hold, a bearish Death Cross formation, and a shift from sideways to bearish momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of improving fundamentals and cautionary technical signals.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>73bdf9429637aadc9884fe524eb90512</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sumitomo Chemical India Ltd Falls 1.62%: Bearish Technicals and Weak Financials Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sumitomo-chemical-india-ltd-falls-162-bearish-technicals-and-weak-financials-weigh-3862253</link><description>Sumitomo Chemical India Ltd closed the week down 1.62% at Rs.401.50, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock faced bearish technical momentum and a significant downgrade to a 'Strong Sell' rating amid weak financial results and elevated valuation concerns. Despite a midweek bounce, the overall trend remained negative, reflecting investor caution in a challenging sector environment.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>366210aef59028c8651cb4839d7c91c0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Universus Photo Imagings Ltd Gains 15.78%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/universus-photo-imagings-ltd-gains-1578-6-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3862252</link><description>Universus Photo Imagings Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 15.78% from Rs.371.90 to Rs.430.60 between 23 and 27 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong momentum with multiple new 52-week highs, despite intermittent bouts of heavy selling pressure and circuit hits, reflecting a volatile yet bullish trend within the micro-cap FMCG space.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>e274b03896cab5845fcf392c8012a416</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharpline Broadcast Ltd Gains 7.64%: Valuation Shifts and Downgrade Shape Weekly Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sharpline-broadcast-ltd-gains-764-valuation-shifts-and-downgrade-shape-weekly-moves-3862251</link><description>Sharpline Broadcast Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 7.64% from Rs.10.74 to Rs.11.56 between 23 and 27 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex, which declined 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable valuation shift signalling renewed investor interest, followed by a downgrade reflecting mixed fundamentals and bearish technicals, both of which influenced daily price movements and investor sentiment.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>45304e8eca7b48c0599b06f95b4ae1b2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Cards &amp; Payment Services Ltd Declines 1.04%: Technical and Valuation Pressures Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-cards-payment-services-ltd-declines-104-technical-and-valuation-pressures-shape-week-3862250</link><description>SBI Cards &amp; Payment Services Ltd closed the week at ₹777.85, down 1.04% from ₹786.00 at the start of the week, slightly underperforming the BSE Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock experienced mixed technical momentum and valuation concerns amid flat financial performance and elevated leverage, leading to a downgrade in its investment rating by MarketsMOJO. Despite some stabilisation in technical indicators midweek, the overall sentiment remained cautious as the stock struggled to sustain gains against broader market volatility.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>deb665ba9e1bdeee219b816334a51a8a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Gains 7.18%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-gains-718-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3862249</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.18% from Rs. 23,873.10 to Rs. 25,588.35 between 23 and 27 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs amid robust financial results, consistent earnings growth, and sustained technical momentum, marking a notable phase of strength in the heavy electrical equipment sector.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>8d74a960fea211b2cfd7c74e2b2b6e63</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Ltd Falls 6.94%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-ltd-falls-694-3-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3862248</link><description>Borosil Ltd’s shares declined by 6.94% over the week ending 27 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% in the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure, hitting fresh 52-week lows on consecutive days amid valuation shifts, weak price momentum, and cautious market sentiment. Despite some operational growth and attractive valuation metrics relative to peers, the stock’s downtrend persisted, reflecting ongoing challenges in profitability and investor confidence.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>dcce40293d5beeea9ad208335ff7c5df</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rossari Biotech Declines 2.44%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rossari-biotech-declines-244-3-key-factors-behind-the-slide-3862247</link><description>Rossari Biotech Ltd’s shares fell by 2.44% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.498.25 from Rs.510.70 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 0.96% decline, highlighting the stock’s relative weakness amid a challenging market environment and company-specific financial concerns.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>87f7044fe89ce007271468987fb2abac</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Minds Technologies Declines 4.62%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/happiest-minds-technologies-declines-462-5-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-slide-3862245</link><description>Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd’s stock declined by 4.62% over the week ending 27 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96%. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows during the week amid persistent downward pressure, despite some operational strengths and an upgrade in analyst rating. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics shaping the stock’s performance.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>afa2a92dee6834bff980b3d493705e3e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Route Mobile Ltd’s 1.40% Decline: 8 Key Factors Behind the Week’s Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/route-mobile-ltds-140-decline-8-key-factors-behind-the-weeks-underperformance-3862246</link><description>Route Mobile Ltd’s shares declined by 1.40% over the week ending 27 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96%. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows during the week, reflecting sustained bearish momentum amid subdued profitability and persistent underperformance relative to benchmarks. Despite some intraday recoveries, the stock remained below all key moving averages, signalling ongoing challenges for the telecom services company.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>e66c7050c8a48a1fe5125f1f2fe8cb7f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Secmark Consultancy Ltd Gains 11.39%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/secmark-consultancy-ltd-gains-1139-3-key-factors-driving-the-volatile-week-3862243</link><description>Secmark Consultancy Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 23 to 27 February 2026, ultimately closing with a robust gain of 11.39% to ₹128.10, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock’s journey was marked by sharp declines early in the week, a dramatic upper circuit surge midweek, and a technical-driven upgrade towards the close, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment, technical signals, and financial performance.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>0ef5a7a457c6216bc68f4be3927fb235</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>